But the good news is
I think it's gonna be between us.
Bad news is the best
man is gonna win.
You can't even watch
them for a second!
It's like... Leaving
them with nobody!
Because you're so good with them.
What does your husband do?
I'm not married.
Don is important.
You know, I found that guy.
I'm gonna hard on you,
only because I think
I see you as an
extension of myself.
Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.adic7ed.com
"Greyhound. The cure
for the common bus."
"Lay-z-boy. The cure
for the common chair."
"Budweiser. The cure
for the common beer."
"Manufacturers Hanover bank.
The cure for the common... Bank."
How about "Alka-seltzer.
The cure for the common cold"?
"The cure for the common cold"
is the idiom I'm playing off.
It's an idiom.
Did you know that?
So other than your summer
internship at Needham,
do you have any actual
advertising experience?
The cure for the common chair.
That's Roger's favorite.
Roger Sterling.
He's the guy I shook hands with
when I came in.
What did Roger think of this ad?
What, are you kidding me?
Everybody loves that.
It's the opposite
of what you expect.
That's what I'm interested in.
Why is it in your book?
I've got a bunch of them in there...
Marlboro man, Maidenform.
I like to put in work
that I admire.
Don't you ever tear things
out of magazines?
Yes, but I don't
put them in my book.
Well, you know what they say:
"Aspiration's as good
as perspiration."
That's not how it goes.
Look,
I'm a 24-year-old kid.
I want to be in the ad game.
I know I've got a lot to learn,
but I'm a hard worker.
I'd sweep up the floors around here.
I don't know if Roger told you that.
He did talk to you, didn't he?
He did.
It was really a pleasure
to meet you, Danny.
- I wish you the best of luck.
- Best of luck in... In what?
- What do you mean?
- You trailed off.
We'll let you know.
Do you know a good place
to eat around here?
Tell my secretary you're hungry
and see what she suggests.
Are we on "Candid camera"?
I don't want to jump
on his grave or anything,
but there's no way he's 24.
I'm 25.
What's his connection to Roger?
Besides being delusional?
He's Jane Seigel's cousin.
It's a relief to see
someone worse than me
and really know it.
Don't get used to it.
Well, you know,
I look at Glo-coat
and see how far
everything's come...
You know, my work.
Glo-coat.
You finish something,
you find out everyone loves it
right around the time that
it feels like someone else did it.
Is that your speech for the Clios?
They don't have speeches.
We're going to win.
Just because it got nominated
doesn't mean they're going
to give me an award.
Aren't you excited?
I try not to think about it.
Then you must be excited.
Well, it'd be good for the agency.
Grey doubled their value in five years
and it was all based on awards.
You got anything on Vicks?
- Actually, it's Vick chemical.
- Answer the question.
We're very behind.
Your new art director has been
waiting for synchronicity,
which involves me coming up
with a bunch of ideas,
chasing him down and having him
draw all of them and lose them.
He's your new art director too,
and you have a deadline.
And don't think you can spend
Monday hiding behind corners
and trying not to make eye contact.
I will find you.
- I'm not the problem.
- You are,
because Stan is talented
and more experienced.
You need to learn how to work
with him, not the other way around.
Well, good luck this afternoon.
You're not supposed to say that.
Oh. Well, break a leg.
Charlie Chaplin was very lonely.
That tramp...
Too much of a sad sack.
Laurel and Hardy...
They were better,
except Hardy was so mean to Laurel.
I hated that.
Why am I talking
about silent movies?
I suppose as part of the chapter
on your childhood?
That part of my book is
getting bigger and bigger.
Why is that?
Who is it?
I thought I should come in
and tell you this in person.
That kid...
A very very cute prank.
Caroline... To be continued.
That's a good idea.
I've been to the Clios before.
We're gonna want
to show up prepared.
His book...
...It was filled with old ads.
Plagiarism... That's resourceful.
He had five originals...
- They were all the same thing.
- I told him to be himself.
That was pretty mean, I guess.
- So when does he start?
- The first of never.
Well, you haven't
been married for a while,
so you've probably forgotten
how these transactions work.
If I don't hire Jane's cousin,
it's probably going to cost me
a personal gift expenditure
of between $500 and $1,000.
- When are we leaving?
- Right after life cereal.
To new business...
And victory at the Waldorf.
I mean it. You deserve it.
So I can show you what's popular,
what's unique,
and the only thing I ask
is that you call me Don.
Well, Don, I can't say
I know my furs that well.
I know my mother had
a chinchilla...
I was always on the verge
of a romantic relationship with it.
- Is this for your mother?
- I bet you never hear that.
I don't. Would you like
to give me a price range?
Well, that's an interesting question.
I have a unique problem.
I need to spend a lot but
be careful not to spend too much.
Not a unique problem.
I don't want to be forward,
but can I assume this is
some kind of an apology?
No no no, I know exactly
how much that costs.
This is "I'm getting to know you,
but I don't want to scare you."
I know what we're gonna do.
So now it's "we"?
It's always the right size
and nothing says mink like mink.
It's a nice way to ease into things
and you can always come back
for the rest of it.
How about we split the difference
so they wear them to their waist?
It's the most popular this year.
"Why wait for a man
to buy you a fur coat?"
That's a dumb question.
Who does your work?
- I do.
- Really?
Yeah. It's an interest of mine
and they let me do it.
Look at that.
Can I give you a call?
First of all, you need 20 of those.
And second of all, no.
I just want you to call that number
so I can give you some
very specific delivery instructions.
Of course, Mr. Sterling.
So what do I owe you?
I saw you leave the office
with something under your arm.
You don't know what it is.
The guy in the elevator
thought it was a hydrogen bomb.
- It's a beautiful box.
- Mm-hmm.
Skip the radio play. Open it.
Oh, Roger, you shouldn't have.
You like it?
I don't know what to say.
Try it on.
But first take off the dress.
One gift at a time.
What is this, an owner's manual?
It's Noah's ark.
It's out of line is what it is.
So?
I love it. It's perfect.
And I think it's a bit much.
If you don't kiss me after that,
I'm gonna believe you.
When I wear it, I'll think of everything
that happened the night I got it.
Caroline!
Get in here. I think I finally
have a work story.
Joan! What's keeping them?
Life.
When do you have to
leave for the clios?
I was late for
the Emmys last year.
Red Skelton gave my seat away.
I would surmise, due to the usual
nature of your stories,
that that's someone of note.
The good news is our friends
at the cereal company
have been grounded
in Philly due to wind.
- What's good about that?
- And the bad news is...
We only have an hour before
we're due at the Clios.
Sorry, kids.
Game called on account of wind.
Well, if it's all about a sendoff,
I'll have a 7&7.
You have legs. Don?
Make it simple but significant.
It's Friday.
For all we know, they're going to
turn around and go home
- and we'll have to reschedule.
- Is Joan going with you?
Yes. We only had four tickets.
There'll be a lot of other
people's clients there.
- Thank you, Joan.
- Peggy, anything?
I have work to do.
"We represent the majority
of the people in Alabama
who hate niggerism, catholicism,
judaism and all the isms
in the whole world."
So said Robert Creel
of the Alabama Ku Klux Klan.
Somebody got it to Goldwater.
Apparently he pissed blood.
"...Needs our help."
This again? Really?
Clara asked.
Clara asked to see your reel?
I just wanted to see that Klan one.
- He said it never aired.
- Which makes it less impressive, Clara.
Girls, do you mind?
Well, all the girls are gone.
What do you want?
Are you going to use the K.K.K.
to sell cough drops?
It's better than waiting on you
to bring me something
that'll get my juices flowing.
Should I get Megan back in here?
Maybe she's not repressed.
Why's it so hard for you to accept
that man's natural state is nude?
- Because I'm civilized.
- Because you're brainwashed
by society into thinking it's dirty.
You take away all this crap
and you'd see it's not.
It's natural and it's beautiful.
Have you been yelled at
by Don yet?
- I'm not scared of him.
- So that's a no.
He said Monday...
And I'm not working this weekend.
Okay okay. Jesus.
Are you on the rag?
It'll get done. Let's go.
Well, I'd say you're lucky
the Glo-coat brass isn't here.
The minute you win they know
the ad's arty, then you're out of business.
Turns out there's almost 50 awards.
Let's say 10 minutes a piece, it's...
Holy crap.
Roger, you remember
Ned Elliot from K&E.
Of course. What are you in for?
New England Merchants Bank,
best local under $2,000.
Stop bragging, will you?
Good luck, Don.
Well well, if it isn't
Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm.
Leave any drinks
for the rest of us?
Don Draper, Roger Sterling,
this is major-general Frank Alvin.
Roger, have you had the pleasure
of meeting Ted Chaough?
Is that how you say it?
C-h-a-o-u-g-h?
Hey, writers, how many
extra vowels is that?
Let's head due south, General.
Well, I hope this doesn't
drag on like last year.
Oh, wait. You weren't here.
General Rufus T. Bullshit.
I've met that guy before.
- In the war?
- No, in a commercial for Bay rum.
Chao-guh-guh hired
an actor to impress someone.
Last time I saw the General,
he had a parrot on his shoulder.
That was not a business proposition.
You catch more flies with honey.
Oh, great...
Actual flies.
Phillip, how are you?
- You remember Joan Harris.
- Nice to see you.
Mr. Cosgrove,
nice to see you again.
I'm surprised he would
bring you over here.
You know, we miss birds-eye
more than we miss Kenny.
Well, that's why
I wanted to say hello.
I hear the old team's
getting back together.
What team?
Uh, Phil, that's not a sure thing.
Well, I'll say this about Guyer...
- They don't have Don.
- Take your seats, please.
Well, we should sit down. Good luck.
Judas priest.
Are we merging with Guyer?
Talk to Lane.
Welcome to the sixth annual
American television commercials awards.
We're here to honor
creative excellence
in advertising and design...
I just ran into Ken Cosgrove.
Don't talk to me right now.
And I do mean everything.
I don't know if it was
that funny, but thank you.
I have to tell you I am very
impressed you got this gig.
Yes. Well, thank you
for making it easier.
Wally, it's me.
You know, when I was
coming up at Y&R,
you were very inspiring.
Raymond Rubicam said
you were a genius.
Great to see you...
I mean, actually alive and everything.
Get your hands off me.
What's with the French service?
God, I miss working with that guy.
I feel like I've already won.
Well, I'm afraid that'll be the limit
to the public speaking
portion of our show.
And, gentlemen,
let's pace ourselves.
In the first category...
That of apparel...
The nominees are...
Hey, that's five.
If you really worked
on the Johnson campaign,
- why are you here?
- Because nobody at D.D.B.
Even keeps track
of who does what...
Except "the Daisy ad". Big deal.
The Klan is probably the best thing
I'll be near my entire life.
Well, let me tell you...
I had a lot to do with Glo-coat...
A lot... The idea especially.
The kid?
Don put the whole
cowboy thing on it.
I don't know if it was
that revolutionary.
It was jarring,
but more cute than I like.
I know I'm not supposed to go,
but when the nomination came in,
Don let everybody
pat him on the back.
He didn't even look at me
and I was... I was right there.
I was clapping and he thought
I was clapping for him.
Who claps for themselves?
Okay, I'm gonna riff
for a few minutes
and just sorta speechatize
the whole Vicks experience.
Should I come back
when you're through?
No, toots, grab a pencil.
Someone's gonna want
to get it down
before it heads
into the stratosphere.
Why don't you
write down my ideas?
Look, I read your brochure.
I have no interest
in the temperance movement.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
And now for best cleansers,
waxes and polishes.
- This is us.
- Glass wax spray's
"gobbles up dirt,"
Campbell Mithun of Minneapolis.
How do I look?
- Great.
- One step floor care's
"bus stop," B.B.D.O.;
Glo-coat,  "Billy the kid,"
Sterling Cooper Draper Pryce;
and pledge, "Runaway chair,"
Benton & Bowles.
And the winner is...
Glo-coat, "Billy the kid"...
Sterling Cooper Draper Pryce.
- Congratulations, Don.
- Thank you.
- Next up, competing in...
- Let me see it.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- What's going on, dear?
- Well, I ran over
because the people from
life cereal rented a car
and now they're waiting
at the office.
- Right now?
- We'll reschedule.
Maybe I can convince them
to stay for the weekend.
No no, they want
to see our presentation.
What do you say we put
a cherry on this thing?
- Aye aye, sir.
- Really?
So the Schusters move into what
used to be the Harrington House.
Meanwhile, Betty gets
extremely jealous
when she sees Allison dancing
with Rodney at the after-party.
But then Michael asked
Betty to dance with him
and also dances with Claire
and that is all I can tell you about
the next few weeks of "Peyton place."
How the heck do
you know all this?
They send me the scripts.
I need to see them. It's my job.
I can't believe Connie goes
through with their wedding.
It is a surprise. I agree.
What more do I need to say?
- It's heavy.
- Don, you remember...
Jim and Dennis,
glad you could make it.
I can't thank you
enough for waiting.
Oh, don't think about it.
I've been unwinding
as Mr. Crane ruins
"Peyton place" for us.
Perfect. Let's get to it.
- Roger, thank you.
- I'll be on my way,
but first... Victory lap!
Come on, Don, Pete,
Crane, Jimmy Olsen!
Wrap it up quickly, gents.
We have an after-party to attend.
Thank you, Roger.
Is everyone set?
That's one word for it.
Joey, you didn't start
without me, did you?
No, Don. I would not do that.
Okay, everybody ready?
So...
Life cereal... Delicious, crispy
and it's got a big name, you know.
And I know you want
to associate it with health,
but that's not fun. Joey?
Ah. You know what?
I've got it.
Look, there are
sweeter cereals than this,
but I kept thinking about, you know,
nostalgia.
How you remember
something in the past
and it feels good,
but it's a little bit painful,
like when you were a kid.
- That's the truth.
- And "Life,"
that's a scary word
to anyone at any age.
So how do we make it fun?
"Eat life by the bowlful."
A little kid, big bowl, big spoon.
Kids see the giant bowl
of cereal and they smile
because, you know, they'd eat
a box of it if they could.
And moms see it
and they get this twinge
of how little their kid still is
even though they have
to deal with life.
Get those two together
in a market
and I think we're going
to sell some cereal.
That's all I have.
I think if you'd invite us into the rest
of your company,
we could build
a Saturday morning tv show
around the whole
Quaker oats family.
In fact, it could be called
the "Quaker oats family."
I like the bowlful,
but I think it's kinda smart
for regular folks, you know?
- The irony, I guess.
- Children look at the picture.
Moms look at the irony.
Yeah, but when
I go back to Chicago,
all they're gonna wanna hear
is a slogan,
and I don't think this is gonna cut it.
Well, why don't we let
Don work that over?
We can either talk on Monday
if you're staying the weekend
or we can come
see you in Chicago.
I've got it. I've got it, Pete.
How about...
"Life is just a bowl of life cereal"?
"Life is sweet."
Uh...
"Enjoy the rest of your life... Cereal"
Don, they're not expecting
you to do this right now.
Give me a second.
"Life. The reason to get
out of bed in the morning."
"Life. The cure
for the common breakfast."
"Life. It's sweetness
never ends."
- "Life. Eat it by the bowlful."
- Oh oh. There you go.
"The cure for the common breakfast."
- Love it.
- It's got the health angle.
Life makes you feel better.
It's got protein.
Very nice.
- That dog will hunt.
- Wonderful.
- We'll get that put together for you.
- Should we discuss media?
- I can keep going.
-  think we've got a home run.
We don't need to take up
any more of your time.
I know you have
some celebrating to do.
I don't know what to say. This is
the most fun I've ever had in New York.
- Anytime, fellas.
- Very good then.
Roger, I'm done!
- Let's go!
- Can I speak with you a moment?
- Got anything on Vicks yet?
- I really need to talk to you.
- You still have nothing?
- The tagline...
Do you think I'm joking when
I give you a deadline?
- You said Monday.
- Ida, book a nice room with a lock on it
for misters Olsen and Rizzo.
Bill it to Vicks.
- Don't come out until you have something.
- Are you kidding?
Pete, we'll walk 'em out.
Do you want to pick
a place or should I?
He wasn't serious. It's the weekend.
We'll work in the office.
Do you want me to go chase him
down to see if he's serious or not?
Go get Stanley.
- I need to speak with you.
- Not now.
- Lane, may I?
- Come in.
I'm only going to ask once:
Are we merging with guyer?
- No.
- Really?
Well, I ran into Ken Cosgrove and
Clarence Birdseye at the Clios.
It came to me that
Mr. Cosgrove was unhappy
and that he and his choice clients
would be a welcome
addition to the firm.
Over my dead body.
I apologize. It was wrong of me
not to consult you.
- I wasn't sure...
- Wasn't sure about what?
Whether to go behind my back?
I'm a partner, damn it. I have
the same status here as you.
You've never liked me.
You picked him
over me to begin with
and now you expect me
to work with him again?
Approval denied.
Roger Sterling is a child,
and frankly
we can't have you pulling
the cart all by yourself.
Ken is proven,
he's hungry,
and he has accounts.
Birds-eye, a beverage
called mountain dew
and Fillmore auto parts,
which has entered
the national arena.
He would more
than pay for himself.
Does that put you at ease?
What would put me at ease
is you and Madame Defarge
not plotting behind my back.
Still, I expect pragmatism from you.
We share that.
Mr. Cosgrove and I are
having lunch on Monday.
If your tantrum has subsided,
you're welcome to join us.
- I'm going home.
- And on a personal note,
I'd like to add that
I'm quite fond of you.
It pains me to hear
you say otherwise.
- Get that thing in here.
- Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
Mmm! General.
You're not flying tonight, are you?
No, it's been years.
Ah. I bet. Name some aircraft for me.
- No.
- No, wait. Who do you report to?
- The President.
- Of what, William Morris?
You know, one of these decorations
is for shutting up loudmouths.
It's a pleasure to meet you, General.
Enjoy your evening.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- You too.
- We're the top of the heap, huh?
- The heap of what?
- I know they give out 50 a year,
but I've gotta say it doesn't get
any sweeter than this.
Roger, buy Ned a drink.
There you are.
Your mom called.
She's looking for us.
It was very nice meeting you.
- What are you doing?
- Rescuing you.
From what, a business opportunity?
Did you see the part
where I won?
No, but I heard about it.
They're gonna put your picture
on a dartboard at Grey.
What is your problem?
Grey won. Everybody won.
That's not true.
Just think how you'd feel
right now if you lost.
About the same, I suppose.
It doesn't make the work any better.
That's very healthy.
Award or no award,
you're still Don Draper.
Whatever that means.
You're incredible.
You smell good.
- Is that right?
- Uh-huh.
What do you say we get out of here
and really celebrate?
I think you're confusing
a lot of things at once right now.
I'm very happy for you.
Are you calling
to give him an update?
I'm calling him about something
completely unrelated to you.
I know you have
a special relationship.
- What does that mean?
- What?
Not that. Jesus.
Of course not that.
Do you think he'd be
caught dead with you?
There's wallpaper more exciting.
But I know you're his favorite.
I bet he takes you hunting
and lets you carry the carcasses
in your mouth.
Are you gonna work
or just stare at pictures
of women who can't stare back?
You wouldn't understand,
but this inspires me,
opens my mind with freedom.
So why aren't you a nudist?
You talk about it all the time.
Well, in a liberated
environment, I would be.
In the presence of the Pope
or say, you,
it's difficult.
You don't know anything about me.
I know you're ashamed
of your body
or you should be at least.
- What are you doing?
- You're lazy.
And you have no ideas.
- Really?
- Yeah. Let's go.
You're a fruitcake, you know that?
And you're chickenshit.
I can work like this.
Let's get liberated.
Fantastic.
What are you waiting for?
Just...
Let's talk cough drops.
Whatcha got?
I'm thinking.
About what?
Don't flatter yourself.
It's involuntary.
Maybe it was left over
from the magazine.
Terrific.
Now I don't think it's that
hard to convince people
that cough drops are medicine,
especially when they taste like it, right?
So you're really gonna leave me alone
with all these naked gold women?
Excuse me. I hate to interrupt.
- You're not interrupting.
- That man over there...
I saw you talking before.
- Is that Don Draper?
- Yes it is.
- Is he attached?
- To that glass? Absolutely.
No.
He's pretty proud of himself.
Well, it's a big day for him.
It's a big day for all of us.
Especially you, okay?
Well, they don't seem
to give awards for what I do.
And what is that?
Find guys like him.
You've crossed the border
from lubricated to morose.
Good night.
Mr. Sterling.
- Do I know you?
- It's Don.
Don Draper. Heller's luxury furs.
Oh, the fur guy.
- What are you doing here?
- I have a meeting in the building.
I saw you standing here
and I thought I'd say hello.
Really? Name one other
company in this building.
I'm sorry. It's just...
I've left some messages for you.
And I've ignored them.
That's my message for you.
I just wanted to know
what you thought of my portfolio.
I threw it out
with the box from the coat.
That was a bad idea.
Maybe it was a bad idea,
but weren't you trying
to get a break once?
Where does your boss
think you are right now?
He knows I want to do what you do.
And what do you think that is?
I think you're a very important man
in a very important agency.
Maybe I am risking my job,
but I'd do anything to buy you a drink
and hear anything you have to say.
It's 10:00 A.M.
My mother always said
"be careful what you wish for,
because you'll get it.
And then people'll get jealous and
try to take it away from you."
I don't think that's how that goes.
You're an expert
on everything, right?
And how can I hire you?
You know too much about me.
You know I've been discreet.
Once you say that,
you're not discreet anymore.
I gotta get out of here before they
open for lunch. This is embarrassing.
I'll buy you lunch.
I'm stuffed. I had a jar of olives.
Oh.
And you're a great fur guy.
I'm gonna need one of those.
Let me get you a cab.
You should go home.
Garçon! Je m'appelle Roger!
Je suis un taxi, si vous plait!
So you use cough drops
when you're sick in bed,
on a car trip, at the movies
and in church.
Anything you'd like to add?
- What?
- This pencil's a little dull.
Maybe I should dip that thing
in some ink and write with it.
- Stop looking.
- I thought it might make it go away.
You know what? Fine.
Are we getting dressed now?
You can do whatever you want.
- I don't care.
- But you do.
- Fine, you win.
- Win what?
Win the prize for the
smuggest bitch in the world.
I need to take a leak.
Hey, Rizzo!
I'm hungry.
Do you want anything?
What did you win for again?
Cake mixes and toppings.
I wrote the jingle.
Oh. Can you hum a few bars?
That sounds familiar.
Oh. Okay.
Hello.
So you finally decided
to pick up the phone?
- Where the hell are you?
- Who is this?
It's me. Where the hell
are you? It's noon.
You were supposed
to be here two hours ago.
The kids are sitting
in the den watching tv,
waiting for someone who
is obviously not coming.
I know you don't care that Henry
and I were supposed to go
to a very important brunch,
but I can't get Carla anymore.
She's in church.
- I'm coming on Sunday.
- It is Sunday!
I'm really sorry, Betts.
I'm under the weather.
Well, thank you for the notice, Don.
Thanks a lot.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Everything's fine.
Ah.
I can't believe we slept so long.
Mmm. Mmm.
Is that yours?
No, it's yours.
I'm...
Really sorry.
I have some things to do.
I forgot about them.
You said you were gonna take
my picture and you never did.
- When did I say that?
- I don't know.
Somewhere around
your third order of French fries
after your sister left.
My sister?
Was that her on the phone?
- No.
- Don't lie to me. It's okay, Dick.
Listen, I don't want to get
in the middle of anything.
Look,
I'm really late.
- I should get ready.
- Oh, okay.
Uh, do you mind?
I had a great time, Doris.
I'm really sorry I forgot I had plans.
All right.
I'll see you around, I guess.
Are you okay?
I tried to call you Friday night,
yesterday it rang and rang
and today it's busy.
My phone's not working.
Can I come in?
What's the problem?
Uh...
I know you don't want to hear this,
but the life cereal tag you sold,
it was that kid's... Roger's idiot.
"Eat life by the bowlful"?
We worked on that for weeks.
No, "the cure for
the common breakfast."
You changed it in the meeting.
I don't think so.
I know I've gotten stuff
stuck in my brain before
and you don't know where
it's coming from.
It's that kid's.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Call Life and tell them it's terrible
- and we changed our minds.
- They loved it.
- It's terrible.
- Well, neither you nor the client was
in a condition to notice.
Think of ten more tags.
No. I've been working
all weekend with that pig
in that stupid hotel room.
I am tapped out.
What hotel room?
You have to bring
him in right away.
Tomorrow. Fix it.
Shit.
Mr. Cosgrove is on his way over.
I've added you to our reservation.
No. When he gets here
bring him to the conference room.
And he's coughing and
everyone's staring at him,
including the priest,
then he sucks on a vicks.
- It's good.
- Mmm.
- It's pretty much how I pitched it.
- That's true.
I only changed one little thing.
- Good morning.
- Call the Pen & Pencil,
see if someone found my award.
What's the category?
Best actress. It's a Clio.
Hey. They told me to wait here.
Your little friend is waiting.
Listen, Danny,
I've been thinking about things and
there was a slogan in your book...
"The cure for the common" something.
Bus, beer, chair?
Which one?
All of them.
I'm gonna give you $50 for the idea.
You liked it, huh?
What did I just say?
I'd like a job.
Fine, $100. It'll be freelance work.
Do you know what that is?
Yeah, it's not a job.
I don't have to buy it.
I could just use it. Take the money.
I don't need money. I need a job.
You wouldn't even be in this room
if you weren't related to Roger.
But I am. It's all I have...
That and my ideas.
This place is fantastic.
Lane, could you leave us please?
Certainly.
I've given this a lot of thought.
Me too.
If you're open to the direction
and tenor of the business
I'm doing here,
I think you'd be
a great addition to my team.
How's that supposed to mean?
That things have changed
in a permanent way.
I'd say nothing's changed.
Look, Ken,
everyone here likes you,
but this is a small shop
and I need to know
you can do as told.
So...
How are the wedding plans coming?
Peggy!
Take Danny over to Joan.
He's starting next Monday.
Are you kidding?
You will not be sorry.
Go away.
Wait here.
I always liked chocolate ice cream,
but my mother made us eat vanilla
because it didn't stain anything.
- I hired Jane's cousin.
- Really?
What changed your mind?
Couldn't live without him.
Well...
One good turn deserves another.
You left it at the bar.
Too much celebrating, I guess.
Yeah, that happens.
I'll give it back
if you just say one thing:
You couldn't have
done it without me.
Did I not say that?
I was wrong.
Thank you.
Mr. Sterling.
- Good morning.
- Jesus. Would you leave me alone?
You told me to come in.
- The hell I did.
- You hired me.
What? When?
Yesterday. You said,
"welcome aboard."
Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net