Previously on
AMC's Mad Men...
Sally needs to see
a psychiatrist.
Why? Because she
couldn't hear.
She's out of control.
I thought you'd be concerned.
You've crossed the border
from lubricated to morose.
Ken has accounts.
Fillmore Auto Parts because
entered the Nation arena.
Abe.
Are you with Joyce?
Are you?
It's basic training.
I'll be back.
What am I gonna do?
Who I'm gonna talk to?
I'm just gonna take
you to your door.
Why is that?
Because that's as far as
I can go right now.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I'm interested in today.
That was Friday.
Look, I'll clear lunch
plus one hour
And we'll grab a sandwich
and discuss this face to face.
I'm hanging up.
Is it broken?
The lamp?
What are you doing
all the way
over there?
It's too hot.
Would you settle for a leg?
I'd be grateful.
It's cold
And soft.
I'm the softest.
So which one of us
is gonna look at
the clock first?
I caught it when I was
picking up the lamp.
I'm already late.
For what?
Secor laxatives.
Did I spoil the mood?
What do you have to do?
I have a 4:00
at Erwin Wasey.
Doing what?
I can't tell you that,
Mr. Bond.
I told you.
What are you working on
over there?
I don't tell 'em
what I'm doing for you.
You're not lying
in bed with them
right now either.
Do you know what
a Chinese wall is?
I really should go.
Can I get in
the bathroom first?
Just take your time.
Let yourself out.
Lock the door behind you
as a courtesy.
You wanna leave me here?
You sure?
I'm taking everything
interesting with me.
I don't understand.
Do you honestly think
My book isn't better
than Ogilvy's?
Mine's got a story.
It's got mystery,
intrigue, romance.
I tell you It's got examples
- Of how to sell things.
Hold on.
I'm on the phone.
It's Mrs. Sterling.
She's leaving
for the weekend.
It's only Wednesday.
They have phones in
Southampton.
Ira, I don't want
to sound ungrateful.
I just think...
Hello?
Shit.
Come in.
These need signatures,
not initials.
Caroline said
you refused?
It's just so much more work.
I was just giving her
a hard time.
Can I interest you in the same?
And I'm supposed
to tell you in person
That Mr. Pryce
will be taking off
The last two weeks
of August for his son's visit.
You had to tell me that
in person?
- So depressing.
- He doesn't want
a memo circulating.
He's afraid people
will stop working.
What are you doing in August?
I'm not sure.
Well, what are you doing
this afternoon?
The same thing I do
every afternoon... working...
Which is what I'm trying
to do right now.
It's not cute.
Joanie.
Jesus.
I'm sorry.
What did you say to her?
What does that have
to do with you?
Her husband got called up.
He's going to Vietnam
right after basic.
Vietnam.
That's not good.
It's okay.
We've all been
walking on eggshells.
Good afternoon, all.
I know you don't like
to be bombarded
The moment you walk in,
but Fillmore and secor
Are both coming in tomorrow.
I can't move forward
with either until you sign off
On what I worked
through lunch to finish.
I'm sorry.
I had a long lunch,
went for a swim.
Come back in an hour.
I'm taking a nap.
It's a business of sadists
and masochists,
And you know which one you are.
- Oh hi.
- Peggy, your
boyfriend's here.
Satisfaction guaranteed.
- Why are you here?
- Thought we could
get a drink,
- Shoot the bull.
- Sure.
- What time? Where?
- ♪ when you're alone ♪
♪ and life
is making you lonely ♪
- ♪ you can always go... ♪
- 7:00, p.J. Clarke's.
♪ midtown ♪
I'll meet you in the lobby.
Ooh, down below.
Give it a break, jughead.
Oh, I'm not shocked
by your lesbian hijinks.
I just hope you know
you can never do
What a man can do.
That's true.
Bad news.
Don showed up.
We're on at 4:00.
How was your siesta?
Are you refreshed?
- Yes.
- Dr. Miller
returned your call.
She said not to wake you
And you needn't return.
But she got the message
and you're gonna
have to wait.
- Thank you.
- Are you going
to the toilet?
- I have to hire
more copywriters,
But these men come in
and I know
The better they are,
the more my job
is in danger.
Oh my.
Look who's here... Abe.
Peggy, I don't know
if you remember Abe Drexler
from Kellogg's loft party.
- Hi, I'm Peggy.
- I remember.
Abe, you want to
join us for a drink?
Yes, please do.
Oh, stay.
I'll just stand here.
Can I get a Johnny Walker
with ice?
Ah, he didn't hear me.
You know what?
I'm gonna go play darts.
- Take my seat.
- Are you sure?
Pay for that.
See you kids later.
I'm sorry.
She's...
Always so damn
self-amused.
What are you talking about?
I was gonna stop by
your office, but I didn't
want to get you in trouble.
Then I thought about
finding out where you live,
but that's weird.
So anyway
- It's nice running into you.
- I don't know what to say.
That's very flattering.
Well, that's how I meant it.
Johnny Walker.
Rocks.
The bartender here
listens to me.
- May I help you?
- Are you Joan Harris?
- I am.
- We're from madam Inga's.
You are to receive massage,
manicure and pedicure.
- Can we?
- I didn't order this.
It's a gift
from a friend,
tip included.
- What friend?
- I'm not allowed
to say this.
In Greece right now?
Make no mistake,
That's a revolution.
We are a hair away
From everything falling apart
in every society.
It's so tenuous.
All these corporations
just throw their money
at everyone
To keep the status quo intact
'cause the people
outnumber them.
But in the blink
of an eye, they could
overturn everything.
It's an illusion
that America's so organized
That it could never happen
over here.
- Are you from Brooklyn?
- I am.
- Me too.
- I don't hear it.
One more drink
and it'll come out.
Okay.
What am I talking to you
about corporations for?
- You must deal with them
all the time.
- I guess.
Vick chemical,
American tobacco,
But most of them
are family businesses...
Samsonite, Fillmore auto parts,
- Sugarberry...
- Fillmore auto parts
is worse than a corporation,
- What with
the boycott and all.
- What boycott?
The Southern stores
won't hire Negroes.
Says who?
It was in "the voice."
it was in a couple
of places.
I don't think that's true.
I would've heard that.
It is true.
That doesn't seem like them.
I'm sure
they're perfectly nice
for racists, you know,
And obviously your
company has an investment
in looking the other way.
Well, it's a complicated idea,
But in advertising,
We don't really judge people.
We try and help them
out of these situations.
Certainly we would try
and stop this.
If it's true,
it's not good
for their business.
Jesus, I don't even know
where to start.
You would've done
a campaign for Goldwater?
You kidding?
That would've
been spectacular.
- Did you vote for him?
- Of course not.
Wha... civil rights
isn't a situation
To be fixed
with some ##p.R. Campaign.
It's an inequality
that the world has
its eyes on.
I know.
But I have to say
Most of the things
Negroes can't do
I can't do either
And nobody seems to care.
What are you talking about?
Half of the meetings
take place over golf,
tennis,
In a bunch of clubs
where I'm not allowed
to be a member
Or even enter.
The university club said
the only way I could
eat dinner there
Was if I arrived in a cake.
There's no Negro
copywriters, you know.
I'm sure they could
fight their way in
like I did.
Believe me,
nobody wanted me there.
All right, Peggy.
We'll have a civil rights
March for women.
I have a really early day.
It was nice to see you.
Wait. Hey hey hey.
I'm just saying
They're not shooting women
to keep 'em from voting.
That's all.
Oh, Jesus.
I'm really sorry.
I'm much better on paper.
You're opinionated
and you're criticizing me.
That's not what I'm doing.
This is discourse.
I knew I shouldn't
have let Joyce leave.
Have a good night.
A three-letter word
for a flightless bird.
Emu.
Nope. It starts
with an "l."
The hell it does.
Good morning, Mr. Draper.
Could I get some coffee?
And let me know when
Dr. Miller arrives.
It's hard... the way
she breezes past me.
She's pushy, that one.
I guess that's what it takes.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- And thank you.
- For what?
That was very thoughtful.
I knew I was rubbing you
the wrong way,
So I thought,
why not have someone
rub you the right way?
- I brought you bear claws.
- Caroline won't let me
have one
Unless it's on the end
of a real bear.
- Well, anyway.
- Joanie.
- It'll be okay.
- People love to say that.
Look, I know you're
having a tough run.
Let me get you a meal, Hmm?
Take your mind off things?
Of course.
I forgot for a second
that you're incapable
of doing something nice
Without expecting
something nicer
in return.
I didn't mean anything by it.
Honest.
Just thought you
could use a night out.
- Thank you.
I'm fine.
- Good.
- What are you doing here?
- I wrote something.
I kind of wrote it for you.
I would love it if you read it.
"Nuremberg on Madison avenue"?
- What is this?
- It's what I was
trying to say last night,
But without,
I don't know,
my abrasive tone.
- Read it.
- Right now
in front of you?
Nah. Take your time.
I'll wait over here.
I have a lot to do.
I came all the way up here.
I want to know what
you think, okay?
These domesticated suburbanites
Still have
a primitive desire
to get their hands dirty,
But have they have become
so removed from nature
that they can't.
They don't know
how to hunt or swing
a hammer
- Or fix their cars.
- You mean like these two.
Actually, no.
I'm from Vermont
And Don's a competitive
fly fisherman.
What our findings show
is that this demographic
Will spend
a good amount of money
For the satisfaction
of being useful with
their hands.
Ladies love a man
who's good with his hands.
You think a mechanic
comes in and sees
these jokers
Looking at fan belts,
he's gonna stick around?
- No offense.
- What's the difference?
Our inventory's the same.
I think if they see
a coat and tie on aisle 4,
They'll think
our prices went up.
I know I would.
Listen, salt of the earth,
we need more than mechanics
to survive.
You ever hear of sears?
They'll kill us.
We agreed we all had to agree.
Don't we have enough problems
with the boycott?
Look, I don't want
to get involved
In a family squabble,
but I can't move forward
Until you agree on a strategy.
What if there were a way
to market to both groups?
"Fillmore auto parts.
Where the pros go
and everyone's welcome."
- It's a little corny.
- It's great and you know it.
That's not a strategy.
That's two strategies
Connected by
the word "and."
I can do "where the pros go"
Or I can do
"everyone's welcome,"
- But not both.
- Sure you can.
Someone has
to make a decision.
There are three of you.
Vote.
Sean, what do you think?
I d-d-d-d...
D-d-d-don't know.
What?
You'll have to excuse me
for a moment.
Continue, please.
Why d-d-do we
Have to c-c-convince him?
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
I am so sorry.
Who are you?
My name is Vivian winters
And I'm going to assume
you're her father
Since that's what
she's led me to believe.
Don. What exactly
is going on?
I found her on the train
between carriages
Trying to avoid the conductor.
I didn't have enough money.
Megan, could you take her
to my office?
Go.
Thank you.
Can I pay you
for the ticket
and your time?
You're just very lucky
I ran into her
Before someone else did.
The types on that train?
Someone should keep
track of her.
You're right.
I didn't know.
Men never know what's going on.
- I offered you money
and I said thank you.
She looks so chubby
in the pictures.
Get her mother
on the phone now.
What do you think you're doing?
I wanted to see you
and I didn't want to
wait two weekends.
Well, you can't do this.
This is very serious.
Mrs. Francis
on the line.
- Guess who's sitting
on my couch right now.
- What are you talking about?
I'm talking about a stranger
bringing Sally to my office
- Because she got on
the train with no money.
- You're kidding.
Carla was
supposed to pick her up
after the doctor.
- How the hell did this happen?
- Dr. Keener thought it would
be good for her
To walk from camp to her
appointment by herself.
Great idea.
Thank you, psychiatry.
Don't yell at me.
She needs to learn
responsibility.
You need to learn
Now come get her.
I've got a business
to run here.
Because it's so easy.
It's so much fun to
take care of her.
Enjoy.
- What?
- Enjoy, don.
I'm meeting Henry in
the city tomorrow night.
I'll get her then.
Don't move
and don't touch anything.
I don't want to hear it.
Just make sure she doesn't
leave that room.
- Hey.
Are you serious with this?
Everyone knows
who represents
Fillmore auto parts.
- We're the agency of record.
- But I was defending you.
We have a religion
in this country
And it's business.
You're not a priest.
You're just another congregant.
So I'm not a war criminal.
Look, why should
someone nice like you
have to do this?
Why should you be a part
of that corruption?
It's a waste of your
and a million other
artists' gifts.
If you publish this,
I'll lose my job.
Maybe you're better than this.
I'm not a political person.
I don't have to defend myself.
You're political whether
you like it or not.
And you're not supposed
to be insulted.
- You're supposed
to be flattered.
- Are you crazy?
You inspired me.
I wrote this for you.
I guess I read you wrong.
You look so earnest.
I need your word that
you'll destroy that.
Sure.
I won't bother you again.
Miss Blankenship.
Miss Blankenship,
are you all right?
Miss Blankenship.
Caroline.
Oh God. Caroline!
- Oh. Do not
come out of there.
- I know!
- What now?
- Excuse me, Mr. Draper.
- I'm really sorry
to bother you again.
- are you sure?
- I'm afraid so.
- What happened?
Jesus.
Poor thing.
Should we call an ambulance?
The coroner.
What about them?
- I'll attend to this.
- Sally's in there.
- Why?
- She's visiting.
Megan, get a man,
and we'll need a blanket.
There's an afghan
on Mr. Crane's couch.
She seemed fine
just a minute ago.
So where are we?
- Have we agreed
on a strategy?
- I'm not sure.
This is where we are.
Correct me
if I'm wrong, gentlemen,
But we believe
by holding onto
Fillmore's reputation
As a place
for professional mechanics,
We can actually attract
men of all types.
So it's something like
"Fillmore auto parts.
For the mechanic
in every man."
And although it seems
immaterial to you,
- The Fillmore brothers like it.
- Unanimously.
What was that again?
Fillmore auto parts.
"For the mechanic
in every man."
My mother made that.
Can we get your signature?
I'm the president.
I think this is a winner.
Gentlemen, always a pleasure.
Ken, can you show them out?
Of course.
This way.
My goodness.
I was just talking to her.
Listen, my daughter
is sitting in my office.
- What?
- She decided
to run away today.
- Sally?
- I'd really appreciate it
If you could go
in my bag, get my keys,
take her to my apartment
And just...
Sit with her.
Are you sure?
I would have
my secretary do it,
but she's dead.
No, of course.
Okay, do you want
to introduce me?
I mean, what do I say to her?
Do we really have to have
this discussion right now?
You're Faye.
Find Cooper and Roger at lunch
And stop them
from bringing
secor back here.
Sally, this is my friend Faye.
She's going to take you
to my apartment.
- Why?
- You don't want this
to get worse, believe me.
Hello.
My name is Faye.
I know.
My dad just said that.
Stop.
- Where are they taking her?
- She's going to the morgue.
No, she's not.
She's going to
Frank e. Campbell.
Anyone track down her family?
She has a niece.
I'll call her.
I'm sorry, Bert.
Roger.
You should go home.
Yes. Take all
my calls up here.
Okay.
So Fitzgerald says,
"I promised to pour
This whiskey over
your grave earlier,
but do you mind
"- If I pass it through
me kidneys first?"
- Are you all right?
- Oh, damn it,
I don't want to die
in this office.
I almost have twice.
Stop it.
If it looks
like I'm going,
open a window.
I'd rather flatten
the top of a cab.
You are not going
to die in this office.
Poor Ida.
She died like she lived...
Surrounded by the people
she answered phones for.
I'm gonna go to
my favorite restaurant
And have a glass of cyanide.
Or you could join me.
I don't know.
- I'm gonna
kill myself, Joanie.
- No, you're not.
Go get your things.
I'll meet you in the lobby.
I got it.
- Hello, daddy.
- Don't "hello, daddy" me.
Go sit down.
- How was it?
- Great.
We watched a little TV,
one of us took a nap.
You want to stay?
You're gonna need to eat.
I know,
but I have dinner plans.
Thank you.
Glad I could help.
- Good night, Sally.
- Good night.
Can we order a pizza?
I want you to
promise me you're never
going to do this again.
I promise.
Why did you always
pick this place?
No chance of running
into anyone
And, of course,
cherry cheesecake.
Well, the clientèle
is older than I remember.
But not us.
I wish you would talk
to me about things.
My husband doesn't like it.
I know it's tough,
But he must've known
about the possibilities
when he signed up.
I wasn't consulted.
You're kidding.
Because you always
tell Jane about all
of your decisions?
She's the woman behind
the man, isn't she?
Did you listen to my memoirs?
I just have them transcribed
And recycle the tapes.
And you're not
a little curious if there's
a chapter called "Joan"?
There'd better not be.
I know.
That's the problem.
And every time I think back,
All the good stuff
was with you.
And I'm sorry
I keep pestering you.
I just can't help myself.
I don't expect
anything to happen.
I appreciate that.
Can I ask you something?
Yes, I'm still mad at you.
Are you going to marry Faye?
What? No.
Is she your girlfriend?
- No.
- She had your keys.
I gave her my keys.
She knew you had peanut butter.
Everyone has peanut butter.
Well, she said
she wanted to meet me.
Why would she want to meet me?
Look, I do like her,
But we just work together
and I talk about you a lot.
Do you like her?
- She seems nice.
- Well, good.
Maybe you'll get
to see her again sometime.
Get out some plates.
'cause I didn't want
to take a cab on Broadway.
It's a beautiful night.
I don't like
this neighborhood anymore.
What happened to it?
Miss Blankenship,
you're not missing anything.
- Do you know
what time it is?
- I do.
Oh God.
You know what to do.
- Rog...
- yes. Yes, we do.
Look down.
Everything's going
to be fine.
- There you go.
- What about her?
Give me your bag.
Rings.
That's everything.
We haven't seen anything.
I can't breathe.
- I want to scream.
- Don't. Come over here.
- You have to calm down.
- My ring. My ring.
Stop it.
Everything can
be replaced.
You're fine.
Don't stop.
Are you sure you don't want
to call your mother
or your brothers?
It's 9:30.
They're asleep.
Daddy, I love you so much.
I love you too.
Did you brush your hair?
I want to live
with you all the time.
You can't do that, honey.
Why not?
I'll be good.
Where are you gonna go
to school down here?
What about your friends?
What about your brothers?
They could live here too.
I'll watch them.
Sally.
Go to sleep.
- Sally?
- I made French toast.
You know I don't like
you using the stove.
Oh, daddy,
I do it all the time.
And there's no shells in it.
Do you want me
to turn on the TV?
We can watch
"the today show."
No.
Where'd you learn
how to do this?
Carla taught me.
What's on this?
Mrs. Butterworth's.
Go get it.
That's rum.
Read labels.
Is it bad?
Not really.
Get dressed
and I'll get you
a bun at the office.
Can't we do something?
All right,
here's the deal.
No negotiating.
I'm gonna call in,
move everything to noon,
And we're gonna go
to the central park zoo.
- And the dinosaur museum?
- One or the other.
We only have till noon.
You finish your breakfast.
I'm going to get ready.
You want me
to get don to do it?
Of course,
he didn't really know her.
No, he didn't.
Caroline,
get Mrs. Harris.
It's regarding
Ida Blankenship's obit.
That ought to get her in here.
This is an insult to her.
I can't think of anything.
And I have no office
in which to ruminate.
Cooper's trying
to write an obit...
Something sharp and sweet.
Well, Mr. Cooper,
Shall we say,
- "beloved friend..."
- Mmm.
"...Devoted caretaker..."
Put "quietly in her sleep,"
of course.
What's her profession...
secretary?
Executive secretary.
She was born in 1898 in a barn.
She died on the ##37th floor
of a skyscraper.
She's an astronaut.
Hey.
Is this what it took
to get you in here?
Look, I'm sorry.
It was in the heat
of the moment.
And there was a moment.
You know that.
I'm not sorry,
But I'm married.
And so are you.
I feel something
And I know you do.
Good afternoon.
- Hello.
- Sally, this is Megan.
- Where's miss Blankenship?
- She went away.
I'm helping out
for a little bit.
Her mother should be
by at 5:00. Can you
handle five minutes?
Are you hungry?
She ate plenty.
I'm gonna get coffee
and check in.
Shit.
Now we can't leave.
Huh. Harry said on
the form where it says
"cause of death,"
They wrote "don draper."
How long do you think
Yvette Mimieux's gonna
last on his desk?
I say we start a pool
On whether she's fired,
quits or dies.
Where's Dr. Miller?
- I don't know
if she's coming in.
- She is.
Well, the Fillmores
want a jingle,
A c-c-c-catchy tune.
- don't do that.
Harry says no rock 'n' roll
if we want middle-class men.
He was pushing Perry Como.
And we had pat Boone,
Roger Miller,
Frankie Laine, Duane eddy.
I'm glad I came in for this.
How about Harry Belafonte?
Everyone likes him.
I'll get you tickets
to Harry Belafonte.
Believe me, he ain't selling
auto parts for these guys.
Well, maybe it'll help them
with their image in the South.
They don't want help.
Have you ever been
to the South?
'cause they have a way
of doing things
And it doesn't include
Harry Belafonte.
The Fillmore brothers
are from Boston.
Same thing.
Well, why are we doing business
With someone that
doesn't hire Negroes?
Our job is to make men
like Fillmore auto,
Not make Fillmore auto
like Negroes.
Pick one,
get it written
and recorded
And if they want
to change it, we will
charge them to change it.
How about Dean Martin?
He's friends
with Sammy Davis Jr.
Does that work for you, Peggy?
Mrs. Francis is going to be
in the lobby any minute.
I have to cover reception,
per Joan's orders.
Go ahead.
Your mother's going to be
downstairs in a minute.
Get your things.
I wanna stay.
Well, you can't.
I want to stay
and I don't know
why I can't.
Because you have to go home.
I'll be good.
I promise.
- Come on.
- No.
- Let's go.
- No! No!
No no! I'm not going
anywhere! Stop it!
- Do you want me
to carry you out of here?
- I'm not going.
I'm not leaving.
I hate it there!
Is everything okay?
- Can you talk to her?
- What?
Please. I can't
bring her back
Kicking and screaming
to her mother.
I don't have
much child psychology.
Just talk to her.
Dr. Faye wants
to talk to you.
Hi, Sally.
Remember me from yesterday?
I know
you don't want to go,
but you have to.
- Your mother came
all the way out here.
- You don't know my mother.
Sally.
Sally,
Sometimes we have to do things
we don't want to do.
- Shut up.
- What's gotten into you?
- I don't think
I'm helping here.
- We don't want your help.
- Let's go, now.
- Stop it! No! Stop it!
It's gonna be all right.
No, it's not.
I fall all the time.
I was coming to get you.
Mrs.... Your...
Sally's mother is in reception.
Thank you.
I was worried about you.
Come on, let's go.
I was waiting
in the lobby at 5:00.
- We lost track of time.
- Well, now I'm late.
Sally?
- Say goodbye
to your father.
- Goodbye.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Hi. Are you here
to see Peggy?
Can you make me one of those?
No. No, I can't.
- I can't do
anything for you.
- Why are you upset?
You shouldn't have
put me in that position.
Things happen.
I didn't plan it.
You asked me to go watch her.
There was no one else to do it.
And just now?
What the hell was that?
I'm not good with kids.
That was not your fault.
Well, it feels like
there was a test
and I failed it.
God knows I'd be lying
If I said
Would I meet your children?
When would I meet
your children?
But I don't have any.
I'm sorry.
I love children,
but I chose to be
where I am.
I don't view it as a failure.
It doesn't matter.
I mean it.
Jesus.
What a mess.
Part of it's good, right?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go.
I didn't really sleep.
We can have
dinner this weekend.
I'll pick a place.
Good.
Why are you drinking here?
Come on.
I don't know what
kind of surprise
you're gonna spring on me.
So Abe Drexler pulled a boner.
It's to be expected.
He seemed so nice.
He's a man.
He won't be happy
until he turns you out.
What's that supposed to mean?
Gotta be their girl.
It's the way they want it.
Maybe it's biology.
It's like men are
this vegetable soup
And we can't put 'em
on a plate or eat 'em
off the counter.
So women are the pot.
They heat 'em up.
They hold 'em.
They contain them.
But who wants to be a pot?
Who the hell
said we're not soup?
I don't think that's true.
It's been my experience.
But you know, I wouldn't
have helped Abe out
If I didn't think he was
some very interesting soup.
Listen, go ahead without me.
Another time.
Are you angry or lovesick?
I don't know.
Night, peg.
Could you hold that?
Hello.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net