I wanna marry you.
Last season on AMC's Mad Men...
Well, ho-ho.
Now it's the time.
Gentlemen, Jai Alai.
I made an appointment with
the divorce attorney.
Forget it. I'm not gonna let
you break up this family.
I didn't break up this family.
P.P.L. is being sold and
us along with it.
- Fire us.
- Why would I?
We'll make you a partner.
- Who the hell is Henry Francis?
- No one.
You're a whore!
Pete, we're starting a new agency.
We're here to talk to
you about joining us.
Henry, I have three children.
I don't want you
owing them anything.
I want you to know that
I'm not gonna fight you.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Mommy, she's not Margaret,
she's Jane.
She's my wife.
I need you to find
me an apartment.
Sterling Cooper Draper Pryce,
how may I help you?
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Who is don draper?
Excuse me?
What do men say
when you ask that?
Well, they usually take
a minute to think about it
Then they do something cute.
One creative director
said he was a lion tamer.
I don't want to do that.
- In the third person?
- I don't know.
Knockout wife, two kids,
house in Westchester.
Take the train...
maybe you take your car
Now that you can afford it.
And who told you that?
Anything?
I mean, now's your chance.
Well, as I said before,
I'm from the Midwest.
We were taught that it's not
polite to talk about yourself.
Obviously your glo-coat
floor wax commercials
caused a bit of a squeal,
On the creative side anyway.
What made you think
of this idea?
I wanted it to be
indistinguishable
from the movies.
I wanted people to be
watching it and say,
"what's happening
in the story right now?"
Oh, it's something else.
"It's not an ad."
At least not for
the first 30 seconds of it.
Very good then.
I think I have all I need.
It's only
a few hundred words,
but on the bright side,
The picture may be
bigger than the article.
Oh, uh, you all should meet.
This is Jack Hammond
from "advertising age."
Roger sterling
and Pete Campbell.
I hope we're not
interrupting this crisp
And engaging portrait
you're painting.
Ahh...
Steady there.
- What happened there?
- Korea.
We're grateful
for your sacrifice.
- Peter.
- Jack.
Well, it's nice
to meet you all.
I'd love to bend your ear
when I finish my book.
Certainly.
Don, it was a pleasure.
- I look forward to the article.
- We all do.
My Uncle lost his leg
hitching a trailer.
Used to ask me
to scratch his toes.
- He didn't have any.
- We don't have time, Roger.
One quick pop, Louise.
All right, where is this party?
- The Sheraton?
- A wooden leg...
They're so cheap they can't
even afford a whole reporter.
I'm Peter Campbell
and I'm assuming you're Jim.
- And this must be Murray.
- Bob... Murray stayed
in Portland.
Too bad.
Missing jackhammer season.
Roger sterling.
- And you must be
Donald draper.
- Don.
Bob.
We're very very excited you
had time to meet with us, don.
Murray told us y&r
had done glo-coat.
Turns out
everybody in New York
except him knows it's you.
And I think they're
a little jealous.
Can't tell who
the client is here.
I know a little,
but what we need to know...
What don needs to know is
What exactly is your concern?
I must say I'm getting
tired of saying this today.
Next time just have
one meeting.
We at Jantzen have had
a steady 25% bite
of the apple.
But the two-piece
is most of our concern.
You have a great bikini.
I've spent some time
with the catalogue
And I would say
no concerns at all.
It's not a bikini.
A bikini is underwear
you wear to the beach.
We make a two-piece
bathing suit.
We're a family company.
And nowadays it's tough
to make a dent
If your ads don't look
like a girlie magazine.
Do you want women who want
bikinis to buy your two-piece
Or do you just want to make sure
women who want a two-piece
Don't suddenly buy a bikini?
My lord.
That question just tied
a knot in my brain.
Our competitors get bigger
The smaller they make
that swimsuit.
We don't do that.
We would like to find a way
without playing in the gutter.
And that's just who
our customers are.
Right now.
I love how they sit there
like a couple of choirboys.
You know one of them's
leaving New York with v.D.
Where the hell have you been?
- What's the problem?
- Don!
- Can you give me a minute?
- I don't mind waiting.
- How'd it go?
- Get back to work.
How was your interview?
Count to 100 and buzz me.
You missed Jeff Atherton.
He came here expressly
to see you.
I'm sorry, I didn't know
he was coming and I don't
know who that is.
You have no idea how tiny
this place looks to a stranger.
Did you tell him about
the second floor?
I refuse to be any part
of that charade.
I wanted an office downtown.
We overspent.
We could have got
a lot more for our money.
And we could have had
a conference table.
Atherton thought the lack
of a conference table
Was deliberate.
He felt that a...
Circle of chairs
demands a conversation.
About why there is no table.
they loved you.
What exactly is the problem?
Well, first of all
they're prudes.
Second of all
y&r were standing in
the hallway when we left.
You've been on
a cattle call before.
When the competition was fair.
Every hour of my time
has to be accounted for
In the growth of this company.
Get me in a room
where I have a chance.
In the end it's going to come
down to big versus small.
There's two firms
Kenyon & Eckhardt,
And D'Arcy.
They'll cancel
each other out.
Y&r has six floors
of creative.
They can throw bodies
at this account for weeks.
- We don't have
that kind of firepower.
- We don't have to.
We're the scrappy upstart.
You don't say that
to the clients, do you?
Your accountant is waiting.
Send him in.
Creatively, y&r is not capable
of living in this neighborhood.
You know why?
Because you don't work there.
- John.
- Marsha.
John!
Happy Thanksgiving.
Oooh, my mother's going
to be over the moon.
Enjoy it.
It's the last thing
we're going to get from them.
- What?
- Did you kill sugarberry?
- That's a third of my work.
- Stop jumping to conclusions.
I guess when Kreutzer
said they were going
to send us all hams
He really meant one
in a cardboard box
with no note.
It's about as subtle
as an atomic bomb.
Maybe they're cheap.
Do you honestly think
this is a good sign?
The work was
old-fashioned.
And whose fault is that?
Well, testing at four
supermarkets in queens,
How much were they
spending? Nothing.
If the test was a success,
they would have gone national
And they could be
a big account.
Damn it!
I thought we were
getting on a streak.
Does this mean I'm down
to two days a week?
- Don hated the work.
- Put the ham on his desk.
He's probably having
Thanksgiving dinner
alone in there.
That's not nice.
Marsha!
I'm serious.
Okay, life insurance policy,
it's a company policy.
It pays the company,
not the family.
What do you think?
It wouldn't be bad to have
a little security for the kids.
According to this,
I'm already a wealthy man.
Uncle Sam will take
a healthy bite.
He already has.
And...
The only other issue
is the house.
What about it?
Well, October 1st
she was supposed to be out.
It seemed so far away
when we agreed to that.
Get her and him out of there
and sell it.
I can call Ben Michaelson
and have him draft a doozy.
Start world war III?
You're carrying a mortgage,
Plus insurance and taxes
For a house you don't live in.
Leave it alone.
So how are your balls?
Are you enjoying yourself?
Come on.
I don't want it like this.
I want it like that.
Not too much of that,
just a little like this.
And then they look at it
and they don't like it.
Two of their test markets
are in Jewish neighborhoods.
They're idiots.
How much does it cost for us
to buy all the product?
Too much and we'd have
to do it every day.
So how much does it cost
for us to get
100 women to line up
at one store, one afternoon,
Clean them out once?
100 people?
Do you know how big
a line that is?
People would talk about it.
- It's a p.R. Stunt.
- We don't do that.
- Why not?
- Because you can't
charge for it.
So what?
Two women
fighting over one ham,
But they have to really fight.
They have to get arrested
or something.
Because it's the last ham.
We don't have to write a play.
It's Thanksgiving.
They're shopping.
The stakes are very high.
Old Chuck Dewey could
probably get a story
In the "daily news"
for a case of something.
$25 per actress.
We could get Gladys
what's-her-name.
Who's the old lady who never
takes off her mittens?
- I don't have any money.
- John!
Marsha!
I can use my expense account
if I say they're whores.
Top-shelf liquor,
what's that gonna run?
Harry gets a case a month
For sticking his nose
up some guy's ass at n.B.C.
Should I run it by don?
Really?
We'll see.
I'll call casting.
Oh, good, I got you
when you're vulnerable.
- What do you need?
- Someone white to carve
our Turkey.
I can't, Roger.
I have plans.
You told me that.
Then you told me you had
the kids the day after.
But you never said no
to Jane's friend Bethany.
- No.
- I was thinking
the other day
About what happens
when you leave here
and it made me very upset.
I could say the same thing.
I'll paint you the picture
that's in my mind.
But if it's true,
I might kill myself.
I've hardly been a monk.
Forget that she knows Jane.
This girl's terrific.
She looks like Virginia Mayo.
She's 25, mount Holyoke
gymnastics team.
See her this weekend.
You hit it off,
come Turkey day maybe
you can stuff her.
Sweetheart,
8:00 Saturday night,
Jimmy's la grange
for beauty and the beast.
- Roger.
- They have chicken Kiev.
The butter squirts everywhere.
- Hello, Mr. Draper.
- Hello, Celia.
I made you some pork chops.
They're good cold too.
I look forward to it.
But you don't eat nothing.
- Have you seen my shine Kit?
- I put it on the top
of the closet.
- the children coming
this weekend?
No.
You need to put things
back where you found them.
I didn't want to leave it
in the middle of the floor.
Okay, good night.
You have a good weekend.
And eat something.
Let me out of here!
Footprints on a wet floor...
That's no longer
a hanging offense.
Glo-coat's
patented formula
Goes on easy
and dries in seconds.
So how do you know Jane?
Before you ask me all
the questions, you have
to let me finish one glass.
I don't have to ask you
any questions.
I think I'm actually nervous.
I haven't done this
since college.
Not that it was so long ago,
although it seems like it.
I borrowed a dress.
You sat down so fast
I didn't get a good look.
Do you want to see it?
I can't believe I did that.
It's hard to believe
there are two girls
who can wear that.
Don, I want to lift
a shadow off this evening.
I know this is your first date.
First that Roger
was involved in.
Oh, of course.
I'm sure. It's just...
I'm breaking
a lot of my rules
seeing a divorced man.
But Jane has made you
her personal cause.
And there are so many
real problems in the world.
I know.
The world is so dark right now.
The country?
My goodness,
you've made me feel very
serious all of a sudden.
I don't know if I can make you
feel better about the world.
One of the boys killed
in Mississippi...
Andrew Goodman,
he was from here.
A girlfriend of mine
knew him from summer camp.
Is that what it takes
to change things?
What do you do?
I'm an actress.
But right now I'm a super
in the opera.
- And what is that?
- A supernumerary.
We're the actors
that fill the stage.
Like the chorus?
Mmm, no singing.
I do a lot of mock drinking.
I'm a wench.
I'm a...
Courtesan.
Part of a harem.
It depends on the opera.
That is truly fascinating.
I love the music.
And I love backstage.
Our costumes are as good
as the singers.
And I love the stories.
They're very romantic.
Have you been?
I have.
But only for business
so I've never enjoyed it.
Well, then you must
come as my guest.
They give the supers tickets
instead of paying
a decent wage.
- Madam?
- Oh, I don't even
need to look.
Chicken Kiev.
They make you wear a bib.
Come on, let's have some fun.
Two chicken Kievs.
The barbizon.
I bet that would
make a great opera.
It would.
Well, I guess
this is good night.
Okay.
Good night.
So am I going to see you
at Roger and Jane's
for Thanksgiving?
It's tempting, but...
I have plans.
Oh, I'm sure the holidays
must be very complex.
It may have been awhile
since you've had to pick up
on messages,
But I want to see you again.
How about right now?
I stopped the meter.
We can start it again.
It'll be like
I just picked you up.
Will you please take a weak no?
Let's see where
we are new year's eve.
- If it's meant
to be, it'll keep.
- Let me walk you in.
No.
I know that trick.
Waverly and 6th Avenue.
I think you both really
acquitted yourselves well.
She doesn't know when to stop.
You don't know when to stop.
My objective
was to get the ham.
No one told you to hit me.
That wasn't part of it.
The important thing is that...
oh, here's Mr. Campbell.
I've been assured you ladies
can look for your names
And perhaps your picture
in Monday's "daily news."
- What section?
- It's the "daily news."
it's one big section.
All in all,
not a bad way
to spend a Sunday.
Can you go back to the market
and get me some aspirin?
We probably shouldn't have any
more contact for the time being.
- shall we?
We really appreciate
your talent
And of course, your discretion.
- You hurt me.
- Ow ow ow!
Ladies, ladies, ladies!
- Daisy!
- Walk her to the train.
- Are you okay, dear?
- Yeah.
Let's get you in a cab.
- Good morning.
- Welcome back.
How was Los Angeles?
Very hard to leave.
I would love a vacation.
It wasn't a vacation.
I had a lot of tsuris
with Lucy and Desi.
Has someone been
using my office?
Mr. Sterling doesn't
have a television.
I'm calling
a meeting for 11:00.
No, make it 1:00.
Do we have a table yet?
1:30 and no.
- Hi.
- Yes?
- Do you know where
the seacore rough cut is?
I got it!
Don't you want to know why?
I sold the jai alai TV special.
Really?
A.B.C.
They're moving towards
All these eccentric
sporting events... go-karts.
Well, that's very exciting.
Can you get someone to track
down a cup of coffee for me?
And I'd love
a grapefruit juice.
And, Joan?
- That is my news.
- I won't even tell people
after it's aired.
Good morning,
Mr. Draper.
Don, can I speak
with you for a minute?
Morning.
- Lane, would you
excuse us for a minute?
- Of course.
Good morning, don.
You know,
No one who's ever been
associated with an actual event
Has thought it's been portrayed
honestly in the newspaper.
"Donald draper,
or don as he is known"
Perhaps in an attempt
to appear humble,
is a handsome cipher.
One imagines somewhere
in an attic
"There's a painting of him
that's rapidly aging."
For a guy from "ad age"
he can really write.
- He also says you're married.
- Jesus.
He never asked me that.
Did he check any facts?
You didn't give him any facts.
- He had to make
some assumptions.
- My job is to write ads,
Not go around
talking about who I am.
Who knows who you are?
This was supposed to be
an advertisement for the firm.
Why do you have so many copies?
I bought one to read.
I was going to buy one
to frame in reception,
and then I read it.
I just wanted
to get them all
before anyone else did.
It'll be lining bird cages
by Friday.
This is a missed opportunity.
You turned all the sizzle
from glo-coat into a wet fart.
Plus you sound like a prick.
Well, it's done.
Stay away from
one-legged reporters.
Yeah, I was thinking
about that...
Who is he to criticize anybody?
Just so you
don't kill yourself,
there was some good news.
Jane's friend found
you to be charming.
Although a little
grabby in the car.
That is good news.
Thank you.
She liked you.
Maybe you should have
fondled peg-leg Pete.
They raise you up
and they knock you down.
I don't know what
I could have done differently.
I believe that you were
being modest, but he didn't.
I'm sorry, but after
the year you've had,
It's just not
appropriate anymore.
He's expecting us!
- Is Joey coming?
- I'm here.
- Oh.
- Why can't you come
to our office?
- Do you want to hear what
sugarberry said or not?
- Shoot.
It was uproarious.
First it's Darryl,
and he tells me about
How they stared at
the article all day yesterday
worrying about a lawsuit.
So I hang up and debate
whether or not to tell don...
Throw myself on my sword.
And then Kreutzer calls
To tell me other papers
picked up the story.
And I think,
"he knows it's us,"
but how could he?
And he said everyone,
especially Darryl,
was very excited.
He's sorry someone got hurt,
But more people will
taste their ham now
And they'll love it.
It's beautiful.
How do you put something
like this in your book?
You can't.
We can't even
charge them.
It wouldn't be a bad idea
For them to increase
their media budget.
- Seize the moment.
- With more crappy ads?
- Hopefully not.
- You use it.
The winner of
the ham battle is you.
Can you imagine?
Lane's dentures would
drop out of his head
If we came in
with an additional buy.
"our hams are worth
fighting for."
A cartoon pilgrim and an Indian
in a tug of war with the ham.
Old ladies will smile.
Why didn't you pitch
that two months ago?
It's good on its own.
A slogan's nothing
when you have a good idea.
Black crayon.
I need it in an hour.
Chop chop, Joey.
Clara, could you get Darryl
for me at sugarberry?
Tell him it's urgent.
I may need you.
Horace cook, Jr.
It's urgent.
Ho-ho!
How was Tijuana?
I have to say,
it's a very flattering
picture.
And I don't think
I'd mind being
described that way.
Mr. Crane,
you're a salesman.
You do not want to be
known as mysterious.
There'll be
no further discussion.
I just got off
the phone with ho-ho.
- Jai alai is leaving.
- What?
- It's over.
- Bullshit. I just sold
a TV special to a.B.C.
Well, apparently don didn't
mention them in the article.
I didn't mention anyone.
That's the reporter's job.
- Spectacular.
- What the hell's ho-ho
doing reading "ad age"?
- Fix it.
- Todd got all the partners
From c.G.C. To call and they
worked him up and down.
They told him
we laugh about him.
I don't!
Get him him on the phone,
Get him in here
or camp out in his driveway.
He hung up on me.
I think he was crying.
How much was left in
ho-ho anyway?
We'll survive with jai alai
off our list.
We will survive,
but for how long?
The loss of jai alai
Makes lucky strike
71% of our billings.
It's an untenably
insecure position.
Harry, why don't you call
and pretend like you don't
know any of this.
Give it an hour
so he'll take the call.
I wish we really had
a second floor so I could
jump off it.
I'm going to have to get
you another interview.
"the wall street journal."
And what do I do differently?
I told him the truth.
Who gives a crap
what I say anyway?
My work speaks for me.
Turning creative success
into business is your work.
And you've failed.
It'll pass.
- Happy Thanksgiving, everybody.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
We started without you.
Oh, grandma Pauline,
I told you mother's
was at noon.
- We already ate.
- You're supposed to overeat
on Thanksgiving.
Ooh, thank you.
Jamie, you'll have something?
We missed dessert.
You're next to your father.
- Put up some coffee, dear.
- Hi, daddy.
Isn't that sweet?
We didn't forget you.
- What do you say?
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- After you eat.
The traffic was simply murder.
That's because that's
what's become of this country.
Everyone has two
thanksgivings to go to.
Maybe we have twice as much
to be thankful for.
Don't you like the food, dear?
- No.
- Sally draper, that's rude.
- You love cranberry sauce.
- It has seeds in it.
- How about the sweet potato?
- I'm not hungry.
Look, there's marshmallow.
oh lord.
She might have a fever.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right, dear.
- Isabel, can you bring a rag?
Ow, stop pinching me!
I love sweet potatoes.
- Isabel!
Happy Thanksgiving.
- Do you want a drink?
- I don't have much time.
- I have supper
with my family.
- Oh.
- Of course you do.
- Should I not have
mentioned my family?
I never know how
you're going to react.
No, that's fine.
- Let me take off my brassiere.
- No. In a minute.
Stop telling me what to do.
I know what you want.
So do it.
Harder.
Again.
Hold on.
Surprise, it's for you.
Why did you answer it?
It was the third try.
I couldn't take it.
- Hello?
- Happy Thanksgiving.
Happy Thanksgiving.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I didn't know you'd have guests.
What's wrong?
I need $280 for bail.
Bye.
- Where are you?
- It... it's not for me.
Spit it out, honey.
You're going to laugh.
Pete and I hired some actresses
To get in a fight
over a sugarberry ham.
You know, as a stunt.
We got them to increase
their media budget.
Hello?
I'm here.
Well, one of them pressed
charges against the other
For assault.
It's $80 bail
And $100 apiece to keep
their mouths shut.
And it has to happen today.
Call Pete!
Do you think
you're my first call?
Hello.
I'm so sorry to bother you.
- I oughta let you
Twist in the wind.
- It still worked out.
- You'll be very happy.
- I'm not happy.
And I don't think
it's funny or cute.
You run something
like that by me first.
I would have kept you
from looking like an idiot,
Or worse yet,
making me look like one.
Is that what you want?
You want people to think
we're idiots, Peggy?
Hey, there's no reason
for name-calling.
- She's been agonizing.
- Who are you?
I'm her fiance.
Mark, don't.
Why'd you bring him
up here if you didn't
want him involved?
I know.
I'm sorry, don.
- Fiance?
- It just came out.
- Did you put the dog out?
- It's cold outside.
But I locked her
in the laundry room.
It's not cold in here.
Sally.
I was calling daddy.
Hello?
I wanted to wish him
a happy Thanksgiving.
You'll see him tomorrow.
You want to call him
to complain about
how awful I am?
Don't expect any sympathy when
he hears my side of the story.
- Don't!
- Go to bed.
I'm going to have them take
that phone out of the hallway.
Mmm.
Tomorrow when the kids go,
Why don't we have Carla
take the baby and we'll
drive to a nice dinner?
Maybe Essex.
The Griswold inn.
Okay.
I'm really full, Betty.
Daddy!
- Oooh!
- Dad.
- How much Turkey did you eat?
- I ate everything.
hello, daddy.
Hello.
- 9:00 tomorrow night.
- Where's the baby?
I had Carla take him.
You weren't going to.
- Henry and I have plans.
- I'd like to see him.
- Hello, don.
- Henry.
Come on, let's go.
Garage door.
- What are you doing?
- You know what I'm doing.
The button fell off my pajamas.
I'll sew it on in the morning.
You know how to sew?
I can do a button.
I'll show you.
I'll leave the light on
in the bathroom
So there won't be
any more problems, okay?
- Okay.
- Good night, daddy.
Good night,
Both of you.
do you have your key?
- Hello?
- Maybe they're asleep.
go upstairs.
Let go!
What the hell is the dog
doing in the house?
You run up to bed.
I'll wait.
For what?
Oh.
It's almost 10:00.
- I thought you said 10:00.
- She didn't.
I've waited for you
plenty of times.
Henry, do you mind?
- Betty?
- It's okay.
Does that mean I should stay
or not stay?
Stay.
When are you moving out?
I don't know.
You were supposed
to be out a month ago.
We haven't found the right
place for the kids.
Well, either do as we agreed
or I'm going to need
to collect rent.
- What?
- Or you could just buy it
from me if you want to.
I can't believe you.
Don, it's temporary.
Believe me, Henry,
everybody thinks this
is temporary.
Good night.
He has some nerve.
I know you don't want
to hear this,
But he's right.
Haven't the kids been
through enough change
already?
I can't just uproot them
with no place to go.
You're not even looking.
There's nothing out there,
and he doesn't decide.
- miss Olson is here
to see you.
Send her in.
They sent one for each of us.
Could have just as easily
fired us.
But they didn't
because they sold
more hams.
And now you get
to tell them why,
if you want.
I think they'll be impressed.
Well, I'm not.
I try and stay away from
these kinds of shenanigans.
But I guess you knew that
or you would have told me.
It was going great
until it wasn't.
Thanks for the ham.
I should have told you.
Since when do you
have a fiance?
I don't.
But you didn't have
to do that that way.
You brought him with you
because you thought I
wouldn't embarrass you.
At least I'm thinking ahead.
Doesn't always work, does it?
You need to think
a little bit more about
the image of this agency.
Well, nobody knows
about the ham stunt,
So our image remains
pretty much where
you left it.
I won't need you in
the Jantzen presentation.
- Now you're being spiteful.
- No.
I just think it would
be better not to have
a girl in the room.
You know something?
We are all here because of you.
All we want to do
is please you.
Why don't I put them
in the pantry?
Christmas is around the corner.
Put them in the basement.
Did the children
like their gifts?
They did.
It's nice the holiday is
memorable in some other way.
I'm sorry a little girl
spoiled your Thanksgiving.
Next time I'll tell her
not to get sick.
I've raised children
in my life, Henry.
They're terrified of her.
You don't know
any of the people
you're talking about.
Well, I know
what you see in her.
And you could have gotten it
without marrying.
Why can't you
give her a chance?
- She loves you.
- She's a silly woman.
Honestly, Henry,
I don't know how you can stand
living in that man's dirt.
You go to the swimming pool,
you go to the beach,
Take off your robe,
you head into the cabana.
There's no other way
to slice it, you're
getting undressed.
Can I put my feet on this?
- Pretend like
it's your living room.
- Thank you.
What separates a bathing suit
from underwear?
The cut and the print
of the cloth
and some sort of
gentlemen's agreement.
"so well built,
We can't show you
the second floor."
I think that's
a little suggestive.
Good. That's what
I was going for.
A wink, but it's not a leer.
We don't want a wink.
I think I explained
our product is for
modest people.
Modest people want
to be stimulated too.
This draws them in in a way
That will make your competitors
seem crude and obvious.
Plus they'll be dying
to see the suit.
They'll be dying
to see the girl.
And for all we know
she's not even wearing a top.
You'll get them into the store.
Isn't that the point?
It's not wholesome.
It's not...
did I tell you we're
a family company?
I think I know what
you're looking for.
A couple of women
bouncing a beach ball,
Little girl in front of them
building a sandcastle.
Your competitors are
gonna keep killing you
Because you're too scared
of the skin
That your two-piece
was designed to show off.
Well, it's somehow dirtier
Not seeing anything.
You need to decide what kind
of company you want to be...
Comfortable and dead
or risky and possibly rich.
All I know is
we don't want that.
Well, gentlemen,
you were wondering what
a creative agency looks like,
There you have it.
Hope you enjoyed
looking in the window.
Give me a minute.
Where are you going?
Control yourself.
Now cool off.
Hopefully Campbell can talk
them into hearing a few more
ideas in a week or so.
What?
No.
That's not the point.
Out.
Get out.
- Don.
- Excuse me?
Get your things and get out
of my office now.
Come on, let's go.
Call Bert Cooper's man
at "the wall street journal."
There's always a name
in every partnership
That defines who they are.
In the case of sterling
Cooper draper Pryce
Would you say
that's Donald draper?
Yes.
Really?
Last year our agency
was being swallowed whole.
I realized I had two choices.
I could die of boredom
Or holster up my guns.
So I walked into lane Pryce's
office and I said,
"fire us."
Two days later
we were operating out
of the Pierre hotel.
Within a year we had
taken over two floors
of the time-life building.
www.tvsubtitles.net