Seems like forever,
since the four of us have
been out to eat, you know?
Just the guys.
Oh, God! Yes, we get it.
You have a girlfriend now.
A little jealous, are we?
No, I'm not jealous.
All right, I'd kill a
hobo if it'll get me laid.
Now, can we order?
Oh, dear Lord, they re-did the menu.
So what? It's the same food.
Oh, is it? Look at this.
General Tso's Chicken
is no longer listed under "specialties."
It's now under "chicken."
So?
Yes, General Tso.
Not "Tso," the chicken, "so" the question.
So?
So, why is it no longer a specialty?
Did the chef lose confidence
in the dish or himself?
And look over here.
"Shrimp in mobster sauce."
What is "mobster sauce"?
It's obviously a typo.
Perhaps. Or perhaps this restaurant's
now a front for organized crime.
For all we know, the mobster sauce
contains actual chunks of deceased mobsters.
No, no, no, no-- I think it just means
it's the kind of sauce that mobsters like.
It doesn't mean any of that!
It's a typo.
You know what? Let's just get a pizza.
Good idea. We'll go to Corleone's.
Sure, no mobsters there.
You know, the more I think about it,
the mobster sauce couldn't possibly contain
chunks of mobster.
And why is that?
It was listed under "seafood."
What if they were mobsters
who slept with the fishes?
Leonard, are we having a
serious conversation or not?
What the...?
The TV is gone.
So are our laptops.
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
It's all right.
They didn't take my comic books.
Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state
Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait!
The Earth began to cool
The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools
We built the Wall
We built the pyramids
Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery
That all started with a big bang
Bang
Big Bang Theory 3x13
The Bozeman Reaction
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com ---
They took our TV,
two laptops,
four external hard-drives,
our PS2, our PS3,
our X-Box, our X-Box 360,
our classic Nintendo,
our Super Nintendo,
our Nintendo 64 and our Wii.
We like games.
Right, games. They took Halo 1,
Halo 2, Halo 3, Call of Duty 1,
Call of Duty 2, Call of Duty 3,
Rock Band, Rock Band 2,
Final Fantasy 1 thru 9, The Legend of
Zelda,
The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time,
The Legend of Zelda:
Twilight Princess,
Super Mario Brothers,
Super Mario Galaxy,
Mario and Sonic at the
Winter Olympics...
...and Ms. Pacman.
Assorted video games.
When does the CSI team get here?
What?
In anticipation of their arrival,
I've bagged some evidence.
One of the thieves had the audacity
to quench his thirst while
ransacking our home.
You should be able to pull
some good prints off this.
And now, here are my prints
so you can rule me out as a suspect.
What about me?
I'm sorry, Leonard.
It's too early to discount
the possibility of this being an inside job.
Would I be completely out of
line to ask you to shoot him?
I'd be happy to put him under a 72-hour
psychiatric hold.
I'm not crazy.
My mother had me tested.
We're done here.
Call this number, and we'll
fax you a copy of the report
so you can submit it to
your insurance company.
I-I'm sorry.
That's the end of your inquiry?
Do you have any more information
that might be relevant?
Oh, my goodness.
Where do I begin? For instance--
my laptop contained
four out of the five gedankenexperiments
necessary for a cogent restatement
of the quantum measurement problem.
How is that going to help them?
Well, they could monitor
scientific publications
and see if anyone posts such a
cogent restatement in the next
couple of months. If so,
the authors are most likely
in possession of my stolen laptop.
Good night, fellas.
Come on, Bochco.
What are we supposed to do now?
The only thing we can do.
Watch TV on our phones
until the criminals return
and bludgeon us to death in our sleep.
Does that mean you've
ruled me out as a suspect?
Oh, how I wish I could.
I do not have to urinate.
I am the master of my own bladder.
Drat.
I can't believe it.
If I hadn't been working the dinner shift,
I would've run right into the robbers.
Hey, there's no reason for you to be scared.
I'm not scared.
I would've gone all Nebraska on their asses.
Leonard and Penny.
Hand me the bat.
We just had a major crime in the building,
and you open the door
without asking who it is?
It won't happen again. What's up?
Nothing.
I just wanted to see if you were both okay.
We're fine, Sheldon.
All right, then.
Good night. Good night.
That was weird, even for him. Mm-hmm.
Leonard and Penny.
Who is it?
Sheldon. Sheldon Cooper.
Yes?
May I come in?
Yeah.
I see you're drinking wine.
Yes, we are.
And we're about to go to bed.
Uh-huh.
Sheldon, do you want to sleep here tonight?
Oh, as small as Leonard is,
I don't think the two of you'd
be comfortable on the couch.
What do you want?
It's not what I want,
it's what evolution wants.
Human beings are primates.
Primates have evolved to live in groups,
both for protection and support.
But you don't like other people.
I do tonight.
It's scary over there.
It's getting scary here, too.
Um... three little kittens?
Three little pigs?
God, I don't know.
Star Wars?
Did we win? Can we go to bed?
Good Lord-- I could not
have made this easier.
Hydrogen atom, H,
plus pigs minus pea-- Higgs.
Bow, General Zod trapped
in the Phantom Zone.
Bow-zone.
Pear. Tickle.
Pear-tickle.
Higgs Boson Particle.
How could you not get that?
He's right, Penny. It's all there.
Sheldon, sweetie,
I know you're feeling insecure,
but we've really got to go to sleep.
All right. I'll take the first watch
and wake you at 0400.
Great. Good night.
Wait, wait-- what's 0400?
4:00 a.m. That's, like, in 45 minutes.
Just keep walking.
It's quiet out there.
Maybe a little too quiet.
Where are you going?
Just gonna take a look around outside.
Bad idea.
No, Jim, don't open the door!
Listen to her, Jim.
Don't worry.
There's no one out there.
Leonard and Penny!
Who is it?
All right, we've got a titanium dead bolt
and a reinforced jamb
controlled by a state-of-th
e-art electronic access system.
What if they cut the power?
There's a 200-watt uninterruptible
backup power supply.
What if someone steals my keys? There are
independent voice and fingerprint scanners.
What if someone kidnaps me,
forces me to record my voice,
and then cuts off my thumb?
I'll send them a basket of muffins.
Now, inside, we've got motion detectors,
infrared sensors,
and cameras connected to a server
running state-of-th
e-art facial recognition software.
Where did you get all this stuff?
Eh, I got a buddy over at
the Department of Defense.
He just gave it to you?
I'm sure he would have if I had asked.
Ironically, their security
isn't all that good.
Raj, your car is blocking me...
COMPUTER VOICE: Intruder alert,
intruder alert.
Intruder alert. What the hell?
Intruder alert. Sorry, let me help you.
Wonderful security system
if we're attacked by a school of tuna.
Don't worry, the net's
going to be electrified.
You picture her on the floor,
spasming uncontrollably.
Better.
Sheldon's journal.
Security system in place.
However, sleep continues to elude me.
I've seen the underbelly
of Pasadena...
this so-called City of Roses, and it haunts
me.
Ah, the injustice.
I lie here awake, tormented,
while out there evil lurks,
probably playing Donkey Kong on my classic
Nintendo.
Oh, dear.
I am the master of my own bladder.
Leonard and Penny.
Oh, my...
God, Sheldon.
What the hell are you doing out there?
I heard a noise.
It was us.
We knocked over a lamp.
Why would you knock over a lamp?
We were going to have... He doesn't need
to know what we were doing, Leonard.
Oh.
No, she's right, I don't need
to know what you were doing.
Carry on.
What are you doing?
Use the door.
Good thinking.
Perhaps I'll check the perimeter
and make some warm milk.
Great, you do that.
Would you like me to
bring you some warm milk?
I'm lactose intolerant.
And you don't wish to alarm
me with any more loud noises.
Very thoughtful.
Warm milk, Penny?
No, thanks.
Fine.
Good night to you, sir.
Miss.
Sorry about that.
Ugh, what can you do?
Here.
Intruder alert, intruder alert.
Looks like Wolowitz got the net electrified.
Sheldon, are you okay?
I-I'm fine...
although I'm no longer the
master of my own bladder.
My new computer came
with Windows 7.
Windows 7 is much more use
r- friendly than Windows Vista.
I don't like that.
Don't you think looking
for a new city to live in
is a bit of an overreaction?
Our apartment was broken into,
our security system tried to kill me,
and as a result,
I'm leaving Pasadena forever.
Tell me how that's overreacting.
Come on, Sheldon, you can't move.
Don't you need to stay in one place
so the mother ship can find you
when it returns?
Oh, if that were only true.
Unfortunately, as I'm earthbound
for the foreseeable future,
I need to find a location
that's more hospitable
than the mean streets of Pasadena, like...
Enid, Oklahoma.
Low crime rate
and high-speed Internet connectivity...
but no model train shops.
Sorry, Enid.
Is he quitting his job at the university?
Oh, no, he's going to telecommute.
Everybody's really excited about it.
All right.
Boone, North Carolina.
"Every summer since 1952,
"Boone has hosted an outdoor
amphitheater portrayal
of the life and times of
its namesake, Dan'l Boone."
Sounds like something that
would attract the wrong crowd.
Penny, you're from Nebraska, correct?
Born and raised.
It will take me a few days to get settled.
After I do, I will e-mail you detailed PDFs
containing diagrams and instructions
that will guide you through
packing and shipping
the rest of my possessions
to Bozeman, Montana.
In the meantime, please forward my mail.
Any place specific
or just the Bozeman, Montana Loony Bin?
I sense you're making a joke,
but Bozeman does have a comedy
club called The Loony Bin,
so do not forward my mail there.
Oh, come on.
So you were the victim of a crime.
That's part of life.
When my great-grandfather
first came to this country,
he put all his hopes and dreams
into this little butcher shop he ran
on the Lower East Side of New York.
You know what happened?
Every customer who walked
into that butcher shop
and asked for a pound of liver,
got ripped off.
But...
those people moved on, and so should you.
I am moving on.
I'm going to be a Bozite.
They call themselves "Bozites"?
They should. It's one of the first things
I plan to bring up upon arrival.
Sheldon, I can't believe I'm saying this,
but I'm going to miss you. Please,
Penny, as you know, I'm not comfortable
with prolonged goo
d-byes and maudlin displays of emotion,
so I prepared a short video.
Greetings.
As you know, I'm not comfortable
with prolonged good-byes
and maudlin displays of emotion,
so I prepared this short video.
The four of you are three
of my closest friends
and one treasured acquaintance.
Though I cannot state
categorically that my life
will be diminished by not having you in it,
I am comfortable if you
choose to believe that.
Since you intend to remain
in this lawless metropolitan area,
statistics suggest that
you will succumb to tragic
and gruesome ends before we meet again.
Live long and prosper.
Sheldon, that's so...
You might want to lock the door behind me.
This isn't Bozeman.
How the hell do I know who's the friend
and who's the acquaintance?
That is a bracing cold,
an invigorating cold.
Lord, is it cold!
Help you with your bags, sir?
Thank you, fellow Bozite.
And may I say, you are the
living embodiment of all
the promises made by our lovely
town's Chamber of Commerce.
Wait!
Excuse me!
One ticket to Pasadena, California, please.
Hey, look who's back!
Interesting.
The acquaintance is the first to greet me.
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com ---
www.tvsubtitles.net