Wow, Sheldon, I cannot believe
you made up your own game.
Oh!
Research Lab is more
than a game.
It's like the slogan says,
"The Physics is theoretical,
but the fun is real."
We must not be playing it right.
All right, five.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, wow, look at that.
My Department of Defense
research grant is renewed.
Oh! Great roll!
Now you can demolish your
Soviet-style cyclotron
and build the large
Hadron Collider.
Yay.
You're a natural
at this, Penny.
And as the first beta testers,
you two'll have quite the edge
when we play with Wolowitz
and Koothrappali on Sunday.
Oh, gee, Sheldon,
I don't think we can
play on Sunday.
Why not?
Because of the reasons
that Penny will now tell you.
Penny?
Actually, I have to pick up my
friend Justin from the airport.
There you go-- she has to pick up
her friend Justin at the airport.
And I can't play 'cause
I'm going with her-- right?
Um, yeah, if you want.
I mean, there may not be room.
He's got a lot of stuff--
like guitars and amplifiers.
Wait.
What are you talking about?
My friend, Justin.
Pay attention, Leonard.
That's why she can't
play on Sunday.
Who is this Justin?
- Your turn, Leonard.
- I told you about him.
- No, you didn't.
- Roll the dice, Leonard.
Yeah-- my friend from Omaha;
plays the guitar.
Anyway, he's coming to L.A.
looking for some session work,
so I told him he could
just crash on my couch
for a few weeks.
Come on, Leonard--
if you roll a six,
Penny dies horribly in
a nuclear meltdown.
See what I mean when I
say the fun is real?
Hang on.
Some guy is going to be
sleeping on your couch?
He's not "some guy."
He's my friend.
So by "friend," do you
mean "friend friend,"
"gay friend," or "ex boyfriend
"who you're now platonic with
but still might have a
thing for you friend"?
Well, he's definitely not gay.
Oh, ho-ho, a definitely
not gay musician
sleeping on my
girlfriend's couch.
Yippee.
Okay, we went out a little
bit, a long time ago.
But we were never
like "going out."
Okay, not to be pedantic,
but last I checked
"went out" was in fact the past
tense of "going out"--
which I think we all know
is a popular euphemism
for "saw each other naked."
I'll just roll for you.
Do you have a problem with
Justin staying with me?
What was your first clue?
Uh-oh! Industrial accident.
You know what?
Don't talk to me
like I'm an idiot.
I'm not talking to you
like you're an idiot!
I'm saying the whole
idea is idiotic!
"You accidentally stare
at a helium-argon laser.
Lose one turn and a retina."
How is that not talking
to me like I'm an idiot?
It's my friend,
it's my couch,
and it's my freakin' life!
It's also your roll.
You know what?
It is your life.
If you want to have some stupid guitarist
stay on your couch, then fine.
Why don't you just rent
some bun beds and invite
The Black Eyed Peas?!
Hey, if I want to invite the
entire lineup of Lollapalooza
to sleep in my apartment,
I will,
and it's none of your business!
Are you listening to yourself?
Do you know how childish
you sound right now?
Oh, now I'm a child?
Well, at least I'm
not an idiot anymore!
(Blender grinding)
The two aren't
mutually exclusive!
Oh, you are such a--
What the hell is he doing?!
He's drowning us out.
He doesn't like fighting.
Sheldon, just stop!
Ok, the fight is over!
Oh, and FYI,
you never even heard
of The Black Eyed Peas
until you met me!
I heard of 'em!
Didn't know they were a band.
(Grinding continues)
Sheldon, she's gone.
You can turn off the blender.
Has your relationship reached
its inevitable ugly end?
No, we just had a little spat.
Look on the bright side.
As the result of
Penny's forfeit,
you have become the world's
first winner of "Research Lab."
Would you like a
commemorative snow cone?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a high, dense state ♪
♪ then nearly 14 billion years ago ♪
♪ expansion started... wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ the autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools. ♪
♪ We built the Wall. ♪
♪ We built the pyramids. ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ that all started
with a big bang. ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory
Season 03 - Episoe 07
"The Guitarist Amplification"
I don't get how she
can just announce
that an old boyfriend is going
to be sleeping on her couch.
Hey, I thought of a game
we can play in the car.
I don't want to play
a game, Sheldon.
It's called "Scientists."
Now, I will name
three scientists,
then you will put them in order
of the size of their
contribution
in their respective fields.
To make this game
even more compelling,
you must consider
only the contribution
of the man to the field,
not the validity
of the field itself.
For example:
Abu Musa Jabir ibn Haiyan
made a greater contribution to
the discredited field of alchemy
than Halbert Vanderplatt made
to neurobiology.
Okay, ready to have some fun?
An old boyfriend who's
definitely not gay.
That's what a guy likes
to hear-- "definitely."
All right, I'll start
with an easy one:
Um... Isaac Newton, Madame Curie
and Niels Bohr.
And then I say one little thing
and I end up being the bad guy!
Hint: Madame Curie had
her husband to help her.
What am I supposed to say?
"Sure, Penny, I'm cool
with your old boyfriend
sleeping in your apartment."
"Well, Leonard, it doesn't
matter if you're cool or not
"because I'm Penny and I'm pretty
and I can do whatever the hell I want!"
"Oh, I get it!
"You think you're doing
me a favor just by
being in a relationship
with me!"
"No, no, Leonard!
I'm doing you a favor
just by being in the
same room as you!"
Leonard! Stop the car!
What?
I can't listen to the
two of you fight anymore.
Come on, come on,
we're late.
Calm down.
We'll make the movie.
I believe my alarm
is appropriate,
given the situation.
The movie starts
in 17 minutes,
which means we'll need
to make all the lights
on Colorado Boulevard,
plus skip the concession stand,
and preshow urination.
Oh, dude, I wish you
had said something
before pounded
that last Red Bull.
SHELDON: Go, go,
Power Rangers, go!
Hey.
We're, uh, going to the movies.
No, we're not.
We're standing
in the hallway,
suffering through
an awkward encounter.
Hang on.
They're showing a new digital
part of Time Bandits.
You wouldn't want to come,
would you?
Not really, no.
All right, invitation
pointlessly offered,
invitation declined
as expected,
everyone's civil,
nobody's fighting.
Have a nice evening.
Just give us a minute.
Oh, take all the
time you need.
So, are we going to talk
about last night?
Are you ready to apologize?
No.
(Imitates buzzer)
Wrong answer.
But thank you for playing.
Oh, come on.
This is stupid.
Oh, there it is again!
You think I'm stupid!
No, there's a difference
between being stupid
and acting stupid.
Oh, yeah? well,
there's a difference
between being a jerk
and being an ass!
No, there isn't!
They're synonyms!
Well, that was
rather unpleasant.
Yeah, I don't think I need my
preshow urination anymore.
Leonard, when that woman
moved in three years ago
I told you not to talk to her,
and now look.
we're going to be late
for the movies.
Hey! Look! Amazing
Spider-Man 183.
Got it.
Remember this one?
Spider-Man loses a big fight
and then his girlfriend
breaks up with him.
Want me to get it for you?
It'll help take your
mind off things.
Hey, guys. What's going on?
Oh, we need to kill
a couple hours
till the next showing
of Time Bandits.
Oh, well, no problem.
I was thinking of closing
early and going home,
but let's face it,
that's just a slightly
smaller lonely room
filled with comic books.
Thanks, Stuart.
Let me ask you something.
Do you think it's okay for Penny
to have an ex-boyfriend
sleep on her couch?
No, I mean, she's obviously
way out of line.
Thank you!
But if she dumps you,
she'll have a new boyfriend
by tomorrow morning
and you'll have
a new girlfriend
when you figure out
how to build one.
So the only question is:
how long until you fold?
I am not going to fold.
Well, excuse me,
I don't think
Penny's out of
line at all.
You don't own her.
It's like my girl,
Beyonce says
"If you like it, you shoulda
put a ring on it."
WOLOWITZ:
Come on.
At the very least,
when she found out Leonard
was upset about it,
she should've
backed off.
You mean like
when a guy's upset
because his friend agreed to
take a cooking class with him
and then doesn't show up
because he's doing a juice
fast with his mother?
I didn't know you were
upset about that.
Really! Did you miss all
the subtle indicators,
like me saying,
"Howard, I am upset."
Okay, sorry.
Maybe it means something
different in this country.
Back in India, it means you're
upset with a guy named Howard!
Yea-- I said I'm sorry.
Sorry doesn't make
up for the fact
that I had to make chicken
and rice with this vegan guy.
Do you know what vegan
chicken and rice is?
Rice!
Yeah, well, you think
I was having fun,
sitting around all night
listening to my mother say,
"Have you ever peed so
much in your life?"
Oh, my God, you are
such a mama's boy.
WOLOWITZ:
Hey, don't bring my
mother into this!
You brought your
Stop it, both of you.
All this fighting,
I might as well
be back with my parents!
"Damn it, George,
I told you if you didn't quit
drinkin' I'd leave you!"
"Well, I guess that
makes you a liar.
'Cause I'm drunk as hell
and you're still here!"
"Stop yelling!
You're making Sheldon cry!"
"I'll tell you what's
making Sheldon cry!
That I let you name him Sheldon."
Boy, what got him so upset?
Oh, sure, you can tell
when Sheldon's upset.
Oh, thank you very much.
Come back soon.
With the other half of my tip.
(Sighs)
Hey, Sheldon.
What are you doing here?
This is a restaurant.
It's lunchtime.
I would think, as a waitress,
you should be familiar
with the paradigm.
Is Leonard coming?
No, I believe
Leonard is waiting
for you to come crawling back
to him and apologize.
Well, that's not
gonna happen.
I assumed that would
be your attitude.
Hence, my true purpose in coming here.
- Which is?
- I want you to crawl back to him and apologize.
I'm busy.
Excuse me, miss.
I'd like to order lunch.
Fine. What do you want?
I have a few questions.
First, I notice that you offer
soup and a half-sandwich?
Yes.
Where exactly does the
half-sandwich come from?
Are you giving me half of
someone else's sandwich,
or do I have to wait
for someone else
in the restaurant
to order the other half?
No, no, Sheldon, they
just make a half-sandwich.
You can't make
a half-sandwich.
If it's the half
of a whole sandwich,
it's just a small sandwich.
Okay, fine, it's soup
and a small sandwich.
Is that what you want?
Of course not.
I'll have my usual.
Great.
Aren't you going to ask me
if I want a beverage?
Don't you usually get lemonade?
- Yes.
- Do you want lemonade?
- Anything else?
Yes-- I want you to
apologize to Leonard.
I am not going
to apologize.
I've done nothing wrong.
He is completely
overreacting.
Irrelevant.
The disruption in
your relationship
is making my life intolerable.
Well, I'm sorry, Sheldon, but
this really isn't about you.
I don't follow.
Yeah, yeah, I'll
be right there.
Look, Sheldon,
I have to go.
All right, let's assume,
ad argumentum,
that in this case,
Leonard is wrong.
Considering the number
of transgressions
you've committed
that he's overlooked,
don't you think that,
just this once,
you could return the favor?
I'm coming.
Good-bye, Sheldon.
(Sighs)
What do you mean, transgressions
I've committed?
Were you under the impression
that Leonard has no
complaints about you?
Like what?!
Yeah, yeah, I see you.
You're making a little
check sign in the air.
I got it.
Just hold your horses.
What does Leonard
complain about?
Your driving.
The plethora of stuffed
animals on your bed
that stare at him during
your amorous activities.
Your constant tardiness,
your singing.
My singing?
That's actually from my list.
But Leonard would be a fool
if he didn't agree with it.
Okay, if Leonard has so
many problems with me,
why hasn't he
just said so?
Because, according to him,
you're oversensitive
and have a temper.
Oh, really?
Well, then, do me a favor
and tell Leonard that
he can drop dead!
And she wonders why she's
constantly undertipped.
Hey.
Oh, good, you're home.
I need you to
do me a favor.
Sure.
Go apologize to Penny.
What?!
Right now would be good.
(Loud knocking)
PENNY: Leonard!
Although, a few minutes ago
would have been better.
PENNY:
I hear you don't like
my stuffed animals,
my driving or my punctuality.
What? Who would tell you
something like that?
Why would you tell her
It doesn't matter
why he told me.
It's true, isn't it?
Okay, yeah, it's true,
but I can live
with that stuff.
What I can't live with is
you casually informing me
that some guy's going to be
staying in your apartment
without even
asking me first!
That isn't even your problem!
Your problem is
you don't trust me!
Oh, come on.
Sheldon, have you ever once heard
me say that I don't trust Penny?
Sheldon?
Where did he go?
PENNY:
Oh, your yelling
must have freaked
him out again.
Where are you going?!
You just walk away
- in the middle of an argument?!
- No.
I'm going to go find
your damn roommate
before he hurts himself
trying to cross the
street or something!
Why didn't you say so?
Oh, now I need your
permission for that, too?!
Well, I can't read
your mind, Penny!
Really?
Why not?
You're so smart,
and I'm so dumb!
Raj?
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Stop knocking!
It's open!
Please tell my parents that
our dark matter research
is at a critical juncture,
and I can't come home
for my cousin Sanjay's wedding.
MRS. KOOTHRAPPALI:
Sheldon,
ask our son what
we're supposed to say
to Mr. and Mrs. Cheldry,
whose daughter, Lakshmi
is flying in from London, for
the sole purpose of meeting him.
I didn't ask you to
set me up with Lakshmi.
You should be thanking us!
Yes-- Lakshmi just got
her stomach stapled.
You have an opportunity
to get in good with her
before she loses weight,
and her self-esteem goes up.
I don't care!
And why don't you
think I can find
a woman for myself?
Because you're 27,
and the closest thing we
have to a daughter-in-law
is that Jewish boy Howard.
Oh... that is completely
below the belt.
Sheldon, tell my parents that
Howard and I are just friends.
Sheldon?
Howard and I are just friends!
Fine. I'll come home
for Sanjay's wedding.
(Sighs)
(Shouting):
Sheldon?!
(Whistling)
What are you doing?
He's not a lost dog.
Hey, why don't you
just let me find him
while you sit there
hitting your imaginary brake?
The brake might be imaginary,
but that stop sign
you just ran wasn't.
What stop sign?
Eyes on the road.
Eyes on the road!
(Doorbell rings)
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, answer the door!
I'm busy!
HOWARD: I'm busy too.
You answer it.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
I can't!
I'm on the toilet!
HOWARD:
For God's sake, I don't
need to hear that!
Can't you just
say, "I'm busy"?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
I said I'm busy,
but that wasn't
good enough for you!
HOWARD:
You know what?
I hope it's one of those
home invasion deals,
And they shove me in the head.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Well, if it's a home invader,
don't tell them
I'm on the toilet!
There's no one there.
You're hearing things,
you crazy old lady!
Hey, Stuart, have
you seen Sheldon?
Yeah, he's, uh, over in
the graphic novel section.
Built himself a little nest.
Thank you.
Uh, Penny?
Yeah?
Is everything okay?
What do you mean?
Uh, Sheldon told me
you and Leonard
were having a fight?
Oh, yeah, kind of.
It's-It's no big thing.
Oh, good, good.
I love you.
I'm not leaving
until you talk to me.
All right,
what's going on?
It's a little hard to explain.
He does this thing
where he pretends
he's in an alternate
dimension that occupies the
same physical space we're in,
but he can't perceive us.
Don't flatter yourself.
I'm just ignoring you.
Ok, come on, Sheldon,
let's go home.
Look, we're done fighting.
I've heard that before.
But then,
the next thing you know,
I'm hiding in my bedroom,
blaring a Richard Feinman
lecture
while my mom is shouting
that Jesus would forgive her
if she put ground glass
in my dad's meatloaf.
And my dad's on the
roof skeet-shooting
her Franklin Mint
collectible plates.
Hey, there's going to
no more shouting
and no skeet-shooting.
Really?
Where's your friend Justin
going to sleep?
Yeah... where's
he gonna sleep?
Oh, my God, would
you let this go?!
STUART:
I'd let it go.
Why should I let it go?
Why don't you just tell the guy
to find another place to sleep?!
(Robot playing ominous music)
Oh, for God's sakes.
(Turns robot off)
So, you have childhood issues.
We all have childhood issues.
At some point, you just need
to grow up and get past them.
ROBOT:
Fire! Fire!
(Robot firing blasters)
Leonard, will you just
let me handle this, please?
Fire! Fire!
Look... let's... just...
(Robot shouting)
(Turns robot off)
Sheldon, please,
try and understand.
Look, Leonard and I
are in a relationship,
and occasionally,
we're going to fight.
But no matter what happens
between us, we will
always love you.
Right, Leonard?
Always is a long time.
Sure. Always.
You know, how about
we buy you this robot,
and then we all go home?
I want that one.
Okay, you can have that one.
Oh, come on, he's just going
to play with it twice,
and then it'll end up in his
closet with all the other junk.
Buy him the robot, Leonard.
Can I get this comic book, too?
(Baby talk):
Yes, you can.
(Sighs)
We meet again.
So what did Justin say
when you told him
he couldn't sleep
on your couch?
He's a musician.
He'll sleep in his own
vomit, if he has to.
I should have asked
for much more
than a comic book and a robot.
www.tvsubtitles.net