- Kites, ho!
Kites, ho!
ALL:
Excuse me.
You're misusing the word "ho."
It's an interjection used
to call attention
to a destination, not an object,
as in, uh, "Land, ho!"
or, uh, "Westward, ho!"
ALL:
Kites, ho!
Hey, guys.
Whatcha doin'?
Going out to discover
electricity?
If you're referring to the
work of Benjamin Franklin,
he did not
"discover electricity,"
he merely used a
kite to determine
that lightning "consists"
of electricity.
He also invented the
Franklin stove,
bifocals and the flexible
urinary catheter.
Kites, ho.
We're heading out for
some kite fighting.
- "Kite fighting"?
- Oh, yeah.
It's an extremely competitive,
cutthroat sport.
Well, actually, the risk of
throat cutting is very low.
On the other hand, severe
string burn is a real
and ever-present danger.
You want to come watch?
Oh gee...
sounds amazing.
But, um, I've got some
friends coming over.
Not a big thing--
we're just
gonna watch the Nebraska game.
Oh. Football, sure.
Good guess.
I would've invited you, but I
know you're not a football fan.
No no, I'm not, so... great.
You've got plans
doing something you like,
I've got plans
doing something I
like, so it's good.
Well, maybe we'll
hang out later--
you know, after
everybody's gone.
Yeah, great.
See ya.
Well, this sucks.
I'm sorry, I got bored
and drifted off.
Where exactly in the interaction
did the sucking lie?
Leonard just realized that
Penny's been hiding him
from her friends because
he's a tiny, little man
who flies kites.
Oh, that certainly would suck.
* Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state *
* then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... wait! *
* The Earth began to cool
* the autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools *
* we built the Wall.
* We built the pyramids *
* Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery *
* that all started with
a big bang *
* Bang! *
The Big Bang Theory
Season 03 Episode 06
"The Cornhusker Vortex"
Wolowitz is trying
to outflank us.
Let out some string,
add altitude
and I'll go under
and cut his line.
Why wouldn't Penny want
her friends to meet me?
Focus, Leonard, focus!
The heat of battle is upon us.
The dogs of war are unleashed.
Maybe Koothrappali's right.
Maybe I embarrass her.
You're embarrassing
me right now.
A grown man worrying
about such nonsense
when in the middle
of flying kites.
Sorry.
Sorry won't bring
their kites down.
Ouch!
String burn!
Oh, they think
we're flanking
they're playing
righ into our hands.
On the count of three, we
execute the flying scissor.
One, two...
Wow!
- Did you see that?
- See what?
That chick--
she smiled at me.
- No, she didn't.
- Yes, she did.
Come on, scissors, scissors!
- Hold my line.
- Wait.
What are you doing?
I can't scissors by myself!
Howard! Come back!
SHELDON:
Victory!
Son of a bitch.
You're a sucky friend,
you know that?
A sucky, sucky friend.
What was I supposed to do?
She gave me that
"come-hither" look.
If she gave you any look at all.
It was a "you suck" look.
I would've caught up to her
if I hadn't pulled a hammy.
Oh, please, you
weigh 80 pounds.
You don't have a hammy.
So, Penny doesn't want
around her friends.
I embarrass her.
What else could it be?
Well, her actions
could be out of concern
for your feelings
perhaps she's excluded you
from these gatherings
because she's scouting
for a new mate
and doesn't want to do
it in front of you.
Oh... how kind of her.
Agreed.
Most primates don't show
that sort of discretion.
A female bonobo will copulate with
a new male in front of the old one
without so much as
a "how do you do?"
You always do
this, you know?
You ditch me for a woman
you don't have a shot with.
- I totally had a shot.
- With a woman
you were chasing
through a park--
that's not a shot,
that's a felony.
What's worse, it cost me my prized Patang
fighting kite. Sheldon, I don't suppose
there's any chance you
could give me my kite back?
I'm sorry, Raj, but the
rules of aerial warfare
dictate at the fallen
kite go to the victor.
And without rules, the
competition has no meaning.
And without meaning,
the following would
be an empty gesture.
I have your kite.
(Knocking at door)
- Hey.
- Hi.
How was your football party?
- It was pretty good. We won.
- Oh, wow.
That's excellent.
It's a weird figure
of speech, isn't it
"we won" when you weren't
actually playing.
When we watch Star Wars,
we don't say, "we
defeated the Empire."
- I'm glad to hear it.
- Yeah.
Oh, hey, on a related subject,
are you embarrassed to have
me around your friends?
Oh, my god, no.
Why would you ask that?
Well, you know, I just noticed
- I haven't really met any of them.
- Sure you have.
Well, yeah, no, I met the
huge ex-boyfriend
and the-- smaller, yet still larger
than me ex-boyfriend.
By the way, were they here today?
- Of course not.
Why would they be?
Why would I ask?
Why am I rambling?
Why don't you stop me?
Leonard, look,
if you want to meet my friends,
that would be great.
I just, you know, I didn't
want you to be bored.
I wouldn't be bored.
- Why would I be bored?
- Well,
'cause they're not
genius scientists.
Penny, I like all
sorts of people.
Th-- some of my best
friends aren't geniuses.
Like who?
Okay, some of my Facebook
friends aren't geniuses.
My point is, if we're
going to be a couple,
I should be friends
with your friends.
Okay, great. Well,
then why don't you
come over next Saturday
and watch the game with us.
Another football game?
They have them every week.
Did not know that.
- You wanted to meet my friends.
- Sure.
Sure, just I don't know
much about football.
Oh, that's okay--
a lot of the guys'
girlfriends don't know football.
They just kind of drink
and talk in the kitchen.
Great.
(Football game playing on TV)
Okay, a complete pass.
First down, New England.
I think I'm starting
to get this.
Really?
The only thing I've learned
in the last two hours
is that American men
love drinking beer,
pee too often and have
trouble getting erections.
Focus on the game, not
the commercials, Raj.
I'm just saying, maybe if you
people cut back on the beer,
you could get out of the bathroom and satisfy
your women without pharmaceutical help.
Raj, what are you
doing here?
You were supposed to help me
pimp out my Vespa.
I'm sorry, are you under the impression
that we're still friends?
(Groans):
Oh come on.
You're not still grinding
on the kite thing, are you?
It's not just the kite thing.
Every time we go some place,
you think you can just dump me
whenever someone prettier
comes along,
even though you don't have
a shot with them.
I had a shot with that jogger.
Fine. Paint green flames
on your little scooter with her.
It's not a little scooter.
It's the second biggest
Vespa they make!
(Door closes)
Are you watching football?
There's no fooling you.
Now, what is this sacks
statistic they put up there?
All I know about Saks is,
my mother shops there.
Sacks, sacks...
SHELDON: It's football nomenclature
for when a quarterback is tackled
behind the line of scrimmage.
Huh...
Scrimmage.
SHELDON:
The line of scrimmage
is the imaginary transverse line
separating the offense
from the defense.
Oh.
Sheldon knows football?
Apparently.
I mean, Quidditch, sure. But football?
(Quidditch: Harry Potter's game)
Sheldon, how do you
know this stuff?
I grew up in Texas.
Football is ubiquitous in Texas.
Pro football,
College football,
High school football,
Peewee football...
In fact, every form of football
except the original--
European football.
Which most Texans believe
to be a Commie plot.
Unbelievable.
If you're interested, I also
know all about frying meat
that isn't chicken
as if it were chicken.
So you could teach me?
Football or chicken-fried meats?
Football.
I'm going to Penny's on Saturday
to watch a game with her friends
And I don't want to look like
an idiot. I want to blend in.
If you want to blend in
with Penny's friends,
I'd think looking like an idiot
would be the perfect camouflage.
Come on, Sheldon, please teach
me football. It'll be fun.
That's exactly what
my father said.
"Come to the games.
Watch the games."
Week in and week out
from the time
I was five until I
went off to college.
Longest seven years of my life.
Please, I'm asking
you as a friend.
Are you making this a tier
one friendship request?
Yes
(Sighs)
Fine.
- I really appreciate this.
- Yeah, yeah.
All right, point dexter,
sit down, shut up and listen.
I'm sorry?
That's how my father
always began
our football conversations.
And if you'd like,
after the game,
I'll take outside and teach you how to shoot
close enough a racoon that did crap itself.
When are you going to stop
making Cylon toast?
When I have enough to destroy
all the human toast
on the Battlestar
known as Galactica.
Is that what you're wearing
to watch football at Penny's?
What's wrong with
a football jersey?
Nothing. That, however, appears
to be a football cocktail dress.
It's the smallest size they had,
except the one for dogs.
I can't believe they
had one for dogs.
Oh, yes.
Canine football fans are
a common sight in Texas.
Cats, however, refuse
to wear sporting apparel.
My sister found that
out the hard way.
Anyway, wish me luck.
Leonard, wait.
Am I correct in assuming that
your attempt to be accepted
by Penny's peers is based
on your desire
to ensure your continuing
mating privileges with her?
Well, I wouldn't put
it exactly that way.
How would you put it?
Yeah, okay, like you said.
Huh.
Seems like an awful lot of trouble
to go through for intercourse.
Don't you have access to women
who will do it for money?
By the way.
Another accepted usage
for the term "ho."
Good-bye, Sheldon.
Hold on.
I believe that
social convention
dictate you not arrive
empty-handed.
Would you like to bring
some Cylon toast?
Yeah, no, I'm trying to fit
in, not get laughed at.
(Door closes)
What's funny about Cylon toast?
It's open.
Hey, pal.
What do you want?
(TV clicks off)
I brought you
a little gift.
New kite.
The kite you made me lose
was an authentic Patang,
an Indian fighting kite.
That my brother sent to me
from New Delhi.
It took me a day to put together
and two days to paint.
This is Hello Kitty.
Yeah, but it comes
with a little coin purse.
Does a Patang?
Wow, you just don't
get it, do you?
Buying me something
pretty isn't going
to make our problem
just go away.
Look, I admit I
haven't always been
the best friend I could be.
You've been a sucky friend,
a sucky, sucky friend.
Stipulated.
And you do it
all the time.
Last week in the mall at
Radio Shack, we were looking
for a phone with giant
numbers for your mother,
and I suddenly realize
you're not even there.
- I know, I know...
- Then where were you?
Getting shot down by the
girl at hot dog on a stick.
But in my defense,
she was gorgeous!
And working that squeezer
to make the lemonade,
going up and down
and up and down.
It was like a
free pole dance
right in the middle
of the food court.
You're impossible.
Hey, at least I can
talk to women
without being drunk.
Excuse me, I have
selective mutism,
a recognized medical disorder.
You're just a douche.
No. You know what?
Maybe that's what this
whole thing's about.
You're not mad at me,
you're mad at yourself.
No, I'm mad at you.
I hate myself,
but I'm mad at you.
Fine. You're mad at me.
I get it.
How about we go spend
the day together?
Just the two of us.
We'll go anywhere you want.
I don't know.
Come on.
Let me take you someplace nice.
I-I do enjoy the
La Brea Tar Pits.
Really, now? With the traffic
and the parking?
Okay, fine.
The Tar Pits.
Let's go.
Oh, why can't I stay mad at you?
(Exclaims)
Go! Go! Go!
Go-Go-Go-Go! Yes!
Are you people watching this?
Is this amazing or what?
Sweetie, that's a highlight
from the '98
Championship game.
Did not know that.
- How much beer have you had?
- None, why?
Oh. I was just kind of
hoping you were drunk.
- Now we're back live.
- Okay, yeah.
I can see the difference.
Oh, where's the flag?
That's intentional grounding.
- Totally.
- That completely was
a forward pass, which they
threw intentionally incomplete
to avoid loss of yardage
or to conserve time
I can't believe they're not
being penalized with
the loss of a down
and by having to move
the line of scrimmage
back to the spot of the foul.
Here, have some pizza, sweetie.
Penny, you know I'm
lactose intolerant.
I know. I just need
you to stop talking.
(Knocking)
SHELDON:
Penny.
Penny. Penny.
- Sheldon, come in.
- Thank you.
I'd like to make a sandwich,
but I'm out of bread.
There's some
in the fridge.
You shouldn't keep your bread
in the refrigerator.
Staleness is caused
by crystallization
of the starch molecules,
which occurs faster
- at cool temperatures.
- On Earth,
we say "thank you."
So Leonard, how
goes the mimesis?
"Mimesis"?
You know. Mimesis.
An action in which the mimic
takes on the properties
of a specific object
or organism.
Mimesis.
What the hell are
you talking about?
I'm attempting to
communicate with you
without my meaning becoming
apparent to those around you.
Let me try again.
Have the indigenous fauna
accepted you as one
of their own?
Nudge, nudge, wink, wink.
Oh, I guess so.
Good. Oh, FYI.
After I eat my sandwich,
I'm taking Koothrappali's
Patang kite out
for a test run.
Would you like to get your
delta-wing raptor and join me?
I don't want to fly
kites, Sheldon.
We're watching football here.
I can see that.
I was providing you
with an alternative.
A courtesy I was never offered
in similar circumstances.
(Whistle blows on TV)
Oh, look at that.
The Oklahoma coach is
throwing down a red flag
indicating he's challenging
the ruling on the field.
I hope he's right, 'cause if
he's not, it'll cost him
one of his three time-outs.
You know, Leonard, honey,
I wouldn't mind if you wanted
to go fly kites with Sheldon.
No, I'll watch the
end of the game.
Besides, there's only
three minutes left.
Until halftime.
This is just half?
We've been here for hours.
And you're gonna be here
for a couple more.
- Oh, you're kidding me.
- No.
Nice meeting all of you.
So, yeah, anyway,
that's my boyfriend.
He is really smart.
I really like my
saber-toothed cat.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Maybe after lunch, we can
go to Marie Callender's
and have some pie.
I'd like that.
(Takes deep breath)
This is turning out to
be a perfect Saturday.
Good. I'm glad.
Oh, man. Did you see the
way she smiled at me?
Fine. Go ahead.
No. This is our day.
If you want to
chase after her,
chase after her.
Ah, who am I kidding? I wouldn't
have a shot with a girl like that.
Don't put yourself down.
You're a very attractive man.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
Absolutely.
It wouldn't kill you
to take a Pilates class
with me now and then,
but you have a certain
wiry appeal.
Yeah, well, it
doesn't matter
'cause she wasn't
really smiling at me.
Actually, in this case,
I think she was.
Really?
- Yeah.
- Bye.
What a douche.
www.tvsubtitles.net