Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Good morning,
Mr. Draper.
Morning.
It's Beverly, isn't it?
He's on 19.
Thank you.
Good morning.
You don't have to
do this every day.
I won't have you lost again.
I wasn't lost. I was late.
I was fibbing.
Well, you can't do that.
It throws off
a very busy schedule.
Not to mention
everything, et cetera.
Can you call housekeeping
and ask them
not to make up my bed
while I'm still in it?
Well, you won't have
to endure the hardships
of The Plaza much longer.
The floors of your apartment
will be done Monday.
If you pick paint, you
could move in next week.
That's great.
Honey, you can just have
this waiting on my desk.
Does it smell
any better in here?
If you like Airwick.
Fruit.
When I was packing,
well, I think these
were best kept from the movers.
Have you thought about
new furniture?
I think it looks great in here.
No, for your apartment.
You only have a bed.
I made dinner reservations
in Farmington tomorrow.
You're taking Sally
back to school.
Oh, thank you.
Jim Hobart's back
from vacation.
No napping.
You and the computer gonna
share an office over there?
No, the old girl
served her purpose.
McCann is Mission Control.
Statisticians, programmers,
five men and 10 women
just handling data.
Maybe they can keep track of your hat size.
Seems to be growing.
Why are you still here?
Somebody's got to
hand over the keys.
Well, I'm on 24
and you're on 26,
but I'll be up there
all the time.
There's an executive
dining room.
You know, I once rode on a bus to
camp sitting next to a guy like you.
We're not going
to be bunkmates, Crane.
I'll make them build
another floor if I have to.
I'm not going to let you
spoil the moment.
My moment.
See you in the funny papers.
I don't know what's keeping
the building representatives,
but I feel perfectly
comfortable--
Forging my signature?
No, that's okay.
You can go.
Well, this is my last day
and I wanted to thank you.
Bullshit.
They can't fire you.
Actually, I took another job.
Travelers Insurance.
My cousin works there.
- Look, I hate Caroline, too.
- No, it's--
- Did I do something?
- No.
It's just I kept thinking about
walking into a new office.
I'm doing it, too.
And now there's going to be
one less person I know.
Mr. Sterling,
it's not you.
Advertising is not a very
comfortable place for everyone.
Oh.
That in mind,
I have to say thank you.
You're very amusing.
Fat lot of good it did me.
Hello, neighbor.
We're the welcome wagon.
We heard you had a window.
Aren't you sweet to come by?
This is Beverly.
And who are you?
- I'm Libby Blum.
- Karen Schmidt.
Can we have a minute?
- We're copywriters.
- I recognized the names.
I was just going over Tampax.
We also did the pill
for Ortho, and--
If it's in it, near it, or makes
you think about it, we're on it.
So Topaz Pantyhose and Butler
Shoes set off an alarm.
But we really love Avon.
This is incredible.
So you just came in here
to get on my business.
And to say hello.
Well, I'm flattered by both.
If you want us, just ask
Frank in the studio.
He'll ask Bobby in traffic,
and he'll tell Carl the
associate creative director.
You can put a request in
however you want.
We'll let the Soviets
deal with it.
You're aware that Peggy Olson
handles all of those accounts?
See, I told you.
Well, we'd love to share
the crumbs with her.
Thank you so much
for the plant.
Oh, we're going to
the Oyster Bar tonight.
We have an informal
ladies' club.
It's not women's lib,
just a bitch session.
We are strictly
consciousness lowering.
When I get settled in.
Incredible.
Did you come to get
your furniture?
There was a mix-up.
My office isn't ready.
Why are you still here?
Well, I'm not going to McCann.
And so far I'm not
going anywhere.
And I'm being paid through
the end of the week,
so I thought I'd make some
long-distance phone calls.
Oh.
- We lost Dow.
- We still owe them work.
Could you get Mr. Kreutzer
at Sugarberry Ham for me?
Why would I do that?
Because Marsha's sorting
things out over there
and I'm not calling myself.
I'm giving you
a standing ovation.
How was the Bahamas?
Oh, it's everything
we say it is in print.
I hope you're finding
everything satisfactory.
Ferg's been
an excellent tour guide.
He's just following you around because
he's our resident impressionist.
Do you do an imitation
of Don yet?
"I'm, um, working
very diligently
on the, um,
matter at hand."
Well, you better not
make a joke of this man.
We've lined up coffee
and baloney with Nabisco,
National Cash Register, and
your old friend Conrad Hilton.
He bought you a gift.
That's never good.
And we just bought
an entire agency
in Milwaukee
to get Miller Beer.
For me?
When I want something,
I get it.
And I've been trying
to get you for 10 years.
You're my "white whale," Don.
Well, maybe you should
send me to the Bahamas.
In due time.
The important thing is
we're expecting you to bring
things up a notch around here.
Jim, I don't know what to tell you.
I'll do my best.
And, Don, this is
a shirtsleeves operation.
We want you relaxed.
And should you ever need
anything in this city,
dinner reservations,
parking tickets...
Just drop our name into yours.
I will.
Oh, Miller Beer
is coming in tomorrow
for handshakes
on their new idea--
diet beer.
For ladies?
For men watching
their waistlines.
Why don't we call it "Tub"?
- Have you said it yet?
- What?
Have you introduced yourself?
I'm Don Draper
from McCann-Erickson.
I appreciate the call.
Mostly because it's hard
for me to walk around here
acting like nothing's changed.
Only some things have changed.
Avon will be serviced
by the exact same personnel.
Creative handled by
Ted Chaough and Peggy Olson.
Forget about personnel.
Every dollar you spend
will now get you
five times the audience.
And once we get you on TV...
Well, we already are on TV.
We know that.
What Dennis is saying is--
You know, I'm in Atlanta
all the time.
How about a trip to
Augusta, play a few holes?
You any good?
No.
No, I'm not.
Listen, my girl is telling me that
it's time for our staff meeting.
Thanks again for the call.
Of course.
Such a pleasure, Barry.
Bye.
- Who's next?
- I don't know what to say,
except Barry
is in a wheelchair.
- What?
- I told you that.
And I wrote it down.
Oh, I thought that
was Charlie Butler
from the shoes.
No, it's not.
And it's Charles Butler.
And it's footwear.
I can't believe you.
It's an honest mistake.
You heard him say he was
"walking around the office."
It's an expression.
Which he shouldn't
be able to use.
I stayed up all night
preparing those briefs.
Mr. Donnelly said you'd be on the
call to help with the transition.
But you seem like you don't even
care about keeping these accounts.
I'm sorry.
Who told you you got
to get pissed off?
All I ask is that you please read
the brief before our next call.
You know what?
Do it yourself.
I thought you were
going to be fun.
I'm sorry to drop by.
Oh, Marsha.
That's so sweet of you.
You didn't have to come up here.
It's not your fault.
Those are actually from McCann.
An apology.
That's classy.
How do I explain this?
All the SC&P girls got flowers.
It's still classy.
Well, all the new secretaries.
They thought I was a secretary?
Did you tell Don what happened?
- Do you want me to?
- No.
Maybe I should call Joan.
That's not her job there.
- I know that, Marsha.
- I am taking care of it.
As well as your mail
and memos regarding
Peter Pan Peanut Butter
and Tampax.
What happened to all my things?
They're putting
your boxes in storage.
You will have
an office any minute.
In the meantime,
you can work in the pool.
I am a copy supervisor.
I am not setting foot in there
until I have an office.
If they want me,
they can reach me here.
At home?
No. No.
I'll be at SC&P.
Hell, that's where
my furniture is.
I will let them know.
Could you hold that?
Good morning.
How are you, stranger?
Homesick.
Well, takes some time
to settle in.
I know.
You should come by for a drink.
When am I going to do that?
Put me on your calendar.
We don't share any accounts.
You're too important.
Not for you.
Believe me,
I'd involve you if I could.
It's been a little bumpy.
I can still interfere.
No, I'll figure it out.
Of that I am certain.
Let's make a date for lunch.
Soon.
Tell me if you
like the general idea
so I can take a few risks.
Where did you learn to do this?
I'm an army brat, remember?
New base every year.
I want to live here.
You're my decorator.
I'll pay you in cash.
Nonsense.
I love it.
Lunch in the executive
boardroom with Miller Beer.
They asked if roast beef
was okay.
Perfect.
Joan, it's nice
to see you up here.
Are you coming to the Sears briefing?
That's a good idea.
No, I was actually
looking for Mr. Donnelly.
- But if now is a bad time--
- Ferg.
Pete, it's your meeting.
You can start without me.
I'm gonna put in a request to
get you involved with this.
Thank you.
That's thoughtful.
So what can I do for you?
It's just--
regarding the Avon transition,
I thought maybe Pete
could be an asset.
Pete's a vice president.
What's wrong with Dennis?
I like Dennis personally.
I'm not sure the client
responded to him.
Say no more.
I'll take care of it.
Hello?
Are those my boxes?
I gotta go.
Yeah, I signed for them, but I
was wondering what happened.
Ugh, you've got
to be kidding me.
You know we're
the only ones here.
Have you been on
the phone all morning?
Stan called.
He doesn't have a phone yet.
He's on the 14th floor.
Come by and say hi.
And...
I prepared this
for your approval.
_
- What is this?
- Do you think "quagmire" should be plural?
We can't do this.
They're never going
to look at it.
Ed, you could easily end up
working for Dow again,
or Ken Cosgrove.
You could even end up
working for me.
That's not very subtle.
I asked you to do one damn thing
and you didn't even do it.
Fine. I quit.
Well, thanks for everything.
When you get settled in over
there, which will happen,
give me a call?
I promise.
I'm sorry.
It's Bob, right?
Yes. Don,
good to see you.
We've got the best
box lunch around.
It should have your name on it.
Is this the Miller
Beer meeting?
It certainly is. Bill
Phillips, Conley Research.
Don Draper and Ted Chaough.
- A pleasure.
- Shall we?
Is this every creative
director in the agency?
It's only half of us.
So are you here to
"bring us up a notch," too?
So they tell me.
Good morning, gentlemen.
As you know this
is Bill Phillips,
Senior Director
at Conley Research.
Bill, why don't you tell us a little
bit about this exciting new beverage?
Despite that pile of facts
and figures in front of you,
I don't look at this as
a presentation of research.
To me, this is
an opportunity to stimulate
some of our industry's
finest imaginations.
I'm going to describe
a man to you
of very specific qualities.
He lives in Wisconsin,
Michigan, Ohio.
Some call it
"the Heartland."
"the Beer Belt."
He has some college.
Makes a good living,
but it doesn't feel like it
because he works long hours.
He has a lawn mower.
Wants a hammock.
Bunch of power tools in the
garage that he never uses.
He loves sports because
he used to play 'em.
And he loves dogs
because they don't talk.
We all know this man.
Because there are
millions of him.
And he drinks beer.
Not just any beer.
No, it has to be his brand.
And what is his brand?
The one he drank in college?
The one his dad drank?
The one that comes in
the best bottle, can, tap?
It doesn't matter
because that's it
and it's not open
for discussion.
Now you all know
that that's not true.
But how do you get him
to open his mind?
Better have something more.
Or in this case, less.
And that's tricky.
When we talk about
a low-calorie beer,
we immediately become feminine.
It's the word
"calorie."
It makes you think
of a reducing plan.
A note on the fridge
to remind her about her diet.
Your girl still at lunch?
Beverly always takes the whole hour.
I insist.
I have a little news for you.
Oh, I hope I didn't
'cause any trouble.
Too early for you?
No, of course not.
So, I spoke with Dennis.
I hope I didn't
ruffle any feathers.
Well, here's how it looks.
Like some junior
account man came in
and started
swinging her elbows.
He didn't read the brief.
And I'm not Dennis's junior.
Joan, see it from his side.
He has a wife
and three children.
He's not going
to work for a girl.
What's he gonna say
to a client?
"She's my boss"?
It happens all the time now.
Peggy Olson was our copy chief.
It's different with a bunch of
writers fresh out of Columbia.
And honestly, I doubt that's
gonna continue here anyway.
I see.
Joan, I didn't come
down here to upset you.
I agree that the best way
to keep the business
is to keep your status
on your accounts.
Oh.
And you'll certainly get
the respect you desire,
now it's just you and me.
You don't have to do that,
but I accept.
Mm, good.
Now, first thing we have to
do is pay this guy a visit.
- Who?
- Barry from Avon.
We owe him an apology.
And let's face it, it would
be good to get out of town,
even if it's to Atlanta.
I appreciate that, but I
don't want to put you out.
Look, I know a good job
when I see one.
No, it's just
that might be too much.
He'll be in New York soon
and Avon corporate
is blocks away.
Hey, I'm easy.
I'm not expecting anything
more than a good time.
Excuse me?
I mean, I want to get
to know you, of course.
Of course.
Good.
For my first act
of benevolence,
you can call Charles
Butler on your own.
We'll take him
to lunch next week.
Thank you.
From now on, no one comes
between me and your business.
I appreciate that.
We can't lose those accounts.
What would you do around here?
Loretta.
Here she is.
- Sally left?
- Yes.
She got a ride with her friend.
And no one thought
to call me, I guess.
Do you want something to drink?
- No.
- They left after lunch.
I told her to call your office.
Your secretary is a moron.
I was out of the office. I
wanted to get the car washed.
She comes and goes
as she pleases.
We can't get mad at her
for being independent.
It's normal.
That what Freud says?
So far I haven't come
across anyone normal.
You okay?
I carried $100 worth
of textbooks yesterday
during registration.
Maybe you're getting old.
- I'm younger than you.
- Mm-hmm.
Always have been,
always will be.
Maybe you could find some nice
freshman to carry your books.
That's fine.
When do the boys get home?
Gene's at Cub Scouts
and Bobby's got baseball.
They won't be back
until 6:30.
I'll let you get back
to your studies.
I've always wanted to do this.
Knock 'em dead, Birdie.
Bye.
Shit.
Your stomach is grumbling.
You never let me eat.
I can make fried chicken.
I don't mind playing house,
but as long as your mother
and Kevin are away,
why don't you call in sick?
Let me take you to Bermuda.
No.
Cape Cod?
I don't want to go anywhere
I don't want to go.
Don't make plans for me.
All right.
I have a lot of work.
Look, I know I told you
not to complain,
but that doesn't mean I don't
want to hear about it.
But you really don't.
What happened?
It's a big place and I asked
the wrong person for help.
And I don't think
I can get out of it.
Well, if you don't like that
job, you don't have to do it.
You got enough and you got me.
They still owe me
over half a million dollars.
I'm not walking away from that.
So this is a business problem.
Now I can help.
You're already helping.
There's two ways I deal
with disagreeable people.
One, you can call a lawyer,
throw a bunch of paper at them,
tie them up in court,
cost them some money.
Nobody wins,
but it loosens the earth.
What's the second?
You can call a guy.
"A guy"?
I'm a developer.
Men get stubborn.
What does "a guy" do?
You get the right guy, all
they have to do is show up.
You've really done that?
You seem to like it,
so I'm gonna say yes.
You're disturbed.
Doesn't seem like such
a big problem now, does it?
♪ I don't want to say goodbye ♪
♪ for the summer...
Beautiful
night out there tonight.
In downtown Cleveland
we have a high of 75,
low of 62.
Not too sticky
and it should stay that way
through the weekend.
I don't know about you,
but I am not ready
to say goodbye to the summer.
But not true of the folks
at Higbee's Department Store
where they're ready to provide
all the back-to-school
fashions.
I'm really tired, aren't I?
You've been driving
for seven hours
in the wrong direction, you know.
Where are you going?
Racine, Wisconsin.
Ever been there?
No.
What's in Racine?
Maybe some waitress
who doesn't care about you?
You shouldn't do that.
That's not gonna stop me.
You like to play
"the stranger."
Remember "On the Road"?
I've never read
that book, you know that.
I'm riding the rails.
"Whither goest thou, America,
in thy shiny car
in the night?"
♪ Yes, it's gonna be a cold ♪
♪ lonely summer
♪ but I'll fill
the emptiness... ♪
- Hello?
- Peggy?
- Yes. Who is this?
- It's Marsha.
I thought I would try this
before I ran over.
- Your phone's dead.
- What do you want?
Well, on behalf
of McCann-Erickson,
I want to welcome you
to your new office.
When can you come over?
Well, I guess right now.
Wonderful. Can you work
at a drafting table
until they bring your things
over tomorrow?
Yes. Thank you.
Hello?
Is someone there?
- Roger.
- Oh, Christ!
I have a heart
condition, you know.
Believe it or not,
I'm not scary.
Organ music is scary.
What are you doing here?
I told Caroline I wanted
to pack my personal things,
which I will eventually do
as soon as I figure out why she
thought my bar wasn't personal.
Did you try Don's office?
All I found was lighter fluid.
I'm not there yet.
Mine's gone.
I don't want to go to a bar.
I did that yesterday.
Listen, sweetheart,
if you don't mind...
I'm not running an errand.
I have to go to McCann.
Three days ago.
They screwed up
my office--
It doesn't matter.
They're finally ready.
I'd do it for you.
Would you drink vermouth?
Yes, I'm afraid I would.
_
I'll be along in a minute.
Oh, Mr. Hobart.
Can I help you?
You're sitting in his chair.
You're obviously
not expecting him.
I told Daphne I don't
know when he'll be in.
Can I take a message?
Sure.
Tell him he missed Nabisco
and National Cash Register just left,
so he might as well take
the rest of the day off.
Thank you.
I'll let him know.
Is he on a bender, sweetheart?
I haven't heard from him,
but he went to take
his daughter to school.
I'm not concerned.
Look at this.
"Christmas Day, 1951."
- Who's Roberta?
- I don't know.
Oh.
Roberta.
Hmm.
We had our drink.
You clearly don't need help.
You need an audience.
McCann made you wait.
You can make them wait.
I'm not enjoying this.
Oh, my God.
What is this?
It's an octopus
pleasuring a lady.
It was Cooper's.
It was in his office forever.
You can have it.
You can put it in your office.
No. They won't
take me seriously.
That's pretty serious.
It's 150 years old.
You know I need to make
men feel at ease.
Who told you that?
So now I gave you something,
you can sit tight
and keep me company.
You think you're gonna have
fun like this over there?
This is more attention than
I've ever gotten from you.
You should see the floor I'm on.
It's a nursing home.
What the hell happened?
You're acting like you
had nothing to do with this.
I'll have you know,
I held this place together.
I know you think that,
but you actually sold it.
You were supposed
to watch out for us.
This business
doesn't have feelings.
You get bought, you get
sold, you get fired.
If the account moves, you move.
Even if your name's
on the damn door,
you should know better than to
get attached to some walls.
Well, hopefully I'll have
that problem someday.
Okay, hot stuff.
It's exciting.
I mean, I know it's going
to be challenging,
but I needed that.
So do you.
In the summer of '44,
it was over 100 degrees
every day in the Pacific.
So we dropped anchor in the
Ulithi Lagoon to go for a swim.
And you can imagine
the men--
it was bedlam.
But...
I couldn't do it.
Can't you swim?
Did I mention
I was in the navy?
No, the real problem was it was a
two-story drop off our cruiser.
We all have regrets.
No, I did it.
I just needed a push.
This was a hell
of a boat, you know?
Come on.
It just looks good now,
but it was miserable when
you were in it. Trust me.
Is that really how you're
gonna remember this place?
No.
Good.
This is the one
for the road, okay?
You gonna show up drunk
at 4:00
on your first day?
You know any Freemasons?
Yes?
Can I help you?
I'm looking for
Mrs. Baur.
I'm Mrs. Baur.
Good evening. I hope I'm not
disturbing your dinner.
Not yet. My husband will
be home any minute.
Well, I really just need
to talk to you.
I'm Bill Phillips
from Conley Research.
We represent an array
of American companies
including Miller Beer.
And out of over 900 entries,
you, Diana Baur,
were chosen to win
a brand-new Westinghouse
refrigerator full of Miller Beer.
Oh.
Now, you have your choice,
white or harvest gold.
That's the fridge,
not the beer, of course.
Well, that sounds wonderful,
but I'm not Diana, I'm Laura.
Can I still accept it?
I don't know.
I'm supposed to speak to Diana.
Is your mother home?
You really should
speak to my husband.
She's his ex-wife.
I guess if he knows where
she is, I could come back.
Or wait in the car.
My neighbors have seen you
on the porch long enough.
Come on inside.
Have a seat. Would you
like some iced tea?
- I don't want to be a bother.
- It's no bother.
I have to check on the chicken.
Are you looking for my mother?
Diana is your mother?
If she won something,
I should get it.
Yes, that makes sense.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It was no problem at all.
I hope you're finding
everything satisfactory.
Well, I'm here
because I need your help.
I'm at your disposal.
I don't know how to put this,
but I don't feel
that my accounts
are getting the right
kind of attention.
Our accounts.
Well, that's just it.
I fully expect to service clients
with the help of your personnel.
But as a partner at SC&P,
I had a certain amount
of status.
You know, more independence.
What's the problem?
You can speak freely.
Well, I don't think that Ferg
Donnelly is a good match.
Ferg's very
important around here.
Frankly, you're lucky he's taken
an interest in your business.
I understand that,
but it's not necessary.
I don't mean to brag, but I've
been handling this account
on my own
since I brought it in.
I'm sure that's true.
But you're gonna have to get used
to doing things the way we do them.
Well, I don't know
how to say this,
but I can't work with him.
Joan, it may not have sunk in,
but your status has changed.
Avon, Butler Footwear,
Topaz Pantyhose--
I guess you don't need
those accounts.
I've tried to be patient,
but I don't care about
your SC&P partnership.
I don't know if somebody left
it to you in their will,
but your little stake
doesn't mean anything here.
Is that what you want?
Because I'm perfectly happy
to take my half a million
dollars and be on my way.
I'll bet people always say
you're the kind of gal
who doesn't take no
for an answer.
But no, you're not telling
me how to run my business.
Now find a way to get along
or you can expect
a letter from our lawyer.
I wonder how many women around here
would like to speak to a lawyer.
I think the Equal Employment
Opportunity Commission has one.
Women love it here.
You want to threaten us?
You'll be all alone.
No.
I think the second
I file a complaint,
I'll have the ACLU in my office
and Betty Friedan in the lobby
with half the women
who marched down Fifth Avenue.
I guess you didn't see the headlines about
what happened at "Ladies' Home Journal."
Or "Newsweek."
Do you have any idea
how much space
McCann buys in "The New
York Times" every year?
We could get them to print "Mein
Kampf" on the front page.
Yes, I'm sure I'll find it
difficult to find a reporter
who wants to embarrass
you this deeply.
Look, you're unhappy.
And now I'm unhappy.
So how about this--
I'm willing to give you
50 cents on the dollar
to never see your face again.
I guess I wasn't clear.
I'm not negotiating.
Then you should get out
of my office immediately.
Go ahead.
I'd rather give it to a lawyer.
So you get to drive
all over America
giving people prizes?
That sounds like fun.
Well, I also give a lot
of boring presentations.
- Hello.
- Hello, honey.
This is Bill Phillips.
He says Diana won
some kind of prize.
A refrigerator
full of Miller Beer.
Really?
Well, there's been
some confusion
because a Mrs. Diana Baur
entered our contest
and, well, she's
nowhere to be found.
Diana never entered
any contest.
Well, I guess it's a mistake.
Yeah, letting you in our house.
And my wife, she doesn't
know any better,
- but I guess you knew that.
- Cliff, please.
Let him answer.
Who the heck are you?
Or do I have to call
the police?
You're right.
I'm deeply sorry
for the ruse, ma'am.
But I work for
a collection agency.
Clearly you're not responsible
for Mrs. Baur anymore,
but I need to know
her whereabouts.
Last I heard,
she was in New York.
- Do you have an address?
- No.
That's all I got.
I apologize for the intrusion.
Guess we're not as dumb
as you think we are.
- I'm leaving.
- The clothes, the shoes, the Caddy?
- You're no collection agent.
- I am.
You think you're the first one
that came looking for her?
She's a tornado
just leaving a trail of
broken bodies behind her.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
Yeah, but you did.
I am just starting
to get back on my feet.
Just starting to get back to even
part of the way to where I was.
Look, I'm sorry.
I was worried about her.
She seemed so lost.
Well, I lost my daughter to God
and my wife to the devil.
I lost everything.
That what you wanted to know?
No.
You can't save her.
Only Jesus can.
He'll help you, too.
Ask Him.
- Look, I--
- And don't come back.
Come on, once more
from the top.
Where the hell have you been?
I had a lot of stuff to move.
Are any of you
planning to work here,
or is this the con
of the century?
Look, calm down.
We're all just settling in.
Calm down?
Where the hell is Don?
He walked out of a meeting
Wednesday and hasn't come back.
He does that.
Well, you may have
sold me a rotten apple,
but it's not too late
to let the ax fly.
Starting with that redhead.
Joan?
I don't want to hear
her name again.
Good morning.
You made it.
You just come to work
like nothing happened?
I'm here and I'm doing my job.
Get the door.
Jim Hobart's not afraid of you.
Then why'd he send you?
To tell you I can't help you.
Well, thank you very much.
Listen to me.
You're not going to do better
than 50 cents on the dollar.
It's not about the money.
It's only about the money.
Don't hide behind politics.
Take the money
and be done with them.
Take half my money?
I know it's all my fault and
I'm trying to take care of it.
You've started something that
could leave you with nothing.
It's plenty.
I made sure he's good for it.
Tell him he has a deal.
- Where you headed?
- St. Paul.
I can go that way.
Great.
I don't want to take you
out of your way, man.
It's not a problem.
♪ This is Ground Control
to Major Tom ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ You've really
made the grade ♪
♪ And the papers want to know ♪
♪ whose shirts you wear ♪
♪ Now it's time
to leave the capsule ♪
♪ if you dare ♪
♪ This is Major Tom
to Ground Control ♪
♪ I'm stepping
through the door ♪
♪ and I'm floating
in a most peculiar way ♪
♪ And the stars
look very different today ♪
♪ For here am I ♪
♪ sitting in a tin can ♪
♪ far... ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net