_
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I've never worn mink before.
It's chinchilla.
And it costs $15,000.
How does that make you feel?
Nervous.
You're not supposed to talk.
Show me how you feel.
Walk over to the mirror.
Look at yourself.
You like what you see.
Don't open the whole coat.
Just try and make it look like
you're just wearing the fur.
Very good.
Now, I want you
to close your eyes
and take a deep breath.
And when I tell you,
you're gonna put your leg
up on that chair,
let the coat slide down,
and show me how smooth
your skin is.
I remember
when I was a little girl
our house caught on fire.
I'll never forget the look
on my father's face
as he gathered me up
in his arms
and raced through the burning
building onto the pavement.
And I stood there
shivering in my pajamas
and watched the whole world
go up in flames.
And when it was all over,
I said to myself,
"Is that all there is
to a fire?"
Is that all there is?
♪ Is that all there is? ♪
♪ If that's all there is,
my friends ♪
♪ then let's
keep dancing... ♪
Very good, Cindy.
Thank you very much, Cindy.
We'll let you know.
♪ If that's all ♪
♪ there is... ♪
So, what happened?
Well, no woman, even
living in that shithole,
wants a toaster
for her birthday.
- Can you freshen this?
- Yeah.
And Abigail wasn't shy.
- That's your mother?
- Stepmother.
So she put the toaster
in the middle of the table
and all the boarders come
down for breakfast, see it.
They weren't
particularly impressed.
And every day one of them
would trip over that wire
and yank it off the table.
Don't go back there.
A lot of roaches.
- Are you surprised?
- Only by the size.
There was one
making a phone call.
Get up, I want my seat back.
Now, toasters were
indestructible back then,
except for the cord,
which was suffering from being yanked
out of the wall every morning.
My Uncle Mack was cheap and
thought he could fix things.
So he wrapped a piece
of copper wire around it.
And, sure enough,
he plugged it in
and it blew him
into the parlor.
He was unconscious.
All the boarders got up,
ran to his aid,
but Abigail didn't move.
She just looked down
at him and said,
"Happy birthday."
Then put the kettle on.
He loves to tell stories
about how poor he was.
But he's not anymore.
Is that your way of saying you
want me to get the check?
Hey, Mildred Pierce,
can I get the check?
- Come on.
- Be polite.
Oh.
Can I get you something else?
No, just the check. And do you
have anything by John Dos Passos?
I'm sorry about my friend.
He's...
Witty.
Do I know you?
I don't think so.
She's a little old for NYU.
$11.60.
You must have had a lot
of hash browns, sweetheart.
Probably only eats once a week.
Let's split it five ways.
No, I think I owe
someone an apology.
That ought to do it.
That's $100.
Well, I suppose I'm gonna
have to drop one of you off.
You decide who.
Don.
Let's go.
Good evening, Mr. Draper.
- Who am I speaking with?
-  It's Joanne.
You have four messages.
At 7:30, Laura called
and said she has a photo shoot
in the morning,
so don't call
after 11:00.
- What time is it?
-  It's 10 past,
but she called again at 8:00
and said midnight was fine.
What else?
9:30, Maxine called.
She met you two weeks ago
at "Cosmopolitan"
and remains intrigued
by your proposition.
And last, at 10:00,
Tricia from TWA.
She's on a layover.
And what are you
doing tonight, Joanne?
You're very funny,
Mr. Draper.
Give me Tricia's number.
So glad you could make it.
O'Hare's a mess.
They canceled everything,
so it seemed to be fate.
You look ravishing.
I feel a little underdressed.
Where were you tonight?
No, it's true. On every single flight,
there's always one blanket that's
completely soaked in urine.
- In first class?
- Oh, yes.
Oh! I'm sorry.
It's your fault.
You scared me.
Do you have a towel?
Don't do that.
Another woman
you're sleeping with?
No, that's the woman
I'm not sleeping with.
My ex-wife.
Hanes calls them L'eggs.
They're crap.
They're definitely not
as high-quality as Topaz.
Well, they're in
four test markets
and they're outspending
you six to one.
And they're outselling
you 20 to one.
It's more than the packaging.
It's the placement.
They're not just selling
them in drug stores.
They're focusing
on supermarkets.
And they're only
$1.39 a pair.
So what, we need to lower our price
and buy more ad time?
This is only a novelty and the inferior
quality will catch up with them.
But we're recommending
a change right now
while it sorts itself out.
Look, I know
you think I'm cheap.
And I know you think
Topaz are cheap--
although, apparently,
not cheap enough--
but I just want to spend money
where it'll make a difference.
They got an egg.
Why don't we have a topaz?
Big plastic jewel.
Green.
Maybe it's see-through.
And Mr. Potato Head
here can relax
'cause he'll still make his
quota when we launch it.
I'd never recommend
imitation as a strategy.
You'll be second,
which is very far from first.
Whose fault is that?
I told you about the
development of this product
and you didn't seem
worried at all.
Art, Marvin,
are you ready for lunch?
Yes, I am, Kenneth.
We had a problem,
but we solved it.
Well, that's great to hear.
What do we do?
We keep the client.
How was the party?
David Bailey wants
to take your picture.
Well, I have plans tonight,
so I'll be leaving at 5:00 on the dot
and I don't want to hear about it.
- Wake me in--
- You have casting in an hour.
Great.
You have lunch plans?
Just coffee
if the wait's not too long.
No, I just thought I'm going
to the coffee shop,
so I could pick
you up something.
Mathis, you're pouring coffee.
I just wanted to ask you
about something.
You want a raise?
Stop acting like a secretary.
This has nothing
to do with work.
My brother-in-law
is in town
and I thought you could
join Julie and I for dinner.
He's very handsome.
The whole family is.
- You're setting me up?
- He has a car.
It's very sweet, but I really have to
question your judgment.
You know, you're a catch.
Thank you, but how could you think
this has nothing to do with work?
I told my wife that and she
said it wouldn't matter
because she has
a knack for this.
What happens if I take
you up on this offer
and it goes badly
or he's homely
or anything happens
good or bad?
Did you think about that?
No, I didn't anticipate
any of this,
I'll be honest with you.
I appreciate it,
but no, thank you.
Tell Julie
she's very thoughtful.
Are you auditioning?
I tried to arrange a meeting,
but Meredith explained
how much work you have to do.
We met with Topaz and had the
unpleasant conversation.
And their solution was a
knockoff topaz container, green.
What was our solution?
We don't have one.
The irony is they're being pushed
out of the bottom of the market.
What's the top of the market,
department stores?
Yeah, but they're
a drug store brand.
That's what Topaz is.
So they're not called
Topaz anymore.
Tell them their idea
for new packaging was good,
but the new packaging
should say Macy's.
That's going to be tough
when department stores
are being blown up by radicals every day.
You know these two.
People haven't
stopped shopping.
So all I have to do
is sign Macy's.
Piece of cake.
Doesn't McCann represent
Marshall Field's?
Remind them
it's a two-way street.
Phil was in plastics
and he's going to metals.
And Greg was in metals
and he's going to
marketing and advertising,
which is my old job.
That means that Tom Schaeffer
is now head of plastics
at Dow Chemical.
Good for him.
Good for you.
Now's a good time.
He's still not up.
Oh.
Never wake a sleeping baby.
I want to see him.
Oh, what's that?
We don't want you to think
of this as retirement,
we want you to think of it as the
beginning of your professional career.
I don't know what to say.
You say, "Jack Nicklaus,
out of my way.
I've got better clubs."
I'm very touched.
Ever since your mother
passed away,
I haven't really
enjoyed anything.
Honestly, Ed.
He thinks he's a comedian.
I'm just glad there's something
that will get him out of the
house besides that boat.
Who says I'm going
to be in the house?
I've got a lot of time
to make up for.
Daddy, I'm so glad.
I mean, most of the men my age have
had a couple of heart attacks.
I'm still young enough
to enjoy things.
New things, even.
I've started cooking.
Actually made myself a--
what is it, honey?
A Pop-Tart, Ed.
It was very good.
Next.
This is another girl.
Rachel?
I'm supposed to tell you
you missed your flight.
Thank you.
Rachel.
Yes?
You're not just smooth,
you're Wilkinson smooth.
Back to work.
Is it morning?
No.
Go back to sleep.
Sorry, did I wake you?
It's okay.
Did Eddie wake up again?
My dad is so old.
Don't worry about him.
He is going to have a ball.
Why did he wait
so long to do that?
Honey, he loved his job.
But you don't.
You're bored and angry because
you know in your heart
it's not what you want to do.
I should never
tell you anything.
And I haven't gotten any
writing done in a long time.
So start now.
You've done very well.
And let's stop pretending like
I wasn't born with plenty.
You could quit your job.
We could buy that farm.
You could write your book.
What book?
Something sad and sweet.
For all the people who don't have
the guts to live their dream.
Why don't you write a book?
You gave them your eye.
Don't give them
the rest of your life.
Your father was a cog
in a giant machine
that makes weapons and poison.
And you sell them.
I'm proud of the company!
And if nothing else, I'd like to
wait and see if I get that raise.
There's always another hurdle.
You're not listening
to me at all!
- You're late.
- It's five after.
Casting always starts on time.
Can't you smell
the cheap perfume?
Can you call Rachel Katz
at Menken's Department Store?
No, you know what?
Set a meeting.
The number's in the Rolodex.
It's regarding Topaz Pantyhose.
Of course.
Well, you're not the
landing party we expected.
What can we do for you?
Well, as I was telling
David here on the phone,
L'eggs Pantyhose
is an unstoppable foe
in the affordable
pantyhose marketplace.
Our client, Topaz Pantyhose,
has the high quality
to wear
a department store name.
It is a growing
and lucrative product.
And in three months,
L'eggs has sold a year's worth.
So they're worried that L'eggs are
gonna spread all over the world?
That wouldn't bother me at all.
We were hoping
that McCann-Erickson
could provide, at the minimum,
an introduction
to your department
store clients
so we can assess their
desire for a store brand.
I know they'd be
happy to meet you.
Especially Dan Higgins.
He loves redheads.
Would you be able to tell him
what's so special
about your panties?
The benefits are listed there.
But, basically,
they're more sheer,
softer, and more
like silk to the touch,
yet still very strong.
So you can pull them
down over and over?
You can wear them
quite a few times
before they run or lose shape.
Oh.
- Do you wear them, Joan?
- I do.
Well, if you talk to Dan,
I'd start with that.
Well, I think anyone
would be equally interested
in the price-per-unit,
which could be reduced significantly
if the demand were higher.
Why aren't you in
the brassiere business?
Excuse me?
You should be
in the bra business.
You're a work of art.
What she's saying
is that wider distribution
would mean bigger
ad budgets for us.
Well, I'd set a lunch,
but I think a dinner would be better.
And warm him up first.
Send a basket of pears
to Marshall Field's.
The one thing Dan likes
is a nice pear.
This guy.
What are their billings?
If you'd take a look
at the sheet there again...
Oh, yeah.
Give us a minute.
Let's read this thing.
Where were you?
Shirley, you're not
gonna believe this,
but I walked to work today.
Mr. Sterling
and Mr. Donnelly are here.
They just walked in.
You wanted to see me?
You know Ferguson Donnelly
from McCann.
Of course. Ferg.
- Good to see you.
- Been a while.
Is this about the Topaz
department store route?
I think it's a great idea.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Did you send Ed Baxter a $200 set of
MacGregor golf clubs from the firm?
Actually,
I hand-delivered it.
It was a retirement gift.
Huh, well, I've got
some bad news for you.
Pete's gonna take over Dow.
Because of the clubs?
No, because McCann doesn't
want you on the business.
Just because Ed's retiring
doesn't mean I can't get
along with his replacement.
I know Greg from metals.
I don't care if you know
a girl from Kalamazoo.
We don't want you
on the business
because we don't want
you on any business.
Look, Ferg,
you're not still mad
at me for leaving?
That was six years ago.
And you never hired me anyway.
When you bought Puttnam Powell &
Lowe, I came with the furniture.
People come in and out of our
doors all the time, Ken,
but they don't walk out with $4
million of Birds Eye products.
Of course they do.
Fine.
They don't walk around the office
like their shit doesn't stink.
And then go out and tell
the world we're what,
a bunch of black Irish thugs.
So you're gonna fire me because
I hurt Ferg's feelings?
It's what he is.
Look at him.
How about a little dignity?
You're firing me!
Yes, but you're gonna get
a generous severance package
if you help Pete secure
all of your accounts.
Including Dow.
Roger said he'd be glad
to recommend you.
Thank you, Roger.
I appreciate your loyalty.
Should we get lunch?
I want to burn this place down.
I know.
They were awful.
But at least we got a yes.
Would you have rather
had a friendly no?
I don't expect you
to understand.
Joan, you've never
experienced that before?
Have you, Peggy?
I don't know.
You can't have it both ways.
- You can't dress the way you do and expect--
- How do I dress?
Look, they didn't take
me seriously, either.
So what you're saying is
I don't dress the way you do
because I don't look like you.
And that's very, very true.
You know what?
You're filthy rich.
You don't have to do
anything you don't want to.
How was the cattle call?
We have to have
another session.
You're shameless,
you know that?
Do I have a lunch today?
No, but you have
a busy afternoon.
Oh, I scheduled
a meeting next Monday
with Mr. Rosenthal at
Menken's Department Store.
Mrs. Katz didn't
want to meet?
Well, it was a very
awkward conversation
because apparently she stepped
down a few months ago
and passed away last week.
What?
Rachel Katz?
Yes.
Well, I'm sorry
to tell you that.
Last week?
I had no intention
of upsetting you.
How old was she?
I don't know.
Younger than me.
From the name I just
pictured some old lady.
I had no idea.
If you'd like, they've asked
that in lieu of flowers,
you can send a donation to the
National Jewish Hospital at Denver.
Do you want to do that?
No.
Yes, sure.
I'm going to run down
and get you a sandwich.
I'm shoving off.
Need anything else?
No.
Ahem, Mathis.
Yes?
Well, if it helps you get back
into your wife's good graces,
I had a cancellation
and I'd love to join you
for dinner tomorrow night.
Shoot, we already
made other plans.
Oh.
Well, it wasn't meant to be.
Stevie doesn't need to come with us.
I'll sell his ticket.
Stevie?
How old is he?
I don't know, 30?
- I don't know.
- Ugh, can I go?
Give him my number.
Tell him to call me.
Okay.
- You want a menu?
- Just coffee.
And could you get
her attention for me?
Di, just coffee for him.
Evening.
Can I help you?
You look so familiar to me.
Do I know you from somewhere?
Yes, from here.
The other night.
No.
I think I know you.
You don't need a line.
I know why you're here.
And it's not for
a cup of coffee.
Vi, I'm taking my break.
My name is Don.
Excuse me, miss.
When are you done here?
You got your $100's worth.
You can go.
- Have fun last night?
- Yes, I did.
He's very handsome,
I'll tell you that much.
Don. Don.
- Are you okay?
- I'm done.
McCann told Roger to do it.
And, boy, did Roger do it.
They want me to giftwrap all my
accounts and give them to Pete.
I'm calling Jim Hobart
right now.
You're the head of accounts.
Do you want to hear
something spooky?
Don't do anything rash, Ken.
It's just a job.
No, my father-in-law
retires
and my wife says,
"I want you to quit.
You're wasting your life.
You should write that novel."
And you know what?
I think I was gonna do it.
And the very next day,
they fire me.
Can you believe that?
No.
That's not a coincidence.
That's a sign.
Of what?
The life not lived.
So that's good?
Yeah. It's great.
Now I just have to figure out
how to drag myself
through those doors.
Joan, you have
a call from Dennis.
- Dennis who?
-  I'm not sure.
His girl just said Dennis.
He's at McCann-Erickson.
It's Dennis Ford.
Should I put him through?
No.
Tell him I'm in a meeting.
So Clara just left?
She was as big as a house.
Is Torkelson going
to marry her?
He's probably just
looking the other way.
People do that around
here all the time.
I swear I found out
after you did.
It came from McCann.
So did your millions
of dollars.
You know, I didn't
really get millions of dollars.
I mean, eventually,
but stepped out
in smaller increments
to stay under that
top tax threshold.
I might have to buy an apartment
building to hold onto any of it.
And then I've got
to be a landlord.
Sounds like a real
pain in the ass.
Look, I was caught by surprise.
But I didn't know
your history with McCann.
What did you do over there?
I never fit in.
I'm not Irish.
I'm not Catholic.
I can read.
Well, it's good you're playing ball
or you'd have no future.
In advertising maybe.
You have other plans?
Well, I may have
let it go for a while,
but damned if I don't have
something to write about now.
No, this world is boring.
You should write
an adventure story.
I mean, do you know how great
you're gonna look on a book jacket?
I've thought about it.
I'm a hell of a lot better
at it than I ever was at this.
Good for you.
I'm envious.
I thought I was really changing my
life when I went out to California.
Of course, now it sort
of feels like a dream.
But at the time,
it felt so real.
Well, that's you, I guess.
I know.
Look, here I am.
And you know what?
If you get tired
of the writing,
I hope you know
you can always use my name.
I have nothing but good
things to say about you.
I appreciate that.
Jesus, Fillmore Auto Parts?
You trying to give me stuff
we don't even have anymore?
This is the same
as the navy one.
Well, don't tell
Oscar de la Renta
because the navy one is $159.
I can wear boots with that.
You know what?
I'll take the boots
and the tan heels,
the chiffon, the red,
and this one.
Didn't you used to work here?
Because you can probably
still get the discount.
That's tempting,
but I think you have me
confused with someone else.
Could you?
Ted wants to see you.
Send him in.
Just got off the phone
with Wilkinson.
They've narrowed it
down to three girls.
They want me to send
over the binder,
but there's 120
Polaroids in here.
It's just gonna
make things worse.
What can I say?
They're perverts. They love casting.
They can't decide?
Use them all.
There are three women
in every man's life.
You did not just think that up.
Fine, I've had it for years,
but I really think
it works here.
You'd rather find new creative
than pick a girl?
Speaking of which, "Vogue" is throwing
a party in the Village tonight.
Cocktails at my apartment.
It's right around the corner.
Apparently, hemlines
are going up.
What time?
- I'm leaving now.
- Okay.
So, you're from Atlanta?
No, I just went
to school there.
Emory, it's the only
game in town.
How about you?
Me? Oh, no.
I didn't go to college.
I went right to work.
I was a secretary.
That's interesting.
Is it?
Ah, here we go.
Oh, this smells delicious.
It does.
Didn't you order lasagna?
This is just as good.
Do you want my cannelloni?
It's like lasagna.
More than veal, anyway.
Are you trying to make
this more complicated?
I don't know why you're eating
something you didn't order.
Do you like veal?
What am I supposed to do?
Send it back
like a prima donna?
So you're just gonna eat
someone else's dinner?
So I can either be a jerk
and send it back,
or eat it and look weak.
I don't want this to get cold.
Johnny said you were the kind of
girl who doesn't put up with things.
Really?
What else did Mathis say?
He said you were funny.
And that you were fearless.
I love veal.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Should I take my shoes off?
No, that's just
for the mourners.
I just wanted
to pay my respects.
I worked with Rachel.
At the store?
I'm Barbara, her sister.
I'm Don Draper.
I'm in advertising.
Oh.
I know who you are.
Excuse me, do you mind?
We need one more
for our minyan.
I'd be glad to help.
He can't.
He's not Jewish.
Okay.
I'll go and knock on some doors.
You shouldn't do it.
Let one of them do it.
Barbara, they're my neighbors.
We're sitting shiva.
It's a seven-day memorial
period after the funeral.
I've lived in New York
a long time.
I brought cake.
You did.
So, how is your family?
I got divorced.
And I got remarried, actually.
You left your wife for her?
No, it didn't
work out that way.
I'm actually getting
divorced again.
I'm sorry.
Are those her children?
Yes.
When's the last time
you spoke to her?
Years ago.
Before them.
What happened to her?
She had leukemia.
I'm sorry. I don't know what
you're looking for here.
I guess I just wanted to find out
what was happening in her life.
She lived the life
she wanted to live.
She had everything.
Good.
I have to help.
I'm sorry.
Johnny Mathis.
How many times has he shown up
and people have been
disappointed?
"You are not
Johnny Mathis."
I've never thought of that.
You don't seem like a lawyer.
Well, I just left
a firm in Boston
because they felt the same way.
I once quit a job because
I wanted to go to Paris.
Do they do that in advertising?
Sure. We shoot commercials
abroad all the time.
Well, some people do.
So all you have to do
is write something in Paris
and you can go.
Am I wrong?
Yes. That's not
how it works.
Well, next vacation.
I haven't taken a vacation...
well, never.
You know what?
Let's go.
Sure. Where?
To Paris.
Let's go to Paris.
Right now.
You think you're
kidding around,
- but I don't have a job.
- I'm not kidding.
Okay. I'm getting
the check.
And I'm getting my coat.
I can't find it.
I've never actually used it.
You've never used
your passport?
- Stop.
- What? Why?
Flight's not till 6:00.
I hate to disappoint you,
but I don't need
that much time.
I can't believe this.
I can't find my passport.
It's okay.
This is a romantic spot.
Stevie.
I'm sorry,
but what were we
going to do in Paris?
I thought you were a fling,
but now I think
maybe you're more.
I don't want to sleep with you
on the night we first met.
That's so old-fashioned.
I've tried new-fashioned.
Well, if I have to go
back to Boston...
I don't even know
if I'm going to get this job.
Don't you worry.
I am going to find that passport.
We can go next weekend.
I have an interview
in DC next weekend.
How about the weekend after?
Perfect.
You really want me to go now?
Just call me when you
get back from DC.
I will.
Good.
10 days ago with my report to
the nation on Vietnam,
I announced the decision
to withdraw
an additional 150,000 Americans
from Vietnam
over the next year.
I said then that I was
making that decision
despite our concern over increased
enemy activity in Laos.
I've secured Birds Eye.
I think Ferguson Donnelly
is one happy man.
More like a man and a half.
As my father would say, he
really puts the mick in McCann.
Ken's here for the meeting.
- Did you invite him?
- To this meeting?
Oh, hello, Pete.
Roger, I just wanted to let you know
I won't be collecting severance.
You got another job?
Good for you.
But you're still entitled.
It wouldn't be right.
My signing bonus from Dow is so big,
it feels like a second helping.
What the hell
are you talking about?
See, I wasn't just
Ed's son-in-law.
They actually value
their relationships.
Well, I suppose they need
a guy in fertilizer.
I'm taking Tom Schaeffer's old post.
Head of advertising.
So you're going to fire us?
No, it's going to be
way worse than that.
I'm going to be your client.
And I hate to tell you,
but I'm very hard to please.
Until we meet again.
Shit.
Taking Fleischmann's
Margarine to the studio.
If you want changes,
we got to talk now.
Sure, fine, just
keep your voice down.
I commandeered these.
Sounds like you had
quite a night.
It was nice.
With who?
She's going to Europe
with my brother-in-law.
You know, Julie and I went
to Paris on our honeymoon
if you need any
recommendations.
I don't know where I'm going,
but you have work to do.
Paris, huh?
Where margarine was invented.
Wow.
First date magic.
I had too much wine
and I totally
embarrassed myself.
Sounds like you
had a good time.
I'm not going to get on a plane
with somebody I barely know.
But you'd get to know him.
Sounds like fun.
It's nothing a couple
of Aspirin won't fix.
Meredith, I'm leaving
for the day.
I got a little research
for your meeting.
Mr. Rosenthal is first
thing Monday morning.
- Who?
- Mr. Rosenthal.
From Menken's Department Store.
Pantyhose.
Thank you.
I've got this.
Hello.
I don't know why you're here,
but that's not
going to happen again.
Wait.
What?
I...
had this dream about
a woman I once knew.
And I found out the next
day she had just died.
Is that who you think I am?
No, I don't think so.
Well, I want you
to think very carefully
about when you
really had that dream,
because when people die,
everything gets mixed up.
I don't know.
Maybe.
Maybe you dreamt
about her all the time.
Maybe.
When someone dies, you just
want to make sense out of it.
But you can't.
I'm not saying this to lead you
on or make you more interested,
but the next time you come in
here, please bring a date.
I just work here.
I just want to sit here.
Okay.
And then I fell in love
with the most wonderful
boy in the world.
We'd take long walks
down by the river,
or just sit for hours
gazing into each other's eyes.
We were so very much in love.
And then one day,
you went away.
And I thought I'd die,
but I didn't.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
And when I didn't,
I said to myself,
"Is that all there is to love?"
♪ Is that all there is? ♪
♪ Is that
all there is? ♪
♪ If that's all there is,
my friends ♪
♪ then let's keep... ♪
I know what you must be
saying to yourselves
"If that's the way
she feels about it
why doesn't
she just end it all?"
Oh, no, not me
I'm not ready
for that final disappointment
'cause I know
just as well as I'm standing
here talking to you
that when that final moment comes
and I'm breathing my last breath
I'll be saying to myself...
♪ Is that all there is? ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net