Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Hello?
Don.
Draper!
Oh, Melanie. I'm sorry.
I must have overslept.
They're coming before work.
I told your service,
but you never called me back.
There's no time for a shower.
I'll make the bed.
Thought you were having
the carpets cleaned.
I did.
I find it hard to believe I have
to replace it to sell this place.
Couldn't you rent
a couple of pieces?
It's so lonely.
It's better.
They can imagine
their own things in it.
Have you ever sold
an apartment?
I've sold a lot
uglier things than this.
Can you go?
I don't want you
crossing paths.
Good luck.
Hello?
Yes, I'll accept the charges.
Yes, Mom, you woke me.
I don't know. I'm not
due at the office yet.
Los Angeles
is three hours earlier.
It's simple subtraction.
I want to talk to him, too.
Well, hello, sweetie.
Do you know
how much I miss you?
What did you and Grandma
Gail do this morning?
Hello?
Room service, please.
I'd like a glass of skim milk,
a grapefruit,
and a pot of coffee.
And some French toast.
- You wanted to see me?
- Come in. Have a seat.
Can I offer you something?
A pad and pen perhaps?
You know, I could have you killed for
drinking anything but a Coke around here.
To whom it may concern?
Our benevolent overlords
at McCann
have invited select presidents
of select subsidiaries
to a godless retreat
in the Bahamas.
So you have to make a speech.
That's what I thought. I figured
it'd be like a toast, you know?
I'm good at that.
Apparently Caroline
looked at the fine print
and they're expecting some
sort of written statement
on the future of this company.
2,500 words.
- When?
- By Monday.
It's plenty of time. Harry's writing
a manifesto on the computer.
Chaough's doing
performance reviews.
And they need to finish with a nice
Gettysburg Address type speech
that tells them where
we're gonna be next year.
Mr. Sterling,
there's a call for you
on line three.
Gettysburg Address.
Got it.
I'd do it myself, but
one of us is very busy.
You're going to the Bahamas.
I'm sorry.
How are you doing?
Never been better.
Well, you've looked better. You
want me to get my barber in here?
Anything else?
Here are the specs.
Just, uh, reasonable
hopes and dreams.
Doesn't have to be
science fiction.
Roger?
You must be Dee.
What a pleasure to meet
you in the flesh.
Top of the morning.
How was your trip?
So far so good.
- How about that sun?
- Yes.
Have you been
to California before?
Listen, I've got
to run an errand.
I'll be back. First
appointment is at noon.
Did we have a cancellation?
You're interviewing people
who already have jobs.
They have to sneak out.
It's lunch or breakfast.
Well, I thought we could
rank the candidates in advance.
Come on, I did it, you did it.
No need to do it together.
Santa Monica or Sunset?
Sunset to Highland to Cahuenga.
Why don't you show me around?
How is the Beverly Wilshire?
Have you seen Warren Beatty?
Not yet.
More money, bigger accounts,
more awards,
international business,
and a space station?
Gas station.
I'm sorry, am I interrupting?
- Do you have my thesaurus?
- Probably.
Listen, you need to sign off
on the Peter Pan cookie.
- He's very busy.
- Stay out of this.
We can't take it out without you
signing off on it and you know it.
- Let's go.
- Do you need me to set it up?
No, just broad strokes.
Peter Pan's best friend
is Tinker Bell.
That's why his delicious
cookie is named after her.
We have a series
of Dear John letters
in children's handwriting
with kid voice-over
explaining why they've
left the competitors
for the unique taste
of Tinker Bell cookies
made with real
Peter Pan Peanut Butter.
Each letter has a little
joke about the competition.
"Dear Nilla Wafers,
it's so plain it's over.
Susie."
"Dear Oreos, don't split
apart, I love another."
"Dear Chips Ahoy,
I hope--"
Okay, I get it.
And then a cartoon touch
of the wand on the cookie.
A sparkle.
"Peter Pan Peanut Butter lovers
love Tinker Bell cookies
more than all others."
Jesus, love again?
We use it all the time.
Kids won't get it and
adults won't hear it.
It's not up for debate.
Do we have another line?
"One Tink
and you're hooked."
What's wrong with that?
I was worried.
How will they know
Tink is Tinker Bell?
Because you're gonna tell them
five times in 60 seconds.
Are we still going to be ready?
That's why we had this meeting.
Jim McCloud is gonna be here any minute.
Where's Lou?
He called.
He's running late.
He called?
From where?
Don't be mad at him.
He's working on
something very big.
What?
Between us,
Hanna-Barbera.
The cartoon studio?
Yes. They're very interested
in this comic he created.
It's like Gomer Pyle,
but he's a monkey.
How long has this
been going on?
Since he was in the army.
- I think he misses it.
- That's not what I meant.
Hello.
How are you?
You must be Mr. McCloud.
Yes. Yes, I am.
And you are?
I'm Joan Harris.
I'm an account executive
and a partner.
Mr. Avery is stuck
in traffic,
but I suppose we can begin.
I'm sorry.
Dee, would you offer
Mr. McCloud some coffee?
Please.
Hope I didn't keep you waiting.
I was catching up
with Jim here.
Jim McCloud, Joan Harris.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Pleasure's mine.
Jim, come on in.
Take a load off.
Dee, can you get me a Sanka?
Who are you?
Richard Burghoff.
I'm looking for my optometrist.
Why didn't you say so?
A woman like you
wants to talk to me--
I'm a little nearsighted,
I'm not blind.
Have dinner with me.
I don't know.
I want to see
if I can get the job.
Joan, are you coming or not?
- I have to go.
- French?
Why am I signing these now?
Because you sign it again
when they cash it.
That's how they know it's you.
But anyone who steals this
could copy my signature, too.
They have it worked out, Sally.
Why are you snapping at me?
This trip was your idea.
I'm going to miss you.
You should really talk to them
about Colonial Williamsburg.
You're driving right by it.
It's 12 states in 12 days.
They can't stop everywhere.
Well, when I did the trip,
it was six states.
Weren't they still colonies?
We got into a little
bit of trouble.
And I want you to know
that's to be expected.
Trouble?
Really?
You know, staying up all night.
We would try and break
all the lightbulbs
in the hallway at every hotel.
We're not going to do that.
Well...
there are going
to be boys everywhere
and you're going to be
away from home,
so I hope you have
the good sense
to not act like you've
been let out of a cage.
I'm sorry, Mother,
but this conversation
is a little late.
And so am I.
Everything is a joke to you.
- How'd it go?
- About how I expected.
They loved the lobby, but
the emptiness is a problem.
There's other ways
to sell things.
I'm using everything I have.
But this requires
too much imagination.
That's the best
opportunity in the world.
Who's your best prospect?
It was a young stockbroker
from New Jersey
with a four-year-old
and one on the way.
Why don't you tell them
somebody lived here
who made a million dollars
inventing the Frisbee?
And they had to move in a
hurry to a castle in France.
Taxes.
A little glamor, a little hope.
I'm not a magician.
I have to show it to people
with their eyes open.
And you know
what it looks like?
It looks like
a sad person lives here.
And what happened to him?
He got divorced,
spilled wine on the carpeting and
didn't care enough to replace it.
Even for himself.
Don't blame your failure on me.
This place reeks of failure.
It is an $85,000
fixer-upper.
A lot of wonderful things
happened here.
Well, you wouldn't know it.
I have a good feeling
about things.
See you tomorrow.
You know I have
a very early flight.
You are not going anywhere.
I'm serious.
Joan, I've been
in prison for five years.
You're acting like it.
Here's the plan.
First, I'm gonna kiss you.
I know the rest of this.
Then you're gonna
cancel your flight.
Then I'm gonna drive you
up to Malibu for lobster
in one of those tourist traps
where everyone's getting engaged.
Then on up to the Biltmore
in Santa Barbara
where I'll sit
on a lounge chair
and watch you get in
and out of the pool.
Richard, that sounds wonderful.
But I have someplace to be.
And I'm sure you do as well.
I told you, I'm retired.
Yes.
And you were
a millionaire developer.
You must think
I just fell off a truck.
Are you a movie producer as well?
No.
But the rest of it
is the truth, honey.
What is the rest of it?
I guess we've been
dancing around this all night.
I'm divorced.
You?
You think I would be
doing this if I was married?
Have you ever been married?
Yes.
Boy, did he blow it.
He did.
22 years.
I stayed in it for the kids.
And when my youngest graduated,
I saw her heading off to Europe
and I thought,
"Jeez, that looks good."
I mean, hell,
I built something.
I built a lot of things.
But I also put off
a lot of things.
And now I'm free.
As a bird.
I need to work.
So you have mouths to feed?
No.
I just finally got the job
I've always wanted.
So you're just an executive
on a trip out of town.
I'll send you flowers.
Morning, Meredith.
Mr. Sterling came by
for your prognostication.
I told him you were
at the library.
That's not a bad idea.
And can you dig up the press
release from when we started SCDP?
That would be December '63.
- Coffee?
- Morning, Don.
No. I'll get it.
Meredith got me two of these.
I only need one.
Sure.
When are you casting
St. Joseph's?
Two weeks.
Did you meet someone
we should see?
No, just organizing
my schedule.
You ever feel like there's less to
actually do, but more to think about?
Not really.
Maybe I'm a bad manager.
Maybe I'm too, what do
they call it, hands-on.
So, going to this casting session.
What's next?
Shoot the ad?
No, what's the future
going to bring?
I mean, it's good as it is,
but is there a scenario
in which it's better?
You're incredible.
You know, Roger asked me
to do that first.
How'd you get out of it?
I thought about it a little
and then I realized
you're so much better
at painting a picture.
So you did have thoughts.
Sure.
We'll have an oil company.
You know, maybe Goodyear Tires.
We know so much about cars.
That's your dream?
No, I mean, obviously
I'd like to one day--
I don't know.
What?
I'd really love to land
a pharmaceutical.
Bigger accounts?
That's your greatest desire?
That's why I'm doing
the performance reviews.
You know, before McCann
all I ever thought of
was will we be
in business next year?
Or will I be here at all?
Now it could be anything.
I have a Richard
Burghoff on the line.
I'll take it.
Hello.
Well, your story checks out.
It's nice to hear from you.
How are things in paradise?
I don't know.
I'm in town.
What?
You're in New York?
Tell me where we're eating.
The Oak Room, 7:30.
Should I pick you up
at work or at home?
I'll see you there.
Well, good.
You can make an entrance.
There you are.
We have a peanut butter
cookie problem.
Don, don't listen to him.
Pete, what are you doing?
- The client hated the layout.
- Exactly, that's the problem.
And then Mathis and Ed
turned on each other.
There was some kind of
"I told you so" exchange
which was already
unbearably inappropriate.
And then Mathis said...
a four-letter word
that starts with F.
Have you ever heard
such a thing?
He was frustrated.
He can't fire my men.
- I can fire you.
- Hold on.
Nobody's getting fired.
- You have to send those idiots back in.
- Absolutely not.
If you send someone new,
it looks like we're starting over.
It was a crime of passion.
They've heard the word before.
Fine.
I want new work fast.
Problem solved.
May I help you?
Is Sally home?
I'm a friend of hers.
Sally.
There's a young man
here to see you.
- What's your name, ma'am?
- It's Loretta.
Is Mrs. Draper home?
You mean Mrs. Francis.
What are you doing here?
I was in the neighborhood.
You know Betty's home.
I don't care.
I just wanted to see you.
See?
You survived finals.
- How's your summer?
- I'm going on a teen tour.
Then maybe be
a lifeguard again.
Do you have something
to do right now?
I got it.
Hey, I'll be out in a second.
I have to use the restroom.
This is Paula.
This is Sally.
Hey there. Could you get me
a map to the powder room?
First door on the left.
- Hello.
- You have a lovely home.
Sally, I didn't know
you had guests.
We just dropped by.
We were on our way to Playland and
thought maybe you'd want to come.
Aren't you going
to introduce me?
I'm Glen Bishop.
We lived up the street
in Ossining.
Glen?
My goodness.
How old are you?
18.
So, you two
have stayed in touch?
- Yeah.
- We've been pen pals.
What have you been
doing with yourself?
You look so different.
You look exactly the same.
Good, you found my backpack.
Yes, it was in
the storage room.
You must be in school.
Yeah, just finished my
freshman year up at Purchase.
That's supposed
to be very good.
I'm actually going back
to school myself this fall.
Very cool.
Can I have some actual money
to take to Playland?
What? Of course.
Go get my pocketbook.
Can't you?
Hey. Sorry for
running past you.
My mother hates that.
Just really had to go.
That's quite all right.
Can I offer you all
something to drink?
- Iced tea?
- No.
I'd take a beer
if you've got one.
- Of course.
- Hold on.
I thought we were going to Playland.
Are you coming?
I'd love to go with you,
but I don't have any money.
Do you talk to
your parents this way?
Do you have any grass?
We can get it there.
Don't stay too late.
You have to pack.
Nice meeting you.
Enjoy the rest of your summer.
- Betty.
- Yes?
I feel like I should say
a more formal good-bye.
Nonsense.
You're welcome here anytime.
No.
It's just that...
I'm shipping out next week.
What do you mean?
I'm reporting.
He joined the army.
Are you kidding?
No.
Are you fucking stupid?
- Sally!
- I don't expect you to understand.
- You hate the war.
- Not anymore.
What about Kent State?
You were crying.
You were gonna join
the movement.
What about a bunch
of Negro kids dying
while we just sit at home getting stoned?
It's immoral.
Was this your idea?
We just met.
You're gonna die.
For what?
Don't listen
to Jane Fonda here.
It's a very brave thing to do.
You know what?
Have fun at Playland.
Just remember those kids
are the same age
as the ones you're going
to be murdering in Vietnam.
Sally, come on.
I'm sorry.
No.
I expected it.
Well, you've obviously grown
into a fine young man.
Thank you, ma'am.
Please don't let this
mar your afternoon.
We'll see you
when you get back.
Sally, too.
Fourscore and seven years ago.
We know where we've been,
we know where we are.
Let's assume that it's good.
But it's got to get better.
It's supposed to get better.
Mr. Mathis needs to see you.
I told him you were busy.
Send him in.
Hello, Don.
Just wanted to thank you
for fighting for me.
Who told you that?
Should we open it?
I'm set.
I appreciate
your confidence in me.
What do you want?
I want you to come
to the meeting.
No.
You have to make this
right yourself.
How?
I mean, do I apologize to them?
Do I apologize to Ed?
Do I slam my hand
in the door over and over?
I once interrupted the client
during a presentation for Lucky Strike,
our biggest account.
What did you say?
I wasn't supposed
to talk at all.
I knew if I apologized, they'd
never want to work with me again.
Why?
Do I really
have to explain that?
Not if you don't want to.
So the next meeting
I walked in,
shook Lee Garner's hand
and said,
"I can't believe you have
the balls to come back
after you embarrassed
yourself like that."
Okay.
I think I understand.
I don't know.
Bring in a bar of soap.
Tell them it's there in case you
need to wash your mouth out.
Something like that.
Thank you, Don.
This was a big deal.
Four golf courses.
Some with estates planned
on the perimeter.
Palos Verdes.
- Is that nice?
- Yes, dear.
And all of a sudden, some
hippies come out of the wall
yelling about low-income
housing, killing birds.
Must be real radicals
to prefer low-income
housing to a golf course.
Come on, whose side are you on?
I just root for the underdog.
Well, let's see
how softhearted you are.
How about a nightcap?
That sounds nice.
Where did you
tell him you were?
Who?
Tell me the truth.
Are you married?
No.
Please don't lie to me.
I have a little boy.
Oh.
His name is Kevin
and he's four.
Four?
That's a very little boy.
Does that make a difference?
No.
Can I get the check?
Yes, I'm fine.
Um, when do you
expect him back?
But I'm going out of town tomorrow
and I want to say good-bye.
Yes.
Just tell him I'm sorry
and I want
to say good-bye.
He has to call me.
I'm sorry. I didn't
want to make you cry.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I want your hands free.
Do you mind
if I make a phone call?
I should tell somebody
I'm going to be late.
Can I offer you a brandy?
Gin and tonic.
May I have
an outside line, please?
Look at this.
Ice.
That's a good hotel.
Harris residence.
Hello, Maureen.
It's Joan.
I wanted to see if you could
stay a few hours longer.
I don't know.
It's already
a quarter to 10:00.
Well, what did
we say, 11:00?
How about 1:00?
I don't know.
I kind of have someplace to be.
Any chance in persuading you
to stay until midnight?
Okay. You know, he had
trouble going to sleep.
He said he was afraid
of a cow or something.
It's a horse.
Is everything okay now?
I don't know.
I haven't heard anything.
I'll check on him.
Wonderful.
Thanks so much.
You need to go?
No. We have
all the time we need.
Or until midnight.
I wasn't going
to spend the night
under any circumstances.
It's the kind of woman I am.
A woman with a little kid.
Would you rather I was married?
Honey, give me a little bit
of credit for the fact that,
well, I could have been a
cad and waited until after
to tell you
I don't like this.
You don't like what?
I love kids.
But I raised mine
already and I'm--
I know it sounds selfish.
I mean, I'm done
with that part of my life.
You're being presumptuous.
I know what this is
and so do you.
Or you wouldn't have lied.
I can't believe this.
You're such a disappointment.
This is not how I saw things.
I have a plan
which is no plans.
You can't go to the pyramids.
You can't go anywhere.
You're right.
Nice meeting you.
Miss Olson
would like to see you
- when you have a moment.
- Send her in.
Ted told me I have to fill out
my own performance review.
I guess he respects
your opinion.
- I'm tired of this.
- I'd start with that.
I'm serious.
I want to have
my performance reviewed.
I've had quite a year.
What do you see for the future?
Well, um...
is that on there?
No, I'm just curious.
I'd like to be the first woman
creative director at this agency.
That's funny to you?
No, I'm impressed
that you know exactly.
What else is there?
That's what I'm asking.
Let's say you get that.
What's next?
Land something huge.
And then?
Have a big idea.
Create a catchphrase.
So you want fame?
Yes.
What else?
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
Create something
of lasting value.
In advertising?
This is supposed to be about my
job, not the meaning of life.
So you think those things
are unrelated?
I didn't know
you'd be in a mood.
Do you want me
to do this or not?
Why don't you just write down
all of your dreams
so I can shit on them?
Where the hell were you?
Good morning to you, too.
I was at class.
Why didn't you
mention that last night?
Didn't Gail give you
my schedule?
You and Gail are quite a team.
She really needed a vacation.
I think you need a vacation.
You know what?
You're ruining my life.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, sweetie.
Anyway, I think
you'll be impressed.
If nothing else, by the speed with
which they turned this around.
Well, nice to see you again.
Can't believe you two have
the balls to walk back
into this place after the way
you embarrassed yourselves.
Did you go to the World's Fair?
That's what I think
it's going to look like.
What was your favorite part?
Oh, good.
You're here.
- Can I help you?
- Get out.
What's going on?
I tried your little saying
and I'm off the business.
What are you talking about?
I made your joke
and it failed miserably.
- The soap thing?
- No!
The one where I told them
they were assholes.
You could have thought of
something yourself, you know.
I did.
It was apologize.
But you don't understand that because
guys like you don't have to do it.
Guys like me know how to do it.
Roger tells that
Lucky Strike story, too.
But he says that Lee Garner Jr.
was in love with you.
That you always had to be at the meetings
so he could think about jacking you off.
You have a foul mouth.
Take responsibility
for your failure.
That account was handed to you and you made
nothing of it because you have no character.
You don't have any character.
You're just handsome.
Stop kidding yourself.
Everybody has problems.
Some people can deal with them
and some people can't.
Look at yourself
because the next thing
you're gonna have to move past
is losing this job.
You're fired.
I guess I kind of assumed that
when I walked in here.
I just knew
I shouldn't apologize.
- Is everything all right?
- Shut the door for me.
There's a Jim
McCloud here to see you.
He's waiting in the lounge.
What are you doing here?
Well, thank you so much.
I'm a heel, okay?
No, it's my fault.
I thought about it and
I'm sending my son away.
- What?
- No, I thought about what you said.
And I like you, too.
And if I have to choose
between you and my son,
I choose you.
That's not what I said.
That's exactly what you said.
Well, I've thought about it
and I want to be
a part of your life.
And your little boy, too.
I live with my mother.
And I've been divorced twice.
I'm buying some property
in New York.
Where do you live?
12th Street.
Okay, I'm not gonna
buy property down there.
But...
I'm gonna get a place
in a nice neighborhood
near the park
and you're gonna visit.
All of you.
We'll see.
I don't want to be rigid.
It makes you old.
Can I call you?
Okay.
I got it.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
Loretta let me in
on her way out.
I didn't want to surprise you.
No, that's fine.
You know Sally's not here.
I know.
Can I get something to drink?
Of course.
What do you have in mind?
How about that beer?
Do you want to sit down?
No.
They have beer over there.
From what I read
in the magazines,
they have all
the comforts of home.
Sally's mad.
My mother's mad.
But you're not.
They're afraid for you.
I am, too, honestly.
But you understand
why I'm doing it.
Do you want me
to say that I like it?
I know you do because I'm
brave and I love this country
and I want to protect it
and everyone in it.
Glen.
I know something
could happen to me.
But I feel safe
because I know you're mine.
Glen, stop.
Why?
Because I'm married.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I understand.
You don't.
Well, I don't know
what I'm supposed to say.
This was gonna be the good thing
that came out of all this.
This is all I thought about.
Glen.
I know you know me.
I know you know
the man I can be.
Glen, please don't tell me
that you did this for me.
I couldn't live with myself.
It's so much worse.
What?
I flunked out.
Oh, no.
My stepdad knew
I was doing bad.
He was gonna kill me.
Kick me out.
After I told him,
he was so proud.
Everything was
peaches and cream.
You're going to make it.
I'm positive.
Don't let me fill up on these.
The bus leaves at 8:30.
Will the food come in time?
They must have run
out of stray cats.
You're so funny.
He always says that.
It's still funny.
What place are you
most excited about?
Washington DC. We're going
to the floor of the Senate.
To protest?
No, we're getting a tour
from Senator Dodd.
We're going to find
an office for Carol.
You want to work there one day?
I want to be a senator.
That's impressive.
Good for you.
I don't know what I want to be.
You'll figure it out.
What are your interests?
I guess I just want
to live in New York.
I want to be
a translator at the UN.
Yolanda's father is a diplomat.
I'm so tired of people
asking me what I want to do.
Well, if you're lucky
enough to think of it,
you should write it down.
Because when you get older,
you're gonna forget.
Did you write down advertising?
I didn't know
what advertising was.
But I wanted to be
in New York City, too.
So, where do you live, Don?
Where do I live?
The Upper East Side.
In a penthouse?
As a matter of fact, yes.
But he grew up very poor.
And now you have a penthouse.
- May I?
- Sure.
When I watch television,
the commercials
are my favorite part.
So what do you want to do?
I just want to eat dinner.
Nothing like having
realistic goals.
- Good-bye, Mr. Draper.
- Bye.
Thanks for dinner.
Sally.
- I'll wave from the bus.
- Hold on a second.
It's okay to be nervous
about going away.
You can't control
yourself, can you?
What are you talking about?
Sarah is 17, you know.
I'm well aware of that, Sally.
But it doesn't stop you.
And it doesn't stop Mom.
Anyone pays attention
to either of you,
and they always do,
and you just ooze everywhere.
Your friend's
a fast girl, Sally.
I didn't want to embarrass her.
You know what I'm gonna
write down for my dream?
I want to get on the bus and
get away from you and Mom
and hopefully be a different
person than you two.
Hey.
I'm your father.
And you may not want
to listen to this,
but you are like
your mother and me.
You're gonna find that out.
You're a very beautiful girl.
It's up to you
to be more than that.
Bobby, Gene, get back here.
It's time for bed.
I want to watch
"The Brady Bunch."
Fine.
Give me that.
Hello?
Oh, um...
This will just take a minute.
It's done.
I did it.
I don't know how,
but they're signing.
Right now?
Asking price.
30-day escrow.
Really?
Now we have to find
a place for you.
♪ the first time ♪
♪ ever I saw your face ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ rose in your eyes ♪
♪ and the moon ♪
♪ and the stars ♪
♪ were the gifts you gave ♪
♪ to the dark ♪
♪ and the endless skies ♪
♪ my love ♪
♪ to the dark ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net