Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ we don't smoke marijuana
in Muskogee... ♪
♪ we don't take
our trips on LSD ♪
♪ we don't burn
our draft cards... ♪
♪ down on Main Street ♪
♪ we like livin' right
and bein' free... ♪
I need your license
and registration
and I need to know
what you were doing.
I'm driving.
Don't get smart with me.
We've been looking for you.
There's been a mistake.
You knew we'd catch up
with you eventually.
I can't find any baking soda.
We're gonna have
to make do with Colgate.
On my arm?
Well, you're back early.
Well, we had to skip lunch.
- Hello, Sherry.
- Hello.
I got stinged.
Oh, sweetheart.
We were up at Lyman Orchards.
It's mostly bees.
Daddy put toothpaste on it.
Yes, and you're
no worse for wear.
Not allergic, thankfully.
I'm terribly so.
I have an hour. I suppose
we could still grab lunch.
No, this is fine.
She should probably rest.
I'll see you Thursday,
Wonder Woman.
We'll go to Friendly's.
Well, I'm off.
Go inside and lay down,
sweetheart.
Every time Bill has the kids,
something terrible happens.
The incredible thing is
I make her lunch,
I take her to school,
I read to her every night,
and he spends Sunday
and Thursday night with her
and that's all I hear about.
Well, I admire you.
Are you trying to get me
to make you lunch?
No, I think it's admirable that you
haven't poisoned her against him.
I don't know if I could
have that restraint.
Yes, you would.
Because you'd be concerned
about your child
and do your best
to forget things.
And not expect your friends
to remind you all the time.
I am so sorry.
That is not what
I was trying to say.
I know.
Would you like some of these?
So what happened
to field hockey?
If I'm on the yearbook,
I won't be a benchwarmer.
Well, can you quit before I buy
you cleats and a stick next time?
I'm going to sell everything.
You know how much
Madrid's going to cost?
I'm not gonna back out of that.
I want to go to Spain.
You think it'll be more
interesting than Wyoming?
I don't know.
Wyoming had a two-headed cow.
You'll see it on the postcard.
So where's next?
Well, I'm in Kansas right now.
I'm going to take Route 35.
Then over on 40.
Then 89 to the Grand Canyon.
I feel like I'm sitting
right next to you.
Is it cold yet?
A little.
I wouldn't rush home.
Well, I want to get your brothers
before they go to sleep.
I'll call you next week.
I really want you
to sell that equipment.
You have no idea about money.
I will. Bye.
Bye, sweetheart.
Are you lost?
No, I'm a student here.
Well, see you around.
Oh!
Hey, give her some room.
You okay, lady?
Just my pride.
New shoes.
I think I need a minute.
Duck, how are you?
Fit as a fiddle, thank you.
28th?
That's top brass.
Actually, it's none
of your business.
Don't be coy. You're helping
them replace Don, aren't you?
I've done it before.
Is it true he left behind
a couple million bucks?
Nice to see you.
Actually, let me
ask you something.
Morning, John, Norm.
One month and you're
already the mayor.
They've been very hospitable.
Of course I delivered everyone.
I even brought
Burger Chef back.
And after Joan cashed in,
I saved Avon.
There have been whispers
about Coca-Cola.
No need to impress me.
What do you want?
Not here.
This will just
take a moment, Sarah.
You can't be in here.
Everyone's going to think
I'm looking for a job.
You mind?
They should always
think you're unhappy.
You're wrong. And for the
first time, they don't.
Now go outside and tell everyone you
staggered into the wrong office.
- They'll believe you.
- Look, this isn't about you.
I've been trying to get this
private aviation company
to have me do all their hiring.
But before any of that happens,
they want to review
their overall strategy.
So I want you to go
to dinner and recommend
that they hire an in-house
senior marketing man.
And I'm the guy to find him.
Because you're the best?
Yes.
And then you can extoll
the wonders of McCann.
Everybody wins.
I don't need to poach.
You know, I helped you for
free after that stupid merger.
And then you sent Peggy to Gerald
what's-his-name when she was in need.
This is how I make
my living, Pete.
I've paid you at some point.
You'd want this business if you
knew you couldn't have it.
Learjet is private,
luxury air travel.
Look, Pete, I just have
to fill this one position
and I'll make it
through the winter.
For old times' sake.
Fine. Who is he?
His name is Mike Sherman and he moved
to Wichita from Philly four years ago.
Princeton '52. You should
have a lot in common.
I'm Dartmouth '56.
I know that.
Don't pretend like you're not
gonna jack each other off.
- Sarah.
- Yes, Mr. Campbell?
Would you remind me that I need to
make a donation to Lincoln Center?
Mr. Phillips
was very persuasive.
Thank you for your generosity.
KOMA, fun-loving 1520.
The capital radio...
...for the capital city,
Oklahoma City, Oklahoma.
Shit.
Look for clear skies with
a high temperature today of 75.
A pleasant day
here in this pleasant city.
Current temperature is 73.
Beautiful weather
out there today.
Dr. Buckley will be right
with you, Mrs. Robinson.
It's Mrs. Francis.
Oh, the boys who dropped you
off said that was your name.
I think that was a joke.
Oh.
Nurse, could you excuse us?
Mrs. Francis, is it possible
to get your husband down here?
I can drive with a broken rib.
It's not even that sore.
Well, I took a look
at your X-ray
and it may be more serious
than just the rib.
How serious?
You can use the phone
at the nurses' station.
I'm gonna sue them.
First I'm gonna go through
the Health Commission
and I'm gonna look
into their funding.
That quack has some nerve
scaring you like that.
What happens to my car?
I'll send my secretary up here
in a cab tomorrow morning.
And I'm gonna call--
call-- call Jim.
Call--
You know what?
I'll just call Rocky's office.
That's what I'm gonna do.
Henry, I want to go home.
Babe, look at me.
You're gonna be just fine.
Afternoon.
Wyatt called from
the service station.
We've got our best
available for you.
If you threw a rod,
it's gonna take some time.
It's the rocker arm.
Well, I've got a weekly for
$37 or a daily for six.
Let's take it
a night at a time.
I'm an optimist.
Oh, hello.
This is my wife Sharon.
Of the Sharon Motel.
This is Donald from New York.
- Don.
- Pleasure to have you with us.
Do you know where
I could get a meal?
There's a cafe a couple
of miles up the road.
He's got car trouble.
Well, I made a roast.
How'd you like leftovers
as room service?
I don't want you
to go to the trouble.
Do you have vending machines?
You can have both.
Give him some change and
have Andy take his luggage.
This is all I got.
Here's two dimes and a nickel.
There you go.
I believe that's one of the
best steaks I've ever had.
Well, it's the best because
they flew it out from Kansas.
Isn't Wichita cattle country?
It sure is.
But I was disappointed
when I got there
that I didn't see
more ten-gallon hats.
But your company is very glamorous.
As far as I can tell, its entire public
reputation is based on Hollywood.
Well, we thought we'd go with
our most exciting customers.
Elizabeth Taylor.
Danny Kaye.
Somebody you want to meet?
Not really.
In fact, I think that's the
problem if you have one.
I have one, or I wouldn't
be talking to you.
Corporate executives should
be your core business.
You can read that
without glasses?
I've looked at your business
and I think Duck's right.
You need a senior
marketing executive.
And not just anyone.
You need someone comfortable
with the kind of boardroom leaders
that see Learjet as a tool,
not a frivolous extravagance for
movie stars and their pets.
McCann could run circles
around Carson Roberts.
But we wouldn't
even be interested
unless Duck found the right
man for your company.
I don't understand.
Are you advocating for
your agency or for yourself?
We're one and the same.
Well, the jobs are not
one and the same.
You can't work for McCann
and work for us.
I'm aware of that.
But I couldn't agree with
you more about who we need.
I told Duck I was looking
for a real knickerbocker.
Right schools, right family.
Someone who can rap
his ring on the table
and let everyone know
they're with a friend.
Well, I'm flattered.
But I'm afraid Duck Phillips has
tricked me into a job interview.
I stand by my analysis,
but I'm very happy where I am.
I expect him to lie to me.
I didn't expect him
to lie to you.
I'm glad we got to meet.
Likewise.
That's never a mistake.
You want a brandy?
Because Duck's going
to get the check.
Well, unfortunately,
we've discovered
that the cancer has spread
from the lung
and metastasized to the bones
and to lymph nodes
in the mediastinum.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
It's aggressive
and it's very advanced.
I wish there was better news.
What do we do?
Well, I'm going to recommend
a radiation oncologist
for therapy to help
mend the rib.
It won't heal without it.
Then a medical oncologist.
She could have
nine months to a year,
but these treatments
are usually palliative.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, sorry about that.
You should put the sign out.
You're the maid?
And the messenger.
I guess they didn't know
you were in here.
Wyatt called. It's a
bushing on the rocker arm,
but it's got
to come from Tulsa.
So I'm gonna need another book.
The chlorine's killed
the piss in the pool by now.
You can go for a swim.
Anything else
to do around here?
There's football at the
high school Friday night.
Revival church every night.
Fairview's got
a drive-in,
but you don't have a car.
Where can I get a drink?
That's a little complicated.
But I probably can
rustle up a bottle.
That'd be great.
Andy.
You want me to clean up?
Don. Maybe tomorrow.
There she is.
Don't run.
I'm in Grand Central.
Come down.
Only to throw you
under a train.
Come on.
I only have one question.
I better have gotten
that lousy job.
You did, and it's not lousy.
I haven't even negotiated,
we're already at 100 a year.
All benefits and unlimited
private jet travel.
It's a flying limousine, Pete.
You can have lunch in New
York and be back for dinner.
Good, because I live here.
I have to go.
- He wants to have dinner with wives.
- No.
He's only meeting
with you and one other guy.
Two last-round dinners.
Help me turn it
into a horse race.
How many times do you think
you can lie to this man?
We both told him you didn't want the job.
What's the lie?
Well, for one thing,
I don't have a wife.
For the other,
I have four years left
on my contract with McCann
and a million dollars
contingent on my presence.
Uh-huh, so now we know
there's a price.
You're talking to yourself.
Have dinner.
Yuck it up.
Don't you want
to sign him one day?
You know the corporate royalty
on those planes?
7:30 Saturday.
Grill Room at the Four Seasons.
Your wife's under the weather,
but you didn't want to miss it.
There's two guys. Hy Epstein wants
to start treatment immediately
and he's conducting a study
at New York Hospital.
The other one--
can't read my own writing.
He's a surgeon.
Very aggressive.
But he's in Bethesda.
Stop brushing your hair.
How's the rib gonna heal?
My rib's not
going to heal, Henry.
You can't waste any more
time being in shock.
- You have to do something.
- Do what?
What do you think would happen
if Nelson Rockefeller got this?
He would die!
Betty, do you want the kids
to hear you talk that way?
I don't want them to hear anything
until I've decided what to tell them.
That's what's
on my mind, Henry.
Do you want to help with that, or do
you want to keep chasing your tail?
You're being morose.
You're a very lucky woman.
You have been your whole life.
Stop yelling at me.
Thanks for the books.
It's $10.
I gave you $10.
It was hard to get.
I'm not paying $20
for a bottle of whiskey
and a couple of paperbacks
somebody left behind.
You've got the money.
I walked into town.
And it's hard for me.
I got flatfeet.
- You want one?
- No, sir.
I'm one-eighth Comanche.
Can't ever touch it.
Folks know the hustle you're
running out of their motel?
My folks are over in Woodward.
And ain't none of their
business how I get rich.
That's true.
How'd you get rich?
I was in
the advertising business.
You make commercials on TV?
Lots of them.
So many you don't
have to work no more?
Anymore.
All right.
Well, I'm around.
Don't forget to take
the pie Tammy made you.
Sorry to bother you,
but my TV just died.
Oh, well, we'll get
you a new one.
Soon as I'm done
fighting this battle.
There you go.
Then it comes loose.
You're the quick brown fox.
Did you learn to type
in the army?
No, night school.
Were you in the service?
Yes.
Well, everybody who's a vet
and likes drinking
will be at the Legion
on Saturday night.
My husband would be tickled
if you joined him.
Why didn't he ask me?
Oh, he's gonna.
Soon as he spies a chance.
He could sure use someone new
to tell his stories to.
I don't know that I'll be here,
unless you know something
about my car that I don't.
Wyatt's gonna overcharge you,
but he'll get the work done.
Let's get that TV
so you can get back
to relaxing.
Hello?
The whole pie is for you.
Eat with me.
There were two pies.
I'm not gonna tell you what
happened to the other one.
I have a favor to ask of you.
I can repay you.
I'll take her for a weekend next month.
You can go away.
What?
I have a dinner
with a potential client
and I'd love for you
to join me.
No.
Thankfully, that's no longer
one of my obligations.
You used to love it.
I daresay it got you excited
trying to close over coffee.
I never closed anything.
I was just trying
to stay awake.
Trudy, you understand
my business.
No one else ever really has.
Well, I'm not comfortable being
your date under any circumstances.
Well, then,
how about for old times' sake?
You know, I'm jealous
of your ability
to be sentimental
about the past.
I'm not able to do that.
I remember things as they were.
It's late.
I'd like to turn off
the lights.
Well, good night, then.
Good night.
Because she got kicked
out of Brearley.
Hold on. Easy.
What are you doing here?
You're not supposed
to be in here.
Could you leave us
alone, sweetheart?
Oh, of course.
Come have a seat.
I have some serious news.
It's bad news.
Your mother is sick.
She has lung cancer
and it's very advanced.
I'm very sorry.
I've got to call her.
She doesn't want
you kids to know.
Then why are you telling me?
Because there's hope
she could have more time.
People do. It's a tough
road, but it's a chance.
Well, that's good.
But she won't do it.
I don't know if she's just
being stubborn or vain,
but she won't even hear of it.
Henry, my ears
are still buzzing.
I don't understand you.
I breached her confidence
because I want you
to talk some sense into her.
She'll listen to you.
I wouldn't know what to say.
It's okay for you
to cry, honey.
Jesus, what am I going to do?
How's she running?
Good as new.
I suppose you're gonna
be on your way, then.
I should settle up.
Sure I can't talk you
into joining us tonight?
I should get going.
Mister, I know
you're not in a rush.
We got plenty of tourists
with cars in the shop.
You made two phone calls
in six days.
Wyatt thought you ran away.
I don't know.
Tell you what.
I'll throw in the room tonight
and I'll give you another night
if you fix the Coke machine.
I don't think I can
help you with that.
I know you were right
about your car.
And Sharon said she
caught you being handy.
Don't they fix it?
They want to give me a new one,
but I like this one.
I'll get my tools.
Hello?
Smells good.
I brought you a surprise.
Betty.
What are you doing here?
I got in trouble
at school again.
What'd you do?
I don't want to talk about it.
Are we supposed to eat?
Genie, come over here.
So, I'm going to tell you
in advance
that I know we seem
like fine people,
but I've been
a little dishonest.
Okay.
This is a fundraiser
for Al Bettendorf over there.
His house burned down.
Well, the kitchen.
The most expensive room.
There's a fine jar.
We're just strangers,
but it does include barbecue
and I'm getting your drinks.
$40 for Don!
What's your rank
and where did you serve?
7th Infantry.
Korea.
Rank?
Lieutenant.
Lieutenant,
7th Infantry, Korea.
Shit, we should be paying him.
That's $5 for swearing.
What are you drinking?
I'll just have
the shrimp cocktail.
Well, as Mother used to say,
"You're not that fat."
No, I have a--
well, something came up.
Since I invited you?
You're always complaining
we never see each other.
Then I ask you to dinner,
miss a very important meeting,
and you have other plans?
It was very short notice.
If you need an alibi,
you're going to have to ask.
Please.
Now, what did you want
to talk about?
Let me ask you something.
How do you know when something's
really an opportunity?
I'm wrong sometimes,
but the girls
aren't shy nowadays.
No, I meant in your career.
Oh. Well, in banking there's a
road and you just stay on it.
Still, you're required
to assess risk.
Pete, I don't buy
or sell anything.
I just distribute
and it's never up to me.
Fine, forget your business.
You're taking a risk tonight.
So now you're jealous and you're
trying to ruin my evening.
Your wife knows.
I'm not asking you
to imagine it,
I'm telling you she knows.
And how do you feel
now that you know that?
Judy's always loved that I was
attractive to other women.
It's part of what
she likes about me.
I'm just supposed
to turn that off?
You're not supposed
to act on it.
But I always have.
That's the way we are.
But why? Always looking
for something better.
Always looking
for something else.
Because Dad was like that.
He really was, wasn't he?
You know, once at
the polo grounds,
some jeweler thanked him profusely
for buying a diamond necklace.
Dad got very cross and called off
the sale right in front of me.
He kept muttering
how the man was indiscreet.
I looked it up.
I didn't need
any detective work.
I just saw the way
women looked at him.
You really think she knows?
I think it feels good
and then it doesn't.
I have to make a phone call.
Don't listen to me.
I'll be right back.
And Wayne's dad ran
the drugstore before Wayne.
He was all 10 Commandments
rolled into one.
He caught us smoking,
stealing, cussing.
My wife went to high
school with these two.
They were hooligans.
I didn't break the real
Commandments till I was in Europe.
Were you in Europe, Don?
Don was in Korea.
You don't just need new glasses,
you need a new hearing aid.
Well, he hasn't said anything.
Did you
introduce him to--
Hey, Jerry!
Jerry Fandango!
Get over here.
Jerry served in Korea.
So, you know, maybe
you've seen him before.
What the fuck
do you farts want?
- Gerald Fanning, this is--
- Don was in Korea.
You two can reminisce.
I don't want to talk about it.
Jerry Fanning.
PFC, 34th Infantry.
Come on, let me see your face.
When and where?
It was before they called it a war.
Near the Yalu River.
Oh, hell.
I wasn't there
till Christmas '53.
I was home by then.
Have a seat.
No, I got one.
Tell you one thing about Korea.
They can keep it.
Go away.
What the hell happened to you?
You stood me up.
Get in here.
I never said I would go.
You did, and Mike was waiting
with Charlene at the Grill Room
for an hour!
For heaven's sake,
you're drunk.
And you're being
very menacing right now.
I'm happy.
Listen to me.
You're on a streak.
You're on one
of those magic--
we used to call it a trend.
You know, because of the graph
where the line just goes up.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Mike called me
from his hotel room.
He was pretty sore.
So I told him that
you wanted to come,
but you were insulted
by the offer.
- You what?
- He wants to do it all.
Company car, company
plane, signing bonus.
And he's gonna get you
out of McCann.
He's gonna give me
a million dollars?
He's gonna get very close
with stock options
and McCann's gonna
cut a deal for the rest
because you're gonna help them.
Learjet's a tiny account.
It's peanuts to them.
You're not the client.
Your passengers are.
Jim Hobart's very excited about
who flies on those planes.
Every important CEO in America.
You talked to Jim Hobart?
You know what $100
buys you in Wichita?
A two-bedroom house.
You stupid wino.
You're going to
destroy everything!
Who's going to win
the World Series this year?
I don't know.
You are!
Because you are charmed,
my friend.
Good night, Duck.
I've been there.
It doesn't last long.
So the doctor says,
"Sorry, son,
but your pecker's got gangrene.
We're gonna have
to amputate."
So the GI goes
to the Jap doctor.
"Oh, good news.
No need to amputate.
In three days will
fall off by itself."
To Don!
For being generous
and not saying shit.
I don't know that many jokes.
Oh, just leave him alone.
Don, you're not allowed to say,
"I don't want to talk
about it" in this place.
That's why I never joined.
You're not listening to me.
You're among friends.
Floyd, tell him.
- Floyd!
- What?
Tell him about
the Hurtgen Forest.
Give me a drink.
Tell him the story first.
Oh, shit.
You know where it is?
It's on the border
between Belgium and Germany.
We were cut off.
Three of us.
Actually...
there were nine of us
originally.
We came on a machine gun nest.
There were four Krauts in
there looking to surrender.
They had their hands in the
air with their papers.
They were starving.
Don't skip that.
We were starving.
Scrounging for grub.
We were boiling bark.
So there's three of us,
four of them,
and more snow coming.
You did what you had to do.
What did you do?
Someone made them
start digging.
And we bounced them.
One at a time.
Took a couple of hours.
One of them was so skinny,
he tried to run away,
his pants fell down.
You know they all
got blue eyes.
You just do what you
have to do to come home.
I killed my CO.
We were under fire.
Fuel was everywhere.
And I dropped my lighter.
And I blew him apart.
And I got to go home.
That is the name of the game.
Hey, where is that kid?
We need a bottle over here!
Over here!
♪ Get that kid
with the booze over here... ♪
♪ 'Cause the Yanks are coming ♪
♪ The Yanks are coming ♪
♪ The drums rum-tumming
everywhere ♪
♪ Over there, over there ♪
♪ Send the word,
send the word over there ♪
♪ 'Cause the Yanks are coming ♪
♪ The Yanks are coming ♪
♪ The drums rum-tumming
everywhere... ♪
- Did I wake you?
- No.
Henry shouldn't
have scared you.
I wanted to tell you myself.
He doesn't know
you won't get treatment
because you love the tragedy.
Sally, I've learned
to believe people when
they tell you it's over.
They don't want to say it,
so it's usually the truth.
Henry said you could
have a year.
And what would
that year be like?
I'll be with you.
I won't let you give up.
I know that.
But I watched my mother die.
I won't do that to you.
And I don't want you
to think I'm a quitter.
I fought for plenty in my life.
That's how I know
when it's over.
It's not a weakness.
It's been a gift to me.
To know when to move on.
These are instructions.
Open it the minute
you know I'm gone.
- No.
- Listen to me.
Things happen very quickly
when people die.
Henry's not going to
be able to handle things.
You're going back
to school in the morning.
I don't want you
alarming your brothers.
Go back to sleep.
What the hell?
We want our money.
What?
We know you took the money.
Let me go!
Sharon, what's going on?
Your car was fixed. You
should have been on your way.
Now, I don't know
who the hell you are,
but you've got five Mississippi
to get our money back.
I didn't take your money.
You threw all that money around
'cause you knew
you'd get it back.
I mean business!
You really think I need
your spare change?
Give us the cash and you
can have your car back.
- Probably stolen.
- We'll find out.
My God, what's wrong?
I need to speak with you.
My goodness,
it's 4:00 in the morning.
Is everything all right?
You're scaring me.
Please, what is it?
It's good news.
Catch your breath.
What on earth is going on?
I was offered a job tonight.
Because its origins
were supernatural,
I realized that its
benefits might be as well.
I want you and Tammy
to come with me.
I want you to relocate to
Wichita, pick out a house,
and be my wife
and family again.
Peter, I'm not
dismissing you...
I'm saying with
respect to whatever
is happening in
your eyes right now,
we both know things
can't be undone.
Says who?
We're not even through
half our lives.
And even if we are,
we're entitled to more.
Of what?
Then we're entitled
to something new.
I want to start over.
And I know I can.
I'm not so dumb anymore.
I'm not ignoring the fact that I
could actually lose your love.
You never lost it.
But I will never allow you
to hurt me again.
I love you, too.
I always have.
I've never loved anyone else.
Never.
You think you can come in here
when I'm all disoriented
and say the things I wanted you
to say to me two years ago
and make me run away with you?
I said it to you 10 years
ago and I'll say it again.
I do.
Wichita is beautiful.
And wholesome.
And not the city
and not Cos Cob.
And you'll have a plane
to use at your disposal.
We will.
To pick up and go anywhere
anytime we want.
Like driving to Montauk.
I want to go
everywhere with you.
Say yes with your voice,
not just your eyes.
Oh!
How will I explain
this to Tammy?
Tell her her birthday
wish came true.
I'm gonna go.
And we're gonna have
dinner on Saturday night.
The three of us.
Like it was the first time.
Good morning.
This one's on the house.
What do you want to know?
You want to know what I told them?
I'm just being
a good citizen, man.
You don't know anything about me.
I could kill you right now.
You took that money
and you set me up.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You have shitty instincts
for a con man.
You're lucky you feel guilty.
That's the one difference between
you and those animals right now.
I don't feel guilty
taking that drunk's money.
He burned his own house down.
He doesn't deserve a pot to
piss in, let alone 500 bucks.
You're gonna get me that money,
pack your bag,
and get out of town.
I can't leave
without that money.
I know you think
you know how to hustle,
but this is a big crime,
stealing these people's money.
If you keep it, you'll have
to become somebody else.
And it's not
what you think it is.
You cannot get off
on that foot in this life.
What do you care?
You got money.
I know you got money.
I cleaned your room
and didn't take nothing.
Anything.
You think this town is bad now?
Wait until you can
never come back.
Can I go?
Go get the money.
I'm not paying for the room.
Could you drop me off
at the bus stop?
Get in.
I'm off.
- Where are you going?
- I have class.
Why are you doing that?
Why was I ever doing it?
"Dear Sally,
I know that you're frightened
and there are many decisions
I can't prepare you for,
but you must immediately
tell the hospital
and the funeral director
that I'm to be interred intact
in the family plot
in West Laurel.
Uncle William has the details
from Grandpa Gene's burial.
I've also enclosed a portrait
from the 1968 Republican
Winter Gala.
The blue chiffon I wore
is my very favorite.
I hung it in a gold garment bag in
the hall closet beside the mink.
Please bring them the lipstick
from my handbag
and remind them
how I like to wear my hair.
Will you show them the picture?
Sally, I always
worried about you
because you march
to the beat of your own drum.
But now I know that's good.
I know your life
will be an adventure."
"I love you. Mom."
Pink slip's in the glove box.
What?
Don't waste this.
♪ every day
it's a-getting closer ♪
♪ going faster
than a rollercoaster ♪
♪ love like yours
will surely come my way ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ every day
it's a-getting faster ♪
♪ everyone said
go ahead and ask her ♪
♪ love like yours
will surely come my way ♪
♪ a-hey, a-hey, hey ♪
♪ every day seems
a little longer ♪
♪ every way
love's a little stronger... ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net