Our elections are
the envy of the world.
It's critically important that we
not make any mistakes tonight.
We made a small mistake.
We called Michigan
when we meant Mississippi.
You have to retract it.
I wonder if maybe
it's not necessary to retract it.
I didn't realize that you were
president of the Oxford Union.
Cambridge. I was president
of the Cambridge Union.
I need you to change
my Wikipedia page.
It's funny the things people try to control
when they feel like they're not in control.
You're going to be a named
defendant by Jerry Dantana.
- He's suing me for giving him a bad job recommendation?
- It's just strategy.
- Say what you want to say to me.
- What?
Fire me.
You're the only one who can do it.
I think your resignations
should be accepted immediately.
- Then why don't you?
- My mom says I can't.
You have to keep trying.
Tomorrow's too late.
You think I'm not firing you because
it would make me look bad?
Give me a break, Billy.
It's not like you're indifferent.
You're fired,
end of the broadcast.
Please don't tell anyone.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
We're just past 9:00 P.M. in the East
and we have another round
of projections.
ACN is able to project
Mitt Romney will win
the great state of Kansas
and its six electoral votes.
Moving south to Louisiana,
we project...
I'm here.
I want to make sure
there's absolutely no confusion.
You would go on the record.
We would use your name.
I want more.
I want a quote.
I'm gonna handcuff you
to this thing.
Did he just say,
"A big prize but no surprise"?
Yeah.
He'll be kicking
himself for that.
All right, well,
we've got a decision to make here
and I'll give you
a heads up either way.
Thank you
and good luck tonight.
It's as confirmed
as anything has ever been.
Two GOP congressmen
we can quote and identify,
two senior DOJ sources we can identify
as two senior DOJ sources.
- You wanted me?
- Yeah.
- All right, I can explain.
- Nope.
- Oh.
- Explain what?
Doesn't matter.
Here's what's happening.
Brody in California
made a statement this morning
when the polls opened condemning Todd Akin.
It's a tight race.
We figure he saw
internal numbers suggesting
he needed a bigger cushion
with women 18-55.
So he went on a local morning show
and slid in a condemnation of Akin,
but two hours ago,
Maggie found a Brody quote
in a Students for America
publication from 1990.
"It's a sad fact,
but women cry rape
to avoid embarrassment, to exact revenge,
or just to draw attention.
If we have rape exceptions
to abortion laws,
women could now cry rape
to terminate an innocent life.
We should be able to look
past the mendacity.
Children are conceived by love,
not by rape."
- How did you find that?
- Prayer and clean living.
- Seriously, how did you find that?
- It's my job.
It's my job, too,
but I didn't find that.
- No, you didn't.
- Knock it off.
So, Don calls Brody's chief of staff
to get a comment.
- John Webb.
- And Webb says...
Given a little time,
he might be able to feed us a better story
in exchange for holding the SFA quote
till after the election.
What's the better story?
David Petraeus is going
to resign on Thursday.
He's been having an affair
with a lieutenant colonel in the Reserves.
So the question is
which story do we run?
- 'Cause it's one or the other.
- It's not even a contest.
- Brody.
- Petraeus. Wait.
It's 6:00 in the West.
The polls are still open.
People are coming home
from work.
Almost 40% of the votes
in Brody's district
are cast between
5:00 and 8:00.
I know,
and I fully appreciate that.
- But this is a special circumstance.
- No, it's not.
Let me make my case.
We're under siege.
If we break this Petraeus story
two days before everyone else, we'll one:
Distract from our own problems,
and two: Earn us back some
credibility and goodwill.
Does the Petraeus story
provide any information
the voters should have
before they punch a ballot?
It does not.
Does it do anyone any good
if we report the Brody quote
tomorrow instead of tonight?
It would help Brody out.
Call your guy back and tell him thanks,
but no, thanks.
We'll report that Petraeus is resigning
when Petraeus resigns, right?
- Yeah.
- Don?
I'm agreeing.
Do I have to be happy about it?
Put the Brody package
together for me to approve.
I want to get it
on the air in 15 minutes.
- Everything all right?
- Hmm? Yeah.
Here's how things
are looking right now
just after
the 9:00 P.M. closings.
Governor Romney is ahead
with 152 electoral votes
to the president's 123.
No projections right now in Arizona,
New Mexico...
They've run out of ballots
in Racine, Wisconsin.
Elliot's got it
and then throw to DC.
Elliot, right now President Obama
has a lead in Wisconsin,
but we're hearing
there are voting problems.
Yeah, they've run out of ballots
in Racine, Wisconsin.
They've got to get some sort
of last-minute ballot supply.
Taylor Warren, is that a good sign
for the president in Wisconsin?
It's a very good sign. Racine,
the whole Rust Belt area of the state
is a very big sweet spot
for the president.
Coming to you, Jane.
Start us off with Colorado.
We're gonna start with Florida.
Take Jane to Florida.
Let's bring in Jane Barrow
and our panel in DC.
Jane, what are you guys
seeing in Florida?
There's an interesting dynamic
in that battleground state right now
and I'd like to go
to our panel.
All right, New York's
on an eight-minute break.
- Don't anyone go too far.
- And clear.
Okay, whew.
All right, turn out, turn out.
- The ground game.
- You talking to me?
I wasn't really
talking to anyone.
I think you just described
the rest of my life.
How are you doing?
A group called Stand By Our Troops
submitted a petition
to AWM demanding
Charlie and I be fired.
They got 20,000 signatures.
- Six and a half times the size of my hometown.
- I saw.
Another group
called Concerned Citizens for Truth
got 50,000 signatures.
We hired a polling firm
to gauge trust.
- And?
- Nobody trusts us.
Men, women, over 49, under 49,
Republicans, Democrats--
our lack of credibility
is immune to demographics.
The op-eds won't stop.
They're getting worse.
And I'm concerned this is finally
what's going to kill Charlie Skinner.
Schadenfreude's been made
very convenient.
Hmm. Yeah.
You know,
I hate to seem like I'm circling,
but I'm setting up
a media consulting firm
and I wanted to get your blessing
to approach Jim Harper.
- About what?
- About joining the firm.
He hates me, but if I only worked
with people who liked me,
I'd have to make
my dog Howard a partner.
I'm lost.
There's gonna be a land rush
as soon as you guys announce.
There's a lot of talent here.
Jim just renewed his contract
a few months ago.
It's in the air supply
around here
that senior staff
is resigning over Genoa.
Charlie is resigning
and I'm resigning.
But as of 1:35
this morning,
Leona Lansing won't even
accept our resignations.
Where did you hear
senior staff was resigning?
- Maybe I shouldn't say.
- Where did you hear that?
From the senior staff.
I make friends everywhere I go.
I want the senior staff
in the studio right now.
- We have seven minutes back.
- Right now.
The mood here is still upbeat.
They like the internal exits they're seeing.
They're not troubled that Obama isn't losing
in a single state he needs to win?
- They like what they're seeing in Ohio and Florida.
- What are they seeing?
Honey, I'm starting to get
funny looks from people here.
- They know I'm Skyping with ACN.
- You're Skyping with me.
No one can see or hear us.
- Hey, Hallie!
- Hey, Maggie.
Will wants senior staff
in the studio.
I'll be right there.
It's mostly the bloggers who
don't want me helping out old media.
You know, why don't you tell
new media that old media
has got a combined audience
of about 80 million tonight?
I will, but new media will
probably respond by saying
that the report you just gave
about Racine, Wisconsin,
running out of ballots
came off Twitter.
Then you should reply
by telling new media to bite me
and my accountability
and professionalism.
Can you get someone
else to do this?
By the way, a little while ago
we called the Michigan first for Dan Benishek.
If you were thinking of
posting something about it, I'd hold off.
- Why?
- I accidentally called the wrong race.
- I meant Mississippi.
- You didn't retract it?
Our decision desk
is 100% confident he's going to win.
- Then why can't you call it?
- They're not confident enough.
You should really retract it.
If you were us tonight,
would you retract something
you didn't absolutely have to?
- No.
- I'm going all in on Benishek.
- Hang on.
- They're waiting for me in the studio.
I think she cut her own hair.
Tonight's really
not the night--
Cutting off your own hair--
That's alarming.
Any chance this can wait?
- No.
- Jim's on his way.
I'd like to announce
something in the meantime.
I was supposed to donate a signed copy
of my book for the Sandy auction
and I went to see my parents last weekend
and forgot to leave the book.
Gary, meaning well,
signed a copy of the book
forging my signature
and writing the inscription.
- In German.
- Almost.
In German the words for enjoy
and shred are a lot alike.
They're nothing alike,
but that's not the point.
Take your time getting to the point,
because as you can see,
- nothing else is happening right now.
- We've got five minutes.
We do not have five minutes.
The producers don't have five minutes.
My point is that someone
bought the book for a lot of money
and Neal's dropping everything
to help me find out who it was
so that I can give him or her
a real signed copy of the book.
So if there's anyone
who was at the fund-raiser
- or maybe knows the person who--
- Excuse me.
You're dropping everything?
No, I'm still very much doing my job.
Except for right now.
And when I'm trying to fix
your Wikipedia page.
Oh, forget that.
Drop it, it's stupid.
- Everybody's here?
- Yes.
Let's go around the room and everybody
tell something about themselves.
- Do you need to go back to the control room?
- Yes.
Go.
- Fix the page. Get it fixed.
- Copy.
I don't know what the hell you guys
are thinking about doing,
but you're not doing it.
Last night, Charlie, Mac, and I
offered our resignations
to Mrs. Lansing.
She refused to accept them,
believing that the right thing to do was to stand by us.
Charlie is working hard on Reese
to get him to change his mother's mind.
The reason, whole reason,
we're trying to resign
is to allow the rest of you
to continue
to do what we started
without the burden of Genoa.
Elliot would take my job.
Don would take Mac's.
Sloan would anchor 10:00
and Jim would be her EP.
So I don't want to hear
any more rumors
about the rest
of you resigning.
- Is that clear?
- No.
- It's not clear?
- No, it's clear.
- We're saying no.
- No to what?
If Leona accepts your resignations,
we're resigning, too.
Everyone who was
involved with Genoa.
I'm not going accept
your resignations.
Due respect, but if Leona accepts yours,
you're not going to be in a position--
We gave you a bad story.
It's our responsibility.
There are principles of...
principle here
and character
and responsibility.
Who put all this in your head?
- You did.
- Now can we go back to work?
You expect me to get choked up?
Meeting's over.
Two minutes back.
I think you insulted them a little
by not assuming
they'd stand behind you
and Charlie and Mac.
Why do you think that?
Because you
insulted me a little.
- Charlie. Hi.
- Oh, hi.
- Excuse me.
- Oh, Charlie.
Charlie,
a woman in Mesa, Arizona,
ran over her husband with their car
because he didn't vote for Romney.
- Can I have a moment?
- Did you hear what I just said?
- No.
- He's in the hospital.
They were in a parking lot.
She was chasing him around a light pole.
He tried to make a run for it
and she pinned him at the curb.
Here's what I find
strange about this.
First of all,
it's not like the husband voted for Obama.
He just didn't vote for Romney.
He didn't vote.
And second,
isn't Romney gonna win the vote
in Arizona by like 200% anyway?
Yeah, but you don't think
the strange part
is the wife driving over
her husband with a car?
Well, she's pregnant.
- Where are you getting this from?
- Twitter.
All right,
can I have just a second?
Sure.
A decision has to be made
before the court clerk's office
opens at 9:00 tomorrow.
I appreciate everything
you said last night.
- I was high last night.
- I know. You told us.
But then I got
a good night's sleep
and an early morning swim
and a full day's work.
And then I changed and came here
and got high again.
- God damn it.
- It's marketing.
They got a stash.
I mean, I don't know
how they do it.
I think they grow their own
in, like, the Galapagos
Islands or something.
And I want to get
the Allman Brothers back together.
Rebecca says that it's your intention
to sue us if we resign.
For breach of contract, yes.
Hey, you want some champagne?
No. For two months, there's been a mob
shouting for our resignations.
- And the mob is right.
- Are you sure they're not just loud?
What does it matter? They'll keep shouting
until Will and I leave the building.
And if we don't leave the building,
what will that do to everyone else?
From what I understand,
if I accept your resignations,
there won't be anyone left
except the DC bureau
because those guys
want your jobs.
Will and I will convince
senior staff to stay.
I'm not worried about that.
Here's why you have
to let Dantana's lawyers
know you're gonna settle
before papers are filed in the morning.
A diary will be made available
to any reporter who wants to read it...
- Which will be every reporter.
- ...of the internal operations of ACN.
And AWM and that diary
will be written by lawyers
whose only objective
is to make us look silly.
I don't feel silly.
You want to split a pizza?
Can you understand me
right now?!
Well, when you speak at that volume,
I think everyone can.
I drove them into
this fucking nightmare.
I led, they followed.
And it's like I led
them to Cape Fear
'cause everyone
we've pissed off--
every congressman,
every reporter,
- every citizen journalist--
- I understand the reality.
You know who I am.
Reese agrees with us.
Oh, the irony that it's come down to
you and Reese agreeing.
- Your son and I seldom agree.
- You disrespect him, Charlie.
- He's given me reasons to.
- No, no, he hasn't.
He's given you reasons
to disagree with him,
but not to disrespect him.
Well, we're not
disagreeing now.
He's thinking
very clearly about this.
He's being a smart executive.
And now is exactly
the right time to listen to him.
Well, I'm doing a lot more
than listening to him.
I'm letting him
make the decision.
- You are?
- Yeah.
- Leona, come on.
- Reese is making the decision.
He went out to take a walk.
- Why?
- Clear his head.
- I meant--
- Maybe get a panini.
I meant why are you letting
Reese make the decision?
'Cause I'm not really sure
Elizabeth Windsor
is the world's greatest mom.
I mean, why doesn't she just
give her son the throne?
On the other hand,
I think being queen is what keeps her alive.
But doesn't she want to be alive
to see her son be king?
Except that
that's not how it works.
It's prince by birth,
king by death. Yet--
Do you have any idea
what you're talking about right now?
Don't think I do, no.
But I want to see
how Reese handles this.
He's already told us
how he's gonna--
Okay.
I'm relieved.
I can tell.
Enjoy the party.
- Oh!
- Oh, my God!
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
- I'm sorry.
- It was my fault.
I wasn't looking.
Did I hurt you?
No, no, I'm fine.
Have we met?
You look familiar.
I'm Maggie Jordan's roommate.
- Sure.
- I'm Lisa.
Lisa.
I'm sorry, Lisa.
Are you all okay?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Oh, Mr. Skinner,
could I ask you a favor?
Would you mind not mentioning to Jim Harper
that I'm working up here tonight?
Yeah, sure.
Why would I mention it to Jim?
Oh, 'cause you guys were--
Got it.
Thank you.
We're ready to make
an important projection
at 9:25 with 27%
of the vote counted.
ACN is projecting
that Pennsylvania
will be won by the president.
Pennsylvania,
a crucial battleground state
which was won by the president
four years ago, will stay in his column.
Suzannah Marquez
is on the scene for us
at Obama headquarters
in Chicago.
Suzannah, was this much
of a surprise where you are?
Will, they're not surprised,
but they're certainly relieved.
This was a state President Obama
was determined to hold
against a late push
from Governor Romney to take it.
There's also something
instructive in these numbers.
According to senior campaign officials
I've been speaking to all day...
- It's not from you?
- Mm-mm.
...was the high
African-American turnout.
And that's a pattern they said
they've been seeing in a number of states today.
But, of course, the night is early
and we'll have much more later.
- Will?
- Thank you, Suzannah Marquez.
- We'll be hearing more from you as the night moves on.
- Battleground update.
Checking in with our
other battleground states--
in Florida with 84%
of the vote in,
the race is as close as it gets
with the president
holding a 50-49 lead.
- It looks like...
- It's close.
Hit refresh.
It just got closer.
657 votes.
- Kathy?
- Very busy now, Jim.
Can I see you one second?
- I'll have to shield my eyes.
- Go ahead.
I'm not allowed
to see other networks.
Just look down.
Aim your gaze at the floor.
The Michigan first
is getting tighter.
Benishek is only up
by 600 votes.
657.
There was a moment in the race
when it was 1-0, right?
- That's not-- Yes, but--
- And then the second vote got counted.
- You're still confident he's going to win?
- Yes.
- And you're just as confident he's going to win.
- 51-49 red.
- Or, if you want to be more exact...
- I do.
- 50.6 to 49.4.
- That's literally as close as a race can be.
- That's why we haven't called it.
- We did call it.
- You called it.
- What's the abbreviation for Michigan?
- MI.
- What's the abbreviation for Mississippi?
- MISS.
- Okay, you're not here as an abbreviation expert.
I'm 100% confident
in those abbreviations.
Go back in your lair.
- Jim.
- Yeah?
Rachel Corey is on the phone
and wants to talk to you.
She's a pollster with the Benishek campaign
in the Michigan first.
Here it comes.
Tam, will you transfer
that call to Maggie's line?
Yeah.
This is Jim Harper.
Jim, this is Rachel Corey
with Dan Benishek's campaign in Michigan.
- Congratulations!
- That's why I'm on the phone.
ACN called the race a while ago,
but no one else has.
Well, I can't speak
for the other networks,
but ACN has the congressman
holding his seat.
Our numbers show
he's only up by 600 votes.
- 657.
- 632.
What the hell is going on, Jim?
Do I send my guy out
to make a victory speech?
I would.
Look, I don't want to kick you guys
when you're down,
but you haven't had the most awesome
history of being right lately.
Well, first, you can't bounce
the words history and lately
off each other
in the same sentence.
Also, in my entire time here
covering national elections,
ACN hasn't missed
a single call.
How many elections
have you been there for?
This is my second.
- Did we win the election or not?
- You did.
Then why has no one else
called it?
You're forcing me to brag,
but it may just be
that we have better people
working the numbers.
You won't be offended if we wait
until someone else has called it, will you?
No, ma'am.
I am a little offended.
- Even though you're lying?
- She doesn't know that.
- We've got a problem upstairs.
- At the party?
The guests were supposed
to hand over their phones and someone didn't,
because they tweeted a picture.
There are people up there who are hearing
information we don't want leaked.
And also this is
a shot of Charlie
on the floor with
broken champagne glasses,
which isn't the best optic
for us right now.
- I don't have the muscle to get security to--
- That's Lisa.
- Kneeling on the floor, that's Lisa.
- That is Lisa.
She didn't want you to know
she was here tonight.
She's been working for a caterer
to earn extra money.
Why didn't she want me
to know she was here?
This is where
I'm gonna check out.
But someone upstairs has a phone
and they're using it.
You know, it might be a good time
for you guys to patch things up.
You really think
this is a good time?
What if none of us
are here tomorrow?
599.
Checking back in
with our analysts.
Taylor, you've been looking over the exits
and working your phone.
Tell us what you're
seeing and hearing.
We're seeing movement
in Florida.
The last exit polls showed
Mitt Romney up by three.
The latest show the president up by one.
So that's a fluid race.
But senior campaign
sources in Boston
are telling me they like
the precinct breakdown.
The Romney people still
feeling good about Florida?
- Take us to break.
- Florida and Ohio.
And hopefully we'll be able
to bring those calls
to you soon.
But right now, what we know
is that Pennsylvania,
the first of
the big contested states...
- Play in and stand by animation.
- Standing.
Stay tuned for more
of ACN's continuing coverage
of Election Night 2012.
We're out.
- Two minutes back.
- That's two and no change.
Will, we're ready to call
the House for the Republicans.
All right, I'll take care
of things out here.
- You do it in there.
- Take care of what things?
Come sit in this chair.
Why?
When we come back from commercial,
you're gonna call the House
for the Republicans and go
to Sloan for the breakdown.
- Where are you going?
- I'm taking a break.
What do you mean,
you're taking--
I want our audience to get used to
seeing you break big news.
That's not gonna be necessary.
- Take the chair.
- No.
Then there's gonna be a camera
pointed at an empty chair.
Oh, fuck. Will!
- Don.
- Yeah?
We're gonna call the House
after the break.
Yeah, we've got Boehner,
Cantor, and Pelosi,
but we have to wait in line for a while,
so you'll need to vamp.
You'll need to vamp.
I'm gonna step out of the room.
- 60 seconds back.
- What?
You've got your cards,
you've got your producers,
you've got Elliot at the desk.
What's happening right now?
We just want to show Reese and Leona
you guys are good at this.
- You guys are good at this.
- See you in eight minutes.
The Republicans are keeping the House.
Let's get that graphic up.
- G-0445 standing.
- Elliot.
I'm here.
You're gonna ask Sloan
how we're able to make that call.
- Copy.
- Sloan, most of the competitive House races
were in states where
polls closed at 8:00.
Republicans were ahead in 12,
Democrats in three,
and that's how
we're able to call it.
- You copy?
- This is getting out of hand.
Ah, don't worry about that
right now, okay?
Copy.
Welcome back.
We are ready to make
a big call.
ACN's ready to project
that the Republican Party
will be the majority party
in the House of Representatives
for at least two more years.
So far, so good.
ACN is projecting at this time
that the Republicans
will hold on to
the majority of the House.
We'll be speaking with
Majority Leader Eric Cantor in just a moment.
But before we do,
Sloan Sabbith,
you've been reviewing
all the information
as far as the House
is concerned.
You've been speaking
with our decision desk.
How are we able to call this?
Well, Elliot,
the Democrats
needed a net gain of 25 seats
to take the House
and 20 of the most competitive
races closed at 8:00.
I was wrong to think the reason
you weren't firing me was vanity.
you weren't firing me
was that it would look bad.
I'm sorry for that.
You want your job back?
I don't think it'll make
that much difference now.
Charlie told me Leona
is letting Reese make the decision.
Yeah.
I tried to explain it
my first day here
the second I saw you.
Do you remember?
I was hung up on him
because he had rejected me.
That's normal.
I liked that he hated
I was dating you.
We weren't just dating.
Later. We weren't
just dating later.
At the beginning we were,
though.
And I was using you to get,
you know.
And then I fell
in love with you
and I never saw him again.
And if I hadn't told you,
you'd never have known.
So why did you tell me?
If I had to do it over again,
I wouldn't,
but I had never been in a relationship
as serious as ours
and I thought it was
what I was supposed to do.
You sure you didn't tell me
'cause you wanted to break up?
Oh, fuck you.
- It's a reasonable--
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Are you sure you're not
just a massive bag of douche?
'Cause let me tell you something,
it's just plain weird
that you were prepared
to marry me,
that you'd bought a ring,
but were unwilling
to read any of my e-mails
or answer any of my calls.
Yeah, I'm sorry for this,
but the ring was a practical joke.
You were having the staff vet me,
remember?
I knew you were gonna find the offer
from when we were together
for me to do something
on the West Coast.
I knew you were gonna come into the office
waving it and saying,
"Aha, you were never
as serious as you said,
'cause if you were,
you'd have told me about a job
you were considering
on the other side of the country."
And that's what happened.
You know, I heard,
"The ring was a practical joke..."
and then I didn't hear
anything after that.
It wasn't a joke.
It was a rejoinder. It wasn't a joke.
You took out a ring
and showed it to me
as proof that your intention
had been to marry me.
I bought the ring that morning.
Scott's assistant did.
Your agent's assistant
went to Tiffany's
and bought the ring
that morning?
Yes. I'm sorry.
And you were never supposed to know.
So I get the irony
and I am really sorry.
That ring had to have cost
a quarter of a million dollars.
I'm not really sure.
We returned it that afternoon.
I asked them to get a nice one.
You once described a ring
you saw in a movie.
- Okay.
- Mac.
You know, no kidding.
I'm gonna step away.
- Hang on.
- Because the thing is I'm serious.
I feel like I'm gonna hit you
and you have to be back on the air.
- You're not going to hit me.
- I'm worried that I am.
And I'm the executive
producer of the show.
I can defend my--
Stand on the other side
of the room.
- This is stupid.
- There is a reasonable chance,
a credible threat
that I'm gonna hit you
and I don't want you
to have a bloody lip
when we come back
from commercial.
That should make sense to you.
Like I said, if I ever thought
there was a chance
you'd find out...
You just told me!
I brutally hurt you
and that's a fact.
And facts don't change.
But in my lifetime...
I've never done it
intentionally.
I'm sorry.
Recap the House and then
look at Colorado when we come back.
Yeah.
- Did you find out anything?
- Yes.
A woman at the auction
management company
was moved by your story
and a little concerned about going to jail
for fraud, so she was happy to fax over
the name and contact information
of the person who bought the forged book,
but you're not gonna be happy.
Was it bought by an inmate?
I have a small, slightly disturbed following
among white-collar criminals.
The book was bought
by Sidney Falco.
- I don't know who that is.
- It's Tony Curtis.
Sidney Falco is a character
from Sweet Smell of Success.
The highest bid was anonymous?
All the bids are anonymous.
Joe Gillis is Sunset Boulevard.
Walter Neff from Double Indemnity.
Archibald Craven
from The Secret Garden.
I don't understand this at all.
Someone wanted to create
the impression
of a bidding war.
So a total of nobody
bid on the book?
Except Sidney Falco from
Sweet Smell of Success
who, for some reason,
bid himself up with other fictional characters.
Who cares?
Someone gave $1,000 to Sandy relief
and they think they have
your signature.
- I'm gonna get to the bottom of this.
- You're at the bottom.
- There are clues here.
- I don't think so.
- There could be clues.
- There aren't.
And you don't want to start
looking for anagrams--
Let's start looking for
anagrams of Sidney Falco
and Sweet Smell of Success.
Okay.
I got your text.
- I've decided to counter-sue Jerry.
- Of course.
- I'm fighting back.
- What are you suing him for?
- To fight back.
- I meant exactly what are you--
- You ready?
- I'm sorry?
- I said you ready?
- Give it to me.
Intentional affliction
of emotional distress.
- How do you even know?
- I Googled it.
- There are four elements.
- One: He acted intentionally.
- By doctoring the tape.
- Two: His conduct was extreme and outrageous.
- He doctored the tape.
- Three: You suffered distress.
I am in extreme distress.
And four: His act
caused your distress.
He doctored
the motherfucking tape, Rebecca.
- You sound upset.
- Do I?
He doctored the tape
and he gets to sue us?
I gave him a bad job recommendation
'cause he doctored the tape
and he gets to sue me?
- The people who want tort reform, they got a point.
- Yes.
The things you're allowed to sue for
and be taken seriously.
And so we come
face-to-face
with just how stupid
lawyers worry we are.
I lost you
in the middle of that.
You know what it says
on a box of chocolate pudding mix?
"Caution, pudding
will get hot when heated."
Go to a hotel, you know what it says
on the shower cap in the bathroom?
"Fits one head."
- You wear a shower cap?
- I read.
And I'm dying to know the suit
that prompted lawyers
to insist on the shower cap directions.
Look at the box
your iron came in.
It says, "Warning,
do not iron clothes while wearing them."
Do we really have to slow down
for these people?
Leona's leaving
the decision to Reese.
I know.
That's not what you wanted.
I don't know what I want.
I want to keep doing the news.
Here.
With Elliot for Charlie.
I want to keep arguing
with Mac and Will.
I want Dantana to iron his clothes
while wearing them.
Could I get another Grey Goose on the rocks
with three olives?
- Sure.
- And you can just bring me some more champagne
if it hasn't all been
soaked up by your clothes.
- No, there's plenty more.
- Just joking with you.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Don't shoot.
Charlie Skinner
wasn't supposed to tell you I was here.
He didn't. Someone tweeted
a picture of you on the floor.
The center of gravity
on champagne glasses is too high.
That's what I've always said.
And what happened
to the old-fashioned ones from the movies?
They're too wide. They let the bubbles out.
I'm working right now.
Yeah, Maggie said you were
working for a caterer.
On the side.
I still work at the store.
It was good seeing you.
I just have a minute.
We're waiting for some Senate information.
I think Sherrod Brown
is gonna keep his seat
and it's looking like
McCaskill's gonna beat Todd Akin.
- Do you know how frustrating this is?
- Careful.
I want to kick
your ass right now,
but I can't 'cause everyone else is.
There's no room.
So I have to feel bad
for you instead.
If those are the only choices,
I'd rather you kick my ass.
- You don't get to decide. You know why?
- I do.
- Do you remember standing in front of me and swearing...
- Yes.
- ...swearing that you didn't have feelings--
- I meant it.
You know that I found out from
that fucking YouTube video, you asshole?
I don't think there's a way
it could have been worse.
- Excuse me, Lisa. Is there a problem?
- No.
It seems like there is because
you're speaking rudely to a guest.
- And the incident earlier, that man was the president--
- There's no problem.
And considering the circumstances,
she's being remarkably polite.
On the other hand,
one of your servers is tweeting pictures
from the party and you signed
a confidentiality agreement.
Well, if that's true,
it's serious.
- It is.
- I'll take care of it.
- Lisa, please be working.
- I'm coming now.
How do you know
it was one of the servers?
- It probably wasn't.
- I have to go.
I meant it.
When I stood in front of you
and when I swore, I meant it.
- I believe you.
- Do you?
Yes, it wasn't till after you got to know me
that you rejected me.
- Champagne?
- No, thank you, I'm good.
I didn't reject you.
And there isn't a way
it could have been worse.
Grey Goose up, three olives.
Because at that point,
my worst fear was realized.
- Spiders?
- You get a kick out of yourself, don't you?
I actually ordered this
on the rocks.
My fault.
I'll fix that.
She got the number of olives right.
She's making progress.
- What was that?
- I beg your pardon?
Jim.
- I don't know what your worst fear is.
- That you think I'm stupid.
And stop trying to make up
for it by defending my honor
to a guy you can obviously
beat the shit out of.
- Stop.
- I can't.
Do you think I think
you're stupid?
- I have to circulate.
- The whole time you thought--
I'm smart enough to know
that I'm not smart enough.
- For what?
- You.
- Stop walking.
- Can we drop it?
Lisa.
- I don't get you.
- Maggie is downstairs being a news producer.
Your new girlfriend's
in Boston covering
a presidential candidate
for her own website.
And I'm up here passing out drinks.
What evidence--
You're working two jobs.
You're thoughtful
and you're authentic.
And I have never seen you
sneer at anyone or anything.
There is, believe me,
no one that you're not good enough for
and there is hardly anyone
who's good enough for you,
including, it turned out, me.
I'm about to turn 30.
And you could just as easily
be someone's date here tonight
or married
to their black Am Ex.
If they can make me laugh,
I'd take a green one.
Did Maggie cut her own hair?
- I don't speak to Maggie.
- You live in the same apartment.
We have our own lives.
Champagne?
Strictly speaking,
champagne should be poured
immediately after
the bottle's been uncorked,
but because you're very beautiful,
I'll make an exception.
Yeah, yeah.
Take the glass.
- Maggie's in bad shape.
- I don't care.
- I don't speak to Maggie.
- Please change that policy.
- No.
- She's in bad shape.
Because you're dating
that reporter from the bus?
- It's hard for me to sympathize.
- Not because of me.
- Because of Africa.
- What do you mean?
I don't care.
Champagne?
They don't want champagne.
Are you saying Maggie didn't tell you
what happened in Uganda?
No. And again,
I don't care.
Did she get hurt?
Did somebody--
What are you saying?
You have to ask her.
I can't tell you
if she doesn't want you to know.
But she wants you to know,
so you have to ask her.
No.
Did she cut her own hair off?
There was hair
on the bathroom floor.
We're gonna make the Senate call
in Missouri and Ohio
and we'll be throwing it to DC
in 10 or 11 minutes.
- Copy.
- But if we're able to call Florida,
or for that matter, the race,
just send it back.
You're not gonna let
DC call the race?
Just send it back.
We'll try not to drop
sarin gas on anyone while we do.
If you've got something to say, Jane,
you should say it to me
and not to the people
in this control room
who simply did what
I told them to do and did it well.
And I have people here who could live
without Genoa on their resumes,
so I'm not sure from where you get
the nerve to insist that Will call the race.
I get the nerve from my mother.
But for the record,
it was a DC producer
who committed
journalistic malpractice.
And if I were you,
I'd be going through every story
he ever produced for you
frame by frame
to find out what else
he's cooked along the way.
Good advice. Let me know
if you have any recommendations
for your job
when I take Will's chair in New York.
It's Charlie Skinner, Jane.
Send it back to New York
when Mac tells you to.
- Copy that.
- The desk says go on Senate.
We're ready to go on the Senate.
McCaskill and Brown.
Because this is something
that needs to be kept in mind.
- The entire world--
- Sorry, we're gonna make an important call.
Two big races in the US Senate.
ACN is projecting that in Ohio,
Sherrod Brown,
the Democratic incumbent,
will be reelected
and Claire McCaskill,
the Democrat from Missouri,
will keep her seat as well.
Elliot, what does that mean
for the Senate?
It's now
mathematically impossible
for the Republicans
to take control of the Senate,
even if Romney wins tonight
and Paul Ryan becomes the tiebreaker.
So we're projecting now
that Harry Reid
will stay in the majority
leader's office.
Taylor, should the Democrats
be sending the Tea Party
a basket of mini muffins
and a thank-you card for that?
I think the Democrats
have a lot of gift baskets to hand out.
Chris Christie,
the media--
- Whoa.
- Okay. Hold the phone.
I can feel warmth
about to happen.
What media are you talking about
when you say media?
- 'Cause there are a lot of us. ACN?
- Yes.
Ah, well.
Please continue.
I worked in
the Romney press shop
and I can tell you that on average
over the last six months,
News Night did
14 negative stories
about Republicans
to every one...
Hey, Molly.
It's New York.
- Copy.
- Coming to you shortly. Stand by.
If Republicans do
14 crazy things in a month,
does that mean
the unbiased thing to do
would be for us to concoct
13 additional crazy Democrat stories?
- Are we doing this now?
- We're doing this.
- Go to Molly in St. Louis.
- Then let me give you another statistic.
- Almost nobody--
- No, we're going to St. Louis first.
- Okay.
- Molly Sadler is with the McCaskill campaign
at the Omni Convention Center.
Molly, do I have to ask
what the mood is there?
I would say the mood
is jubilation, Will.
Is there a chance I can get you
to ask Hallie a favor for me?
- What's the favor?
- I need her to post a story tonight.
Which I've already written--
About the effect the debates had on the outcome.
In this story she quotes Mac,
who's identified
both as the EP of News Night
and a former president
of the Cambridge Union.
That's the only way
to get Wikipedia to change the entry?
- Yeah.
- Are you proud of your army of citizen journalists?
Have you called any more
elections on your own?
- No.
- Just the one?
I'll ask her.
But, you know, she's a little busy.
And ethical.
I'd like to do this
for Mac tonight as a gift.
I'll do it
when I have a minute.
The left doesn't have
a version of the Tea Party.
What's OWS?
There wasn't an OWS candidate
on the ballot tonight.
The left's crazy people
hardly ever run for office.
And when they do,
they don't win.
Who's Allen West on the left?
Who's Joe Walsh
or Michele Bachmann?
A 14-1 ratio of negative stories
and your takeaway is
is that there's a problem
with the storyteller.
What are your thoughts about that,
Taylor Warren?
- Cannot remember the question.
- Any word from Reese?
- He's still walking.
- He's what?
He's walking.
He's walking around
the neighborhood with a Rockette.
Presumably trying to decide
how to announce the personnel changes
and how much money to pay Dantana
to not file in the morning.
- What's a Rockette?
- The dancers.
He's dating a Rockette.
A real one.
Is there anything that'll convince you
it wasn't your fault?
Get together with Sloan
and talk about
a 90-second segment on income
and voting preferences.
- Okay, Jane, we're coming to you.
- If I can jump in...
Let's go to DC for
a whip-around on the Senate.
I have to cut you off there
and throw to Jane Barrow
and our panel in Washington.
Jane, the Republicans
will control the House
and the Democrats
will control the Senate.
A billion dollars later,
are we right back where we were?
- That's the question I want to put to our panel...
- We're out.
DC has the con.
5:30 back.
No.
No what?
There's nothing
that'll convince me.
I just got an e-mail
with an attachment.
- From me?
- Yes.
The attachment was
an article about the effect
of the debates on the election.
- Yeah.
- You know who wrote it?
- Neal.
- Nope.
- I can explain.
- The byline says I did.
- He knew you were busy.
- What the hell is going on?
We need someone
who doesn't work here to post an article
that contains the information
that MacKenzie
was president of the Cambridge Union
and not the Oxford Union
so that Wikipedia
would edit her page.
- You know, now that I'm saying it--
- Not until just now?
- What's the mood there?
- I know. I know.
- Okay, well, I have to go.
It's starting to sink in
that they're gonna lose Florida.
And between you and me,
he didn't write a concession speech.
- Can I ask you something?
- I really do have to go.
So do I, but...
do I ever make you feel
like you're dumb?
Seriously, honey,
what's going on there?
I'm asking because I really like you
and I don't want to blow it.
Well, first of all, you're not smart enough
to make me feel like I'm dumb.
I was hoping you'd say that.
And I really like you, too.
You're not blowing it.
I knew there had to be a reason
why I liked you so much.
'Cause just physically,
you're hard to look at.
- You're not so much homely...
- Talk to you soon.
...as you are
just weird-looking.
- Jim.
- Yeah?
Maggie says to tell you
they're 93 votes apart now
and you'd know what that means.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
The gender income gap
starts at 50K.
Men 50K and above
are breaking for Romney.
Women at 50-200K
were more likely to vote for the president.
And it's the top 1%
of female earners that went red.
Now here's where I'd like us to focus
because this is crucial.
- I'm sorry, but they need you.
- Wow.
- They're calling Ohio.
- We're on our way.
You're back in 90 seconds.
We'll pick this up after, okay?
We're calling both,
and we're ready to go to Chicago.
- Tess.
- I'll get estimates from Boston.
- Thank you.
- And let's get Ben standing by.
I don't see Sloan.
Is that Sloan out there?
We'll go without her.
We're calling it.
Get in the studio.
...go blue,
and that takes the president to 262.
At that point, he has a lot
of different roads to 270.
Colorado, Florida, Ohio
and Virginia in that scenario.
Any one of those states
would throw the president over the top.
Getting Mitt Romney
to 270 at this point
seems very, very difficult.
So the president's getting
closer and closer
270.
He's winning in the states
he needs to win...
- What I have can't be taught.
- Get her in the chair!
I mean,
it really started in the last hour
when Florida started
to slip away.
We're hearing from
very unhappy Republicans.
But right now we're going
to Will McAvoy in New York
who's got a new projection.
Will.
It's 11:14 in the East
and ACN is able to project
that Barack Obama
will be living in government housing
for the next four years.
President Obama
has been reelected
President of the United States,
Ohio having just put him
over the top.
Once again,
the ACN decision desk
is calling Ohio and the White House
for President Barack Obama.
We're gonna go live
to Suzannah Marquez
and show you some images
from Chicago
where the celebration
is under way.
Will,
as you can see, the news
has gone through this crowd
and the celebration has begun.
How about
"binders full of women"?
Was the media response to
"binders full of women"
in rational proportion?
That's a perfectly good question.
Thanks,
I was asking it to you.
And now he's losing.
Why'd you cut your hair?
I wanted a change.
I'm not crazy about it either.
The stylist kind of
talked me into it.
- Maybe I'll get used to it.
- There wasn't a stylist.
You cut it yourself.
You cut off your hair
and dyed it a different color.
Lisa told me.
How would Lisa know?
How did you not tell her
what happened in Africa?
- Did you?
- No.
- Don't.
- How did you not tell your best friend?
- It's been a year.
- And it's been a year since we were friends.
He's losing by 17 votes
with 8,000 votes uncounted.
Why did you cut your hair?
He'd never seen
blonde hair before.
While I was reading to him,
he was playing with my hair.
So I cut my hair.
- How'd it work?
- It didn't.
Right.
I'm trying to find out
where the uncounted votes are, but even if--
Listen.
Listen for a second.
You went back
into the building.
You went back in there.
You and Gary.
You pulled him out
from under the bed.
- You weren't going without him.
- He was safer under the bed.
Bullshit, Maggie.
You pulled him out and you carried him
on your back to the bus.
What was your crime?
You turned around
when you heard Gary fall down.
There's a difference
between being tough and wanting to be.
You and Mac are tough.
Don's tough.
I want to be.
You are.
You know when
I first noticed you?
When I ran into the room
and got tackled by Mac's luggage?
Did you know--
No. It was funny,
but I didn't notice you until later.
There was a beep.
It was an iNews alert.
But it was yellow.
You've got a news alert.
- Nobody was paying attention to it.
- It was yellow.
You clicked on it anyway.
You couldn't help yourself.
You ran back into the building.
He's dead and I'm alive.
That's what I'd keep in mind.
It's after midnight now
and I feel like I can ask a question.
- Sure.
- I meant to Will.
Yes.
Who did you vote for today?
You know I'm not
answering that.
I thought you might
because you revealed
your party affiliation
on the air last year.
I did.
I identified myself
as a Republican
because I thought it was fair
to give to the viewer given
the commentary I was delivering.
A commentary
that ended with you
calling the Tea Party
the American Taliban.
- Yes.
- And in the body of the commentary
- was a blistering indictment of Republicans.
- Exactly the opposite.
It was a blistering indictment of people
who aren't Republicans.
- Well, who's to say who is and who isn't?
- On that night, I did.
I want to remind you
you asked me to pursue this area.
- I understand.
- And I'm wondering, with all respect,
do you call yourself
a Republican
so you can make a claim
to credibility
when you attack the GOP?
No, I call myself a Republican
'cause I am one.
I believe in market solutions
and I believe in
common sense realities
and the necessity
to defend ourselves
against a dangerous world
and that's about it.
Problem is now
I have to be homophobic.
I have to count the number of times
people go to church.
I have to deny facts and think scientific
research is a long con.
I have to think poor people
are getting a sweet ride.
And I have to have such a stunning
inferiority complex
that I fear education
and intellect
in the 21st century.
But most of all,
the biggest new requirement,
really the only requirement,
is that I have
to hate Democrats.
And I have to hate Chris Christie
for not spitting on the president
when he got off Air Force One.
The two-party system
is crucial to the whole operation.
There's honor in being
the loyal opposition.
And I'm a Republican
for the same reasons you are.
So I hope your voice gets louder
in the next four years.
Well, I don't like losing,
so count on it.
You know, just jumping
on top of that idea--
- I'm sorry, Sloan.
- Come on!
We're gonna go to
Jane Barrow in Washington
for an update on some
West Coast House races.
Plenty more coverage
coming tonight. Jane?
- And clear.
- Are you doing it on purpose now?
No, it's just working out
unbelievably well.
You ever read Jedediah Purdy,
For Common Things?
No.
He talks about cynical times.
People having terminal irony
with a studied refusal
to hope or care openly.
- Does that sound like us?
- No.
No.
Have you asked yourself tonight
why we never reported
the Petraeus story?
- The Petraeus?
- Remember?
David Petraeus
is resigning on Thursday.
- We didn't report it.
- That's funny. I forgot.
Yeah. It's because
we never made the trade.
The decision was
that the other story had information
voters needed,
the Petraeus story didn't.
Not that many voters.
It would have affected maybe a few thousand, tops.
In one district, one seat.
As opposed to breaking
two days early
what will be a giant story.
Breaking it in front
of an Election Night audience.
And the decision to decline the trade
was made instantly
and unanimously.
Don pushed back reflexively,
but he came around
in seven seconds.
Don.
We've come a long way.
I'm not resigning.
And neither are you.
What, are we out
of our fucking minds?
Dantana doctored the tape.
That's what happened, Will.
We know the truth
and the mob doesn't.
When did we decide
it was an institutional failure?
We waited 11 months.
We know people
who would have gone
after the second red team meeting
or even the first.
You agree with what I'm saying?
I believe, except for the things we did wrong,
we did everything right.
And I can't live with Mac
taking the blame for--
We'll get the audience's
trust back.
Like Leona said,
we're gonna overcome
the terminal irony.
And the laundry list
of embarrassing things in the complaint?
I've got to tell you,
I'm not embarrassed.
The Zimmerman tape,
Jim going to New Hampshire,
Sloan punching a guy
in arbitrage--
I actually like that one.
I can't tell
what you're thinking.
Will?
It's gotten strange now.
Are you able
to hear me speaking?
She-- Except for the things she did wrong,
she did everything right, too.
- The rest was me.
- I'm lost.
Uh, yes.
We're going to do
the things you just said
for the reasons you just gave.
I missed parts of what
you were saying at the end,
but that's just
gonna have to be--
I'll be right back.
Yes!
Way to go.
Yeah, no,
I'm definitely resigning.
Does anyone know
where MacKenzie is?
- I think she's in the hair and makeup room.
- She's not.
- Did you look in her office?
- So, no, no one knows where she is?
We're back in seven minutes,
so she's gonna turn up.
- Have you seen Mac?
- I haven't.
But I have facts about
the Great Lakes region.
Right this moment is the least I've ever cared
about the Great Lakes region.
Has anyone seen Mac?
I'm right here.
Okay. I didn't--
- Could you come here away from the cameras?
- Yeah.
There's-- Okay, okay--
- There's a story.
- What?
There's a story about
a little kid who keeps shredding paper
and his parents take him to all kinds of doctors
to get him to stop shredding paper.
And finally they take him to
the most expensive doctor in the world
who turns to the kid and he says,
"Kid, if you stop shredding paper,
your parents will stop
dragging you to doctors."
And the kid turns to his parents and says,
"Why didn't you just say so?"
- Well, all right, then.
- The point of the story
is that the kid could make himself happy
by just stopping.
I think that's the point.
I don't know.
I've been trying
to figure it out.
But I didn't return it.
Because I'm in love with you.
- What did you say?
- And because of-- Will you marry me?
- Wait.
- I said will you marry me?
And before that,
I said I'm in love with you.
That's-- that's--
That's what I'm getting at.
I feel like I can do this so much better
if I can have a second.
What in the fuck
is happening right now?
If-- if I--
I don't ever want to not be-- No.
I love you. I'm gonna go back to that.
And will you marry me?
And let me just say I really think you should.
I think you should say yes.
But no matter what you say,
there's no chance
I am ever gonna hurt you again.
And no matter what you say,
I'm gonna be in love with you for the rest of my life.
There's no way out of that.
That's just a physical law of the universe.
- You own me. No matter what you say...
- Yes.
- ...I will never stop--
- Yes. I'm saying yes.
You're saying yes?
Yes.
Thank God.
Took you long enough.
Seriously?
That's what your--
Shut it.
So your mother was a Rockette?
That's right.
And her mother, too.
- Third generation Rockette?
- Yes.
How great is that?
- And if you were to have a daughter...
- Crazy lady.
...which would be
my granddaughter,
would it be important to you
that she also be a Rockette?
- I don't think important, but if she--
- Okay, good.
- Charlie.
- 'Cause over here you have a Harvard MBA.
Over here you have a line
of synchronized nutcrackers.
- Charlie.
- Reese.
Leona.
Rebecca.
- I'm sorry, I don't know who--
- Jackie. I'm here with Reese.
Third generation Rockette.
That's how we roll.
I've studied the findings
of the report
and I've consulted with counsel
and I've reached the conclusion
that the news division
handled Genoa as well
as I'd want it handled.
Furthermore, this company
will give Dantana money
when a federal judge
orders us to do so.
And furthermore after that,
I don't take my instructions
from a petition.
If you read Jedediah Purdy's excellent book
For Common Things--
What, did you e-mail
everybody excerpts?
- Yep.
- I'm not accepting your resignations.
We're not resigning.
That's fine, but I'm surprising you
by taking the high road
- and I'm not accepting your resignations.
- We're not offering them.
This isn't about
the bottom line.
This is a bad business decision,
but it's a good decision.
- I'm doing the right thing.
- There's no right thing to do.
I've already made the decision
that we're staying.
The wrong thing to do
would be to accept your resignation.
That's not an option,
'cause we're not offering them.
- You two about done?
- History should reflect that I acted admirably.
There's really no way
of knowing that.
Is it possible the greater glory
belongs to me?
You're all idiots.
Not you, you're sweet.
Everyone, just listen up
for just a second.
This'll just take a second.
First of all,
no one's resigning.
And the only reason you need
is 'cause I said so.
Also I think we're just starting to
get the hang of this.
More importantly,
I would like to introduce
the future Mrs. MacKenzie
Morgan McHale McAv--
That's not gonna work.
What?!
- I'll be damned!
- I know.
I know.
- Wake him up.
- Cynthia's office should draft a statement.
Let's start identifying
who our friends are.
That shouldn't take long.
What did you do?
I wrote it myself.
A gift from new media.
Thanks for that
Romney interview.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net