You have questions about my--
About drinking and men?
- You want to warn me about something?
- No.
I'm afraid to sleep
alone at night,
so sometimes I go out.
- Will is not aware of Genoa.
- Do you mind if I ask why not?
Because I might need him
for the red team.
Look, it's a completely
unbelievable story.
If you believe it
enough to be thinking
about a red team,
you believe it enough.
- What do you got?
- Some bullshit on Twitter.
Look, I get that it's stupid,
but it has an effect.
And we haven't been getting
the bounces lately.
- What was the third tweet?
- "You just lost a viewer."
Is this the right time to ask
why you date men like this?
You're saying I knew he was like this,
but didn't care?
I'm saying you don't have a very high opinion
of yourself and I don't get it.
You're impressive.
Operation Genoa--
This is the first piece of paper
we've seen with that name.
It happened
and we're gonna prove it.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
Here's where we are.
August 24 of last year
we had a guest on a panel
about drones named Cyrus West,
a retired Air Force captain
who now teaches
at the Maxwell School.
When the panel was done,
Captain West gave Jerry a tip
about a black op
with the codename Genoa.
What did he tell you
about Genoa?
He told me that in March 2009,
two Marines
were separated from
their unit in the Hindu Kush.
Intelligence told us that they were
captured by Taliban fighters,
taken across the border into Pakistan,
held in a small village,
and in a matter of a few hours
they were gonna be sold
to Al-Qaeda
and publically beheaded.
A MARSOC unit
was deployed to attempt an extraction.
Two MH-60s, Black Hawks,
came in with 15 MARSOCs apiece.
The first unit was overrun by the enemy
and trapped behind cover.
They were wearing MOPP gear.
Mission Oriented
Protective Posture.
The second unit,
also in MOPP gear,
came in and successfully
extracted the prisoners
as well as the first
MARSOC unit.
- How?
- By dropping sarin gas on the village.
How would the prisoners
have survived?
We hit them with atropine
and dragged them onto the helos.
- Everyone else was wearing MOPP gear.
- Everyone but the civilians.
That was Cyrus West's story
and that was last August.
Jerry then tracked down a retired
gunnery sergeant, Eric Sweeney.
Jerry and I met
with Sgt. Sweeney
and the full transcript
of that meeting
begins on page four
in your binders.
Sweeney describes rehearsals
for the mission...
- In MOPP gear.
- ...and then describes the mission itself.
He witnesses blinding smoke
and women and children
with boils and burns
on their faces.
Back on the helicopter
he asks another member of his crew
what that was all about
and he's told it was sarin.
Jerry put a team together
to track down other members
of the crew and any ground support,
but no one was talking.
Neal then did a search
of any tweets from the area
sent around March '09
and came up with Hamni8.
The tweets from Hamni8
would seem to be describing
what we'd heard from Sgt. Sweeney
and from Cyrus West.
"Helicopters. Grenades."
Then a moment later,
"Men in gas masks. Machine guns."
A moment later, "Burning."
Then, "Americans. White smoke."
Then, "Two helicopters.
No markings on them, but they're American."
It's 32 minutes
before the next tweet.
"I think everyone's dead."
We believe the reason
for the 32-minute gap
is frequency hopping.
We'd have jammed
the radio frequencies cell phones use.
West is one, Sweeney is two,
Hamni8 is three.
Four is a humanitarian report
from a guy named Leon Deit.
Deit was in the region
working for an NGO
and traveled to the site
of the extraction
on verbal reports
of a mass grave.
The eyewitness accounts
are consistent with the use of sarin gas.
And as you can see,
the report includes
pictures of the victims.
Five is a confidential source
who confirmed the story
and provided a copy
of the munitions manifest.
The manifest included this item--
MX-76.
MX-76 doesn't exist.
It's a euphemism for
classified material.
We believe
it's the sarin canisters.
The five of us
as well as some other staffers
have had a role in putting
this together so far.
We've purposely kept
a number of people out of the loop
including Will for fresh eyes.
Are there any questions?
- Sarin gas?
- I don't believe it, either.
I also don't believe in Santa Claus,
but if I saw eight reindeer take flight--
To be clear,
you haven't seen eight reindeer.
You've talked to someone
who says he's seen eight reindeer.
And we have someone
who's tweeted about the reindeer
and a third witness who's interviewed
victims of the reindeer
and a highly-placed
confidential source who's confirmed
that in this place at that time,
reindeer flew.
It couldn't matter less,
but Santa Claus has nine reindeer.
- Rudolph.
- Mac, I don't think--
- Dasher, Dancer.
- Vixen, Blitzen.
- How many was that?
- It really doesn't matter.
- You believe we used sarin?
- Yes.
- On civilians?
- Dasher, Dancer, Prancer.
- What are you doing?
Well, I'm digesting
what I just heard.
I'm doing a fact check
on the number of reindeer.
Dasher, Dancer, Prancer,
Comet, Blitzen, Cupid,
Donner, Vixen,
and somebody else.
- Rudolph.
- Thank you.
- Wait, how many was that?
- Start again.
No.
Do we even have sarin gas?
We aren't supposed to.
It was supposed to be destroyed by 2007
according to the Chemical
Weapons Convention.
But it wasn't. We still have it.
The DOD confirms that.
We may have it,
but we've never used it.
We didn't use it
in World War II,
Korea, Vietnam,
the first Gulf War,
and we were fighting
people that did have--
Those all happened before 9/11.
We torture people now.
We kidnap them, wire tap them--
- Drop deadly gas on civilians?
- It happened, Jim.
This is the one we know about.
- The original tip came from Cyrus West?
- I know, but--
- He's not reliable.
- His crime was not being good on television.
But he led us to Eric Sweeney,
so who cares?
What about the Marines
who were rescued?
We don't know their names
and they wouldn't have been
in a position to know what happened.
Sweeney says they were in a hole
in back of one of the houses.
And then they were
exposed to the gas.
They would have known
if they were hit with an atropine.
Probably, but it doesn't matter.
We don't know who they are
and we've been looking
for seven months.
We have 30 names
and here they are.
These were given to us
by Sweeney.
None of them is talking
with the exception
of Lance Corporal
Herman Valenzuela who's dead.
It sounded like you said
Herman Valenzuela,
in spite of being dead,
is talking.
- I wasn't saying that.
- I was confused by that, too.
Valenzuela was killed in action,
the other 29 aren't talking.
What about Hamni8?
Have you tried to track him down?
Yes, but he's gone.
We believe given his proximity to the raid
that he was killed.
Well, or that he couldn't
pay for his cell plan.
Those are two
pretty different things.
Have we put boots on the ground
to see if there's any locals we can talk to?
You can't send Americans in there
or anyone working for Americans.
- A local fixer?
- It's much too dangerous.
- What does Tapley say?
- Who?
Mike Tapley,
our military analyst,
who I don't know why
we didn't use him instead of West.
'Cause I was producing
the segment.
Neither Mike nor our Pentagon correspondent
have been brought in.
The Pentagon would go
into shutdown.
We'll ask for comment
24 hours before air.
Before air?
We're really
talking about--
Charlie,
be the voice of reason.
I think it happened
and I think we're two inches away
from proving it.
It's always 50-50 when you ask Charlie
to be the voice of reason.
- Nobody's saying it's ready to air.
- I'm saying it's ready.
It certainly is not.
And we can keep
calling the names
on the list
till St. Swithin's Day,
but we have a better chance of getting
Herman Valenzuela to talk
than any of the other 29.
So we started looking
for someone not on the list.
A flag officer who'd be in a position
to confirm the mission. Neal?
We ran five separate searches
and cross-referenced
the five search parameters
which were the following:
recently retired generals
who have attempted
to publish work that
was heavily redacted,
commanders who have
served as head
of the Marines Combat Logistics
and Munitions Element,
generals who've taken
academic positions since retiring
who've been critical of the US stockpile
of chemical weapons,
and flag officers who were on active duty
when Genoa took place.
When we think Genoa took place.
There's one name that meets
all five criteria.
This is three-star Marine General
Stanislaus Stomtonovich.
He was a munitions
consultant at White Sands
and an expert on the US
chemical weapons program.
He retired six months after Genoa
and lives in Silver Spring.
You're gonna call and ask him
if we dropped sarin gas on a small village?
- No, we're going to his house.
- Charlie, God damn it.
He's already alerted
the Pentagon's Office of Public Affairs.
He thinks we're coming
about something else.
We're just getting
in the vestibule.
But eventually,
you will ask him the question?
Yeah.
Do you understand
what we're accusing them of?
We do, Jim, yeah.
And I think we're less concerned
with what we're accusing them of
than we are with what they did.
What you think they did,
which I still can't hardly believe
my fucking ears
we're even talking about.
- What was the general's name?
- Stomtonovich.
How are you gonna question Stomtonovich
without him knowing what you're asking?
We're gonna ask him how chemical weapons
would be stored and deployed.
- What's the cover story?
- Libya.
You've been on this
for seven months?
Do you believe the story?
I don't know.
Have we nailed down
the number of reindeer?
I see you.
You seem really excited
every time this works.
Is it because you're seeing me
or is it because of the technology?
- The technology.
- I get that.
But tomorrow night
it'll be because I'm seeing you.
I'll tell you why you should be excited
about tomorrow night.
I got a suite
at the Soho Grand.
- It cost three years' salary.
- I like you.
- That's such great news for me.
- It really is.
So I'll pick you up
at the event at 10:00.
I'll be out in the lobby.
We'll go to dinner
and then back to the hotel for,
you know, discretionary time.
- Speaking of dinner...
- What's about to happen?
- Do you know Aubrey Lerner?
- No.
- Her byline is AK.
- I don't know her.
- AK Lerner.
- I don't know her,
but I feel like she's about to be
an obstacle in my path to--
- Discretionary time?
- Yes.
No, she's been
on the press plane
for a couple of weeks
and she reports for mtvU.
It sounds like she'd have a really good time
staying home by herself tomorrow.
I don't think you
should rob her of that.
She stays at her parents' place
when she's in New York
and I thought she could
come out to dinner with us
tomorrow night
and you could bring Neal.
I think they'd
really hit it off
and you said he just
broke up with somebody.
Neal's always just
broken up with somebody.
He calls it going home
in the morning.
It'll be a fun foursome.
- Dinner and then straight to the hotel.
- How many of us?
Jim, I'll have just finished covering
a $5,000-a-plate dinner.
I'll be in cocktail attire.
Do it. Do it.
Whatever she's asking to do, do it.
Do it now.
- You gonna be okay?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Gary.
- Hey, Hallie.
In terms of what you're gonna be wearing,
could you describe exactly what--
I'll see you guys
tomorrow at 10:00?
- In the ballroom lobby.
- I've got to go.
I'll talk to you later.
Neal.
Harry Truman dubbed the 80th Congress
the "Do-Nothing Congress."
Its productivity,
measured by this bar,
shows the number of laws
they passed.
The productivity of the 112th Congress
is measured by this bar.
The 112th Congress has not yet
passed 1/6 of the laws
of the Do-Nothing
Congress.
But let's look at the laws
they have passed.
Congressman Peter Roskam
represents the 6th District of Illinois.
Illinois has the fourth
highest unemployment rate
in the country with 9.9%
of its workforce out of work.
So Congressman
Roskam introduced
House Resolution 21-39,
which would require
the Secretary of the Treasury
to mint coins in commemoration
of the centennial
of the Lions Club.
Congressman Randy Forbes
of Virginia
sponsored a bill reaffirming
"In God We Trust" as our national motto,
a motto already
made official in 1956,
2002, 2006 and now 2011.
One in four American children
are living in poverty,
but the motto
should take care of that.
We're fighting a war,
a stagnant economy,
a failing education system
and climate change.
The 112 Congress
has renamed 40 post offices.
Richard Shelby,
the ranking Republican
on the Senate
Banking Committee,
blocked the appointment
of MIT economist Peter Diamond
to a vacant seat on
the Federal Reserve Board.
Said Shelby, "I do not believe
the current environment of uncertainty
would benefit from
monetary policy decisions
made by board members
who are learning on the job."
While Senator Shelby held up
Peter Diamond's nomination
on the grounds that Diamond
was insufficiently qualified
to counsel
the Federal Reserve Board,
Peter Diamond won
the Nobel Prize for economics.
- You busy?
- No.
Hey, this may sound nuts,
but I'm looking at the movie John Carter
- as a possible subject for my News Night segment.
- What about it?
Well, it's about a Civil War
Confederate officer
who's transported to Mars,
which is a lush planet
inhabited by
12-foot-tall barbarians.
Because of his different
bone density
and the planet's low gravity,
John Carter can jump--
I said, "What about it?" not, "What's it about?"
Also, you know, spoilers.
Okay, well, it's projected to lose
about 200 million for Disney.
You want to do
the economics of Hollywood?
Say what you want,
but they're one of the few American industries
still making a product
people want to buy.
Doesn't sound like
they want to buy John Carter.
Well, that's my point.
Nobody's gonna ask for a bailout
and Disney stock
is relatively safe.
Entertainment is one of our highest
revenue-generating exports
and they employ members
of 17 different unions,
all of which have excellent
minimum basic contracts.
They may take it in the teeth on John Carter,
but nobody's gonna get hurt.
It's still early.
It's just a first idea.
- Yeah, no, it sounds good.
- What are you doing?
Looking at last night's show.
- They did a focus group?
- No.
There are dial lines
on the bottom of the screen.
Yeah, those are just--
That's--
What's going on?
I did a focus group.
I did it myself.
I called our company
and did it on my own.
They did the dials
and a moderator got comments after.
- Why?
- Yeah.
- To check in.
Why does a politician
take polls?
To find out what people
want him to say the next day.
Are you comfortable
with that analogy?
Charlie doesn't allow me
to be tested anymore.
So I did it myself.
We have kind of a
big brother-little sister relationship.
- Which one are you?
- And the little sister always ends up
chewing out the big brother and he says,
"Thanks, sis."
This is on Nickelodeon?
- Never mind.
- Are you preparing for a chewing out?
Nah.
You forgot to ask me
how the test scores were.
I didn't forget.
427. 427.
Are the odd numbers
on the right side or the left side?
I can't see any numbers yet.
All right, you look on the right side,
I'll look on the left side.
I'm already on the left side.
Why don't you look
on the right side?
I'll look on the right side.
Oh.
Hey, found it.
- Is it this house or that house?
- I don't know.
Let's just clean this up
and ring both doorbells.
What are you doing
in my garbage cans?
- General Stomtonovich?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry we're a little late.
What are you doing
in my garbage cans?
We ran over them
with our rental car.
We're just gonna
get this cleaned up.
Were you texting?
No, sir.
It was regular negligence.
Well, hurry up
and tell me what you want.
I'm sorry, sir.
You're General Stom--
I know who I am.
I'm asking who you are
and how I can help you.
- I'm Charlie Skinner.
- MacKenzie McHale.
Mm-hmm.
How about if I write you
a check for $100
and you send the magazine subscriptions
to whoever you want?
Sir, we spoke to you
on the phone yesterday.
We made an appointment
to see you here at your house.
Yeah, right.
That's too bad.
I like arguing with
Jehovah's Witnesses.
- You want to know how chemical weapons are stored?
- Yes, sir.
All right.
What is the Marine
Combat Munitions Element?
We oversee all or almost all
of the munitions supplies
for the entirety of the Marine Corps.
- Bullets, bombs...
- And that includes chemical--
Foul him.
Foul him now!
And he buries a three.
Mmm.
March Madness.
Best sporting event on Earth.
Better than the Super Bowl,
World Series--
- Better than the World Cup?
- World Cup?
What are you, from Brazil?
Brooklyn.
2003, Gaddafi announced Libya
would voluntarily
eliminate all materials,
equipment and programs,
but they've still got 'em.
- How about us?
- The US?
- Yeah.
- Do we still have chemical weapons?
- We do?
- Yeah.
Do you believe chemical weapons are
a legitimate weapon of war?
I believe chemical weapons,
like any other weapons,
are tools to be used
to kill the enemy.
Which tool you use
depends on battlefield circumstance.
- And collateral damage?
- It doesn't make much difference
to the collateral damage
whether it's damage by gas
or a Hellfire missile, does it?
So you think chemical weapons
should be part of our arsenal?
Part of ours, not Libya's.
Do you think we should be able to use
chemical weapons?
Missed free throws
is what kills you.
- General?
- I don't think I want to talk about chemical weapons.
- We think you do.
- Yeah?
During a speech at the War College
two years ago,
you were openly critical
of the destruction of our stockpiles.
You've commissioned two studies
citing the potential need
for chemical weapons
in combat situations
and your book
was so heavily redacted
that all that was left
were pronouns.
Why are you two big shots
in Silver Spring, Maryland,
running into my garbage cans
and asking me about sarin?
General,
we never mentioned sarin.
We know about Genoa.
You can't touch a shooter
while he's in the process of shooting the ball.
It's against the rules.
Shooter goes to the foul line,
takes two free throws.
But what happens
if the shooter brandishes a knife?
He's dribbling the ball
and he suddenly takes out
a switchblade.
You're allowed
to grab his arm now
because we're not playing
basketball anymore.
This is a helo manifest.
Can you confirm it's authentic?
It's an authentic
helo manifest.
Can you confirm
that Genoa happened?
Why would I confirm,
even off the record,
the existence
of a classified mission?
Because you believe
very strongly that if the shooter
takes a knife out,
it shouldn't be illegal to grab his arm.
Hmm.
Here are my conditions.
You black out my face.
- Sure.
- Alter my voice.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's it.
We do it right here
noon tomorrow.
I want to be able
to watch the games.
- Not during the interview.
- I'm not turning that TV off.
I don't know how many years
I have left after this thing goes on the air.
The producer's name
is Jerry Dantana.
He's from the DC bureau
and it's been his story from the beginning.
We have to head back to New York,
General.
It was nice meeting you.
We won't have any more communication
after this unless it's necessary.
How did he find it--
Dantana?
How did he find the story?
Just a lucky tip.
And then very late
in my political career,
I had the opportunity to read the speech
and I almost threw up.
The speech that almost made
Senator Santorum vomit
was given by John F. Kennedy
in Houston, Texas, in 1960.
The presidential candidate
was answering concerns
that his Catholicism would be
his compass in the Oval Office.
And the Houston speech
made a forceful argument
for a firewall between religion,
any religion, and government.
With us by satellite from Boulder, Colorado,
is Randall Dell,
President of the League of Catholic Voters
and a Santorum supporter.
- Mr. Dell, welcome.
- Good to be here.
The common wisdom is that
political candidates
- shouldn't be asked about their religious beliefs.
- I agree with that.
But what if a candidate makes their religious
beliefs part of their candidacy?
Is there a candidate
who's doing that?
- The candidate you support is doing that.
- That's not true, sir.
Is Rick Santorum devout?
Yes.
Does his faith guide his actions?
Does he say so every day
in campaign speeches? He does.
Let's put this quote
up on the screen.
- G17-A.
- Got it.
Rick Santorum speaking
at a Tea Party event in Columbus.
He said this in regard
to President Obama's climate change agenda.
"It's not about your quality of life.
It's not about your jobs.
It's about some phony ideal.
Some phony theology.
Oh, not a theology based on the Bible.
A different theology."
Mr. Dell, one of
Rick Santorum's problems
with the president's plan
to combat climate change
is that its roots
can't be found in the Bible.
We have a lot of reasons to be
concerned with Obama's plans,
but you're plainly distorting
Rick Santorum's words.
I don't think I am,
but let's go to this instead.
- 17B.
- Up.
- 30 seconds.
- Let it go long.
...at the Press
and People of Faith
in Politics forum in 2008.
"I think there are a lot of problems with
the theory of evolution
and I do believe
it is used to promote
a world view that is anti-theist,
that is atheist.
You should have academic freedom
in the classroom when teaching about life."
- That was 2008. Mr. Santorum...
- Ready 18.
...made those remarks
when he didn't hold office.
- He was speaking as a private citizen.
- Ready.
- Go.
- He was speaking in defense of an amendment
he offered in 2001
when he was a US Senator,
making it a federal law that,
"Where topics are taught
that may generate controversy,
such as biological evolution,
the curriculum should help
students to understand
the full range
of scientific views that exist."
By full range
of scientific views,
- he's including Genesis, right?
- That's right.
It seems like far from
objecting that religion
be brought up in political campaigns,
he's insisting on it.
And here's Rick Santorum's opponent,
Mitt Romney,
- asking us not to ask about his religion.
- 22.
That idea that we should
choose people
based upon their religion
for public office
is what I find
to be most troubling,
because the founders
of this country went to great length
to make sure,
and even put it in the Constitution,
that we would not choose people
who represent us
in government
based upon their religion.
And now here he is
invoking his religion.
The Declaration of Independence
established our rights
by saying that
they were created
not by government,
but by the Creator.
We are endowed by our Creator
with certain unalienable rights.
I will fight to preserve
America's tradition...
...as a religious nation.
So, can we really not ask
these candidates questions
- about what they believe with regard to religion?
- Well, like what?
Like is it important that you and I
have the same definition of "creator"?
They plainly meant God.
That's not plain to everybody.
Like right there.
Just a smile would have made it folksier.
Also, honey,
you've got to stay away from religion.
You know you're
just asking for it.
What else am I supposed
to talk about
with the President
of the League of Catholic Voters?
You don't have him on as a guest.
That's another thing.
You want guests that don't
make you look so combative.
That's why your likability
numbers are down.
- I don't know. I think I'm likable.
- I think you're lovable.
- Thank you.
- But your numbers are problematic.
Listen to me,
I'd like dinner to last
10 to 15 minutes.
You don't like to linger.
I'm doing my lingering
somewhere else tonight,
so we're not ordering anything
that takes a long time to prepare.
We're not ordering
anything well-done.
anything cooked.
It's okay with me
if we don't order anything.
- It's not going to be okay with the restaurant.
- Screw the restaurant, Neal.
The restaurant hasn't
not seen his girlfriend in a month.
The restaurant's girlfriend
isn't wearing cocktail attire.
- You gonna be okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Six minutes and 20 seconds.
God, it's you.
That's how long you spent tonight
on Etch-a-Sketch.
- Six minutes and 20 seconds.
- Hey, Taylor.
- Hi, Jim.
- You look very nice.
- Thank you.
- This is Neal Sampat. We work together.
Neal, this is Taylor Warren,
a Romney campaign spokesman.
- Woman-- Uh, spokesperson.
- Nice to meet you.
- You work for ACN?
- Yes.
I loathe you in ways
that are unquantifiable.
Cool.
- You must be excited to see Hallie.
- I am.
I mentioned to Hallie that I didn't
have anything to do in the city tonight.
- No.
- And she said that I should join you guys for dinner.
You should see the look on your face.
Don't worry,
I know you had a special night planned,
so of course I'm coming along.
You know why?
- Because we spent six minutes and 20 seconds--
- On Etch-a-Sketch, yeah.
- It was a story and you know it.
- No, it was a gaffe.
He came out and said,
"Don't worry about anything I've said during the primary.
I can be whatever
you want me to be."
He didn't say it.
Fehrnstrom did.
And how do you
expect us to juggle
very diverse coalitions
inside the Republican party?
- Really glad I came tonight.
- There's no way you're coming to dinner.
Jim.
- I've missed you.
- You look amazing.
- Plus?
- I've missed you, too.
There it is.
This is Aubrey.
Hey, it's nice to meet you.
Neal.
Okay, full disclosure--
The press wasn't allowed any food,
but we stole a couple
bottles of Chardonnay
- and I am wicked hammered.
- Okay.
- Neal, this is Aubrey.
- Hey.
- Nice to meet you.
- Full disclosure-- The press wasn't allowed any food,
but we stole a couple
bottles of Chardonnay--
- Wicked hammered.
- You said that already.
We're gonna get some food
in your stomach.
Maybe that's not necessary.
So, listen,
Taylor's kind of sad tonight.
I don't know why,
so I asked her to come to dinner.
She's not sad.
She's mad 'cause we did
six minutes and 20 seconds
on Etch-a-Sketch.
And now I have to have a dinner with her
that could last up to a half hour.
You're afraid of Taylor.
Being afraid of Taylor
is just good common sense.
- Anybody hungry?
- I can boot and rally.
Let's do it.
- You here alone?
- Yeah. You?
I am.
This is what I do now.
I drink alone at bars
late at night.
See, men can do that
with no stigma attached.
- Women--
- Women can vote
and your vote counts
the same as my vote.
I'm really supposed
to worry about a stigma?
Oh, Don.
Don, Don.
Don.
Are you happy with that name?
Pretty happy.
Never really thought about it.
How'd it go in Maryland?
He confirmed.
Will he do it on camera?
- Find out tomorrow.
- Hey, Mac.
- What do you say, Chelsea?
- You here alone?
- Don't stigmatize her.
- Where's the gang?
Jim and Neal
are on a double date,
Sloan is out
with a New York Giant,
and Will's having a quiet night at home
with Mrs. Macbeth.
He took some questions
from the audience
and somebody asked him
if he thought the court
was going to overturn the ACA.
And I thought he was
gonna duck the question,
but he answered
for about two minutes.
- What did he say?
- I swear to God, I don't know.
Can I ask something?
What's the fucking obsession
with Ann Romney's horse?
- Reagan had a horse.
- His horse didn't dance.
So fucking what, James?
It's a clever horse.
It's an Olympian.
It's a horse.
And what in this is bad?
And how do you know
that Reagan's horse didn't dance?
It's a reasonable question,
James.
How did you get
into campaign reporting?
I told my bosses that nobody
was covering Ron Paul
and they were like,
"Go do it yourself."
And I was like, "Really?"
And they were like, "Really."
So Ron Paul, 2012!
- Is this your--
- Whoo-hoo!
- Okay.
- Seriously?
Yeah, she's into it.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- You're back again.
- Yeah.
- It was Stoli and tonic?
- I'm Devon.
- Maggie.
I admire MacKenzie.
- And Charlie.
- So do I.
I know you do.
But I wonder if it's blinding you
to certain things.
Like what?
Well, honey, every night
you cross examine somebody.
They're using your
prosecutorial skills.
Wait. First, they're not my puppet masters.
I'm the managing editor.
But don't you always
listen to MacKenzie?
- Not always.
- What percent of the time?
I don't know.
But the idea is
that we cross examine people
from time to time.
- We?
- A lot of staff prep goes into those segments.
But the staff's face
isn't on camera.
What are we talking about?
Are you being sacrificed
so that Mac and Charlie
can do the show
they want to do?
It's the show
I want to do, too.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
Then that's that.
If it's the show you want to do,
then who cares how many people like you?
I like you.
It actually doesn't measure
how many people like you.
It measures how much
people like you.
- How much?
- Yeah.
That's not something
that can be measured.
That's right.
So this is really
all there is to go on?
Do you fully trust
Jerry Dantana?
- Why wouldn't I?
- No reason. I was just curious.
- But there's a reason you're asking.
- There really isn't.
- Can I tell you what it is?
- It was just curiosity.
- It's 'cause he's not Jim.
- Please.
Jerry has committed the crime of
not being Jim Harper.
You know how long
it took you to trust me?
- How long?
- I'll let you know when it happens.
I completely trust you.
- Do you?
- With my life, Don.
Thank you.
That's nice to hear.
You know,
when I look at you--
- Sloan's going out with a football player?
- Yeah.
- Who?
- I don't remember his name.
- You know what position he plays?
- No.
- Offense or defense?
- I don't know.
Why don't you just ask her out?
After she's gone out
with a professional athlete
who's 10 years younger
than I am with 3% body fat
and ripped muscles
that have been conditioned
over a lifetime
of two-a-days sweating--
How long have you been
thinking about this guy?
How am I supposed
to follow that?
- And, you know...
- Get it done?
I can get it done.
I'm saying...
get it done in
a spectacular fashion.
This is how most men think?
This is how every
single man thinks
except for the guy
out with Sloan right now.
And that's why you
haven't asked her out?
Sometimes she subs in
for Elliott
and sometimes she does
a segment with us,
which means sometimes
I'm her boss.
That stopped absolutely no one here,
including you and Maggie.
That worked out
phenomenally well.
Nothing that happened to her
is your fault.
That's the spicy
Shanghai soup noodles,
- chilled silken tofu garlic and herbs?
- Yes, it is.
- How'd you recognize that?
- It's kind of a hobby.
And here's the charred
chili rubbed beef skewer.
- With Thai basil dipping sauce.
- That's right.
- So, Jim.
- Yeah?
- I have to tell you something.
- Okay.
The Sex and the City story
is off-the-charts awesome.
- What's the Sex and the City story?
- Please, no.
Is it an embarrassing
story about Jim?
It's not embarrassing.
It's sweet.
I'd like to hear it
as many times
as ACN's run the "I like to fire people"
sound bite.
- Everybody ran it, Taylor.
- And everybody, including you,
knew what he meant
when he said it.
Let's play the game
where we identify the food.
- What's this?
- You're pointing at rice.
I believe that's correct.
You know,
I could tell the story...
- Yep.
- ...or we can watch it on YouTube.
Oh, sweet.
I'm starting to feel
responsible for this.
What about ACN Morning?
- You think I should go on?
- I think you should start there.
I think you need
to warm yourself up
and a morning show
is a great place to start.
Just go on and do some jokes?
Just be you.
Nebraska farm boy.
The guy who knows
how to build his own cabin.
I don't know how
to build my own cabin.
Well, you seem like you do.
You need to seem like you do.
Midwestern.
You used to steal
your mother's pies
when she put them out to cool.
You're confusing me
with a hobo.
- You know what I'm saying.
- I think I do.
- Then do it.
- Okay.
- How about tomorrow morning?
- Well, it's after midnight.
ACN is a network
built around one person.
You call the EP,
tell him you're coming on in the morning.
You'll feel better
once you start to turn this around.
- I will feel better.
- 75s become 85s fast,
but they become 55s faster.
All right.
That gentleman over there
would like to buy this for you.
This is nice of you,
but I have to tell you
I'm just hanging out
alone tonight.
- That's okay.
- It's nothing personal.
The drink's on me anyway.
Very kind.
Thank you.
- I'm just thinking my thoughts.
- Understood.
I have a number of questions.
I'll try to answer them
with the same detail
and honesty you've
always answered mine.
What were you doing on a Sex and the City
tour bus to begin with?
My girlfriend at the time
liked the show
and I was showing an interest
in her interests.
And Maggie didn't know you were on the bus
when she shouted that she loved you?
That's not what she shouted.
- And she didn't know someone was filming it?
- No.
- So it was kind of a gaffe?
- Lady, I--
Life and death and you guys can't get past
corporations are people.
How fast are we
supposed to get past
"Hispanics
should self-deport"
or "I'm not concerned
with the very poor"?
"There's a safety net there"
was the end of that sentence,
and plainly his concern
is with the middle class.
The middle class
are the very poor.
The better point is we don't need clean air
and water regulations.
We don't need FEMA.
We don't need antitrust laws.
We don't need the IRS or the Department
of Education or the Federal Reserve.
We need freedom.
What the fuck did you just say?
If you listen
to Ron Paul--
I have.
He's a batty old crank
who wrote instruction manuals on
how to get away with shooting the black kid
who's stealing your car.
He's not Betty White.
- He didn't write those letters.
- Yes, he did.
And then he signed them
and then he charged money for them.
So I don't give a shit
if he wants to legalize weed.
I can already dial the phone
and have an ounce
delivered to this table
before the check comes.
- Then for God's sake, do it.
- The check will never come.
They won't let Romney
get his message out, either.
Someone should tell him
if he wants to get his message out,
he should consider
appearing on a network
where the entire audience
isn't already voting for him
and that if he's gonna be
the businessman president,
he should run on his business record
instead of pretending he's never heard of it
and that if faith is important
to his good works and personal narrative,
he shouldn't be afraid
it'll creep us out.
- It's been suggested.
- And?
I was fired.
- I was fired tonight.
- You were fired?
- Yeah.
- For suggesting--
No, I suggested
other things, too.
I'm sorry.
You were a good
spokesperson for him.
You should go work
for Ron Paul.
We need to rebound from dinner.
- Yeah.
- Bounce back.
- I've already bounced.
- It's just us now.
With a little over six hours.
This is...
Maggie?
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
I'm just having a drink
with a friend of mine from college.
What are you doing here?
Jim's fixing my computer.
I'm staying here.
This is Hallie Shea.
Hallie, this is Maggie Jordan.
- Hi.
- It's nice to meet you.
You, too.
Well, we should, um--
- I have to be on the press plane pretty early.
- Yeah.
- Good meeting you.
- You, too.
See you later.
- That was nice of you.
- I doubt it mattered.
Wow.
Is there something
wrong with the room?
I am not unskilled
in the ways of courtship.
I know, babe, but still,
just saying that...
I am pouring you some champagne
and then taking a hot shower.
Can I offer you
a Toblerone from the minibar?
- Honey.
- What is it?
They just added on an event
at a base in Colorado
for the morning.
For tomorrow morning?
I have to be on a plane
in 90 minutes.
Are you religious?
In my way.
Me, too.
I think the way you know
you've broken one of God's rules
is if you can't put it
back together again.
You kidnap an entire people,
make them slaves--
It's 300 years later
and we can't put it
back together again.
You and Will?
Doesn't really seem
like the same scale.
- As slavery?
- Yeah.
No.
But here we are.
You should go out.
I do.
You'll meet someone.
You're sure you trust Jerry?
I have no reason not to.
Mac, if Charlie green lights it
and Will and the lawyers...
you still have to consider
not running it.
- I know.
- The size of this...
- I've thought about the risk.
- Embassies will be attacked.
- POWs will--
- There'll be protests.
Protests in some countries
look a lot like riots.
Muslims will go crazy.
I was at Newsweek in 2005.
For the guy who flushed
a Koran down the toilet?
Yeah.
We report the story
and two months later,
the London subway blows up.
- It's not clear the two were connected.
- The bomber's cousin said--
- Somebody was gonna report it.
- Ah, maybe not.
Maybe not.
Anyway, I hope you're
considering cause and effect,
'cause if we broke
one of God's rules,
it might be best
just to shut up about it.
Where's your friend?
She took off.
I'm just paying the check.
Did you fix her computer?
No, I wasn't really able to.
Because you don't know shit
about fixing computers?
This thing we've
been talking about,
- Jerry's thing...
- Yeah?
Secrecy is
incredibly important.
I've been working on it
for seven months
and you didn't hear about it,
right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Just be careful
when you're drinking.
I will.
- Hey, you ready to go?
- Yeah.
I think you're supposed
to be paying the check.
She's all covered.
- And you were a high school athlete.
- That's right.
There's another thing
we didn't know about you.
Baseball and football.
Pitcher and quarterback.
- It was a small school.
- The question is were you any good?
- I wasn't bad.
- Well, we're gonna find out right now.
- Uh-oh.
- We're gonna have you stand on this line
- and make five throws.
Mm-hmm.
Every throw that goes
through the tire is $1,000
to the Sloan-Kettering
Memorial Cancer Research Center.
It seems like cancer research
shouldn't have to depend
on my throwing accuracy.
- Come on now, don't chicken out, McAvoy.
- All right.
Wait, there's one more
piece of apparatus.
I don't think
I'm gonna need a helmet,
- unless you guys plan on--
- Oh, it's just for fun.
It's a morning show.
We have fun here.
- Yeah, all right.
- There it is.
All right,
this is for cancer research.
On the line.
On your mark.
Get--
I know you think it went badly,
but it didn't.
I have to do two things--
I have to write a huge check to Sloan-Kettering
and then I absolutely
have to break up with you.
They're both important.
I get why the first one has to come first,
but the second one has to come right after,
no delay.
Why didn't you just say
I shouldn't worry about the number?
Because you should.
I was aiming for
the fucking light tree.
You didn't care that
you scored in the high 90s
in trust and intelligence?
- You looked like Dukakis riding in the tank.
- I know.
I've done a comprehensive study on
your psychological profile.
Introduction to First Year
Adult Psychology.
I haven't read the whole thing,
but I read from page eight to--
Well, I've read
most of page eight.
And here's
what happened to you.
A long, long time ago,
you were doing a show you liked
with MacKenzie.
Then she broke your heart.
Then you started doing a different show.
A softer show.
A show built around your likeable personality.
And the love you got
from the audience filled, almost,
the hole in your heart.
You're happy
from 8:00 to 9:00
and miserable
the other 23 hours.
You feel more comfortable
with strangers than with friends.
Then suddenly
Mackie's back in town
and she's making you do
the show you're supposed to be doing
and she insists
that you and everyone else
do the news, and you like that.
But that does mean
you might lose
some of your invisible friends.
That sound about right?
- I don't believe it really said that in the book.
- I extrapolated.
You gonna tell me I'm supposed to love myself
before anyone else can love me?
- Mm-hmm.
- "Self-love, my liege,
is not so vile a sin
as self-neglecting."
I read page eight
of Shakespeare, too.
"A woman is like a tea bag. You can't tell
how strong she is until you put her in hot water."
- Who said that?
- Eleanor Roosevelt.
- Does that have anything to do with this?
- No.
Okay.
That's it?
I thought I was getting chewed out.
I can't say anything that would make you feel
worse than you do right now.
- I like that you know that.
- You know what a Goldilocks planet is?
It's a planet
with the potential to support life
because of its
proximity to a star.
- Not too hot, not too cold.
- Right.
Near liquid water,
but not made of liquid water.
Enough oxygen,
but not too much nitrogen.
And we use something, um...
- Transit spectroscopy.
- I think that's what it's called.
To analyze the atmosphere
and find planets
that match the different
requirements.
1,300 planets were identified,
but only two confirmed.
And of those two,
one turned out to be...
something.
- Radioactive.
- Yeah.
So right now
that leaves one planet
in all of space that's perfect.
You're talking about
what I think you're talking about, right?
- I probably am.
- All right.
Okay.
How'd the date with
the Giant go last night?
Not that good.
He ditched me around midnight.
But I did end up dancing
with Savannah Guthrie for a while.
That girl can dance.
Have you seen the sheer length of her legs?
I embarrassed the whole team
this morning and I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
I love you, Will.
Thanks, sis.
- You look tired.
- I'm not.
- When'd you get in?
- On the first shuttle.
What are we going to do
about the screen?
Oh, it has to be on.
It's a condition.
I can't frame it out.
There's gonna be a piece of the game in the shot.
We're gonna blur it out.
Why not just move the chair?
I want the hardware
for gravitas.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
- General.
- Let me just see what's going on here.
It's a good game.
- Jerry Dantana?
- Yes, sir.
This is Maggie Jordan.
She's also a producer on the story.
She'll be leaving
before we start.
No, she's a producer
on the story.
- She understands--
- I was told Jerry Dantana.
Sir--
Charlie Skinner and MacKenzie McHale
told me Jerry Dantana,
and Jerry Dantana
is who I had investigated,
not Maggie Jordan.
- Um--
- It's all right. I'll wait outside.
Just check your levels
once in a while.
Fellas, you all set?
- Yeah.
- Okay, could you wait outside?
- Mmm.
- You can sit right there, sir.
You understand we're going
to ask about Operation Genoa
- and that it was a classified mission?
- Yes.
Okay, you're all set.
I'm stepping out.
- And you're going to confirm it happened.
- It happened.
What was Operation Genoa?
An extraction.
Two Marines were taken
by the enemy
and I won't say more than that.
Who carried out the extraction?
MARSOC--
Marines Special Operations Command.
Were any exceptional measures
used in the operation?
Exceptional measures
were called for.
Were they used?
General?
- Was sarin gas used during Genoa?
- It is right.
It is moral and necessary to use
any means in that situation,
in the situation they were in,
to use the means
at your disposal to rescue
captured prisoners.
- Did we use sarin gas?
- If we used sarin-- Let me put it this way.
- Sir.
- Here's how we would have used sarin.
I'd like the logistics
in a moment,
but right now I'm asking you
if we used sarin gas.
If we used sarin--
- General--
- Listen to me.
If we used sarin,
here's how we used sarin.
It would have been stockpiled
in a depot in Okinawa.
That's first.
It was guarded...
Two Marines...
- ...we used sarin gas?
- If we used sarin--
- General--
- Listen to me.
If we used sarin,
here's how we used sarin.
...how we used sarin.
...we used sarin.
It is right.
It is moral and necess--
It is moral and--
Who carried out the extraction?
MARSOC-- Marines Special
Operations Command.
Did we use sarin gas?
We used sarin.
And how is that used?
Here's how we used sarin.
It would have been
stockpiled...
- I want to see the raw footage.
- Yeah.
Here we go.
Were any exceptional
measures used in the operation?
Exceptional measures
were called for.
Like what?
We used sarin.
It is right.
It is moral and necessar--
We're not there yet.
- You're joking, right?
- It's compelling film.
- Compelling?
- When Mac and I showed up at his house yesterday,
he'd forgotten he'd talked
to us on the phone.
He thought we were selling
magazine subscriptions.
He wasn't being asked about--
Did it seem to you like
he was shaky during--
I want another witness.
- We have our key witness.
- He wasn't there.
- He knew about it.
- Didn't remember we'd called.
- He didn't remember at first, right?
- Jerry--
We've got evidence
of a war crime.
Just sit with that
for a second.
We dropped sarin gas
on a village.
We have a moral imperative
to question
the flagrant disregard
with which the president
and the national security
establishment
treat the Constitution
and international laws.
What does this have to do
with the Constitution?
We've killed four American citizens
without due process.
And those are the ones
we know about.
Five times as many
drone strikes
as the entire Bush presidency.
Dramatically increased
wire tapping,
detentions,
prosecuting whistle blowers,
several of whom
are willing to go on camera for us.
- What your problem is...
- Careful, Jerry.
...is that you like him.
You like this president.
You trust him.
Go ahead, we trust you.
Chase Nielsen flew
the Doolittle Raid after Pearl Harbor
and got water boarded
by the Japanese,
and we executed
the Japanese soldiers who did it!
What the fuck is going on?!
We have it.
How long before
you're comfortable?
Former Pennsylvania Senator
Rick Santorum
suspended his campaign
for the presidency...
President Obama told ABC News
Robin Roberts
that same-sex couples
should be able to get married.
Texas Representative
Ron Paul said today
that he will stop actively campaigning
in the Republican primaries.
And now,
thanks to the Lone Star State,
Governor Romney can officially drop
the word "presumptive."
Wisconsin Governor Scott Walker
is still the governor...
Chick-Fil-A's president,
Dan Cathy said,
"I think we are inviting
God's judgment on our nation."
The White House is exercising
executive privilege
over documents requested by
the House Oversight Committee
in its investigation
of Fast and Furious.
Chief Justice John Roberts
wrote the majority opinion
in the historic
5-4 decision.
The constitutionality of the Affordable Care Act
has been challenged...
With eight weeks left until
the Republican National Convention in Tampa,
speculation has turned
to Governor Romney's choice of running mate.
...introduced
Representative Paul Ryan,
one of the Republican party's
young conservative leaders as his running mate.
Representative Todd Akin,
who won Missouri's GOP Senate primary
earlier this month,
and who will face Democratic incumbent Claire McCaskill,
said Sunday that he misspoke
when he claimed "legitimate rape"...
With three days to go before delegates
converge on Tampa Bay, Florida,
GOP officials are moving
forward with their plans
to kick off the Republican
National Convention on Monday,
despite the looming threat
of Tropical Storm Isaac.
The storm is currently
headed for Haiti.
I'm gonna ask you to hold on
just a second, please.
Lance Corporal Herman Valenzuela
is on the phone.
Valenzuela is dead.
No, he's not.
He's on the phone.
How'd you get that wrong?
There were two
Herman Valenzuelas.
Both lance corporals.
One was killed in action.
Why were you calling him
if you thought he was dead?
The messages were left for him
before we got the service records.
We stopped calling,
but he'd been deployed.
And when he got home,
he got our messages and returned our call.
And that's when you gave
the green light?
We had Sweeney,
we had Hamni8...
- Charlie.
- ...we had the report from the NGO,
- we had my source...
- Who you won't reveal.
...we had the helo manifest,
we had Valenzuela
who was the crew chief.
We had a story
that the US used sarin gas
on a village in Pakistan
and we went.
Anybody would have.
Most people would have
gone months earlier.
To not go would have
been to participate
in the biggest
cover-up since...
These were war crimes.
It was a Sunday special report.
9:00 P.M. Eastern.
Neilson tracking showed it was gonna be
a monster audience--
Three and a half, four million.
It ended up closer to six.
By 10:05,
I knew we had a problem.
None of it was true.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net