You can't possibly
believe this story.
At what point do we
have to take it seriously?
We'll never find that out.
Find me an informed
representative of the pajama party
and I will give them
five minutes
of national prime time
air with Will McAvoy.
- Hallie, ask the question.
- Don't let Jim egg you on.
Don't change the fucking subject.
Which is it?
We can force them to answer our questions
if we do it together.
Who's with me?
You and Gary are going to
an orphanage in north Uganda
that shelters kids whose parents
have been killed in the wars.
- I'm going.
- You're going.
- What's Willie Pete?
- It's white phosphorus.
Hamni8. Americans.
White smoke.
Hamni8. Burning.
He's describing Genoa.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
My name is Rebecca Halliday.
I'm a litigator
at Lowell Tiller.
This is my deputy,
Ross Kessler,
along with Ken Weinraub
and Mark Gage.
Our firm has been hired by your employer,
Atlantis World Media,
to represent them in a multimillion dollar
wrongful termination suit.
This is not a formal proceeding.
You are not under oath.
Your statements, however,
will be recorded
and a full report along with
part or all of your statements
may be turned over to
the plaintiff as discovery.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
This is gonna be simple.
Your testimony revolves
around two words.
- It happened.
- The general didn't say that.
- Okay.
And even if he had,
he never said it on the tape.
Whoa, whoa, whoa there,
little onion.
Okay.
Let me start with
a really tough question
and I want you to take your time
and think about it.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- What's your name?
- I'm sorry?
These guys need your full name,
address,
and occupation for the records.
Margaret Claire Jordan.
344 East 75th Street,
New York, New York.
I'm an associate producer with ACN,
Atlantis Cable News.
- Do you like the East Side?
- Yeah.
I don't know.
I always thought the best thing about it
was you got to look
at the West Side.
I'm on the third floor.
My window faces another window.
I just got shown
a place on 5th Avenue.
High floor, wraparound terrace.
It was listed at 17 million,
but the broker thinks
it's gonna go
as low as 14.5.
They're very motivated.
I looked at the same place,
but I need a bigger ballroom.
On March 22 of this year,
you and Jerry Dantana
conducted an interview
with General
Stanislaus Stomtonovich.
- Am I pronouncing the name correctly?
- Yes.
- Those Dutch don't make it easy, do they?
- It's Polish.
I know, but I just have
a thing about the Dutch.
The interview was
conducted at his home
- in Silver Spring, Maryland?
- Yes.
Every four years, we give these guys
a gold medal in flukentot
when they grew up having
to flukentot to school.
- Who?
- The Dutch.
- I'm Dutch.
- Well, then fuck you.
Look, it's not like I don't know
what this is gonna be about
and I also understand
the strategy
of trying to rattle someone
before an interview.
That's not what I'm doing.
I'm trying to see
if you laugh anymore.
I make these guys laugh
all the time.
Don't I?
I crack these guys up.
I am known as a funny lawyer.
You should check me out.
I have checked you out,
Rebecca,
and you don't handle
wrongful termination suits.
- You're a First Amendment lawyer.
- I am.
And I haven't read the other ones yet,
but they're on the list.
Well, I'd like to
once and for all
abudiate the notion
that I am messed up.
- Once and for all.
- I understand.
- Thank you.
- But I'm gonna challenge you on abudiate.
- Yeah, there's no such word.
- Then why'd you use it?
Because I am funny, too.
We are going to expel
or dismiss or expunge
the notion that I am damaged.
I'm hardly the only person in my newsroom
who's ever seen a dead guy.
And that part of this case
would be hanging on my--
- I don't know what to call it.
- State of mind.
Seriously, that part of this case
would be hanging on my state of mind
six months later, by the way,
when we interviewed Stomtonovich...
- Dutch son of a bitch.
- ...is insane.
- I'm not kidding.
- I know.
I'm here to help you abudiate.
- That's what we're doing this morning.
- Okay.
So you're gonna
have to tell me about Africa.
The fact that you're even asking
implies that it's relevant.
The fact that it's in Jerry Dantana's affidavit
implies it is relevant.
He says that you were on prescription medications
when you came back from Africa,
probably a series of SSRis,
- serotonin reuptake inhibitors.
- I wasn't.
And that you're in no position
- to say whether Stomtonovich said...
- It happened.
- ...it happened.
- He didn't say it.
What I would do if I were them
is I would put you in front of a jury
and I would make you
tell the Africa story
and I would be good and sure
that you broke down while you were telling it.
They're free to try.
Well, I'd like to get a first look at
how it's gonna go.
Gary Cooper and I
flew to Uganda.
Is his name really Gary Cooper?
Yes.
Oh, I laugh
every time I read that.
I can't wait to meet him.
Why did you fly to Uganda?
I pitched a story about
the hundred US combat troops
that were sent to hunt
for Joseph Kony,
who's the leader of
the Lord's Resistance Army.
In exchange for access
to Camp Kasenyi,
which is our forward
operating base out of Kampala,
the Pentagon's Public Affairs people
wanted us to shoot some film
of soldiers building
an addition onto an orphanage.
That's a sad project
when you think about it.
Yeah, I could fall apart
any second.
I wasn't baiting you.
When did you and Gary leave?
A year ago September.
The night of September 30.
How do you get to Uganda?
Practice.
You fly to Dubai
and get a connecting flight to Entebbe.
We left straight
from the newsroom right before--
Right before-- God,
right before Will
just murderlized
this woman from OWS.
Gary and I watched it
in the cab.
The new Fox News poll has the former
Massachusetts governor
back in the lead
with 23% of Republicans,
followed by Rick Perry with 19%
and 17% for Herman Cain,
reflecting a big boost
for the former Godfather's Pizza CEO.
On the other side of the break,
I'll have one of the early organizers
of the Occupy Wall Street
movement.
- We'll be right back.
- Three minutes back.
- We're leaving.
- Souvenirs, let's go. Shout them out.
I would like any traditional
tribal weapon--
Short spears, hooks,
sticks, bows.
They're not gonna let them pass security
with short spears.
And I'll have an intern
get you local sticks.
- Who's next?
- A silk kaznu.
- That's a colorful wrap dress.
- Yeah.
Got about
two and a half minutes.
I got a lot of friends
who think this is a bad idea.
- How many?
- I don't know, a lot.
It's just that
it's a unit of measurement
I hear invoked more and more.
"A lot of my friends."
Mainstream media's been making us
look like idiots since this thing started.
Don't refer to the mainstream
media out there.
It always sounds like a losing team
complaining about the ref.
'Cause that's what
you always make it sound like.
Excuse me one second.
Two minutes.
We've spidered
every social networking site
and public board
looking for Hamni8.
We've sent an e-mail to Hamni8
at every public domain,
including the ISPs
most likely to service that region.
We've got some bounce backs,
but no responses.
We're out of here.
What's going on?
Late Wednesday night,
they found a tweet
from a user in the area,
Hamni8.
A fast series of tweets
where he describes Genoa.
- We think he's describing Genoa.
- He is describing it.
- Jesus.
- He's dead.
- We don't know that.
- What's the other option?
- That he can't afford his cell plan anymore.
- Come on--
In most of the developing world,
phones and plans are extremely expensive
relative to income, and almost all are prepaid.
This was two years ago.
He's standing there describing gas
being dropped on a village.
Then the tweets stop and you think
it's because his cell plan ran out?
Maybe they stopped then because
we were jamming their frequency.
- I'm saying it's years later.
- Fuck!
- It's just gone.
- I need to get Shelly.
It's time.
What do we do now?
Something's got to fall
into our lap.
Something's got to fall out of the sky
and right into our lap.
A preposterous stroke of luck
has to occur.
Neal, I meant to tell you.
A guy down at OWS
was telling a campfire story
about working for an NGO
and getting the NGO shut down
by the Pakistani government
because he wrote a report
saying US troops
used chemical weapons on civilians.
You should talk to him.
You can just follow me, okay?
- Wait, what?
- Did that just--
Shelly, wait!
Stop!
- What did you say?
- The Pakistani shut down the NGO.
- She needs to be in the studio.
- No. What was the reason?
He wrote a report that said US troops
were using chemical weapons.
- What's his name?
- I don't know.
Does he tend to hang out
in the same place
- in Zucotti Park every night?
- We are not hanging out.
- Neal.
- I understand.
Yes, he's in the same place
every night.
- Yes, I can take you there.
- Take her to the studio.
This way.
Okay. Okay.
30 seconds back.
And here comes dinner.
- How you doing?
- Good, thank you.
- Yeah, I got it.
- I'm sorry?
I was talking to my producer.
- How do I look?
- Good.
No, producer again.
- Is he just screwing with her?
- Mm-hmm.
- Come on.
- In three, two...
It's been two weeks
since a group of protesters
began camping out
in Zucotti Park here in New York City.
The Occupy Wall Street movement
has turned to social media
and held marches through the streets of
the financial district.
Here in the studio today
is one of the leaders
of Occupy Wall Street,
Shelly Wexler.
- Don't take the bait.
- Shelly, thanks for being with us.
It's good to be here,
but I am not one of the leaders of OWS.
- We don't have leaders.
- Is that a good idea?
- Not having leaders?
- Yeah.
Yes, because this way,
everyone's sure to have a voice.
Sounds like a lot of people
talking at once.
But tell us in a few words
what OWS is protesting.
We are protesting
a variety of issues--
The co-opting of the government
by the rich,
the lack of any prosecution
for the crimes
that led to
the collapse of 2008,
Citizens United,
social inequality.
So not any particular thing?
Not one particular thing.
You're protesting
against lots of things?
The list of things
we're protesting against
is as varied
as the protesters themselves.
I've seen protesters holding signs that say,
"We are the 99%."
- Yes.
- I am the 1%.
Some people would say I'm overpaid,
but I'm not.
I'm paid exactly
what the market will bear,
which means I'm paid
what I'm worth.
So which system would you
replace capitalism with?
We wouldn't--
I wouldn't replace it with any system.
I would make the system fairer.
- By passing new laws?
- Yes.
- It's Congress who does that.
It's legislation like Dodd-Frank
that the banks really fear, right?
Yes.
If your congressman
or your senator
or the Chairman of the House
Financial Services Committee
or the Speaker of the House
wanted to hear the demands
of OWS,
who would they meet with?
We're not looking
for a meeting.
- They wouldn't be able to meet with anyone, right?
- Look--
I'm trying to find the virtue
of a leaderless movement
where everyone's
voices are heard.
That isn't the point.
We want everyone to look
at Occupy Wall Street
and ask themselves the question,
"Why is this happening?"
I think that's
been taken care of.
But what happens after
people ask themselves that?
- Change, we hope.
- How?
The same way change
has always happened.
What is your best-case scenario
for how this ends?
- That it doesn't end.
- Oh, God.
- That it doesn't end?
- That's right.
Even if you put the heads
of the banks in jail,
overturn a Supreme
Court decision,
ensure greater social equality
and give everybody money,
you're still going to be
sleeping in Zucotti Park?
Like most of the media,
I don't think you're taking this seriously.
Is there any chance
that's because you're not?
- Hey, it didn't go that badly.
- Fuck off!
- Come on.
- I am humiliated and in shock.
This whole thing is messed up
and he's a fucking asshole,
by the way.
- He's not.
- Trying to be funny at the expense of the guest.
I don't think it was
as bad as you think.
Which way do I go
to get out of here?
- You need to take me to the guy.
- What?
- The guy in the park.
- You think I'm disposed to doing you a favor?
No, Shelly.
Shelly, we need to meet this guy.
- We need to read the report he wrote.
- No.
- Shelly.
- Forget it.
No, I can't tell you
what this is about,
but it's way too important
to use as a payback--
I could have gone anywhere.
I did this as a favor to you.
I need you to take me
to this guy.
Then we're both
having a bad night.
He didn't do anything to you.
You tanked.
She's gone.
Good evening.
Welcome to the Radisson Concord.
We're with the Romney Press Corps.
Three rooms under James Harper,
Hallie Shea and...
You know what?
I don't know your first name.
- I'm sorry.
- Stillman's my first name.
- Stillman's your first name?
- Yeah.
- What's your last name?
- Frank.
You sure it's not
the other way around?
It's three rooms.
Harper, Frank, and Shea.
I'm sorry,
I'm not seeing anything.
You said you were
with the Romney bus?
Yeah.
The Romney Press Corps
is all checked in.
Mm-hmm.
I understand what's happened.
- We got off the Romney bus.
- Oh, 'cause you said you were--
Yeah, we're still covering the campaign,
we're just--
It's not--
We're staging a protest.
I don't want to bore you
with the details.
It has to do with accountability
and access and just--
So we got off the bus
and now I understand
that the campaign
isn't going to be arranging our hotel.
Does that make sense?
- No, you should explain it some more.
- So we'll need three rooms.
I'm sorry.
We're very full with the campaign staff
and the press.
I'm showing I have one room.
That was a predictable plot twist,
don't you think?
Hey, guys.
What do you say, Slim Jim?
- Checking in.
- I thought you said the press was checked in.
The press that's on the bus,
the press we're responsible for.
- Ah, not the freedom riders.
- We have a room.
- I have seven rooms.
- Of course.
Six of which I'm willing to rent out
to anyone who says, "Romney rocks."
I'll say "Romney rocks" if you give me
30 minutes with the candidate.
Why do you keep asking when you know
the answer is going to be no?
So I can say I kept asking.
I hate the press in ways
you can't even comprehend.
- I can comprehend the ways.
- And hating the press
is an excellent credential
for a press officer.
We'll be in the bar
or on our half-empty floor.
Two queen beds?
- Can we get a cot?
- Absolutely.
- And some walls?
- It's one night.
- I call the cot.
- Got it.
These things aren't supposed to happen to me.
I went to Vassar.
- Did you like it?
- Yeah.
And Vassar versa, I'm sure.
How long you been keeping
that one in your pocket?
A while.
_
My friend's plane is about
to take off for Uganda.
Why is she going to Africa?
He. A guy named
Gary Cooper.
New York to Dubai to Entebbe.
- Yeah.
- Emirates first class.
It's like flying
in the Bellagio.
So you have a comprehensive
understanding of our operating budget.
- I'm just saying.
- Talent and EPs fly first class,
senior producers fly business,
and Gary and I get
duct-taped to the wing.
What time did you
land in Entebbe?
Around 8:00 A.M.
local time.
We were picked up
by a fixer named Ronald.
He works for ACN?
We don't have
a bureau in Africa.
He's freelance.
He works for National
Geographic Channel,
The Amazing Race,
that kind of thing.
The Army doesn't trust us much,
so before we could go to the base in Kasenyi,
we had to go to the orphanage,
which was in the Nakapiripirit District
in the Karamoja region.
Excuse me,
how do you spell Nakapiripirit?
Two As and four Is.
It's a four-to-nine
hour drive
depending on the condition
of the roads.
What condition
could the roads possibly be
that the drive time
fluctuates four to nine hours?
Sometimes there's mud.
Sometimes there's a genocide.
But there wasn't much
of either that day,
so we got there
by early afternoon.
Gary rode in back for 100 miles
'cause Ronald told him
he was gonna see drug lords.
Drug lords?
You're an idiot.
There were no drug lords.
And I didn't see one animal
I haven't seen in my apartment.
We were met
by Lt. Bill Casey,
the Community Relations Coordinator
for the 490th Civil Affairs Battalion.
Bill Casey.
I'm the Community Relations Coordinator
- for the 490th Civil Affairs Battalion.
- Maggie Jordan.
Gary Cooper.
Nice to meet you, Lieutenant.
Is your name really Gary Cooper?
You'd think I'd have gotten
tired of that by now.
We didn't have that much time.
We just wanted
to get it over with,
so Gary started getting
B-roll of the soldiers.
Kids here have either
lost their families
to regional conflicts,
HIV/AIDS, malaria.
This project lets us give
the kids medical checkups,
books, textbooks.
Right now
they've got two rooms--
A classroom
and a living quarters.
We're building another
two rooms here today.
One of the things
they have there are cattle raiders.
- Cattle raiders?
- Yeah.
They're heavily armed,
usually with AK-47s,
and they come
and steal your cattle.
And then rape and kill people.
After we'd gotten enough film on the soldiers,
we went inside.
- Asia!
- Good.
- South America!
- North America!
- Excellent!
Antarctica!
That's where I'm from.
I'm Pastor Moses.
You must be Maggie Jordan.
- Yes, sir.
- The children are learning geography.
Don't let me stop you.
- No. No, no, no!
- They think the camera's a gun.
- Put the camera down.
- Children.
It's okay. Shh, it's okay.
And they thought
you were cattle raiders?
Yeah.
And that's it?
That's what happened?
- I'm sorry?
- That's what happened?
No.
- What?
- Friday night, the woman from OWS--
- Shelly Wexler.
- She said there's a guy at Zucotti Park
who wrote a report
for an NGO in Pakistan
that got the NGO shut down
by the Pakistani government.
The report was about
the US using chemical weapons.
You didn't get the name of the guy
who wrote the report?
She doesn't know the name of the guy,
only where he hangs out in the park.
You should have got her to
take you there after she was done.
Well, that was the idea,
but then after the interview with Will,
she was angry and bolted.
- How angry?
- She punched me in the stomach.
She's probably
calmed down by now.
I called her all weekend
and she's willing to negotiate.
- We're not paying her.
- She doesn't want money.
- She wants an apology.
- Apologize.
First of all, I did.
Second, she doesn't want the apology from me.
And third, she punched me
in the stomach really hard.
Who does she want
the apology from?
- Will.
- Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
- On air.
- She wants an on-air apology from Will?
- Yeah.
- That's insane.
- She found him smug.
- Me, too.
- He wouldn't have to mean it or anything.
- Forget it.
This is it.
The trail is cold after this.
Couldn't you maybe convince him
to take one for the team?
Will is not aware of Genoa.
Do you mind if I ask why not?
- Because.
- Because?
Because I might need him
for the red team.
- So you believe it?
- No, I--
No, it's just--
Look, it's a completely
unbelievable story,
but I can't ignore evidence.
It's not like I'm in Congress.
If you believe it enough
to be thinking about a red team,
you believe it enough.
You have to talk to Will.
How'd you lose a bus, Jim?
It's a bus.
It's big and it's slow.
And it's a bus.
You let a big bus get away.
- This is a nice picture of her.
- Who?
Maggie.
I shouldn't have
turned around to look.
- Mm-hmm.
- Everybody all right?
I'm good.
That's me.
You paired your phone
to the car?
I got here first.
- Hello?
- Hallie, what the hell is going on?
Why is everybody but us
writing about the job speech
Romney's gonna give
in Las Vegas?
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry, Evan.
The rest of the press corps
got an advanced copy.
- Why didn't you?
- I wasn't on the bus.
You said this stunt wasn't
gonna fuck anything up.
- It won't.
- It just did.
I'm at all the campaign stops
and I'll be in Vegas
for the speech.
But everybody else
got an advanced copy
and they're writing about it.
We look like we're
doing this from home.
We've got something they don't.
- What?
- Guts.
I couldn't be less in the mood
for you to be a wiseass, Hallie.
I'm giving you $500
a week plus expenses.
To be fair, you're not giving it to me.
You're paying it to me.
No, if I don't get something back,
I'm giving it to you.
So unless you want to put on heels
and fuck me for an hour,
you need to stop being
a little bitch.
- Yeah.
- Tell me if you can't do this
- so I can find someone who can.
- No.
No, I can do this.
You left The Denver Post
for that?
Feel free to be superior.
He doesn't set
the bar very high.
The world's first fat tax
was announced in Denmark.
- That's mean.
- How?
Taxing people
who are overweight?
No, imbecile.
It's not a tax on people.
It's a tax on saturated fat.
But you're right,
that would have been mean.
About an hour ago
on Fox and Friends,
Hank Williams Jr. compared Boehner
and Obama playing golf
to Hitler and Netanyahu
playing golf.
Tell me something
and tell it to me straight.
Who is Hank Williams Jr.?
He was a country music star
until about an hour ago.
"Pentagon has decided military chaplains
may now perform oral sex."
What?
Give me my real rundown.
Idiots.
"The Pentagon has decided
military chaplains
may now perform
same-sex marriages."
And, Kendra, I apologize,
but the Washington Post
reported last night
that Rick Perry
leases a hunting ranch
called Niggerhead.
I accept your apology on behalf
of all the black people
in the room.
- I get that that was a thinly veiled--
- It wasn't veiled.
Okay. "Obama defends loan to Solyndra,
calling it a good--"
Stop doing that!
Good morning.
What happened with
the tweet from Hamni8?
They can't find Hamni8.
But something else happened.
The woman from OWS
who was on Friday night--
- Has murdered Will?
- She's not happy.
And that's relevant
because she says that a guy
who hangs out in her area
at Zucotti Park
has mentioned a report he wrote
for an NGO in Pakistan
about us using
chemical weapons.
She was gonna lead Neal and Jerry there
after the show, but then--
- She met Will.
- Yeah.
- Well, fix that.
- How?
You put a help wanted ad
in the paper
- for someone who can do your job.
- Good. Anything else?
- I just want to know that it didn't happen.
- That's not easy to do.
You should include in the ad that applicants
need to able to do hard things.
- Got it.
- When's Jim coming back from New Hampshire?
- Soon.
- He gets paid way too much for an embed.
Do you know what we pay embeds?
Some weeks it's in coupons.
I'll see you later.
Kendra, run the meeting.
I'll be back in a minute.
Okay.
Good morning.
- Hi.
- So, great news.
Let me tell you
something about liberals.
He didn't paint
the word on the rock.
His father didn't paint
And the word was painted over
after his family leased the ranch.
You're absolutely right
and that's a good point.
But I wanted to talk to you about--
What does that have to do with liberals?
You all should be asking yourselves
if you're condemning him
because he's from the South
and this is a good way
to distance yourselves
from our shared heritage.
Let's talk for a second about
unintended consequences.
- Sure.
- The woman we had on Friday night,
- from OWS, Shelly Wexler...
- Yeah.
Would you be willing
to apologize to her?
- Sure.
- On air?
- Absolutely.
- So no?
What were the consequences?
Jerry's been chasing a story
for a few weeks
- and I'm not gonna tell you what it is.
- Why?
If I tell you the reason,
you'll be more curious about the story.
But now I'm more curious
about the reason.
There's some evidence
to suggest
that the Army is thinking about having
different uniforms
for home and away games.
I don't believe
that's really the story.
At some point,
I might need you for the red team.
You could have just said that.
I understand that.
- I'm not a child.
- Okay.
- You have to tell me what the story is.
- No!
At least tell me how it relates to
the woman from OWS.
She can lead us to someone
who might be able to help,
but she won't
unless you apologize.
Her movement is idiotic
and she's unprepared.
So as a courtesy,
I was dismissive.
What does she want
an apology for?
- Being smug.
- That-- Really?
I know. I've never heard anybody
say that about you before
and I certainly can't
identify personally.
You're just chock-full of beans today,
aren't you?
So that's a hard no
on apologizing?
I was asked to ask.
Come in.
- Hey, how was your weekend?
- It was good.
It was good and then
I saw Titanic for the first time.
You'd never seen it before?
You know how I am
about sad movies
and the title suggested
it wasn't gonna end well.
But I still
didn't see it coming.
Mac, what is more important
than the people you--
Kodak is dropping
like a sack of flour.
I'll never let go, Kodak.
I'll never let go.
But people should really sell their stock
in Kodak because by this afternoon--
- I need you.
- That's all you ever have to say.
- Get it together.
- Yeah, all right.
The woman we had on
from OWS Friday night
- thought she was mistreated.
- She was.
And it's possible that she can
lead us to information
that can help with a story
I can't tell you about yet.
But to do that,
we have to make her happy.
- How can I help?
- Neal's gonna set up a meeting.
And you're gonna--
You're just gonna make her feel
like she's being heard
by a financial expert.
You're Sloan Sabbith
and you went to meet her.
- Just lather it on.
- Got it.
Whatever she says,
you couldn't agree with more.
I'm gonna lather up just to
honor the memory of Jack Dawson.
- From the boat?
- Yeah.
Okay, but it's not lather up,
it's--
Don't worry about it.
Talk to Neal.
Will McAvoy is an asshole.
I know how you feel.
But the thing is, he's not.
You had a rough time.
That's okay.
You've got information
that you don't realize
could help Neal and his team
with a story I'm certain--
Certain you'd want told.
- What's the story?
- I shouldn't have said that,
because I don't have
the first idea what the story is.
What the fuck
is with you people?
She doesn't know
what the story is by design.
On a big story, you want to bring in
some people at the end
and run everything by fresh eyes
and let them try to punch holes in it.
They're called the red team.
When's your story
supposed to air?
This?
Probably never.
You know,
I teach three classes on Mondays.
I came up here.
I'm supposed to be impressed?
- No one's trying to impress you.
- Yes, you are.
Because here's what happened.
This woman's here
at Shake Shack
because someone asked
Will to apologize and Will said no.
Do you see how things are worse
than they were before?
'Cause before you could assume
that no one ever asked Will,
and now it's pretty clear
that because of the story,
he was asked.
- You guys didn't think this through.
- No.
This is exactly
why we need a red team.
Shelly, can we just say
that we're honestly very sorry
- that appearing on ACN was an unpleasant experience?
- Please, no.
Your apology,
which was meaningless in the first place,
is now just a symbol
of the other guy's refusal to apologize.
This is getting a little nutty.
Shelly, can you just tell Neal
what he needs to know?
And I am supposed
to be impressed
'cause here comes your money honey
all solicitous.
- Hey! I can hear you.
- Like I'm a fucking rube
who's never seen a TV star before
or who would even care.
- Listen. Wait.
- I teach college.
Hang on. Let me ask you something
and I'd like an honest answer.
Sure.
- Do you really think I'm a TV star?
- You know...
You called me a money honey
and I made a self-deprecating joke.
I didn't do it in front of a million and a half people
and this isn't a joke to me.
I've got to leave.
You guys are condescending.
Really?
'Cause I'm pretty sure I wasn't just the one
who distinguished myself from rubes by saying,
"I teach college."
Did Will say no
when someone said,
"We need you to apologize
to Shelly Wexler.
We badly need you
to apologize"?
I wasn't in the room,
but I'm sure he said,
"Hell, no, and who the fuck
is Shelly Wexler?"
Well, now you know
how much of a prick he is.
Yeah.
No.
Sloan was smug.
So there was this kid
named Daniel
who was by himself
the whole time.
Who's he?
That's Daniel.
His parents are both alive.
I'm a family friend.
His father has a lot of cattle
and there have been some clashes
with Pokot raiders from Kenya.
So Daniel's here
to be safe for a few days.
I started talking to him.
Do you want me to read
that book to you?
I'm not gonna take it.
You can hold it and be the page-turner
and I'll just read it.
Come on.
Scoot over.
"This is the house.
The house on East 88th Street.
Mr. and Mrs. Primm
and their son Joshua
live in the house
on East 88th Street."
I read it to him maybe
three times.
- Again.
- Okay.
- Three times.
- Again.
We've read it seven times now.
That's a lot of trust, Daniel.
All right, one more.
"But if Lyle was happy,
he was making someone else unhappy.
Perfectly miserable, in fact.
That someone else
was Loretta."
"The house
on East 88th Street."
"...the voice called out.
Lyle recognized the voice."
"Have you seen
a crocodile going past?
He was wearing
a red scarf."
"If Lyle was happy,
he was making someone else unhappy."
"I have no information
about a crocodile wearing a red..."
Scarf.
"There was little they could do,
at least for the moment,
to prevent Mr. Grumps
from putting Lyle in the zoo."
He's never seen
hair like yours.
That color's called blonde,
Daniel,
and it's nothing but trouble.
Maggie.
Ronald.
- Yeah?
- Time to go.
No, we can't drive
these roads at night.
- It's not night.
- It will be.
When were you gonna tell us
we couldn't drive back?
I just did.
- Lt. Casey.
- Yes, ma'am?
Could we possibly get a ride back
with you guys?
- We're flying out.
- Even better.
We're going to Djibouti.
Is that near where we're going?
No.
You're not a great fixer,
you know that?
I don't know how The Amazing Race
is as amazing as it is.
Again.
I don't really
understand your reasons
for not being on the campaign,
but I'm going to have to insist
that you at least be near
the campaign.
I am. Everybody's here.
I'm making all the stops,
or at least the ones
I can MapQuest.
You can't just follow the bus?
They're making
really fast buses now.
Do me a favor.
- Romney gave a statement.
- Yeah?
He called the name
of the ranch offensive.
He should be asked
about the church.
Can you get a comment
from someone?
On that?
I doubt it.
Try hard. Charlie doesn't know
what you're doing there.
All right.
- Taylor.
- Jim.
- I need to ask--
- How was your day?
Fine, thanks.
I need to ask
about the governor's response
to Rick Perry's ranch.
There was a statement
in this morning's e-mail,
which you don't get,
so you're free to watch TV.
I know he said he thought
it was offensive.
He does and that is the official comment
of the Romney campaign.
And now we are going
back to business,
which for me
is a glass of red wine right now.
He was a leader in his church
in 1977, right?
Do you think I'm gonna talk about
the Mormon Church?
By commenting on the Perry ranch
you already have
because it wasn't until 1978
that Mormons allowed Mormons to be black.
People of faith
are also people of free will
and they are able to disagree
with their church on a number of issues.
The governor was one
of the leaders of his church.
- Did he ever object--
- And Joe Biden is Catholic.
Catholics don't allow
women to be priests.
Is Joe fighting a war on women?
Is that the official comment
of the Romney campaign?
You know,
go fuck yourself, Jim.
That is the official comment
of the Romney campaign.
All right.
All right,
just tell me what you need
to forget I said that.
You're gonna have
a 30-minute one-on-one
with the governor
tonight at 10:00.
Thanks.
I, too, believe Will and Sloan
can be a little smug
and I think you guys are
showing a lot of wisdom
by having me
be the one to fix it.
You were really
the only one left.
- The only guy for the job.
- The only one left.
- The only one who can get it done.
- There was nobody else.
- Nobody but me.
- Left in the office.
- One man--
- There she is. Hey, Shell.
I have another class
from 8:00 to 10:00
and this is my only break and I don't want to
spend that much of it with you,
so let's get this over with.
This is Don Keefer.
I'm the executive producer
of our 10:00 hour
Right Now With Elliot Hirsch
and I'll give you a segment.
It'll be a much
gentler interview.
And if I came on
Elliot Hirsch's show,
would I be able to talk
about my treatment?
The treatment OWS got
during the first interview?
You'd be able
to talk about OWS,
but I can't produce your revenge fantasy
if that's what you're asking.
- Please stop arranging meetings.
- Just listen to what--
- It's a very important story.
- Do you know what the story is?
- I don't, but I know it's important.
- How?
- Because Neal says it is.
- And when you say it's important,
what you really mean is that
it's more important than OWS.
- We apologize for anything--
- "We" don't apologize.
- Many of us do.
- Bye.
Oh, Shelly, please take Neal to see
the guy in Zucotti Park.
Let this serve as
electroshock therapy.
Every time you want
to look down your nose at someone--
Maybe we're not the ones
who need therapy.
Maybe your debilitating
persecution complex could be,
if not cured, then put in remission by
a team of Viennese specialists.
Anything else?
- Nope.
- Wait.
I shouldn't have said
that last thing.
Psst.
- Me?
- I'm killing it.
You know why?
Vassar.
Kaboom.
Sorry.
Can you make it fast?
'Cause I'm a little on fire.
There's no signal
in the hallway.
Hey, Mac.
Just one second.
They're stepping out.
Taylor just called me.
Did you give away an interview with Romney?
If you could give me just a second.
I don't have the room yet.
You know exactly
how fucked up it is that you gave it away.
And that you gave it
to a girl you like.
It's not exactly like that,
but it was definitely wrong
and I apologize
and I'll call Will.
- Don't call Will.
- If he finds out another way--
I'll take that chance.
I don't know how to predict his behavior anymore.
Or yours.
And now I've got
to pull you off.
I understand.
Well, you know, I don't.
Her boss--
Here are my notes.
You write it.
I caught Taylor in
an on-the-record moment I could trade
and you were in trouble
with your boss.
And, frankly,
I didn't like him.
It must save you
a lot of time to be able
- to reach that conclusion in 15 seconds.
- It does.
- But he happens to be a genius.
- Okay.
And either you don't know
or don't care
how insulting
your favor was to me,
but it's either
one or the other.
I'm experienced at this, Jim.
More experienced than you.
I got you on the bus.
And then, unbelievably,
- you got us off the bus.
- Yeah.
Yeah, and since you don't know what the hell
you're talking about anyway,
you shouldn't make
a giant assumption that is totally wrong
about my personal life
or my professional life.
Every-- Both of them.
It was the second one.
It was that I didn't care.
- How insulting it was?
- Yeah.
'Cause but for a couple things
that I didn't foresee,
you wouldn't have found out.
What the hell?
Am I suddenly
a fucking receptacle
for every woman
who's pissed at a guy?
I did a fast calculation
and it was unlikely
he was gonna break news
or be interviewed on camera,
so I didn't think I was
robbing my network of much.
You didn't need it and I did?
In that call from your boss,
your--
- I don't know what to call him.
- Evan.
I've always--
I hate that name.
I did it because I wanted to.
Everything about it felt right.
But if it was insulting,
I still don't care.
I'm going downstairs.
Yeah, I always hated
the name Evan, too.
I'm talking about a plan.
This plan has come to symbolize
the struggle
for justice in India.
Proponents claim
that it is urgently needed development.
And opponents claim
that it will disrupt
underprivileged communities
and service the wealthy few.
What plan am I talking about?
Narmada Dams!
Excuse me.
I'm right.
It's the Narmada Dams.
I can't believe what it takes
to get you to apologize.
I have absolutely no intention
of apologizing.
But you should enjoy me
while I'm here,
'cause as soon as I leave,
so does the attention.
Your movement sucks, Shelly.
I'm sure it looks that way
from the outside.
And right there is your problem,
'cause who the fuck cares
what it looks like
from the inside?
Slavery, suffrage,
civil rights, Vietnam--
What all those things have in common
is there were leaders.
And the only thing the leaders cared about
was getting it done.
And if you guys had leaders
who could find a map with a fuckin' map,
they'd tell you the thing about capitalism is
it's politically accountable.
Did you watch my show tonight?
Did you see anybody
courting the OWS vote?
'Cause all eight candidates
for the Republican nomination
said the words
"Tea Party" today
in a bite they knew
would get picked up.
We're not trying
to get anyone elected.
We're just trying to point
so that people will look.
And you're looking at us
and not what we're pointing at.
I was terrible on the show.
I was embarrassed
in front of my friends
and my students
and the people in my area
at Zucotti Park.
If you had to slap me around,
couldn't we at least have talked about corruption,
financial crimes,
predatory lending,
unlimited campaign donations?
You're not qualified
to talk about those things on our show.
But, yes, I could talk about
those things more on our show.
I slapped you around
to burnish my reputation as a moderate.
You were a handy prop
and I'm sorry I embarrassed you.
I'm not smug.
I'm having a crisis
of confidence.
That's a pretty
startling admission.
I don't have that many
people to talk to.
- That's ironic.
- I know.
- You're not married?
- No.
- Girlfriend?
- Well...
No.
What was the "well"?
Hmm.
I'll take Neal to where
the guy usually is.
- We found him already. We tracked him down.
- Are you for real?
The interview was fun for me
and it shouldn't have been.
Well, you know what
my mother would say?
I absolutely do not.
Who are you really mad at?
You really want to tug
at that thread?
I wouldn't be surprised
if it has something to do with the "well."
Can I audit the rest
of your class?
- It's almost over.
- Perfect.
...as she sought exoneration
in the murder of her college
roommate in Italy.
And tomorrow morning,
nearly four years after her initial detainment,
Amanda Knox will fly back
to her hometown of Seattle.
- Go.
- 77 up.
- Got that locked.
- Ready 77.
...as the Washington Post
reported over the weekend
that Perry's family ranch,
where the presidential hopeful
has hunted with his family
and friends
and to which he has invited lawmakers,
has a name,
and that name is Niggerhead.
What the hell, fellas?!
- You want to take it?
- No.
- All right, well, Elliot wrote the copy.
- Oh, fuck you.
- You approved the copy.
- And I approved.
I don't know how to tell the story
without saying the name.
Bullshit.
You say the N-word.
N-wordhead Ranch?
Something like that.
What did everybody else do?
- They bit around it.
- Don Lemon said it.
- Don Lemon's black.
- Yeah, I don't know these rules.
The story is about the word
and we decided not to play
a game of Hangman
with the audience.
N-head Ranch?
Is there a G?
Shut up.
What if it said
Motherfucker on the rock?
It would be
a much different story
and one a lot harder to
get to the bottom of.
Would you wait for me a minute?
Because that's how long
it's gonna take
before Reese calls
saying that the Family Foundation
for the Foundation of Families
is threatening to boycott
our advertisers
unless Elliot stops
being Jewish or something.
- Can I ask?
- What?
Other than that,
was it a good show?
- Get out.
- All right.
"Upon which was painted
a derogatory epithet for an African-American."
- I'm sorry, I nodded off while you were saying that.
- Get out!
- His name is Leon Deit.
- Deit?
Rhymes with beet.
We've been interviewing
him for about an hour and 20 minutes
and we're the first ones
who've spoken to him, though.
He doesn't know why we are.
He was working for the Commission for Human
Rights in Conflict Zones
out of Islamabad
and they sent him to interview
some people in Waziristan
who said they'd survived a raid
of what they say
were US military forces.
He wrote this report.
He believes that as a result
of this report,
his NGO was shut down.
Have you read it?
Name some signs a person
would exhibit if they'd been exposed to sarin gas.
Vomiting,
severe muscle twitches,
and then death by choking
on their own vomit.
Read what I've highlighted
on the third page.
"Villagers report
that many of the dead
seem to have aspirated
into their mouths...
and had been asphyxiated
by their own vomit."
Was it absolutely necessary
for you to tell my boss?
I wouldn't say
it was necessary,
but it was what anyone
would do in my job.
And the reason
you don't know that
is because you've never
done this before.
You know,
we're doing this thing, Jim.
We're running for president.
It's on.
And it's a big, hard thing
and we understand
that we're gonna have to do it
during a relentless onslaught
of absurd bullshit
from you and your friends.
It was just my way
of saying that
we're gonna be around
for a while.
Perry's done.
It's not the ranch
that's gonna get him.
It's his intellect.
Not the world's worst reason
for a Republican
candidate to lose.
I wonder if anyone's
gonna notice that.
I know I'm gonna see you
somewhere again before November.
Take it easy.
Take it easy, Taylor.
You were lying before.
About the fast
calculation you did.
It was a big deal.
I think you got in trouble.
You have to go back
to New York.
Yeah.
Well,
I don't like that.
It's all right
'cause I--
I'm the rebound.
And I went to Vassar.
I think that Vassar has
a really strong hold on you
'cause you seem to
have a lot of anxiety about living up--
What-- I should have
asked this an hour ago--
Are we counting as messed up?
What do I--
Here's what I'm asking.
What do I have to look like
for my testimony
about the interview with General Stomtonovich
to not be discounted?
The way you look right now.
Just the facts, ma'am.
We slept over at the orphanage.
Sometime--
I didn't look at my watch,
but the police report
said it was sometime after midnight--
- We heard some--
- I heard. Don't say we.
I heard a popping sound
in the distance.
Maybe 100 yards away.
Pop, pop.
What are they saying?
It's Lugisu.
There were gunshots.
Do you know Lugisu?
No.
Not in front of the kids.
Pastor Moses's wife Kissa
started quietly waking the kids
and keeping them calm,
making sure they didn't scream.
But then we heard another
pop, pop, pop.
Shh.
What is happening?
It's okay, child.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Ronald was trying to tell them
that this was an orphanage
and there wasn't any cattle.
But he was doing it in Luganda.
Ronald and Gary
flew back inside.
Get the children
on the bus right now.
Out the back on the bus,
head below the windows.
Where are we going?
We got the kids out the back door
and on the bus.
Seven, eight, nine,
10, 11,
12...
13, 14...
And Pastor Moses
did a head count.
Daniel?
What...
He was under my bed.
Daniel.
Come on.
We've got to go to the bus.
Daniel, please.
Come on, Daniel.
Please, come on.
The frame was maybe
six inches off the ground.
I don't know how
he got under there.
It's bolted to the floor.
Daniel, come on.
No, not the front.
Daniel.
Come on, Daniel.
Get back.
Be careful.
Come on, Daniel.
Come on.
Okay. Okay.
No, come on.
Here, get on my back.
Grab on here.
Okay.
They speak 1,944 languages
in Africa.
I've learned
some Luganda phrases,
but I didn't know any Lugisu.
I don't know where
the cattle bandits were from,
so once I got home,
it took me a while
to translate what
they'd been shouting.
It was
"Give us the camera."
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Again.
All right.
"This is the house.
The house on East 88th Street.
Mr. and Mrs. Primm--"
He died right away?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Okay. Okay.
I can't find a pulse.
His pupils are dilated.
There's no pulse.
Yeah, the hospital said
the bullet hit his spine.
And that's it?
That is it.
We never got to Kampala.
The company brought us back
'cause we had to be debriefed by HR.
Jim Harper, under oath,
is gonna testify
to your state of mind.
Is there anything
he'll be asked about?
Maggie?
You're back.
I read the HR report.
There's honestly
nothing to ask about.
It was upsetting.
I don't want to minimize it, but--
- Were you sent to a doctor?
- By HR.
- A psychiatrist?
- Yeah, and I'm fine.
The doctor prescribed Paxil,
but I don't take it.
- You don't?
- No.
A psychiatrist examined you
and prescribed a very strong psychotropic
that you're not taking?
I don't need it.
Oh, God, Maggie.
That's a terrible answer.
I was there.
It was Stomtonovich, Jerry, and me.
- He never said, "It happened."
- He said that you were in no--
They were there 'cause they spotted us
filming the engineers
and I pulled him out
from under the bed forcibly
and his spine ended up stopping a bullet
that was plainly gonna hit me,
so it's obviously something
I'm gonna remember, but...
you know...
What do you want?
He didn't say it.
I can testify to that.
I'm fine.
"There was little they could do,
at least for the moment,
to prevent Mr. Grumps
from putting Lyle in the zoo."
He's never seen
hair like yours.
That color is called blonde,
Daniel,
and it's nothing but trouble.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
I'm fine.
Fuck.
www.tvsubtitles.net