Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
And where are you from,
Mr. Brown?
Sheldon, sir.
I'm a retired police officer.
Well, then I can only imagine
that Sheldon must be
one of the safest places in this state.
We do our best.
But my son, he's a marine,
stationed at Camp Dwyer.
He keeps our country safer than I do.
Me and my wife were wondering,
if he got sent over to the Jordan
Valley, will that really keep us safer?
Because it sure seems like
the whole peacekeeping mission
is only making things more dangerous.
Thank you for that. May I?
Well, first of all, let me say how
grateful I am for your son's service.
I know we all feel exactly the same way.
And now, uh, let me try
to answer your question.
Have we run into some difficulties
with the Russians?
Yes, we have.
Is there tension between
the Israelis and the Palestinians?
Absolutely.
But, that is the very reason
that this mission is so important.
We have gathered together
a coalition of seven nations
to bring stability to a region
that has suffered
from unrest for decades.
It will take time.
And there may be lives
that will be lost.
But this is not just important
for the Middle East's security,
it's important for the security of the
United States and the rest of the world.
And I hope that I've
answered your question.
Now, who was next?
Uh, let's see here.
Well, how about
this young woman right here?
Now, I'll give you my microphone,
but only if you promise to give it back.
He seemed to want to hang
onto it for a while.
- There you are.
- Um, my name is Annie Wietz,
and I'm also worried
about what the officer was just saying.
- I want a safe world for my grandkids--
- Give me back the mic
- and I'll answer your question.
- I haven't asked my question yet.
Oh!
Apologies. I'm ahead of myself.
Go ahead.
The covert operation, the one
that caused the Israelis to invade.
Was that us? Because that really
seemed to make a mess of everything.
- May I?
- Please.
Thank you. Now, Annie?
- Is that your name, yeah?
- Yes, sir.
Now, I have said this
on this matter before,
and I know it may be frustrating,
but it is the truth.
When it comes to covert operations
by any nation,
or matters of intelligence,
for security purposes,
including the security
of our own soldiers,
I simply cannot comment on these issues.
But, sir, I'm sorry, but what is
the point of having us ask questions
- if you won't answer them?
- Well, she's got me there. Uh...
I can answer any question but that one.
In fact, I hope that we can
ask some questions
about how we're gonna focus
on things right here at home.
How about someone up there
in the cheap seats?
Anyone have a question there?
The situation in Jordan Valley,
it threatens to bleed across the border.
We already have refugees
requesting to enter Jordan.
Forgive me, Prince Ryad.
You may be dealing with
a few hundred refugees,
but we are facing mortar attacks.
Fourteen in the last two weeks.
None of your people have died yet.
The last one came
within 50 meters of a school.
Your troops have killed over
a dozen Palestinians in house raids.
- You expect us not to fight back?
- We need the violence to stop.
If it continues, the peacekeeping
mission will fall apart.
And it's our best hope
for long-term stability.
Can you speak to Hamas and Hezbollah?
Get them to agree to a cease-fire?
Israel has twice as many troops
in the region
as before the peacekeeping
mission began.
No, it is we who are defending ourselves.
You agreed to remove
two thousand troops.
If there's a cessation of mortar
attacks, and if the Russians leave.
A one-third troop reduction.
That should be enough
to convince your people, no?
Once the troops leave,
I engage them, but not before.
Show some goodwill.
You'll still have 4,000 troops there.
Because we cannot accomplish anything
unless we have proof
of de-escalation on both sides.
What about Russia?
That's a separate issue.
We will tackle that another time.
Can you convey to Jerusalem
the importance of this troop reduction?
Yes, but no promises.
All right. Thank you, everyone.
We'll meet again tomorrow morning.
Thank you, madam.
Eliana.
We need to discuss the no-fly zone.
It's only for the Russians,
not the peacekeepers.
They can't stay
if they have nothing to eat.
What are you going to do,
shoot down a supply plane?
We hope they won't make us
face that choice.
They'll ignore it.
And you're just going
to antagonize Moscow.
I'm sorry, but the no-fly zone
is above my pay grade.
Perhaps your husband can talk
to the prime minister.
When are we looking at?
Could be tomorrow, could be a week.
I'm not a part of those
conversations anymore.
We could vet the questions.
That doesn't work in Iowa.
It'll piss people off.
Even if we did,
it wouldn't make a difference.
The country is preoccupied with
the Jordan Valley. We're off message.
In the meantime, we can put the town
halls on hold. Just do the stump.
I think we should also
postpone the debate.
Dunbar'll hit you hard for that.
Say you're dodging.
Have Jackie request
the postponement.
- What's her reason?
- I don't care.
Just as long as it isn't coming from us.
Talk to her. Thank you, gentlemen.
What's next?
Uh, you're slated for fundraising calls
until 4:15, then a DOD briefing.
Also, your friend
from The Sentinel called, Tim Corbet.
Thank you.
You know, I can fold my own clothes.
Took me two seconds.
You remember when we
shared a room my senior year?
And if I left, like, one sock
on the floor, you'd freak?
Yeah, I started doing that on purpose,
just to see you flip out.
Yeah. I remember.
Come on, leave it.
Be a rebel.
Hey, sweetie.
Well, tell her if it wiggles,
it means it's gonna fall out.
Okay. Let me talk to her.
Hi!
Uh, now, listen to me. You--
I know your mom
doesn't want you playing with it,
so you have to do what she says.
Well, because the tooth fairy
doesn't want fingerprints all over it.
Okay, I'll do it,
but you have to promise me
that you and your brother
will stop playing with your tooth.
Okay, you ready?
Are you super ready?
Boogala, boogala, boogala,
boogala, boogala.
Okay. Put your mom back on.
How much of a postponement?
Until we get this crisis resolved.
Dunbar will see right through that.
Not if it's coming from you.
Say you want to focus on meeting people
face to face, not a televised debate.
We'll back you up.
All right, I'll talk to my staff.
We'll draft some language
and I'll run it past you.
Jackie?
I want to talk to you about
what happened a couple weeks ago.
- I crossed a line.
- Remy, you don't have to.
I want to. I want to explain myself.
I still have strong feelings,
I'm not gonna deny that.
Maybe a different job...
a different time, different place.
But, uh...
Look...
I've loved people before,
and I've learned to let 'em go.
I'm not gonna put you
in that position again.
It's been hard for me, too.
Hm...
You've got work.
I'm glad you said something.
Hello?
Tim, it's Frank.
I'm sorry it took me all day
to get back to you.
Ah, no worries.
Your plate must be pretty full.
Well, more than I'd like at the moment.
Is this a bad time?
I think I can spare a few minutes
for the President of the United States.
- Are you good?
- Yeah.
Good. Uh, last kid got off to college,
so Beth and I are on our own.
Finally. Yeah, the business is strong.
I'm actually, uh, I'm thinking
of expanding to Glenwood Canyon.
That's great.
Listen, I called because that, uh...
that writer reached out to me.
You know, the one doing your book.
Said, uh, he wanted to talk
about The Sentinel.
What'd you say?
I said I was in a rush
and I'd call him back later.
I didn't want to say more
without talking to you first.
Well, he should've checked
with me beforehand.
I don't want him harassing my friends.
He wasn't harassing me at all.
He's a nice guy, actually.
I mean, I'm happy to talk with him
if it'll help your book.
Well, the book isn't really
about The Sentinel,
so I don't know why he'd bother, but
I'll talk to him and I'll let you know.
Whatever you need, Mr. President.
Stop that.
Hey, listen, uh, we run a half-price
special for Commanders-in-Chief.
So, uh... if you're ever in Colorado
with some time on your hands...
Well, I hope the same goes
for ex-presidents, too.
Nope. Only sittin' ones.
So you better win that damn election.
I'll do my best.
Nice talking to you, Tim.
You too, Frank.
I want to set aside time
for Tom Yates, in person. Tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Francis?
I just got off the phone with Cathy.
The Israelis are
instituting the no-fly zone.
I'm scheduled to have a call tomorrow
with the prime minister.
They want to cancel the call.
Let me see if I can get him
on the phone now.
They just sent out a communiqué
to all embassies.
Good morning.
As you--
Excuse me.
It's been a long night.
Thank you.
Israel instituted a no-fly zone
over the Jordan Valley,
6:00 a.m. today, Israeli time.
And while I disagree with this action,
I understand the reason behind it,
and we must stand with our ally.
Our chief goal remains
de-escalation in the region.
Ambassador Underwood
and the State Department
are working with all interested
parties toward that end.
Our utmost priority
is guaranteeing civilian safety.
- And Israel has confirmed--
- When are you off to Des Moines?
A couple of hours.
I have to make some donor calls first.
You have surgery today?
A double bypass.
Triple tomorrow.
But nothing scheduled
for almost a week after,
so maybe I can come out
to Iowa and we can--
- Russian aircrafts that ignore this...
- What's going on?
...could potentially be subject
to military action...
This Jordan Valley thing's a mess.
He's in big trouble.
...any such actions...
And then there's the whole
AmWorks thing.
All the baggage from last year.
- You having doubts?
- I don't know.
Maybe.
That sounds serious.
If there was an ideal time
to walk away, now is it.
Mm-hm. And then what?
Focus on Congress.
Yeah, but you want more than that.
I could spend more time
with you and the kids.
Well, I don't want a wife
who's miserable
because she turned her back
on the White House.
Look...
The thing about surgery is,
once you're in, you're in.
There's a beating heart in front of you.
Someone's life.
There's no room for doubt.
So, whatever goes wrong...
say hemorrhage or a blood clot,
you deal with it.
You don't get to walk away.
But that's life or death.
This isn't.
It is for you.
...to maintain international peace
and security.
The United States is committed
to defusing this situation.
We are here for Israel,
we are here for Palestine,
we are here for Russia.
And we are here for--
- Ready to go to your meeting?
- Yeah.
Come on.
I was thinking...
you know how a while back, you mentioned
the kids coming out from Ohio?
You want them to visit?
Well, maybe you don't want them
to see me like this?
- Doing my 60 days?
- You've been doing great.
I'd be thrilled for them to come
out here and meet their uncle,
if that's something you want to do.
I could hit the couch for a few nights.
You guys can have the bedroom.
I'll call Sarah.
I say to Israel,
keep your airspace.
Keep your no-fly zone.
I will be flying through it, nevertheless.
Shoot me down, if you wish,
because nothing can stop me
from standing side by side
with my countrymen.
I will embrace the men
who serve this country,
because I am Russian,
and Russians... do not abandon their own.
Russian TV.
Forty-five minutes ago.
It could be hot air.
Petrov wants the world to see this.
He wouldn't put it out there
unless he meant it.
Israel says they're prepared
to enforce the no-fly zone.
They'll never shoot down
a head of state.
Yeah, which means they'll
lose face and compensate
by increasing their ground presence.
I got Jerusalem to agree to a pullout.
- Two thousand troops.
- Not if Petrov flies there.
If we downplay Petrov's move
as political theatrics,
I might be able to convince
the Israelis to follow through.
No, we need to respond
to Russia directly,
not waste our time with Israel.
Israel is our ally.
We're far more likely
to have a productive dialogue
with them than with Russia.
What's our main objective here?
To get Russian troops
out of the Jordan Valley.
Let's stop poking around from the sides.
We need to tackle this head on.
Open up a line of communication
with Moscow.
Tell them I'm coming
to the Jordan Valley myself.
Sir, I--
I'm gonna meet with Petrov face to face,
on the ground.
- Mr. President, the risk factors of--
- I'm well aware.
I want to be notified the moment
that Petrov is on his way.
You work with the CIA and DOD
to figure out any logistics
and security you have to.
Talk to Seth.
Let's start drafting our message.
Cathy, I want to sit down with you and
Defense, and work out bargaining chips.
Thank you all very much.
I meant now.
- I'm not to be disturbed.
- You have a meeting with Mr. Yates.
Have him wait and tell him
it might be a while.
Yes, sir.
You're on
with Ambassador Moryakov.
- Alexi?
- You're wasting your time, Claire.
We can't let Petrov go.
I'm powerless.
Then tell me who we can speak to
who can influence him.
His mind is made up.
No one would dare challenge him on this.
All right, then I'll come to New York.
Let's meet with Caspi.
We'll ease Jerusalem's fears together.
I can't.
I'm on my way to Washington.
- What for?
- The embassy sent for me.
I'm being recalled.
- Is it because...?
- I don't know.
Alexi, if you need anything--
The ambassador
has ended the call, Mrs. Underwood.
- Mrs. Underwood.
- Hello.
- Edward?
- Wait here a moment.
Yes, ma'am?
What's he doing here?
The president wanted to meet with him.
He asked me to have him wait upstairs.
- Thank you.
- Yes, ma'am.
If he wants the same terms
as we had before,
I'll smooth it over
with our NATO allies.
It's tough to lose Poland,
but I think that we can compensate
with anti-missile subs
on patrol here in the Finnish Sea.
- Thank you.
- Francis? Do you have a moment?
I'll be right back.
Give us a minute.
I think this is a mistake.
You're chasing him.
- Let me work with Israel.
- You've been working with Israel.
Now there's a no-fly zone.
One step forward, two steps back.
Diplomacy takes time.
Iowa is in two months.
You can't let the campaign drive
our foreign policy.
If I don't win in Iowa,
there is no foreign policy.
Excuse us, Mr. President.
Let's not talk out here.
If you go to the Jordan Valley,
you have to walk away with a solution.
And he knows that,
which means he gets all the leverage.
Well, it's not as if we have much
leverage at the moment.
He's going to want
the peacekeeping mission out.
That's right.
And the missile defense system, too.
And I'm prepared
to give him both if necessary.
What are you talking about?
Don't toss the mission aside, Francis.
Claire, you're too invested in this.
The mission is dead.
It was dead the moment
those troops got blown up.
Your plan failed. I'm sorry.
It's my fault. I approved it.
But now, I have to fix it.
Why won't you place faith
in a diplomatic solution?
This is diplomacy.
Sometimes it comes down
to two men in a room.
I have no faith in the UN anymore.
I do have faith in my ability
to negotiate with this man.
Francis, I know you value my opinion.
Absolutely, above all others.
We have both put a great deal of effort
and thought into how to handle Russia.
I'd like for this to be a decision
we make together,
instead of an impulsive response--
- Not right now.
- Petrov's in the air.
Get Admiral Dale on the line.
Claire, I value your opinion.
I just don't agree with it this time.
Mr. Yates.
The president's
gonna have to reschedule.
Thomas.
You give us a few moments, Edward?
Yes, ma'am. I'll be by the stairs.
How's the book coming?
I've hit a bit of a roadblock.
There's a big piece missing.
- What is it?
- You.
He hasn't... mentioned me at all?
Plenty of times, but...
it's not enough.
What has he said?
You're putting me in an awkward
position, Mrs. Underwood.
You don't want to betray his trust.
He and I have an agreement.
I understand. I shouldn't pry.
I'll leave you be, then.
He said he loves you more than anything.
That there wouldn't be
a White House without you.
He showed me your first house...
in Gaffney.
Where you planted the tulips.
And he said he was ashamed.
Of what?
That you married him.
Because you deserve better.
You should really be in this book,
Mrs. Underwood.
I've got a lot of stories
from his perspective.
Not a single one from yours.
Well, he's the one running
for president, not me.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I think people need
to hear your voice to hear his.
Can we set up a time to meet?
Um... I'll think about it.
Thank you, Thomas.
Mm-hm.
Okay.
Seth, this is good,
but downplay expectations even more.
There's no telling
what we'll walk away with.
- Yes, sir.
- We shouldn't inform the press
until after you land,
for security purposes.
Donald...
- If anything should happen to me--
- I'm prepared.
- But nothing will.
- God help us.
Danton will walk you
through the full brief.
Everything's set up in the Situation Room.
- Good luck, Mr. President.
- Thank you. I'll be right back.
Now, listen, I know you have
reservations about all this.
You're doing what you think is best.
Please be careful out there.
I will.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Let's go.
Hello?
- Hi!
- Hi.
Hello! Wow! You guys really look alike!
- Okay.
- Oh...
We're a hugging family.
I see.
Hi, you must be Francine.
- No, I'm not!
- She likes Franke better.
Oh. Nice to meet you, Franke.
- No.
- Yep.
- I told you!
- Careful.
It's your Uncle Doug.
Do you want to give
your Uncle Doug a hug?
Come here, you.
We'll land in Tel Aviv,
then take a special forces convoy from
there to the perimeter of the valley.
The Israelis will provide air support
until we get to the valley,
then our helos will take over.
Once we get to the camp,
the Russians insist on ground units only.
- We'll pass through a checkpoint--
- How secure is this location?
The position is not fortified
to our liking.
It's not blast-proof.
Sir, we're going to ask that
you wear your Kevlar and helmet.
- Sir?
- Mary.
- Why were no press allowed to go?
- Given the security situation,
we didn't want to put any press
in harm's way,
or risk any hostile elements
knowing in advance.
So the president has already landed?
About 90 minutes ago.
Mark.
What exactly does the president
hope to achieve?
Ideally, we'd like the Russians
to vacate the region.
We can't promise that they will.
But the president hopes that we can
make progress toward a withdrawal.
Kate.
This could be seen as an election stunt.
He's trailing Dunbar in the polls,
so he wants to save the day.
I guarantee you this is no stunt.
The president is taking extraordinary
measures to end this crisis.
Mr. President.
You can take your vest off now,
- We're safe here.
- You trust these walls?
If you're frightened,
you shouldn't have come.
When I was in the KGB,
I spent six months in Afghanistan.
This place is a palace compared
to the hole in the ground I lived in.
Here. You should stay hydrated.
I brought a shipment of water
- in on my plane.
- Thank you.
So much for the Israelis
stopping our resupply.
I wish we were in the fertile part
of the valley, though.
I hear it's quite green and beautiful.
Well, this is better for pictures.
How do you mean?
Well, if you flew into a paradise,
wouldn't be as effective, now, would it?
You do have a flair for the theatrical.
I can say the same about you,
showing up on my doorstep like this.
This isn't your doorstep.
You're squatting where you shouldn't be.
I don't think my men
will see it like that.
Do your men know that you're
responsible for killing their comrades?
Accusations.
That's how you plan to convince me?
What do you require
to pull out of the valley?
That your troops leave as well,
and the entire peacekeeping operation.
Well, as soon as your troops withdraw,
I'll make sure the UN
forces do exactly the same.
Hm. And you scale back missile defense.
As we agreed to twice already.
That's when we were making
an entirely different deal.
The main difference now is that
we're both standing in the desert,
and you can't leave with nothing
to show but sand in your shoes.
I'll agree to the scale-back.
Same terms as before.
How soon can you mobilize a withdrawal?
Well, the moment UN forces begin
to pull out, we will do the same.
I've had the Pentagon come up with
an exit plan that we can put into effect
as early as tomorrow.
As for the rest of the UN forces,
I can reach out to
the Secretary General immediately.
You or... your wife?
Well, yes, she would probably
make the call on my behalf.
I don't think she should.
You think I should make the call?
More than that.
I think she should be gone.
Gone in what way?
Gone from these negotiations?
As ambassador.
My final condition.
That cannot be on the table.
It is. And it's non-negotiable.
Ms. Dempsey.
I'm a friend of Lisa's.
- Uh, Max?
- That's right.
Yes, she told me to tell you
she's running a few minutes behind.
Okay, I'll just wait outside.
Thank you.
No, it's... chilly.
You can come on up to her room.
Okay.
I just want you to know...
I'm so sorry.
Lisa told us and our prayers
are with you.
Thank you so much.
She said you and your husband
were like parents to her. I see why.
Come on in.
Max, hey.
Sorry I'm late.
Here, I want you to take that back.
No, no, no, that money's yours.
No, I can't. I can't take it.
Everyone at the fellowship pitched in.
- Just give it back to 'em.
- I can't.
You said that you needed the money
for the medicine.
Yeah, sit down.
Sorry, please.
Okay.
What I'm about to tell you
is gonna sound fucked up,
but just hear me out
before you say anything, all right?
Okay.
I'm leaving.
And I'm not coming back.
And... I have to leave
because I'm in danger.
My name isn't Max.
I don't have AIDS.
- Wait. Hold on.
- Let me finish, please.
I want to explain everything to you,
but I can't.
The less you know, the better.
But listen to me.
If the FBI comes here,
you can't say anything.
You have to tell them you don't know me.
- The FBI?
- Yes, and if they do,
I want you to contact this man.
His name is Doug Stamper.
- And he can help you.
- Max. This is crazy.
It's not my name.
I made it up.
I made up everything.
The name, the girlfriend, the clinic.
No, I was there with you.
I faked it. I had to.
If you're not Max... then who are you?
Take this. He will help you.
- Oh...
- He can protect you.
Please. I know it's not fair.
- Please leave.
- Let me leave this with you.
I don't want to have
anything to do with it.
Please, just take it with you.
Please leave.
You're a good person, Lisa.
I'm just not.
And I'm sorry.
What can I offer you instead of her?
Nothing.
What about a humanitarian relief fund,
for your allies in Africa?
You can distribute it
any way you see fit.
A few billion dollars?
I'm not that easily bought.
All right, let's say that we
re-examine our base in Izmir.
Congress would never let you.
And realistically, you're willing
to barter major strategic airfields
on account of your wife?
You can't make this about her.
She was never equipped
to be an ambassador.
You know that.
I understand.
How could you say no to your own wife?
But she's blinding you.
- I'm doing you a favor.
- You are being petty.
The SEAL team you sent.
Look how easily we manipulated her.
Moryakov didn't have to work too hard.
Did we blow up our own men?
Maybe we did.
Maybe we didn't.
But we made her believe that we did.
And she convinced you.
Now, wouldn't you call that blindness?
You want to kill me now. I can see it.
I read an amusing article about, um...
a Civil War re-enactor,
who said that your
great-great-grandfather
killed a Yankee soldier
with his bare hands.
When I was in Afghanistan,
we were ambushed by the Mujahideen.
And the man who shot me here and here,
he stabbed me when his rifle jammed.
I pulled the knife away
and slit his throat.
Yes, I know, you've told that story
dozens of times to the press.
The part I don't tell is that after
I slit his throat, I kept going.
We strapped his head to a donkey so
it would carry it back to his village.
I've killed a man with my bare hands.
It wasn't make-believe.
Do you think you're capable?
I think you are.
You're ruthless.
Like me.
Sometimes we must be ruthless
with those who hate us.
And sometimes we must be ruthless
with those we love.
I don't see why Claire
means so much to you.
Because she means so much to you.
And if you do this,
I will know you're serious.
Your wife is on the line, sir.
Tell her I'll call her back.
I've told her that twice now.
- Tell her again.
- Yes, sir.
- You don't have to do that, Sarah.
- I don't mind. It doesn't take long.
No, no. Let us do it.
You go relax.
I'll move the monsters in a few minutes.
- Okay.
- All right.
See you in bed.
See you tomorrow.
I wish I could sleep like that.
You ever think of settling down?
Gettin' a couple of these for yourself?
Hasn't ever crossed my mind.
Never?
It's not for me. A life like that.
You mean a life like mine?
- That's not what I said.
- I know you've always felt that way.
A mortgage, nine to five,
wife, two kids, a dog.
No.
It's just my freedom's important to me.
I'm freer than you are, pal.
I stayed in Columbus because I liked it,
not because anybody made me.
I chose to put down roots.
You've always been running
from something.
Hey, I don't judge you.
Don't judge me.
Listen to your big brother
for a second.
No, last thing I need
is a lecture right now.
During your whole recovery, all you kept
talking about was getting back to work.
Over a month I've been here,
using all my vacation time
and then some.
If you don't want to be here,
then maybe you should go home.
It's not about that, Doug.
I'm here because you're family.
Because you're more important than work.
Hey... If I lost my job because of you,
I'd find another one.
What do you have?
Frank Underwood?
You don't even have that.
You got two pictures
on your fridge,
and they're of my kids.
That's not freedom.
Petrov wants a diplomatic change.
At the UN.
- Me.
- It was non-negotiable.
Clearly, you didn't say no.
I wanted to discuss it with you first.
I called more than once.
I wanted to convince myself
to refuse what he asked.
But... I couldn't do that.
I told you it was
a mistake to go, Francis.
And the resolution was a mistake.
And Corrigan was a mistake.
We could tally up all our mistakes,
but we are where we are.
I need to concentrate
on what's in front of me right now.
I am. I'm in front of you.
The Russians need to leave.
It's as simple as that.
You want me to say this is okay.
No.
Francis, I would've preferred if you had
walked in and just told me I was fired.
They played you, Claire.
Moryakov was not having
some crisis of conscience.
It was all so that we would
send our SEAL team in.
So that we would provoke the Israelis.
And I didn't see it,
because I trusted you too much.
I didn't look at it objectively...
because you're my wife.
- Petrov told you that?
- Yes.
- And you believe him?
- I do.
I'll resign.
I wish it didn't have to come to this.
What do we say to the press?
That you want to focus on the campaign,
that that was your plan all along.
That I want to see
this crisis through, first.
No one will question that.
Tell Petrov.
And I will...
make the announcement
whenever you want me to.
Claire.
You were right.
I shouldn't have gone.
It was your decision to make.
Not mine.
Good night.
My decision.
Sometimes I think the presidency...
is the illusion of choice.
What is it?
I have to go to the White House.
It's the middle of the night.
He's the president.
Thank you, Meechum.
Have a seat.
I wake you up?
It's fine.
I'm a light sleeper anyway.
If it wasn't you, it would've
been a siren or a dump truck.
I get woken up in the middle
of the night all the time.
Some crisis somewhere in the world.
Some... situation...
in the Situation Room.
Well, that's better than a dump truck.
You reached out to Tim Corbet.
I did.
I spoke to him a few days ago.
He called to let me know.
So you two are still close.
Not anymore.
At school we were.
I thought he might have some insight
to how you were back then.
Those are formative years.
More formative for you than for me.
I learned how to march and shoot a gun,
that's about it.
I would've been better off
in military school.
Yeah? Why's that?
You go from turning tricks
to being on the bestseller list
before you can legally drink,
it messes with you.
You told me your friend
was the one who, uh...
I lied.
Why? You ashamed?
First time I did it,
I was scared out of my mind.
I knock on the door, it opens...
guy's in a satin robe.
He's fat.
Stringy hair, combed over his bald spot.
Beads of sweat
rolling down his cheeks.
I almost ran back to the elevator.
But you didn't.
No.
I needed the money.
Before I got undressed...
he tells me that his wife just died.
Car accident.
Says they had plans
to visit Tokyo in the spring.
Tells me about his three kids.
The one that was born with a cleft palate.
Describes his house in Westchester,
with a Juliet balcony in the living room.
Says how beautiful she was.
Tells me he doesn't want to die.
Never touched me once.
Sometimes it was just sex.
But a lot of times, it wasn't.
They would tell me everything.
These men.
That access.
Those stories.
It was an addiction.
I craved it.
I lived for it.
And then you wrote about it.
When I got famous...
I had to stop.
I tried it once, I got recognized.
I wasn't invisible anymore.
I couldn't escape myself.
I wish I could do that sometimes.
Escape myself.
Is it Claire?
You didn't ask me here
to talk about Tim Corbet.
What's in this for you?
I'm addicted.
To me?
I betrayed her.
How?
I'm not asking as your biographer.
I'm asking as your friend.
Are we friends?
We could pretend to be.
This isn't pretend.
I'm real.
You're hurting.
She's hurting more.
Everyone's hurting.
Go home.
You should get some sleep.
And so should I.
Thirty years is a long time.
You've made it this far.
Okay!
Double!
Jesus.
- Hey.
I didn't hear you come back.
I didn't want to wake you.
Wow.
- What is it?
- Mid-East bureau.
They say the Russians
are pulling out their troops.
Whatever he did out there
must have worked.
Mm... I wonder what it cost him.
We ran the different looks
by a couple of focus groups.
These are the three favorites.
Not this one.
Uh, this one. What do you think?
I like it.
- The hair color as well?
- Do you mind going back to blonde?
I'd prefer it dark.
The groups, in Iowa, in particular,
they like the blonde.
Fine. We'll go blonde then.
You're popular among women.
We want to push those numbers as high
as we can, and every little bit counts.
You don't have to explain.
We'll do the color change
after we announce the resignation.
Thanks, Abbie.
If you don't want to,
you don't have to do this.
It's fine.
The nomination is not
gonna hinge on your hair.
You heard what Abbie said.
Every little bit counts.
We'll do what we have to.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net