Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
"Title One of the Stafford Act:
'Emergency' means any occasion
or instance for which,
in the determination
of the president..."
"Determined" by the president.
- Any instance?
- As long as we can make the argument
that this saves lives
and protects health and safety.
Well, unemployment leads to crime,
to malnutrition,
to improper medical care.
There's no doubt it'll
be challenged in the courts.
Well, even so, by the time that happens,
people will see what
America Works looks like.
Tell me, in your legal opinion...
is there enough leeway here?
Yes, the language is sufficiently vague.
But just to be clear,
this is completely unorthodox.
No president has ever tried
to reappropriate funds this way.
Thank you, gentlemen, that's all I need.
The states won't go for this.
Too radical.
And if I call just one governor
who says no and leaks it to the press,
Congress will be on my ass
before I get this out of the gates.
But, the District of Columbia...
- No governor.
- Just you, the mayor.
Now, Barney, I know
this puts you out on a ledge.
I love it.
I love everything about it.
We have to fight Congress for every
dollar in our budget, each year.
If my people see me take the money
they won't give us...
well, I just won reelection.
This is why you put a brawler
like Barney Hull in office,
aside from paying a debt.
Add up 50 governors
and 535 members of Congress,
you don't come close
to the gumption of one bold mayor.
I want people registering for jobs
in every part of the city
as soon as possible, before
the court challenges bubble up.
What about one big tent right
in front of the Capitol?
Make Congress see the people line up all
the way back to the Lincoln Memorial.
Can we do something by July Fourth?
You bring the fireworks,
I'll bring the people.
Good morning. Please, sit.
I know Remy has just briefed you all,
so, aside from the Secretary
of Homeland Security,
who is no longer with us,
does anyone else object to this plan?
Good. Until a new
secretary is confirmed,
FEMA will report directly to me.
Thank you all very much.
Unemployment doesn't constitute
a natural disaster, Mr. President.
The Stafford Act gives me
full authority to define an emergency.
But, sir, we've only got
about three billion left
in the Disaster Relief Fund, and we're
about to go into hurricane season.
So we use the three billion
that's there, and if a hurricane hits,
Congress replenishes the funds,
just as they always do.
When it comes to a disaster,
every hour counts, sir.
- If we're waiting around for Congress--
- Mr. Silva, this is moving forward.
People could die, Mr. President.
People are dying
because they don't have jobs.
Slower than a flood or an earthquake,
but dying just the same.
You can't compare unemployment
to a cat four hurricane.
I came to your office because
I want this to remain your office.
There's a reason three presidents
have kept you here.
You're dedicated, you're relentless,
you're exceptionally competent.
If we have to stretch dollars even
further, you're the man to do it.
It's either you
or someone far less experienced.
The two of you head to Iowa
at the end of the week.
That's right.
Eighteen counties this trip.
By January, I plan on hitting all 99.
John will join me at every event
until his husband is released.
Have you had any
contact with Michael since his arrest?
The Russian government has refused.
They won't let him speak to a lawyer.
That's why it's important John join me.
We need to keep the pressure
up on Moscow.
You know,
gay rights is controversial
in many parts of the country.
Do you think that appearing
with Corrigan's husband
could possibly hurt you?
I think the American people want
a candidate who doesn't dodge,
who is truthful about where she stands.
Not someone who shies away
from controversy.
It's one thing to shy away
It's another thing to court it.
Well, Michael was arrested
for speaking his mind.
If defending free speech is
controversial, then...
we're no better than Russia.
I wish that there were more people
in our government defending it.
Are you talking specifically
about the Underwood Administration?
I think the president
could do more.
You know, the White House
has said hat they've been speaking
directly with the Kremlin,
that they, and I quote here:
"Have to tackle this issue
as it relates to the larger
diplomatic relationship
between the two nations."
Then why haven't we seen
any evidence of those talks?
When I'm president,
the American people can rest assured
that I will take my oath to defend
and protect our citizens seriously.
- What do you think of her?
- What, Dunbar?
Yeah.
I believe that the
administration could do better...
- You worked for Underwood.
- Not anymore.
I won't be offended.
Uh, I like a lot about
what she has to say.
Would you vote for her?
I don't know. I might.
Yeah. Probably would.
- How soon?
- Tomorrow.
We're gonna get hit hard on this.
- Better than getting hit on Corrigan.
- You saw Vieira?
Dunbar's smart. She's running
against us before we're even running.
She'll attack us on the FEMA thing, too.
Then let her. At least
we're controlling the narrative.
When we first spoke,
you mentioned early fall.
Look, Dunbar's got momentum
because no one's challenging her.
But once we drop the FEMA plan,
that'll take her off message.
And your candidacy will distract her.
It's a one-two punch.
We'll start bleeding away
the woman's vote.
I'm just not sure how smart it is
to rush into a campaign
- with so little preparation.
- This isn't a real campaign.
But it needs to look like one.
I thought you wanted to be on my ticket.
It's my reputation at stake.
- I don't want to look foolhardy.
- Look, no one--
Mayor's announcing in the morning.
Seth's working with his office.
You see, Jackie, this is perfect timing.
The FEMA plan goes into action,
you announce in a couple of weeks,
you say you had to run.
President Underwood
is being reckless with FEMA.
You come out against me and America
Works and you steal Dunbar's thunder.
And then I flip-flop when I pull out
and you put me on the ticket?
By then, 50,000 people will have jobs,
and it won't look like a flip-flop.
It'll look like you saw the light.
Now, look, why don't you go off
with Remy and you discuss the details,
and just give it some thought
before you decide.
- Thank you, Mr. President.
- Let's talk in my office.
My biggest concern is funding.
I couldn't fly coach to Iowa.
I'll get you some PAC money
rolling your way.
Should be enough to get you started.
If I run, it shouldn't be half-ass.
Which is why we should talk about this.
You want a candidate
with a family.
We are after the woman's vote.
Alan and I have already talked about it.
You have?
Yeah. We joked about getting married
on our first date.
I get two kids
without the stretch marks.
And when I mentioned I might run,
it stopped becoming a joke.
Is Alan open to it?
- It was his idea.
- And what about you?
We do love each other.
Hm. He seems like a good guy.
He is. And his children are wonderful.
You should think about getting hitched.
Should we talk timeline?
- For marriage?
- The campaign.
This is far from an offer.
This is a conversation.
And it's a conversation
that never happened.
I took the back door in,
I'll take the back door out.
We keep you off the payroll this quarter.
You start officially September 30th.
Next quarter's FEC filings. It's fine.
What are you thinking
in terms of salary?
Twenty-two thousand per quarter.
That's way below what I'm worth.
Even in this state.
What do you think's appropriate?
Two-fifty and three points
on the ad-buy.
- That's beyond our means.
- No, it's not.
It's a drop in the bucket
from your estate.
You said you wanted in
because you believed in this campaign.
- That's right.
- Sounds like it's more about money.
It's about being valued.
Two-fifty and the points is a bargain.
I want to work for you,
just not as a beggar.
We don't trust you yet, Doug.
We don't even halfway trust you,
so you are a beggar.
And you shouldn't trust me...
until I prove myself.
That's a gamble you don't get to take
without putting chips on the table.
Cynthia and I will discuss.
Thank you for your time.
Let me check first.
Okay, it's clear.
- What do you think?
- Why take the gamble?
I don't want us
to start making decisions
from a position of weakness.
That is how you lose.
I think we're inviting the fox
into the hen house.
Anyone who wants to be a mole accepts
the first offer without question.
He's negotiating.
So you actually believe him?
Not necessarily.
But that doesn't mean
that he doesn't have value.
Yeah, we're not gonna need any of these.
We're gonna keep these right here.
- Kate Baldwin, the one and only.
- I thought I heard somebody in here.
Welcome to the White House.
Or welcome back, I should say.
It feels smaller than I remember.
- Where do they have you sitting?
- Right there, second row.
Oh. I would've thought
you wanted first row.
I heard you spit when you talk.
What's the president speaking
about tomorrow?
- You don't waste a minute, do you?
- No.
I gotta say, I was surprised
that the Telegraph sent you
to cover the White House.
- I mean, who leaves the London bureau?
- Ayla was a protégée of mine.
I see, so now they
bring in the big guns.
Just one gun, but big enough.
- Don't get any ideas.
- About what?
This is gonna stay around my neck.
You can't boot two reporters in a row
from the Telegraph.
- Certainly not two women.
- I have no desire to do that.
It's an honor to work with you.
Pulitzer, Peabody.
Get yourself a Nobel,
you'll have a trifecta.
Oh, you're almost charming.
Kate, I'm not your enemy here.
You punished Ayla for doing good work.
She hit hard and you hit back.
Fair enough.
Well, I'm gonna hit twice as hard
as she ever did
because I can
and because someone should.
I look forward to it.
You're such a terrible liar.
I'll see you bright and early.
You got a minute?
Sure.
Here's the draft
for the statement tomorrow.
I want it to be perfect.
Congress will fire back,
all guns blazing,
and I'm sure Dunbar will make
a meal and a half out of it.
But I gotta say, I feel good.
To be on the offensive.
If I can't scrape the money together
behind the scenes,
I'll rob the bank
in broad goddamn daylight.
We'll cram America Works down
their throats and watch them choke.
Enough tiptoeing.
Here.
Oh, these changes are good.
It makes me happy to see you excited.
I feel free again.
- I wish I felt the same.
- The resolution?
Just some last minute
hand-holding, but...
I think we'll get there.
I have complete confidence in you.
- Do you like this room?
- It's fine.
You know,
I haven't spent the night here yet.
- Maybe I could--
- My plane leaves at seven.
I should probably get some sleep.
You watch the news tomorrow.
Should be fun.
- I will.
- Good night.
Seventeen years,
I served the Metro Police.
I've seen robberies and murders.
I've seen the blight of drugs.
I've seen little kids whose only meal
each day was the one they get at school.
You know what's at the root of all that?
Folks don't have jobs!
There are 60,000
unemployed people in Washington.
It's a disaster.
And it's a disgrace here
in the nation's capital.
So this morning,
at the president's urging,
I am declaring a state of emergency
in the District of Columbia.
And I am formally requesting
three billion dollars
from FEMA's Disaster Relief Fund
to put people back to work.
Motherfucker.
Anyone, and I mean anyone,
who registers for work
in the District of Columbia
will be guaranteed a job.
I'm working with my cabinet
to increase workforce
devoted to infrastructure,
maintenance and repair.
The Defense Department will ramp up
recruitment and civilian employment.
And any private sector companies
who hire AmWorks registrants
will get up to $45,000
toward the yearly salary
of each job that they create.
Our goal is full employment
within twelve months.
Our hope is that success in Washington
will convince Congress
to fund America Works nationwide.
Now, I'll take a few questions.
Mr. President!
Madam Ambassador. A word, please.
Excuse me.
We are withdrawing support
of the peacekeeping resolution.
- Why?
- Because Israel is.
Palestine is open to the plan,
but without consensus...
This came directly from Jerusalem?
- Yes, the foreign minister.
- Nothing came from Eliana?
No, but I came to speak to her.
I'll speak to her myself.
Thank you, Hasan.
Thank you, Ambassador.
Moscow is threatening
to sell arms to Iran.
They always make that threat.
The feeling in Jerusalem
is that this resolution
may push them over the edge.
It's not worth the risk.
Why didn't you come to me?
The vote's in two hours.
I got the call 30 minutes ago.
Russia doesn't want to be humiliated
because we did this without them.
You know it's a bluff on their part.
The prime minister feels
that this vote is just symbolic.
That the US won't
actually contribute troops.
No, we will absolutely follow
through once it's passed.
The prime minister has his doubts.
I'm sorry, it's out of my hands.
Claire?
Ambassadors, I need you
to withdraw the resolution.
We lost consensus.
I need to postpone the vote
until we get it back.
Secretary Travers is a good example.
Homeland Security?
- Former secretary, I should say.
- He's done?
They haven't announced,
but Steve called me.
Said he stood up to the president
on this FEMA nonsense.
Homeland Security has jurisdiction
over FEMA now.
Right. The president demanded his letter
of resignation right then and there.
- This is all off the record.
- Yeah.
- Paul's got a big mouth.
- So it's true?
- This is off the record?
- Completely.
- Let me call you on my encrypted phone.
- My number is blocked, so--
This is Homeland Security.
I have your number.
Incoming call.
Press the pickup bu--
- Mr. Secretary.
- It's true. I resigned.
Why are you still in the office?
Punching the clock until
the White House wants to go public.
Why wouldn't you go public yourself,
if you're so against the policy?
I serve at the pleasure
of the president.
I have Landry on background.
I'm writing about the resignation.
And I can't stop you.
But there won't be a quote from me.
Don't let the administration
off the hook.
This an opportunity to speak out.
You don't have the career I've had
by criticizing your bosses publicly,
no matter how strongly you feel.
Talk to Arnie Silva,
the FEMA Administrator.
He's more disgusted
by all this than I am.
People's lives are in the balance.
And he doesn't care.
Our projections
for the next 12 months.
We're in a La Niña phase, which means
falling temperatures in the Pacific.
We expect at least two
major landfalls this season.
Homes destroyed, billions in damage,
tens of thousands without power.
And that's just hurricanes.
If we get a major earthquake,
or flood, or forest fire...
It's all in there.
Has he asked you to resign?
He threatened it.
But I said I'd cooperate.
Why?
Nobody has more experience.
I couldn't forgive myself if I left.
But you just said, if the Relief Fund
is depleted, then--
People will suffer.
But on my watch, fewer will suffer.
I need a quote, Mr. Silva.
I can't do that.
People could die,
you have a responsibility.
The president has built
a culture of silence and fear.
That can end with you.
That folder will speak louder
than anything I could say.
Two front page bylines
on the same day for Ms. Baldwin?
You kicked out a pit bull
and you let in a dragon.
I didn't think the Telegraph
would send someone like her.
Well, maybe you just didn't think.
You wanted me
to implement discipline, sir.
To send a message. And so I did.
Well, they've sent back an even
stronger message, haven't they?
I take responsibility for that, sir,
and I will do my best
to keep her in line.
Your best?
It's their top bureau chief.
She's untouchable.
I don't want to pretend that I can
control her 100 percent.
- Travers?
- Denied speaking with her,
but it must be him. I don't think
anybody else in the cabinet would.
Let's confirm his resignation.
No point in keeping it a secret now.
Tell Steve he can vacate his office.
And what about Silva?
The details on the disaster projections
are very inside baseball.
We can't fire him!
If there's a hurricane,
he's the only guy that can keep
a disaster from becoming a catastrophe.
- And what's Dunbar saying?
- Nothing yet, publicly.
- She's probably letting this play out.
- Letting me dig my own grave.
We have to sell America Works.
It should sell itself
once we get people employed.
Well, that's the idea,
but we don't stop there.
- Commercials and billboards?
- On whose money?
And even so, we need more than ad-buys.
We need...
We need the philosophy behind it.
We need something of substance.
We need something...
We need something
that will capture the imagination.
- Either of you play Monument Valley?
- What's that?
- It's a video game.
- I don't play them, sir.
I sold my Xbox on eBay.
It was too addictive.
No, it's not a console game.
You both read this and then tell me
that you wouldn't want to play this.
I'd say there's nine consultants in the
country who truly know foreign policy.
Me, I'm number one.
Me in a coma is number two.
But that still leaves seven
who are cheaper.
I value good counsel, and I'm smart
enough to know what I don't know.
What would be your assessment
of us so far?
You're making a big stink
out of this Michael Corrigan thing,
but that's just surface.
You have to understand
why Corrigan got arrested.
Petrov's appealing
to his traditional base.
No. This is about the Jordan Valley.
I don't follow.
Retaliation.
It goes back to the summit
a couple of months ago.
Look, this... is the Jordan Valley.
All right, hold on, I'll make it easier.
That's the Valley. Right there.
Occupied by Israel since 1967,
it's been a major roadblock
in any peace accord
with the Palestinians.
Underwood sends peacekeeping troops,
the Israelis leave,
- the Palestinians are happy.
- It's not that simple.
Everyone gets hung up on this
little patch of land ten miles by 40,
but you have to look outwards,
past Jordan and Syria, past Iraq.
Here... to the Caucasus.
That's Russia's sphere of influence.
They don't see the peacekeeping force
as a Middle East issue.
They see it as strategic
deployment of US troops
less than a thousand miles
from their southern border.
So you're saying Corrigan's a pawn,
a play for leverage?
More of a first salvo.
Moscow wants to show it's serious
about fighting this resolution.
Now, if I had to guess,
Underwood tried to bring Russia
into the mix during the summit.
Get involved early on as partners.
And when Petrov didn't play ball,
Underwood went on the offensive,
which is a huge gamble.
- Tell me how.
- Nobody wants UN troops there.
Not the Israelis,
not the Palestinians, not the Arabs.
They're playing along
because the US is pressuring them.
But just one little thing
needs to go wrong,
and you've got a tinderbox
where everyone's holding matches.
So why is he following
this course of action at all?
Because he's smart.
- You just said--
- He's being too smart.
If it pays off, hey,
he wins a Nobel Prize. But...
if it backfires,
he leaves himself wide open.
And that's when you need
to hit him hard.
A disastrous foreign policy
that made the world more dangerous.
And he had his wife
with zero foreign policy experience
- lead the goddamn charge.
- I'd like to bring you aboard, Joe.
- When can you start?
- I believe I already did.
I'll get the paperwork
over to you later today.
Let me ask, who referred me?
- You have quite a reputation.
- Yeah, for being an asshole.
Somebody you respect
must have recommended me highly.
- A former Underwood staffer.
- I never worked with any of his people.
Which is one of the reasons
he recommended you.
Touché.
What is this?
A list of the Russian officials
who will be sanctioned
if you sell a single truckload
of arms to Iran.
I didn't even make the top ten.
These sanctions can and will escalate.
And then what?
We'd build a coalition
to impose their own sanctions.
And then what?
Alexi, you know what an economic
crisis that would be for Russia.
Like the trade war you waged with China?
Except in our case, only three percent
of exports go to the US.
And Europe needs our natural gas.
They won't forfeit that over
a few short-range missiles to Iran.
You don't want to challenge us
on the armament of a terrorist state.
We'll never be presented
with that problem.
You can't assure the Israelis
you'll provide troops.
The president doesn't have
the support of either party in Congress.
No troops, no Israel.
No Israel, no consensus.
No consensus, no resolution.
I will get this resolution passed.
Don't underestimate my ability
or desire to do so.
I've indulged your
enthusiasm long enough.
You've bit off more
than you can chew, Claire.
Leave this to the professionals
and let your little resolution
die a painless death.
The truth is, you have
no business being ambassador
any more than I do being First Lady.
That's a very nice dress, by the way.
"She stabbed the floor with a broom.
Karaoke every Wednesday.
Some tone-deaf drunk girl
mutilating Britney Spears.
She knew they couldn't hear
the broom in the bar below.
But we all need a ritual,
and this was hers.
Three short thrusts, wood on wood,
a hollow sound
which accomplished nothing.
David would be home soon.
'It's too hot,' he'd say.
She opened the window.
The music was so loud,
she couldn't ignore it."
Here.
Aren't you gonna buy the new one?
I will, on my Kindle.
But will you please sign this?
- Who should I make it out to?
- Lesley. L-E-S-L-E-Y.
Scorpio totally changed my life.
The energy and the anger...
It's my favorite book of yours.
Probably my favorite book, period.
- Make sure you read the new one.
- Yes.
Who should I make it out to?
It's a perversion of the Stafford Act
and you know it.
It's a reading of the Stafford Act.
We read it differently.
You can't just raid funds that Congress
appropriated for a specific use,
- then use them however you want.
- Clearly, I can.
This is a direct challenge
to Congress, Mr. President.
Bob and I have agreed.
Both parties will fight you on this.
Well, at least I'm
cultivating bipartisanship.
Gentlemen, I don't want to do this,
but what choice have you left me?
Our branch is here to check yours.
If we didn't feel America Works
warranted taxpayer money,
- then it's not fit to be law.
- Now, look.
This is the first time
that the leaders of both parties
have met with me in one room,
and not because I didn't invite you,
because you declined.
So, now that we're here,
let's make the most of it.
I'm willing to walk back on FEMA
if we can discuss
putting AmWorks on the floor.
- You bullied us on the Education Bill.
- And the government freeze.
It's not gonna work this time.
You watch it work
and then tell me it didn't.
We're drafting a law,
saying this use of the DRF is illegal.
And who's going to enforce that law?
We were ready to impeach one president.
We'll do the same with you if necessary.
And put Donald Blythe in this office?
You know he's not up for the job.
Congress would get killed
for malpractice.
As crooked as you may think I am,
you know I can handle the pressure,
and you know Donald can't.
So pass your law, I'll veto it.
And when you overrule me in the Senate,
we'll let the third branch decide.
Don't declare war on Congress,
Mr. President.
Not on Congress.
I'm declaring war on atrophy.
But these days,
who could tell the difference?
Oh! Oh...
Oh...
- So how about this?
- Hm?
I'll order a pizza.
When it gets here,
I bring it into this room...
with a paper towel
draped over my arm.
Voilà. Just like... room service.
You don't let your kids eat pizza.
Well, because I've seen
what it does to a carotid artery.
- And you're not my kids.
- Mm...
Do you think they like me?
They adore you.
Matt asked if you could teach him
how to drive.
- Really?
- Yeah.
He says you'd be less judgmental.
Do you want to get married?
To you, or in general?
I'm serious.
So where'd this come from?
- We've talked about it.
- Hm...
We say "I love you."
I want a husband.
You want a wife.
This works, the two of us,
don't you think?
- It's very romantic.
- Aren't we past romance?
I bought you a ring.
Why didn't you say anything?
It's the element of surprise.
That's kind of the point, isn't it?
It's in my glove compartment.
I can go get it if you want.
No, I want you to order the pizza.
We can do the whole ring thing tomorrow.
- Hey.
When did you get in?
- Couple of hours ago.
- Well, come and sit down.
I feel like I haven't seen you for what,
has it been three days?
Four, I think.
It's just all been a big blur.
Mm. Same in New York.
- Any luck?
- They're like a broken record, Francis.
Do I need to call the prime minister?
Oh, I think it's gonna take more
than a phone call.
- Tell me.
- That's not why I'm here, actually.
Hang on, hang on.
So much has been going on in the past
few months, we hardly have time to talk.
Here, use this.
I feel bad about the other night
when you wanted to sleep in my bed.
Oh, that. You shouldn't.
I just--
I don't know why
I started sleeping in there.
Well, if I remember correctly,
you had a cold.
But why I stayed.
You don't have to explain.
I want you to know that I love you.
It has nothing to do with that.
I love you... as much as ever.
Not another word.
Let's finish talking about Israel
in the morning.
You said more than a phone call?
They need it in stone, Francis,
that we'll contribute troops.
- An executive order.
- Congress won't be happy.
Well, they're already not happy.
I spat in one eye,
I might as well spit in the other.
Consider it done.
Thank you.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you. Oh, sure.
Did you get it?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you for your support.
- Thank you, sir.
- I liked your speech, Ms. Dunbar.
- And I've heard more than a few.
- I appreciate you saying that, sir.
I know Iowans aren't easily impressed.
What you said about integrity?
Well, if you can bring that
to Washington, I'll caucus for you.
One supporter at a time.
That's how we'll win this.
And that young man? I feel for him.
He's an inspiring individual.
John, there's someone
I want you to meet.
- Your name, sir?
- Clive Reynolds.
- Mr. Reynolds, nice to meet you.
- I'm praying for your husband.
- It's awful he's still stuck there.
- Stamper's in the cafeteria.
Thank you, Mr. Reynolds.
Thank you.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you for coming out.
You could've just called.
I hate July Fourth in DC.
Plus, I wanted to see you in action.
What'd you think?
I need her to leave.
I'll meet you at the car.
- Heather--
- Cynthia.
Read that.
Mrs. Underwood asked me to destroy it.
- I didn't.
- You should have.
She lied on national television.
I am not running that sort of campaign.
But it's good to know it's available.
I would never do that to another woman,
and neither would Cynthia.
Hm. Cynthia was a good choice
for your manager.
She'll run a top-notch operation.
But you need someone
who's willing to do the things
that people like her won't do.
When you asked me for a job,
you said you wanted
to turn over a new leaf.
I have a certain skill set,
Ms. Dunbar.
For me, turning over a new leaf
is using my skills for the right reasons.
Like putting you in office.
One-fifty.
One point on the ad-buy.
No points.
But I'll do a hundred thousand win bonus
if we get the nomination.
I hope I came over here
for some good news.
I'm in. You can tell the president.
August 19th.
We wanted you to announce
a lot earlier than that.
No, not the announcement. This.
Cardiology's good money.
Aren't you gonna say congrats?
I've never seen you be this girly.
It's a fucking diamond.
I'm allowed to be a little girly.
Congratulations.
I'm happy for you both.
Are you?
Sorry. That wasn't fair.
Maybe we should talk about dates
for announcing the campaign.
Yeah, I have a few ideas.
Let me pull up my calendar.
Um...
Week after next seems
to be the best option.
You have plans tonight?
For the fireworks?
Alan and I are taking his kids.
Right. Makes sense.
You were saying,
about a week after next?
- The Ambassador's inside.
- You want me to go in there?
She's just putting on makeup.
I can wait until she comes out.
She's going straight to her plane.
If you don't mind.
Alexi.
The day got away from me,
so I have to head down to DC
for the July Fourth celebration.
You may consider me
an ambassador from the men's room.
Don't make me laugh.
I'll have to start over.
- Good?
- Quite.
Alexi, I think we've gotten off
on the wrong foot.
We need to find a better way
to work together.
You're letting go of the resolution?
- Eyes?
- Perfect.
It's always nice
to have a man's opinion.
You were right, by the way.
Israel won't back us
unless we commit troops.
You called my bluff, Alexi,
and I shouldn't have insulted you
- with one in the first place.
- I'll be outside when you finish.
The president signed
an Executive Order this morning.
Five thousand US military reassigned
to permanent standby
for UN Peacekeeping operations.
Jerusalem has been informed.
Your husband doesn't have
that kind of authority.
It's occupied territory.
He's not deploying on sovereign land.
So, as Commander in Chief,
he doesn't need Congressional approval.
Israel's back on board again, Alexi,
so the moment you sell arms to Iran,
we will shoot the planes out of the sky,
the trucks off the road,
and the ships out of the water.
Now... maybe you'd be able
to afford sanctions...
...but you sure as hell
can't afford a war.
Come back to the table.
Engage us in good faith.
Or the resolution goes
to a vote next week.
I have always been willing to talk.
Not you and I.
President to president.
Oh, and we need Michael Corrigan
released, also.
I'll communicate your message to Moscow.
Please.
Hand me a towel, would you?
What a gentleman.
You ever been to the White House before?
When I won the National Book Award.
- Nancy was a fan.
- I'm surprised.
That story doesn't exactly
revere family values.
She's got the astrologer in her.
I think she liked the title
more than anything.
Scorpio was a very good book.
- Still pays the rent.
- Have a seat.
Why am I here, Mr. President?
Remy briefed you.
He said you needed a book.
He didn't say about what.
America Works.
Not just the policy, but the origins.
How a boy grew up
in a dirt-poor shithole
and climbed his way out
through hard work.
A story of dignity.
The pride that comes with one's labor.
- Propaganda.
- You could call it that.
This sort of thing...
it's not in my wheelhouse.
You need a salesman, not a novelist.
"Whoever you are,
whoever you think you are,
believe that you're
also a silent princess.
Your name is Ida.
Your journey is one
through a forgotten landscape
of twisting staircases
and morphing castles,
atop floating stones
defiantly crossing an angry sea,
within dimly-lit caverns
cobwebbed with ruins
M.C. Escher could
only grasp at in a dream state."
You read my video game reviews?
I tend to play shoot-'em-ups.
The indie games don't really interest me.
I need adrenaline and action.
But when I read this, I had to try it.
If you can convince me to be a silent
princess with just a hundred words,
imagine how many millions
you can convince with this book.
You are a salesman, Thomas.
I wasn't trying to sell anything.
Just describe my experience.
That's exactly what I want you to do
with my story.
No sales pitch,
just your honest curiosity.
Besides, these kinds of books
are always so boring, so safe.
I want something different,
something... unique.
Your voice.
I don't even know if I believe
in your program.
Come with me.
I want to show you something.
You build it and they come.
Today, the Washington Mall
is the real Field of Dreams.
Three thousand people have registered
since we set up shop this morning.
Now that's what I call
a Fourth of July party!
And we're gonna keep the party going
'round the clock, 24/7,
till everyone in DC who wants a job
can make their way
down here and sign up.
Have a look.
- Do you see that line of people?
- The AmWorks tent.
It stretches from there all the way
to the Lincoln Memorial.
They started lining up before sunrise.
It's really something.
Thomas, at best,
I'm going to be a footnote in history
if I can't help those people.
At worst, I'll be a joke.
I am those people.
I want you to tell that story.
What do you say?
- I don't know.
- What's your gut say?
That you don't add up,
and I'm intrigued.
- But not sold.
- Not yet.
Well, I'll pay you well,
and at the very least,
this sort of access
is worth its weight in gold, isn't it?
Sir, the First Lady's back.
I have to go give my Fourth of July
speech before the fireworks.
- How quickly would you need the book?
- By January.
I've never written anything
in less than a year.
Well, you don't strike me as someone
who shies away from a challenge.
I'd need to be able to write it
the way I want to write it.
Absolutely. Look, take your time.
Enjoy the view.
Meechum will show you out
when you're done.
And I promise, if you say yes,
you won't regret it.
No writer worth his salt
can resist a good story,
just as no politician can resist
making promises he can't keep.
Viktor, we'd be honored
to accept the invitation.
Yes, I agree,
there's much to discuss.
I'll have my office reach out
to the Kremlin.
We'll find dates
that work for both of us.
Thank you.
Well, you should get some sleep.
It's late over there.
Good night.
Hold off on the vote?
Until we sit down.
But we keep it in our back pocket.
Michael Corrigan?
They're going to release him
when we visit.
You made a miracle happen.
We did.
...each unique citizen
contributes to our future.
Can you turn that up?
Our forefathers,
when they declared independence,
understood the power
of the individual,
the value of self-determination.
They freed us from tyranny.
- They proved...
- He is a tyrant.
I don't know,
there's a lot of people out there.
He might be onto something.
Executive Order for UN troops?
He's out of control.
At least he's doing something.
Walker didn't do shit.
I think we replaced a dud
with an atom bomb.
They had to fight
to secure their freedom.
And now we have to fight to maintain it.
The freedom to work.
The freedom to live with dignity.
The freedom to hope.
Thank you, and God bless
the United States of America.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net