Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I'm glad you
brought up nepotism, Senator.
Um, if this were an outright
appointment, that would be one thing,
but in this case,
the president can only nominate.
It's the Senate that deems me worthy.
I'm here to convince you that I am.
Although, I must admit, my husband never
remembers to put the toilet seat down,
so he could be trying
to make it up to me.
My larger concern is your experience.
You have very little.
Well, a decade ago,
I founded a small nonprofit
and I built it into
a major global player.
I shepherded a number of bills
through Congress on its behalf.
And over the last year, I've dedicated
myself to sexual assault reform,
and have made meaningful strides.
Now, while this
may not qualify as statecraft,
it does illustrate my effectiveness,
the same effectiveness I plan
on bringing to the United Nations.
Thank you, Mrs. Underwood.
I yield the remainder of my time.
Uh, Mrs. Wallace of North Dakota,
you have eight minutes.
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Mrs. Underwood,
allow me to get specific.
What is your take
on UN Resolution 9214,
the imposition of sanctions
on the Congo for the--
The illegal mining and smuggling
of mineral resources.
Yes. The United States voted
against this resolution.
The DRC is already wracked
with economic hardship,
compounded by an unstable government.
It ranks 192 out of 194
in GDP per capita.
I think we need
to encourage foreign investment
and develop new forms of economic growth
rather than make one of the world's
poorest countries even poorer.
From a national security perspective,
the United States maintains a strong
interest in the success of the DRC.
- We want a stable nation...
- They're here.
...that can help us
in combating the spread
of Islamic radicalism
throughout the continent.
And in order to achieve that,
we need to work as its ally,
not its disciplinarian.
Good morning.
Mr. President.
Jackie. Terry.
Shall we?
Now you all have the, uh... overview.
But what we have here today
- is the comprehensive breakdown--
- Sir, before we begin--
Look, Bob, I know you have some
serious doubts about this program.
But just let me flesh it out first,
and then I promise
we can address any questions
that you might have.
- Uh, Mr. President--
- Ten million jobs.
Can we all agree that that's
a good thing for this country?
Universal employment.
It's the key for our keeping
the White House in 2016.
It's the only chance we have
of winning back majorities in Congress.
Now, the election's
only 18 months away.
We need to do something bold,
something decisive.
We need to redefine our party.
Actually, that's what
we wanted to discuss.
You're right, we do need
to redefine the party.
We need to do it
with a fresh face.
2016. We don't want you to run.
You weren't even elected
to the office in the first place.
The pardons hurt you.
Approvals are low.
We're not casting blame, sir.
We just believe that this
is best for the party.
I suspected this was coming,
but months from now.
I was hoping by then I'd have something
to show for my efforts,
that I could preempt their doubts
with progress.
They're nervous.
They're being impulsive.
It's a bit early
to be deciding something like this.
Shouldn't we revisit this
when we're closer to the primaries?
What do you think, Terry?
Like you said, sir, we only
have 18 months until the general.
Less than half of that to Iowa.
We would want to settle
on a candidate soon.
Someone who the whole party
can get behind
like the Republicans
are getting behind Mendoza.
And who would that be?
We haven't had
a discussion on that yet.
We came to you first, out of respect.
- Well, there must be a shortlist.
- No, not yet.
It'll be a process
to find the right person.
And we were hoping that
you would be a part of that process.
Obviously, this is a request,
Mr. President.
It's your decision.
But if you do run, sir,
you won't have our support.
Jackie?
I stand by the rest of the leadership.
Well, this is certainly a lot
to think about.
Let's table our discussion
on America Works for another time,
but thank you all
for being so forthright.
I'll get back to you
on this issue a little later on.
Would you like us
to stick around for a while?
We wouldn't want the press
to think we came all the way here
- for a five-minute meeting.
- That's a very good idea.
No raised eyebrows.
I'll have some refreshments sent
for you into the Map Room.
Wonderful.
Thank you, Mr. President.
As a vocal proponent for the
Sexual Assault Bill last session,
are you concerned about
your relationship with the US military?
No, I'm not, Senator.
I worked closely
with the Joint Chiefs on that bill.
What if there were a peacekeeping
mission in, say, Burma,
to quell civil unrest, and the United
Nations asked us to contribute troops,
to put our servicemen
and women's lives in peril.
If you're using Myanmar
as a hypothetical,
I think we're a long way from that,
but as Ambassador--
My question concerns
the use of US military.
The US military is irrelevant.
The current situation--
Excuse me, Mrs. Underwood.
The US military is irrelevant?
Well, I-- That's not what I said.
You said verbatim:
"The US military is irrelevant."
Well, in the, in the context of--
I meant... uh, that there are plenty--
I have the utmost respect
and appreciation for our troops, sir.
Not with statements
like that, you don't.
Senator,
if I may, I can explain.
How do we explain
to the men and women who serve,
who put their lives on the line,
that our ambassador
thinks they're irrelevant?
I think that's an unfair
characterization of what I intended--
I am not characterizing anything,
Mrs. Underwood, you said the words.
And now you're trying
to backpedal your way out of it.
- You're trying to take my words--
- Don't interrupt me.
If you will stop interrupting me,
I can explain--
No, you see, we ask the questions,
you answer them.
You're not allowing me
to answer the questions, Senator.
If you could maybe listen
instead of grandstanding.
The position
you're being considered for
requires calm, cool diplomacy.
What concerns me even more than
the military comment is your demeanor.
Is this what we're to expect
from our ambassador?
A hothead?
Go ahead, Mrs. Underwood, I'm listening.
Maybe it's leverage for another play.
Scare the wits out of me
and then come with the big ask.
- You sure there is one?
- America Works. They want to kill it.
Or soften me up to consider
another VP candidate for the ticket.
They're no fans of Blythe.
Could be anything,
any combination of things.
- What?
- You saw it?
- Saw what?
- The First Lady, sir.
- Jesus. I better call her.
- She's still in the hearing, sir.
I need to see this whole thing.
Let's get ahead of it if we can.
- The Solicitor General is here.
- Cancel it.
- You've already postponed twice.
- Postpone it again.
We can't put it off, sir.
It goes to the Supreme Court
in less than a month.
We have bigger fish to fry.
An American citizen was injured
by a drone strike.
That Walker authorized, not me.
But you're
the sitting president.
If we lose this,
it undermines your authority.
The media is all over it.
We need our rhetoric in line
with the Solicitor General's.
All right. Christ!
Send her in.
I'll put this clip on your computer,
for when you're done.
Terry Womack. Today. Privately.
Ms. Dunbar.
Before we begin,
I'd like to clear the air.
Your report.
You did good work, necessary work,
and I admire you for it.
I appreciate you saying that, sir.
And you understand the position
I was in with the pardons.
That's politics, sir.
Not my expertise.
What's past is past?
My focus is the argument
I'll present to the court.
She sees me as the bank robber
who made it to the county line.
But she's smart enough
to leave her badge at the door.
So, the case.
As you know, sir, we think
the State secret defense is strong.
When I consulted with the CIA on the--
I'm wondering if State secrets
is the best tactic.
Both of Mahmoud's legs were amputated.
He will be in the gallery,
in his wheelchair.
That's a powerful image.
Even Supreme Court Justices have hearts.
We need to stay in their heads.
A procedural route is clearly--
Excuse me.
Yes?
Uh, tell her I need to watch something
and I'll call her back
from my study in two minutes.
- It's my wife. I'm sorry.
- Please.
- ...you answer them.
- You're not allowing me
to answer questions, Senator.
Maybe you would benefit more
from listening than grandstanding.
I just watched.
How can I help?
I'm calling Senators. I think it would
be heavy-handed if you did too.
Well, I don't blame you
for getting upset.
- You didn't deserve that.
- I'm a target now.
- That's the price of admission.
- We both are.
The leadership,
they don't want me to run.
- What?
- Yeah, that's what they said
before I could even present the program.
- This soon?
- Yeah, that's what surprised me.
- The entire leadership?
- All of them, including Jackie.
- That woman has no sense of loyalty.
- Well, we'll see.
I'm gonna meet with Womack.
Turn him around.
They only have strength in numbers.
Continue, please.
As I was saying, we think
our procedural defense is strong.
State secrets prohibit
the introduction of evidence.
Assuming they won't dismiss outright,
the argument will focus
on deference to the executive.
Separation between the courts
and foreign policy.
They simply don't
have the security intelligence
to second-guess covert operations
while we're facing threats
on multiple fronts.
Sir?
- I can't do this now.
- Excuse me, sir?
My office will be in touch. Apologies.
Thank you very much.
Maybe you would benefit more
from listening than grandstanding.
Joining me now from Capitol Hill,
CNN's Chief Congressional
Correspondent, Dana Bash.
- Dana, what is the mood at the Capitol?
- Right, I understand, but...
We already have several
Senators publicly saying
that they're gonna vote against
Mrs. Underwood because of her comments.
A number of others I've spoken to
have gone from supporting her...
- Right.
- ...to being on the fence.
But, Dana, she's correct, isn't she?
Mendoza was grandstanding.
Maybe. But even so,
if you look at the numbers here,
this is doing real damage.
The vote was always going to be close...
Yes.
...things aren't looking good
for the First Lady.
- No, I understand, but--
- Could her military remark be...
- It's Mendoza.
- ...a slip of the tongue?
I appreciate your time, Senator.
I hope you'll reconsider.
- He's on now?
- Yes.
Turn that off?
Senator, hi.
Thank you for returning my call.
Sorry it took so long.
I had a ton of interview requests.
I just wanted to apologize if I came
across as disrespectful in any way.
- That was wrong of me.
- I know you didn't mean it, Claire.
It's just unfortunate
how things are playing out.
I realize you can't
vote for me yourself,
but I was hoping that maybe you
would say something to the effect to--
What, to the press?
- Or even privately, to your colleagues.
- I can't do that.
Senator, the vote should
center on my merits,
not a few moments
where you and I took the gloves off.
Well, I think that was telling,
don't you?
How you behaved under pressure?
Senator, you know you were
taking out of context what I said.
Of course I was.
I was trying to rile you up.
And I succeeded.
I wish I hadn't, because it's gonna
make things really tough for you.
But, if you can convince my colleagues
to change their minds despite that...
why, you'd make a great Ambassador.
- Thank you for your time, Senator.
- Good luck, Claire.
He's a son of a bitch.
Let's try Peterson next.
Approvals go up and down.
We can't allow ourselves
to be held hostage by public opinion.
We're being held hostage
by the Republicans.
We can't beat them with you
as the face of the party. Period.
Have you all really
thought this through?
I'm a sitting president.
But not an elected one.
But still, to abandon the incumbent,
and all the advantages
that that entails?
Which is the problem.
We don't see any advantages.
And if you were to come on board with us,
if you were to announce
that you're not running,
it wouldn't seem
as if we're abandoning you.
The party looks unified.
Bob Birch has been trying to do me in
since I forced the Education Bill
down his throat.
I think he's using shaky logic
to get you all on board
so he can carry out
some personal vendetta.
It was my idea.
Not Bob's.
I hope you work with us.
We meant it when we said it.
We would like for you
to be a part of the conversation.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
Hey.
- I can't hear you.
- Hang on a second.
- Seth?
- Yeah.
I was just calling to check in.
See how things are going.
Good. Things are going really good.
Hey, hold on one quick second.
Hey. Listen, uh, I know you're
rolling out the AmWorks program soon.
I'm sure Remy has a plan in place,
but I've been putting together a list.
Some key representatives and what they
might want in exchange for support.
Skeletons in the closet,
that kind of thing.
Yeah, that's on hold for the moment.
- You're not rolling it out?
- It's just on hold.
- Is something up?
- No, everything's fine.
We're focused on the summit
next month with Russia.
But you're good?
You getting stronger?
- Yeah.
- In good spirits?
Never been better.
I'll email you my ideas.
Let me know what he says.
- Will do.
- Thanks.
Senator, when we met
in your office last week,
we had a long,
productive conversation.
I can't imagine ten seconds
during the hearing would--
Senator, may I call you back
in five minutes?
Thank you.
- Francis?
- No luck. It was his idea.
What are you going to do?
Top 50 bundlers from last cycle.
I don't need the leadership
if I can get the money.
- You?
- Too early to tell.
Well, I'm here if you need me.
I've always said that power
is more important than money.
But when it comes to elections,
money gives power...
well, a run for its money.
It's Francis Underwood.
I thought you said he was handsome.
Sorry to interrupt.
Well, if she doesn't receive
a text with the word "urgent,"
it's not an official date.
How are you? Alan Cooke.
- Remy Danton.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm just gonna go, uh...
take a few calls.
There's an espresso coming
with your name on it, okay?
Nice meeting you.
So here we are.
I wasn't part of the decision.
They told me ten minutes before.
Who are they talking to? About running?
No one yet,
as far as I can tell.
There has to at least be a list.
Even a mental one.
Some ideas.
We need you to find out.
You know, when Walker resigned,
Frank's president,
you're Chief of Staff.
- But me?
- You're still in the leadership.
- Assistant Whip.
- It's a bullshit title.
I'm out of the inner circle.
What do you want?
I want to be on the ticket.
His VP.
All we want is a little information.
What you're asking is...
disproportionate.
It's repaying a debt.
A big one.
I whipped the votes for impeachment.
I should get to cash in on that.
There's no way he'll go for this.
Then there's no reason
for me to be your eyes and ears.
I'll get back to you.
During business hours.
No, Mark, we ran it in the White
House screening room and I swear to God,
when those jets crashed
into one of our Seawolf subs,
the Joint Chiefs screamed.
No, they didn't want you to use it
and certainly not for free.
David, I'm not just
asking you for money,
I'm asking you to be one
of my campaign chairmen.
That buys you a lot more
than a night in the Lincoln Bedroom.
Claire Underwood for Senator Hylbrook.
I agree. We can never rely solely
upon Security Counsel support.
Scott, we're 18 months out.
Now, if you wanna be
on the ground floor,
you got to shit or get off the pot.
The key is to provide leadership,
to lead by example.
I was hoping we could
hit Maidstone for a quick eighteen.
No, I'm a terrible golfer.
Exactly, you'd have the pleasure
of beating a president.
Now wouldn't that be
a good cocktail story?
I've spoken to almost every Republican
in your committee, sir.
Yes, they're taking their cue from you.
Is there another number
where I can reach him?
It's important
that we speak this evening.
Yes, anytime, no matter how late.
A little faith, Tom.
That's all I'm asking.
Oh, yes! I know, I don't
like being called "ma'am" either.
If I made every decision based
on what makes people feel good,
I'd be a talk show host,
not the president.
Well, I know Admiral Jennings
is a good friend of yours,
- I can call him personally.
- Don't let fear drive you.
That's not how you
run your business, is it?
I know you've been in my shoes,
and sound bites are not who we are.
- Penny-wise and pound-foolish.
- I'm so sorry, Senator, did I wake you?
Yes, no, I'll try back again tomorrow.
I can't fault you
for being shortsighted.
I hope you won't fault me
for having a long memory.
Good night!
I'm waking people up now.
I'll start again in the morning.
- How's it looking?
- I had to flip a coin? I don't know.
- You?
- Not a single backer yet.
- Not one?
- California's still awake.
Maybe I'll have better luck out west.
I'm going for a run.
I need to do something.
- It's late.
- Well, I'm too restless.
Well, I'll be here,
singing for my supper.
It's humiliating to have to beg
from some kid who was on Facebook
before his testicles descended,
but that's--
Derrick, Francis Underwood.
Do you have a few minutes?
I'll be running along the Mall tonight.
That requires a full detail.
How soon can you be ready?
We'd far prefer you ran on the track.
I'll be running along the Mall.
Yes, ma'am. We're going to need
the First Lady's detail, ASAP.
- This is off the record.
- Agreed.
You've called my office every day for
the last six months with one question.
I call everyone in the leadership.
I get the same non-answer
from all of you:
"Frank Underwood is our president..."
He has our undivided support.
Birch slipped up once. He said
"unwavering" instead of "undivided."
I wanted to drug-test him.
There was a meeting this morning
in the White House.
I was there on Pebble Beach
when you came out.
It lasted four and a half minutes.
- You were in there for an hour.
- We were inside for an hour.
Doesn't mean the meeting
lasted that long.
What happened? Why so short?
You're the Pulitzer finalist.
America Works?
Is that why the president went
to the Capitol this afternoon?
No one from the White House would say.
Have a good night.
You chose me.
What's your play?
When you write about presidents,
people pay attention.
Oh...
Oh!
Ah...
It'll come down to the wire.
I'm confident, but I don't
want to leave anything to chance.
Well, according to Erikson,
I have 47 votes as of this morning.
Well, I know, Senator,
but that's not enough.
I need yours.
I have every intention
of running for president.
I need to know you two are with me.
If you have any doubts,
now's the time to let me know.
Nancy, wipe the schedule clean.
Yes, everything.
We don't leave this office
until we have a plan.
Ma'am? The Easter Egg Roll
we were scheduled for?
- Right.
- If this is a bad time...
No, that's fine.
Please, come in.
Hello?
Yes... Claire Underwood.
He's expecting my call.
Hi, Sheila.
They're beautiful.
Would you mind setting them up, please?
I have a couple more calls to make.
Hello, Senator.
Yes, I'm well. How are you?
The nomination of Claire Underwood,
of Washington DC,
to be the Representative of the United
States of America to the United Nations.
Yeas and nays have been ordered
and the clerk will call the roll.
- Mr. Abner.
- Yea.
Mr. Braun.
Mr. Bray.
- This one's a little too pink.
- Girls like pink.
This is more than pink.
It's neon.
- Uh, I'm choosing four?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Willa?
- Up by two: 48 to 46.
- Ma'am, we can finish up later.
- No.
- Uh, what's next?
- The commemoratives.
These are really special.
A black egg?
- Yes, with patriotic tipping.
- It's still a black egg.
Engraved with POTUS
and FLOTUS signatures.
Ma'am? Final tally: 52 to 48.
Against.
- The press?
- In the briefing room.
I'll just be a few minutes.
Would you mind waiting?
Not at all, ma'am.
Hey.
I just heard.
I'm so sorry.
The press is waiting.
Well, they can wait.
- Do you want me to come with you?
- No. I just want to get it over with.
Claire. You--
Good morning.
Naturally, I'm disappointed
that the Senate did not confirm
my nomination today.
But I'm very grateful to have been
afforded the opportunity.
I'd be remiss
if I did not thank my husband
for all the faith and trust
he placed in me.
He's always supported me
in achieving my goals.
I look forward to continued service
as First Lady.
Thank you.
Um, let's go with the...
green, the blue, and the cream.
And for the rare one?
The Golden Ticket, so to speak?
Red. That one's beautiful.
Thank you.
Excuse me, please?
You ever try to do this?
Balance an egg?
We used to do this as kids.
You can't change
the laws of physics, can you?
I was wrong. It's too hard.
Sir?
Fighting the leadership, raising money.
We can't get them to do
what they're dead set against doing.
We'd need six months
just to get them back to square one.
We have to reverse our thinking.
When the wind's blowing at gale force,
there's no point in sailing against it.
What do you have in mind?
The White House
Counsel's office, please.
I don't care about their schedules.
If not today, tomorrow morning.
Should I invite Jackie, too?
Well, she qualifies as leadership.
- What about her ask?
- Stall her for now.
Let's see how the meeting goes.
I want you to write the speech,
every word.
- Yes, sir.
- And no leaks.
You'll have a draft in three hours.
And, sir... Doug emailed me
a lobbying strategy for AmWorks.
- Do you want to look at it?
- Of his own accord?
- You didn't tell him?
- No, I didn't say a word.
It must be what he gathered
from watching the news.
- How is he?
- Uh, Doug seems fine.
I've been calling him, like you asked.
- But he seems all right?
- Well, he tells me things are good,
although I don't think
he'd admit it if they weren't.
Why don't you stop by
from time to time, since I can't.
- See him in person.
- Yes, sir.
And send me his email.
Claire?
I'll be in my study if you need me.
What're you working on?
- Brought you a coffee.
- My savior.
The leadership meeting
yesterday morning.
It lasted four and a half minutes.
Where'd you hear that?
That's not long enough
to reject a major domestic agenda.
I wasn't in the meeting.
I don't know how long it lasted.
- Something went down.
- If you say so.
Uh, I didn't hear anything about it.
Could've been the president
was called away.
- That happens all the time.
- Not this time.
How do you know?
Clearly, I have a source
that knows more than you.
Most sources do.
At least they pretend they do.
Thanks for the coffee.
Two sugars next time.
I'll remember that.
You talked to Ayla Sayyad.
I can either be an asset or a liability.
You think this puts you
on the ticket now?
Not if you tell him.
But the smart move would
be to advocate on my behalf.
Don't strong-arm me, Jackie.
You're the man in the middle.
Who else would I strong-arm?
I want to be on your team, Remy.
We do well when we're on the same team.
You have more calls?
No. I'm done.
- Who spoke to her?
- I have no idea, sir.
- Well, it's your job to know.
- Things are moving fast.
I'm just trying to stay ahead of them.
Well, we need to move faster.
Has the meeting been set?
Eight a.m. tomorrow.
I just heard back from Birch's office.
Good. Let's have the networks
ready to go live by nine.
One more thing. Jackie.
I think you should decide
sooner rather than later.
If we're gonna go this route,
we need every ally we can get.
After the meeting. We'll discuss then.
You've emerged.
Hi.
I took a nap.
Last night was...
I didn't get much sleep.
Me, neither.
We're gonna find something for you.
Some other position, or something
as First Lady, I promise.
I know.
- What are you doing up?
- I've got to go over my speech.
It's happening tomorrow night.
What speech?
It's premature, isn't it?
Read on.
Yes?
Yes.
Thank you. Please.
I put a great deal of thought
into what you've all asked of me.
I challenged myself
to keep an open mind.
And my decision is:
I will not run for president.
Look, they're thinking
it's too good to be true, and it is.
I lied in the Oval Office before.
I didn't want to take
the chance this time.
It's too big a deal to jinx myself.
At nine o'clock tonight, I will
announce to the nation my decision.
What's the catch?
I wanted us to meet here
in this room for a reason.
For the past five months,
my team has sat at this very table,
developing America Works.
You know how much
the program means to me,
and I want it to mean as much to you.
- So there is a catch.
- No, an opportunity.
Look, we all know the--
All right, let's just say for...
argument's sake
that this table here represents
the next year and a half, all right?
So, this is us right now.
And down there at the end,
that's the election.
Now, if I did run, I'd spend
the next few months fundraising.
And then somewhere around here,
I'd formally announce.
And then even if I did win the nomination,
say, somewhere around here,
I'd start to have to face off with
a Republican challenger, probably Mendoza.
And then things would get brutal.
Daily, daily events.
Fending off attacks.
Launching my own.
And... you're right.
In the end...
...I'd probably lose.
I would spend 18 months campaigning,
which would leave no time to govern.
But you have opened my eyes.
I feel liberated.
I want to spend these next 18 months
dedicated to one thing:
America Works.
But I need your help to do it.
You're putting an awfully big price tag
on this, Mr. President.
No, you've put an awfully big
price tag on this.
You're asking me to be a placeholder
for 18 months and I intend to govern.
And if America Works succeeds,
then whoever you choose to run in 2016
not only has the backing
of a united party,
but a formidable legacy.
But Social Security?
Benefits. Entitlements.
We don't want to present a fresh face
only to shoot ourselves in the foot.
Then let's not pretend
to unite the party,
let's unite the party
behind this legislation.
We'll never get it past the Republicans.
We are not here to negotiate!
You want forward-thinking, Bob?
Then think forward.
You want a fresh face for 2016?
You wanna work together?
Then present my program to Congress.
And if it dies there, so be it.
But I want us to fucking try!
I am prepared to vacate this chair.
Meet me halfway.
Any moment now,
the president will be addressing
the nation live from the East Room.
The White House has remained silent on
the subject of the president's speech,
but sources in Congress say it
will focus on the jobs initiative
he's been planning
to unveil for several months.
The program, dubbed America Works,
was developed in secret. Any details
are the by-product of speculation,
but sources suggest
it will have elements
from both liberal
and conservative agendas.
What remains to be seen is whether
a Republican-controlled Congress
will cooperate in pushing
the program forward.
The White House has faced
significant opposition from the GOP
since Congress began
its current session,
and many speculate that the president's
liberal application of veto power
may leave congressional
leaders disinclined
to support this new jobs program.
Additionally, many Democratic
supporters of President Underwood,
from his days as House Majority Whip,
were voted out of office in November,
diminishing his personal influence
over legislators.
Low approval ratings
are a continuing concern
for the Underwood administration.
And congressional sources suggest
the choice to tackle unemployment
may be part of a campaign strategy
for 2016.
Recent polls indicate that less than one
third of all Americans say they would
consider voting for
President Underwood...
...job growth has remained a popular
platform in national elections,
and if today's announcement
is received well,
President Underwood's campaign
certainly has an opportunity to benefit.
Thank you.
Sir, we're ready for you
in five seconds.
Good evening.
For too long, we in Washington
have been lying to you.
We say we're here to serve you,
when in fact, we're serving ourselves.
And why? We are driven
by our own desire to get reelected.
Our need to stay in power
eclipses our duty to govern.
That ends tonight.
Tonight, I give you the truth.
And the truth is this:
The American dream has failed you.
Work hard? Play by the rules?
You aren't guaranteed success.
Your children will not have
a better life than you did.
Ten million of you can't even get a job,
even though you desperately want one.
We've been crippled
by Social Security, Medicare, Medicaid,
by welfare, by entitlements.
And that is the root
of the problem: entitlements.
Let me be clear.
You are entitled to nothing.
America was built
on the spirit of industry.
You build your future.
It isn't handed to you.
And the problem with Washington
is that we haven't given you
the tools to build it.
The only way for us to serve you is
to give you the means to serve yourselves.
Well, that's exactly
what I intend to do.
Not handouts. Jobs.
Real paying jobs.
In the next few weeks,
the Democratic leadership
will introduce a program
called "America Works."
Its goal is simple:
to put the ten million Americans
who are unemployed to work.
All of them.
If you want a job, you get one.
The cost
is five hundred billion dollars.
Now, that's a lot of money.
To pay for it, we'll need
to rethink Social Security,
healthcare and benefits
from the ground up.
We can't maintain
the welfare state as we know it.
Now, that's not a popular thing to say.
Anyone running for office
wouldn't dare utter those words.
Every advisor and consultant
and staff member
would beg a presidential candidate
not to say them.
But I can say them.
Because I will not be seeking
the Democratic nomination in 2016.
Candidates are cautious.
They must equivocate.
They dodge and tiptoe.
But I'd rather leave this office having
accomplished something of value
than secure another four years
having done nothing at all.
Franklin Delano Roosevelt
ushered in an era of hope and progress
when he proposed the New Deal.
And at the time,
his reforms were considered radical.
But he once said, "This country demands
bold, persistent experimentation.
It is common sense
to take a method and try it.
And if it fails,
admit it frankly and try another.
But above all, try something."
Roosevelt would have
understood better than anyone
the necessity
for trying something different.
The New Deal succeeded for many years,
but we must now try something newer
before it fails us.
If America Works succeeds,
we will reinvent the American dream.
If we fail in our attempt,
we will admit it frankly
and try another.
But above all, we must try something.
Thank you, and God Bless
the United States of America.
Hey.
It's two in the morning.
Yeah, I just left the White House.
The press conference,
phone calls, emails,
the rest can wait until tomorrow.
- Were you asleep?
- No.
This is a cool place.
How much is your rent?
I thought you said AmWorks was on hold.
Well, it was and then it wasn't.
The leadership didn't want him to run.
Who told you that?
Nobody. But I figure it's the only
reason he'd make that speech.
Hm...
- He's still gonna run though, isn't he?
- He says he's not.
I know him better
than you ever will, Seth.
There's no way he doesn't run.
Is that why you're here?
Because he needs my help now?
No, I just-- I wanted to check up
with you in person this time.
- He asked you to.
- Yes.
I did send him your email, though.
- What did he say?
- I'm not sure if he's read it.
You should probably get some sleep, huh?
Big day for the press team tomorrow.
You can report back. Alive and well.
Is it okay if I stop by now and then?
Do I have a choice?
I don't, but I can't force you
to open the door.
- Whatever you want.
- Thanks.
I'll see you soon.
Ms. Dunbar.
Mr. President.
I had a lot on my mind
when we last spoke.
- The speech last night, it was--
- Yes, it was a big decision
and I apologize if I was distracted.
- Not at all, sir.
- So, the drone strike case.
You've been pursuing
the State secrets defense.
Yes, sir.
- Heather-- May I call you Heather?
- Please.
The American people are sick of secrets.
That's the point I was
trying to make last night.
I promised the truth,
and now we're going to deliver.
What truth is that, sir?
A man had his legs blown off.
An American citizen.
We're going to own up to that.
We're going to admit that
the CIA conducted the drone strike
- and explain the reasons why.
- That information is classified.
Not anymore. You have my permission
to make the classified brief public.
Sir, that is not a sound legal approach.
- But it's what the country needs.
- We're not appealing to the country.
- We're appealing to nine justices.
- Wrong.
We're appealing to both
by taking responsibility.
Yes, a man was maimed,
his family members were killed.
But hundreds, perhaps thousands
of lives were saved as a result.
I understand the emotional logic,
- but we can't--
- You sat right there and told me
- even Supreme Court justices have hearts.
- Yes, but--
Far be it from me to tell you
how to do your job.
I've never practiced law
a day in my life.
But I have written them.
And occupying this office,
I know what the country needs.
It needs closure.
Let me work on a new argument.
- Thank you, Heather.
- Thank you, Mr. President.
- Where do you want these, ma'am?
- Anywhere. Just not in here.
Okay.
- Scott?
- Yes?
Here's a couple more.
Hey. You want a peanut butter and jelly?
No, thanks.
Is everything all right?
I want the UN job, Francis.
The Senate goes home in two weeks.
I want a recess appointment.
I prepared for it. I can do this.
And after it's all over,
if I've done the job I know I can do,
I'll be positioned
- for anything I want.
- Claire--
Now, I checked
with the White House Counsel.
There is precedent for a recess
appointment after a rejected nomination.
Only once,
but you wouldn't be the first.
And I know
you'll take a hit politically.
And I know people
will think I don't deserve it.
They'll have doubts in me.
But what if... this is as far as we get?
What if it's all over in 18 months?
I don't want to wait,
or settle for something else,
- when I've put all this work into--
- Okay.
I'll do it.
- You sure you don't want half?
- I'm not hungry.
I'll be in my study.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net