Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
More water, ma'am?
Yes, please.
How much longer, Ben?
Estimated four hours and 16 minutes.
Some breakfast, maybe? The usual?
That would be wonderful. Thank you.
Only about an hour until sunrise.
Last chance for those Northern Lights.
I could tell you about working
at a movie theater, some paper route.
Riding my bicycle five miles
to deliver seven papers
for ten dollars a month, but...
the truth is,
I didn't have a bicycle,
and I spent more time sneaking
into the movie theater
- than tearing tickets.
- So what was it, then?
My first job?
Oh, that can't go in the book.
Why not?
I worked for a man
who grew cannabis in the back woods.
A weed dealer?
No, a farmer. Uncle Henry.
He wasn't my uncle, but that's
just what everybody called him.
- What did you do for Uncle Henry?
- I packaged the product.
For some reason,
he trusted me with the scales.
Mm. And did you...
partake of the product?
No. Good old Uncle Henry,
he fertilized his crop
from his own septic tank.
Oh...
But it was a good job, though.
I saved up a lot of money.
It's how I bought all my books
my entire four years at The Sentinel.
Tell me about The Sentinel.
What was your first job?
No, no. Book's not about me.
The hustler in Scorpio.
That was you, wasn't it?
What makes you think that?
Don't writers write what they know?
The hustler's based on a friend of mine.
I didn't turn tricks.
I just... waited in the hotel lobbies
in case he got into trouble.
Tough life for a teenager.
Better than digging around in Dumpsters.
What happened to him? Your friend?
He died.
Was it AIDS, like in the book?
Suicide.
Why didn't you write it that way?
Because it was fiction.
Because... suicide is too selfish.
Let's talk later.
I have a few things
I gotta run over with Claire.
Sure.
It's a tight schedule, so we may not
be able to speak until the flight back.
No worries. First time in Moscow.
I've got a date with Gorky Park
and Swan Lake.
How's it going?
Cathy emailed me the statement.
We got the Kremlin
to tone down the language.
Do you think Corrigan will say it?
I'm sure he'll hate every word,
but if it means coming home...
The only reason that
Petrov is considering this
is because we have leverage in the UN.
You're both confident
that this is rock solid?
If Petrov doesn't cooperate,
the Secretary-General
will call an emergency session
the moment we land in the States.
Let's hope we don't
have to play that card.
Just don't give too much away.
Oh, listen, he's been marginalized
in the Security Council,
he's detaining an American citizen,
he wants to wash his hands of.
I think we'll find that we're dealing
with a much more reasonable man
than the one that visited Washington.
We fly back with a peacekeeping deal
and Corrigan.
Lemons to lemonade.
I think we should give Corrigan
our suite on the way back,
give him some privacy from the press.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
- Have you slept at all?
- No.
- Eaten anything?
- Not yet.
Here.
Come see this.
Isn't it the most beautiful thing
you've ever seen?
Earth to Max.
- Hey.
- You seem distracted.
Yeah, maybe a little.
Is it Kara?
Kara? What?
You should ask her out.
I know she'd say yes.
It'd be good for you.
Meet new people.
I can't. I don't trust myself yet.
What do you mean?
Hey, Max. Tell me.
You promise you won't judge?
I won't, I promise.
Well, after she left,
there were a lot of nights
of drugs and women.
And some of the women,
I don't even remember.
And Kara's a nice girl, so...
- But you're not that person anymore.
- There were some dangerous situations.
It was all really fucked up
and I wasn't always safe.
- Well, have you gotten tested?
- No.
Well, then you need to be tested.
I know, but it scares
the shit out of me.
Well, sure.
Do you want me to go with you?
No, I don't.
There's a clinic in Towson.
Plenty of my friends go there.
- You just walk--
- I get it! I get it.
I could go with you tomorrow
if you want me to.
- I don't need a mother.
- Hey, I'm not trying to mother you.
I just-- I care about you
and I want you to be safe.
Just--
Max.
Max!
Oh...
Thank you for releasing Mr.
Corrigan. It means a great deal to us.
And I'm sure a great deal
to his loved ones.
We all want the same things.
This is just a first step.
Mr. Litsky, my chief of staff,
will escort you to the facilities.
- Shall we?
- Mr. President.
- Thank you.
- After you.
So... we start over.
As though we meet
for the first time. Hm?
Please.
- Promise him a prison.
- A prison?
A brand new federal
corrections facility.
Why would his constituents
want convicts in their backyard?
They don't.
They do want jobs in their backyard.
He's been trying to get federal funding
for years. Birch has fought him on it.
Tell him you'll get Birch
to come around. If that doesn't work,
hint there might be a place for him
as Transportation Secretary.
He's owned by the auto industry.
His stance on carbon emissions
is deplorable.
Then balance him out
with whoever you have running the EPA.
I am not ready to make
cabinet commitments this early on.
It's not a commitment.
You're just open to considering him.
Doug? We should get started.
Use the auto industry to your advantage.
Whoever Winkowski supports,
every superdelegate backed
by Ford and Chrysler follows.
And if that doesn't work,
tell him you're considering Dick Butler
for Transportation. He hates Butler.
I gotta go.
Let me know what he says.
You're here to work on your body,
not work on your work.
When the boss calls...
Well, while you're on my turf,
I'm the boss.
Let's get in there
and lie down on the mat.
Yes, ma'am.
- Michael.
- Mrs. Underwood.
Claire.
You've been treated well?
Very well, as you can see.
Thank you, Mr. Litsky,
but I'd like to hear it
from Mr. Corrigan.
Yes, they've treated me well.
- You've seen a doctor?
- I have. Yesterday.
- You look thin.
- I've always been thin.
The president asked me to see you
in person to share the good news.
The terms of your release
have been finalized.
We'll be bringing you home
with us tomorrow.
I thought you'd be pleased.
What are the terms?
There will be a joint press conference.
- With Petrov?
- Yes, both presidents.
The agreement asks
that you make a brief statement.
I'm sorry, um, the type
is too small and I don't have glasses.
- We offered glasses to Mr. Corrigan--
- They did.
Mine broke during the arrest.
The other inmates don't get glasses.
I didn't want special treatment.
We provide glasses to anyone
who needs them, Russian or American.
That is a lie.
I will read it.
It says, "I, Michael Corrigan,
apologize to the citizens
of the Russian Federation
for breaking your laws.
I regret my part in exposing minors
to nontraditional sexual attitudes.
I am grateful to President Petrov
for the clemency my release demonstrates,
and for allowing me to return
to the United States."
Who wrote it?
It's the result of extended negotiations
between representatives
of the State Department
and the Russian Ministry
of Foreign Affairs.
I'm sorry, I can't say it.
I know it's far from ideal, Michael.
There is no ideal.
Other than repealing the law.
May we have a moment?
President Petrov asked me
to remain with you.
And I'm asking you to give us a moment.
Mr. Litsky?
I'm assuming this cell is bugged?
I know nothing about the facilities.
- Where is it?
- Mrs. Underwood.
If Mr. Corrigan and I
are to speak privately,
I would like to be assured
that it is truly private.
Show me where the bug is.
Thank you.
They're not going to repeal the law.
The statement is a prerequisite
for your release.
There are no negotiations here, Michael.
That part already happened.
- What about the 27 others?
- They're not American.
Well, if they're not gonna be released,
neither should I.
There's nothing we can do for them.
You're the First Lady,
and the ambassador to the United Nations.
And you're telling me there's
nothing you can do?
I refuse to believe that.
Michael, it was hard enough
to negotiate just for your release.
You'll have to drag me out of here
because I'm not giving that statement.
It's just words.
Words you can disown
the moment you're back on US soil.
Petrov's gay propaganda law?
That's just words, too.
So, command and control rotation.
Semi-annually, after the first year.
We pushed for immediate rotation,
- but the Israelis have--
- No, of course.
We need to earn their trust.
But we would never make
any major decisions
without consulting your generals first.
As long as there is transparency
and communication.
Well, that's the key
to this entire enterprise.
Mm-hm. Then after the first year
is fine and, uh...
troop numbers look agreeable,
are you sure you can procure
this many on your end?
Yes. I don't need Congress for that.
No, but the funding.
It comes out of the DOD budget
like any regular deployment.
Now, infrastructure
and logistical supplies for your troops,
well, we can add that expense
as ancillary support.
Hm. We can pitch in.
Well, whatever you could spare
would certainly be welcome.
Hm. But... that brings us
to the elephant in the room.
- Missile defense.
- Mm-hm.
Now, I can accept
a partial scale-back in Poland.
And it doesn't have to be... announced.
But we need to consider
the Czech Republic.
Tell me your concerns.
Your wife values privacy.
Excuse me?
We were talking missile defense.
Why did you bring up Claire?
She's... talking privately to Corrigan.
- It's no matter.
- Is there something wrong?
I hope not.
Now, missile defense.
A statement
for the Russian media.
- That's all it is.
- Let me ask you something.
Would you read that statement
if you were me?
Yes, I would.
You'd thank a man who says
you're dangerous to children?
You don't have to mean it.
You just have to say it.
I went on a hunger strike for six days.
Then I stopped.
Too hungry.
I couldn't go on.
One of the others that, uh,
I was arrested with, Sergei,
hung in there for 28 days.
They decided to force-feed him,
and they finally agreed
to let his mother visit.
Turns out it was too late,
on both counts.
Lots of news stories about me.
None about Sergei.
A man dies
and it's like nothing happened.
Because he's Russian.
I can't abandon the others in here.
Or the millions of people out there
who are told the way
they are born is wrong.
But back home,
you can share Sergei's story.
That doesn't do anything
for him or the others.
We will drag you out if necessary.
You don't have any power over that.
But the one thing I do have power over
is not making that statement.
Okay.
What if I can get them
to change the line
about nontraditional sexual attitudes?
- That's what bothers you most, right?
- You can't parse this.
- It's all or nothing.
- That's not how politics works.
But it's how revolution works!
How are things going?
May I speak with you for a moment?
- What are you up to?
- What do you mean?
Corrigan.
- Tell me what's wrong.
- You wanted him to refuse.
To embarrass me. Your wife told him
not to make the statement.
- That is ludicrous.
- You came here with false intentions.
No. Viktor, we knew
that he might be stubborn.
But this is a man with strong beliefs.
This statement is important to me.
Well, if anything, Claire
is trying to convince him to make it.
Then why did she ask for the
surveillance audio to be removed?
I don't know.
Perhaps so he wouldn't feel on the spot.
But, look, I wouldn't worry
about this just yet.
Claire is very persuasive.
Let me be very clear.
If there is no statement,
there is no deal on any front.
Not between us. Not for him.
He gets tried, convicted, sentenced.
Now, I asked Mr. Litsky
to inform them both.
I have complete confidence in my wife.
And Viktor, you must know,
this isn't part of any plan.
That's it.
There's no flexibility
with regard to the statement.
You don't cooperate, you go to trial.
Good. They can't keep me
from speaking in court.
What about your husband?
You've spoken to John?
I let him know we were hopeful.
How is he?
He's worried about you.
He wanted to come with us, but that
wasn't possible, for obvious reasons.
I promised to call after I saw you.
I was thinking... you'd call instead.
From Air Force One.
He'll understand.
He misses you, Michael.
I miss him. I miss a lot of things.
My parents. My friends. My dog.
More than two square feet of sunlight.
But it's the life we chose.
It's what our bond is built on.
John has been very vocal back home.
All he talks about is your release.
You're causing him pain.
And you don't have to.
And he didn't have to marry me.
- That's selfish.
- Maybe.
But so is contradicting everything
I believe in just to get out of this cell.
I think what you're doing
is more selfish. It's about ego.
Proving something to yourself.
And a man back home
is hurting because of it.
John is weak.
He'd say the statement in a heartbeat
if he spent more
than a few days in here,
which is why I'm here and he's not.
If he thinks I'm being selfish, so what?
Either he accepts it or he doesn't.
Isn't that what marriage is about?
Accepting your partner's selfishness?
You of all people should understand.
You know nothing about marriage.
You think it's about... sacrifice?
I think it's about respect.
And you're not respecting his pain.
- His pain doesn't matter.
- How can you say that?
Because mine doesn't either.
You know what I've been asking myself
ever since the hunger strike?
Am I truly willing to die for this?
I don't know the answer
to that question.
But at least I have something
that I care enough about
to even ask the question.
Have you asked that of yourself?
What are you willing to die for?
Are you ready yet, Mrs. Underwood?
Not yet.
How much longer, if I might?
Please inform the president
I won't be leaving
until Mr. Corrigan comes with me.
- You can't stay here, Mrs. Underwood--
- Pass along the message, would you?
We can't have the First Lady staying--
You're not going to forcibly remove me.
So, please, do as I ask.
What are you doing?
Viktor is beside himself.
You need to convince him
to let go of the statement.
Look, you have to assume
we're being overheard.
This is not a secure line.
Anything I'm saying, I'd say
to Petrov himself if he were here.
I thought you were convincing Corrigan
to make the statement.
Francis, I'm doing my best, but we need
to come at this from both sides.
Well, he's adamant. He's not gonna
back down and I don't blame him.
Corrigan's adamant, too.
The entire deal hinges on this.
Now, Viktor made it very clear
what his needs are,
- and we made promises before we--
- I'm trying to salvage the situation.
There isn't much time. We're scheduled
to get back on the plane tomorrow
and the press expects Michael
to get on with us.
Viktor, if you're listening to this,
please know I'm advocating
on your behalf.
But you might want
to consider letting the statement go.
He's not gonna do it, Claire.
Just talk to him, Francis.
If he won't let it go,
see if he'll tone it down some more.
He doesn't want all of this
to fall apart either.
All right. I'll see what I can do.
I'll keep you posted.
- Oh, this is great. Thank you.
- Uh-huh. If I could have a receipt...
- Oh. Excuse me. Sorry.
- I appreciate it.
Hey, Max.
I'm here at the clinic.
Are you okay? You sound--
I'm scared. They're about to take
the blood sample. Can you come?
Please, I'm really scared, Lisa.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
I'll be there as soon as I can, okay?
Yeah. Just hold tight.
Hey, um, I need to go.
Do you mind taking care of all this?
- Mm-hm.
- Okay, thank you.
Good news, Mr. Orsay.
You're negative on all fronts.
There are the results, for your records.
I've got some literature if you like,
on protection,
preventative strategies,
how to avoid high-risk encounters.
No, thank you, I'm... I'm good.
Yeah, actually, I will take those.
I'm positive.
I just I can't--
I can't be alone right now.
Come with me. Come with me.
Okay?
- Stamper.
- You're good.
He said yes?
Took a couple of hours,
but he's on board.
Did you have to bring up Butler?
- The prison was enough.
- Great.
- Who's your next target?
- Willis Morrison, Twelfth District.
Ohio. I have his file at home.
I'll call you in an hour.
Surprise, surprise.
You're on the phone again.
I'm on my time now, not yours.
You outta here?
Yeah, you were my last appointment.
Did that work today help?
It did. I feel great.
Well, you're making great progress.
And when you're fully recovered,
you know,
we'll have that cell phone
surgically removed from your ear.
See you later.
But isn't it even more powerful
coming from me?
It would ring hollow.
The words must come from him.
But no one will believe
he means them, anyway.
Whether he means them doesn't matter.
The fact that he says them
shows respect for our laws.
I wish he'd make the damn statement too,
and maybe he will. But if he doesn't,
you're willing to let all the work we've
accomplished today go down the drain
because of one loud-mouth protester
over a law you can't
possibly believe in?
No, you're right.
I don't believe in it.
Two of my cabinet ministers are gay.
My ex-wife's nephew is gay,
the one who is basically
like a son to me.
Personally, I don't care.
So if you don't care, let's haul him out
and put him on the plane.
Look, I don't want our deal
to fall apart any more than you do.
Your wife was right on the phone.
But there is more than just our deal
for me to consider.
I need to show strength.
No one's going to see this as a weakness.
On the contrary,
you'll be applauded for letting him go.
By who? Hm? The West?
You don't understand Russia,
Mr. President.
If people don't like the job you're
doing, they vote you out of office.
If they don't like the job I'm doing,
they topple statues.
Blood is spilled.
Chaos takes over.
Is the gay propaganda law barbaric? Yes.
Of course it is.
But religion, tradition,
for most of my people,
it's in their bones.
This law was passed for them.
I have to represent my people
the same way you do.
And if there is no cost
to Corrigan's actions,
many of my people will feel betrayed.
There won't be a revolution
because you freed one man.
Revolution sneaks up on you,
one small step at a time.
I don't take chances,
even with the smallest of steps.
No stone left unturned
when the First Lady's in town.
Can I ask you something?
If you pass the salt.
How did Michael Corrigan
become Michael Corrigan?
- Gay?
- An activist.
I'm sure you got a briefing
from the FBI.
Yes, but I would like
to hear it from you.
A friend of mine,
and this is in the early '90s,
she invited me to go with her
to a community organizing meeting.
I had nothing better to do,
so I said okay.
We get there and there's maybe
12 people in the room, tops.
It was pretty sad, actually.
And the guy speaking
is talking about garbage.
- Garbage?
- Recycling.
And the guy is putting
all 12 of us to sleep.
What he was saying made sense,
but... zero charisma.
It was worse: anti-charisma.
But I noticed
he had this habit of, uh...
tilting his head when he was
making an important point.
It was...
it was so endearing.
It was like this.
Like...
I couldn't help it. I fell in love
with him right then and there.
This was John?
A long time ago,
in a galaxy far, far away.
Well, he's pretty charismatic on TV.
He learned charisma.
I learned how to think.
We rubbed off on each other well.
I didn't know you'd been
together so long.
Twenty-one years.
Only been married for five
because, well, we couldn't earlier.
Francis and I just celebrated 28.
Over half your life.
That's true.
I haven't even thought about that.
You were young.
Twenty-two.
You ever regret it?
No. No. I love Francis.
Now more than ever.
I regret it.
Committing to someone
before I even knew who I was.
We didn't take legal vows,
but we had our own version.
- Stupid.
- Why?
Because all I've ever done is hurt him.
Um, kept him in my shadow,
cheated on him, you name it.
Well, it's the history that counts,
not the other things, right?
That's true. No substitute for history.
But it's unfair to him.
I don't believe in fairness.
I don't think you do either,
even though you fight for it.
And I don't believe
you love your husband more than ever.
- How could you possibly know?
- Takes one to know one.
John and I haven't slept with each other
in almost two years.
We don't even sleep in the same bedroom.
We've talked about separating,
but we never follow through.
It seems wrong to fight this hard for
marriage equality and then get divorced.
Bad for business.
Honestly, I don't think
it's how humans are built.
To be with each other for 50 years.
You don't have that option either,
do you?
How do you mean?
Well, if you wanted something else,
that would be really bad for business.
You should eat.
Said the snake to Eve.
Eat your apple.
The world won't end.
You need to get on the phone
and tell her to leave.
She wouldn't listen to me even if I did.
She's dead set on convincing this guy
for your benefit.
I'll have the guards escort her out
if necessary.
They will not lay a finger on my wife.
You'd actually prefer that,
wouldn't you?
So you could tell the world
we dragged the First Lady out by her hair.
I'm finding it more and more difficult
to tolerate your paranoia.
I could say the same of your lies.
When I lie to you, you'll never know it,
and it will be for a good reason.
Corrigan doesn't fall
into that category.
I should never have invited you here.
You and I can work together.
This afternoon is proof.
I would've been better off
holding my ground.
And forcing us to pass the resolution?
The United Nations?
They mean nothing to me.
If they meant nothing to you,
you would have held your ground.
But you want to be respected abroad
as much as you are at home.
And I came here out of respect, Viktor.
And I sympathize
with the situation you're in.
That we're both in.
Let's not let Michael Corrigan
dictate the course of nations.
Can we at least discuss
what a statement from me might look like?
You look exhausted.
I didn't sleep much on the plane, so...
You should go back.
There's no reason for you
to be in here with me.
I'm not leaving.
You're more stubborn than I am.
Why won't you let me help you?
I've made my demands clear.
Michael, let me tell you
what's going to happen
if you refuse to make this statement.
You'll help no one.
In fact, life will get worse
for the others you were arrested with.
Petrov will feel embarrassed.
He will arrest more people.
He will pass worse laws.
He's not going to let some American
homosexual dictate his policy.
This man is ruthless.
You think he's gonna become reasonable
suddenly when all of this falls apart?
You're being naive!
And you're letting other people suffer
because of it.
Don't undo what you've
fought so hard for.
You think you can shame me.
But you can't.
I'm giving you the truth.
I don't care how that makes you feel.
But do yourself the favor
of hearing what I said.
- I heard you.
- I hope so.
I can't betray myself.
What would I be then?
You'd be a politician.
And that's what you are.
Let the others do
all the yelling and screaming.
You want change?
Then learn how to compromise.
- Be a fucking adult about this, Michael.
- I need to think. Okay? I need time.
The plane leaves tomorrow.
You should go back.
I need time to think alone.
- Clear my head.
- I'm not leaving here without you.
I need time!
Just... lie down for a little bit.
Just get some rest.
- I just can't talk anymore.
- Okay.
Okay, I will.
For a few minutes.
Thanks.
There's treatment now.
The thing that angers me the most
is that I let her do this to me.
Did you feel that way about your ex?
The pain that just consumes you?
Oh. For a while, yeah.
Still, on bad days.
Mm...
What was she like?
Sorry, you don't have to...
No, I don't mind.
She was...
She'd had a tough life.
She had a lot of baggage.
Which I did, too.
We started out as friends
and then we moved in together.
And then it just happened.
We fell in love.
And I don't know, I guess...
I felt stronger with her.
And I think she felt the same way.
And I guess maybe it was naive,
but I thought that together,
we could let go of all that baggage.
Then we'd just be us.
Well, why did she leave?
She said everything
was happening too quickly.
Have you spoken to her... since?
Nope. She stopped coming
to the fellowship.
I stopped by her apartment once,
her landlord said she was gone.
Just no idea where she is?
We used to lie in bed
and fantasize about where we'd go
if we could go anywhere.
Paris, Australia, Timbuktu.
That was Rachel, the far-off places.
I didn't need that.
Where would you go?
The Jimenez Trail.
Where is that?
- New Mexico.
- Oh.
Cuts across the whole state.
It's got hot springs and waterfalls.
We used to say we'd go there, hike it,
find a good spot, build a cabin.
I'm sorry, we shouldn't
be talking about me.
I asked.
That tea smells good.
I think I'll have some, too.
This looks good.
- You say every word.
- Of course.
And then you take him
directly to the plane.
Viktor... thank you.
Hm... But the Czech Republic,
I want all the missiles gone,
not just a scale-back.
You can keep something in Poland
for show, but that's it.
- Agreed.
- So, we have a deal?
Including everything we discussed
about the Jordan Valley.
- Yes, of course.
- Then we have a deal.
Come, Mrs. Underwood.
Please. You shouldn't be here.
Mrs. Underwood.
I'm sorry.
Would you like to lie down for a bit?
Change your clothes?
- No, I can do that on the plane.
- Well, you go straight there.
- We have the press conference to do.
- I should be with you, Francis.
We have that handled.
I'd like to say something.
A few warm words to his family.
Yes. Yes, of course.
I'll echo your sympathy and then...
then say that I was planning
on releasing him today.
I'll thank you for your...
your generosity.
How tragic this has been.
And then a few words
about the Jordan Valley,
or if you'd prefer
to announce our agreement.
No, no, it's fine if you do.
Would you... mind if your people
showed me a draft of your remarks?
Yes, I'll have them
draft something right now.
And yours, too, Mrs. Underwood?
Yes. It's fine. Whatever you want.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Good morning.
Mrs. Underwood would like to start
by saying a few words.
As you all know, Michael Corrigan
was found dead in his cell this morning.
He had hung himself.
Michael and I spoke briefly yesterday.
He was being treated well
and was grateful to President Petrov
for granting his imminent release.
We don't know why...
Michael chose to do what he did.
We all wanted nothing more
than for Michael to come home today
and we offer our heartfelt condolences
to his family and his loved ones.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mrs. Underwood.
Mrs. Underwood?
I didn't just speak to him yesterday,
I was there when it happened, asleep.
He hung himself with my scarf.
I do know why Michael
decided to take his own life:
because he didn't want to lie.
And I can't dishonor him
by telling a lie now.
Claire...
I was trying to convince him
to say that he broke the law,
to thank President Petrov.
But he refused, because he didn't want
to leave until the law was repealed.
Until the Russians who were arrested
for the same crime were also released.
Michael was willing to die
for what he believed in.
- Thank you, Mrs. Underwood.
- He was brave.
- And his voice deserves to be heard.
- That's enough.
If it weren't for this unjust law,
and ignorance and intolerance
of your government,
Michael would still be with us.
Shame on you, Mr. President.
My wife has been under a...
great amount of stress
these past 24 hours.
She's clearly in shock.
My apologies to President Petrov
and to the Russian people.
If you'll excuse me,
I need to be with her now.
- Claire.
- Don't, Francis.
It's imperative that I speak to him.
Well, keep trying, Cathy.
If Petrov won't get on the phone
with me, then I'll speak to Bugayev.
Whoever will get on the phone
with me, then.
All right. Thank you.
Your coffee, sir.
Thank you, Ben.
- Mr. President.
- Later.
I just got off the phone with Cathy.
The deal's off.
Everything we negotiated.
We have to discuss the next move.
I know what I did. It seemed impulsive,
- but it wasn't--
- It happened. Let's move on.
If you have something
you would like to say, Francis...
I just want to minimize the damage.
If Petrov won't come around,
we have to move forward
with the resolution at the UN.
We're prepared for that.
Good. Thank you.
Try to get some sleep.
Shouldn't you be in the back,
with the press?
- I'm not press.
- You're not staff either.
My apologies.
Mrs. Underwood?
You did the right thing.
I know you're angry.
You should be.
But I had to do it.
Is this some sort of apology, or you
need to get something off your chest?
I want you to try and understand.
Understand?
- What you did was beyond--
- I know.
You're not only the First Lady,
and an ambassador,
you're also my wife.
- In what order?
- Oh, come on, Claire.
I said what I said for him.
Not for myself, not for us.
I felt we owed him more
than a few false words.
So you want me to forgive you?
To say that it was okay?
- No.
- Because I can't do that.
- I'm not asking you to.
- Then why are we even discussing it?!
- Because I want you to know why.
- I don't care why.
I don't care what your reasons are.
There is no reason
that can possibly convince me
that you should have sabotaged
a peace plan we spent months on!
It was a political mistake.
Yes, I admit that.
But if I had said nothing,
- his death would have meant nothing.
- No. Not death. Don't give him that.
- Suicide.
- No. Something undeniable.
I was not gonna try and deny it.
- I don't even understand that.
- If you'd give me a chance.
I gave you a chance with the recess
appointment, with the resolution,
with handling Corrigan.
He didn't have a choice, Francis.
We cornered him.
- He did have a choice.
- Not in his mind.
No one forced him to protest in Moscow.
And we sure as hell didn't ask him
to tie your scarf around his neck!
If you had spoken to him...
and heard what he had to say--
Oh, what, I would have
had some moral epiphany?
- Yes, you would have.
- I don't think so.
Because I'm the President
of the United States
and I can separate the big
from the small.
He wasn't small.
He was a coward and I'm glad he's dead.
He had more courage than you'll ever have.
Do you really want
to discuss courage, Claire?
Because anyone can commit suicide,
or spout their mouth
in front of a camera.
But you wanna know
what takes real courage?
Keeping your mouth shut,
no matter what you might be feeling.
Holding it all together
when the stakes are this high.
We're murderers, Francis.
No, we're not. We're survivors.
If we can't show some respect
for one brave man
and still accomplish
what we set out to do,
- then I'm disappointed in both of us.
- I should've never made you ambassador.
I should've never made you president.
What are you looking at?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net