And here's another
interesting weather fact.
Another? Great!
Changes in jet streams
can affect the speed
at which the Earth
rotates on its axis,
so bad weather can actually
make the day longer.
Well, there must be a hell
of a storm somewhere.
Joke if you must, but you're
going to miss these moments.
With Leonard home
in a few days,
this was your last time driving
me to the grocery store.
You know, I will miss this.
I'll tell you what, if
my apples are mealy,
we'll hit the produce section
for one last crazy blowout.
Heck, you can even
push the cart.
Please don't take my looking
forward to Leonard's return
as criticism of the job you've
been doing in his absence.
I won't.
That criticism will come
later in your report card.
Yeah, I didn't stay for the detention,
I'm not gonna read the report card.
- Hello.
- Leonard!
- Shh, shh.
- Hi!
- Keep your voice down.
- Oh, my God.
You weren't supposed
to be here till Sunday!
We finished the experiment early, so I
thought I'd come home and surprise you.
Oh, my gosh, why
are we whispering?
I didn't tell Sheldon, so we
could have a few days alone.
Oh, that is so romantic.
Uh, sure, that's why I did it.
Oh... I just cannot
believe you're here.
Penny, it's your lucky day!
Three of the eggs are clearly
not jumbo. Grab your keys.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x02 ♪
The Deception Verification
Original Air Date on September 26, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Uh, Stuart, I was wondering if you
could help me find something.
Happy to, unless it's
hope or a reason to live.
Oh, you make me
laugh, sad clown.
Anyhoo...
Leonard will be back in a couple days
and I need a welcome-home gift for him.
As he's been at sea, perhaps something with
a nautical theme might be appropriate.
Okay, well, I don't know how
much you want to spend,
but I do have this pretty
cool Aquaman statue.
Aquaman?
Oh, this isn't a
gag gift, Stuart.
Yeah, just as well. It's
a pretty rare piece.
I'd rather just sell it
to a real collector.
I'm a real collector.
How rare is it?
Oh, I shouldn't even
have mentioned it.
How about a Batman squirt gun?
Don't try and trick me into
buying something I don't want.
Now let's talk Aquaman.
What were they thinking, putting Doctor
Octopus's mind in Spider-Man's body?
Well, I've been
quite enjoying that.
It combines all the
superhero fun of Spider-Man
with all the body-switching
shenanigans of Freaky Friday.
Both versions:
original and Lohan.
"Both versions: original and
Lohan." You're an idiot.
Hey, what's your problem?
I'm sorry, I've been
kind of snippy lately.
It's probably this
stupid diet I'm on.
Why are you on a diet?
I've put on a couple pounds.
Had to buy these pants
in the men's section.
Well, we've all seen your mom.
That Butterball turkey was
bound to come home to roost.
$1,200!
That's my final offer!
All right, Sheldon, you win.
I'm sure Leonard
is gonna love this.
Oh, right, a present
for Leonard.
You better throw in
that squirt gun.
Yeah, I don't know. This squirt
gun, it's, uh, it's pretty rare.
Ooh.
And this is me doing
the Titanic pose on the boat.
Ah.
And... oh.
That's me getting rescued
after I fell in.
Oh.
- Oh, that's the pizza.
- Yep.
- Here's some money.
- Thank you.
And I'm gonna hit the head.
That's what us salty sea dogs
say when we have to go pee-pee.
- Hey.
- $22.50.
Okay, here's, uh, $25.
Keep the change.
Seriously? I just walked up,
like, four flights of stairs.
Oh. Okay. Well, here's, um...
30-something cents and a
promise I won't call your boss and
tell him you reek of marijuana.
Oh, Penny, I see
you've ordered pizza.
- I have Chinese food.
- That's nice.
Oh, that's a rather
earthy cologne.
My uncle used to wear that.
Perhaps we can enjoy one last meal
together before Leonard returns.
Yeah, thanks, but I kind of feel
like eating alone tonight, so...
Are you sure?
With your Italian pizza and my Chinese
noodles, we could play Marco Polo.
I mean, of course, a
reenactment of a meal
in the life of Marco Polo
the Venetian explorer,
not Marco Polo the
terrifying water sport.
Uh, yeah, it sounds
fun, but no thanks.
- Have a good night!
- What, now... do you have company?
No. No, no, no.
You know what? Th-The
toilet's been doing that.
I called
the building manager, so...
- Oh, I can take a look at it.
- Well...
I'm quite familiar with plumbing.
Not to brag,
but I spent most of fifth grade
with my head in a toilet.
Yeah, no, no, no. You know
what, Sheldon, it's okay.
You don't have to go
into the bathroom.
That's curious.
If there's no one here, why are there
two glasses of wine on the table?
Oh.
Well, you know, I-I've got two hands
and a bit of a drinking problem.
- Of course. Ask a silly question.
- Oh.
- That's odd.
- Um, what?
There are takeout containers
in the trash can.
So? That's my dinner
from last night.
What's odd is they're
in the trash can.
Okay. Look, honey, I promise there's
no one's here. I've had a long day.
I just want to have
a quiet dinner by myself.
Oh, very well.
I'm no stranger to enjoying
the pleasures of solitude.
- Oh!
- What?
Have you gotten Leonard
a welcome-home gift yet?
- No.
- Oh, great.
Do you want to go halfsies
on a $200 squirt gun?
- Hi, honey.
- Hey.
I made some brownies.
You want one?
You're kidding, right?
I mean, you know I'm
trying to lose weight.
God, I thought we were
partners in this marriage.
We are. Stop it. And for the
last time, you're not fat.
Really? Tell that to the bathroom
scale, 'cause one of you is lying.
Fine, forget I asked.
- How was dinner at your mom's?
- Awful.
I had to rub her ointment
all over her again.
Why can't she do it?
'Cause we've got a deeply
unhealthy relationship.
Which reminds me, do you think you can
get any samples of this from work?
This was supposed
to last her a month,
but they didn't take into account
the square footage of her back.
Let me see.
How long have you been
putting this on her?
I don't know. Few weeks. Why?
This is really strong
estrogen cream.
Please tell me
you've been wearing gloves.
Like these swollen sausages
could fit in gloves.
Howie, the estrogen's getting
absorbed by your skin.
That's why you've been all bloated and
moody and a giant pain in the ass.
You're full of estrogen
and you don't act like that.
That's 'cause I'm a woman.
I've had years of practice
riding the dragon.
Fine. I'll wear
gloves next time.
It's still gonna take a few weeks for
the hormones to leave your system.
I feel so stupid. And fat.
It's okay. You still
look great to me.
In fact, why don't we go in the
bedroom and I'll prove it to you?
Sex? Really? I mean, that's just
your solution to everything!
Oh, and here's a fun thing.
I worked it out so that there are
two different words for spoon:
"planko" and "janko."
"Planko" is a spoon with food,
"janko" is a spoon
without food.
"Janko" is spelled
with a silent "ptang."
Sheldon,
you're not even listening to the
rules of my made-up language.
Yes, I am.
Then what does
"tweepadock" mean?
Uh...
elephant?
Lucky guess.
I'm sorry. I'm just distracted by
something that happened over at Penny's.
What happened?
I fear Penny is being
unfaithful to Leonard.
What?
She claimed to be alone when there was
obviously someone else in her apartment.
I have no choice but
to assume the worst,
given Leonard's lengthy sea voyage and
her famously ravenous nether regions.
I don't think Penny
would cheat on Leonard.
Oh, really?
She and I once had
a staring contest.
She clapped really loud
and made me blink.
It's a small leap from
there to sexual infidelity.
You're being ridiculous.
Amy, there were Chinese
food containers...
in the trash can.
Poor Leonard.
- Do you hear anything?
- I hear a woman's voice.
- Is it Penny?
- No, it's you.
All right,
I hear whispering and giggling.
Now I think I hear kissing.
Yeah, like you know
what kissing sounds like.
There's kissing in Star
Trek, smarty-pants.
Let me listen.
- Sounds like Leonard.
- Please.
Why would Leonard come home early
and waste his time kissing Penny
when he could be hanging
out with his best buddy?
Yeah, that's it.
I'm catching her in the act.
No, Sheldon, don't.
- Aha!
- What the hell?!
Leonard?
Sheldon, you cannot just
barge in here like that!
Right.
Penny!
Are you going to answer the door or
should I open it and say "aha" again?
I'm sorry, Sheldon. I should've
told you I was back.
I just wanted to have a
couple days alone with Penny.
Oh, no, I should apologize.
Uh, I never realized to what extent
our friendship was a burden to you.
That is not fair.
I complain about what a burden
it is at least once a month.
Oh, no, no, let's
not sugarcoat this.
You find me finicky,
pedantic and annoying.
No, he doesn't.
I actually have used
those exact words before.
In that order.
Well, Leonard, I think it's high time you
and I address the "tweepadock" in the room.
The what?
- Amy?
- Please leave me out of this.
Uh...
fine. Leonard,
there's no need for you to
pretend to like me anymore.
Come on, I said I was sorry.
No, no, you save your apologies for after
you've had disappointing coitus with Penny.
It was fine.
Come on, this is silly.
Hey, um, I brought you back a
little present from my trip, huh?
It's that sailor cap
that you wanted.
It's neat, huh?
You honestly think you can buy back
my friendship with a cheap souvenir?
I don't.
No, I really don't.
Just try it on.
Oh, yeah.
- Hello, sailor.
- Ooh, now we're talking.
Excuse me.
This changes nothing.
Except the Halloween costume
I'm wearing this year.
Amy, you're going to be Olive Oyl.
Lay off the donuts.
- Thanks for coming over.
- No problem.
Ooh, you made
little sandwiches!
Yeah, that's cucumber and cream cheese.
That's turkey and loganberry.
And don't tell my hips, but I'm
warming up a brie in the oven.
Nice. So...
Mmm. What's up?
Okay, well, I've been reading up on all the
side effects
you can get from
estrogen, and...
I need you to be honest with me.
Do my boobs look bigger to you?
Well, it's kind of hard to tell.
Come on, Raj, it's a
"yes or no" question.
I'm not sure.
Um, wait.
Jump up and down--
let's see if they jiggle.
Uh, no, I... I still
can't tell, uh...
Oh, you know what? Okay,
uh, give me some of this.
- Seriously?
- Do you want my help or not?
Fine.
Okay, yup.
See, see, that-that looks like...
that looks like they could be bigger.
But you know, I bet... I bet when
I do it, mine do the same thing.
Yeah, they kind of do.
Hmm. Uh, let me
see something.
Hey, easy!
- My nipples are sensitive.
- Oh.
Sorry, sorry, uh...
Okay.
I mean...
Yeah, m-maybe.
Okay, let me feel.
No, I am definitely
up a cup size.
You know, b-but they're very firm,
so you've got that going for you.
- You think?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, very perky.
Thank you.
I really needed
to hear that today.
- Ooh, brie's ready!
- Yay!
- Good morning.
- Hello.
So am I driving you to work
or are you still mad at me?
I'd like a ride.
Assuming you actually
do take me to work.
Where do you think
I would take you?
Who knows?
Uh, you said you'd
be home yesterday,
but you came home
three days ago.
You say you're taking me to
work, but for all I know,
I'll end up in a
deserted amusement park.
Or a cornfield maze.
Or a back alley dog fight.
You tell me.
I'm going to work. You
can come if you want.
Okay.
By the way, you have
something on your shirt.
No, I don't.
Hurts, doesn't it?
You know, I find myself wondering if
anything you've ever told me is true.
I didn't make it back. The
ship sank, I'm in hell.
You say you're from New Jersey,
but how can I believe you?
Why would anyone claim to be
from New Jersey if they weren't?
All right,
I'll give you that one.
Hey, I said I was sorry. What
else do you want from me?
I want you to admit that
what you did was wrong.
Fine. What I did was wrong.
I wish I could believe you.
You know what? I'm not
driving you to work,
because you're
incredibly annoying.
You say one thing
and do the other,
so then you are driving me
and you find me a delight.
- Stop it.
- Keep it up?
- Bye!
- Hello!
So I guess you're really holding
up the other four fingers?
Oh, hey, what are you
doing here so early?
Driving Sheldon to work.
- He's still mad at Leonard, huh?
- Well, he's mad at you, too.
He says you're the succubus
who led his friend astray.
I don't know what
"succubus" is, but...
it has "suck" in it,
so that can't be good.
- Thought I heard you out here.
- Hey, Sheldon.
You don't get a "hey."
You get a "hmm."
Come on, don't be like that.
We had so much fun together
the last couple of months.
You're right.
Which makes your betrayal
all the more devastating.
Sheldon...
I let you buy feminine hygiene products
with my supermarket club card.
You have any idea the kind of coupons
I'm going to get in the mail now?
Sheldon, your fight's with Leonard.
Penny's got nothing to do...
Careful, Amy.
The friend of my enemy's
girlfriend is my enemy.
- Really?
- Yes.
You're either with me
or against me.
You want to take
the bus to work?
Maybe there's a third option.
FYI, I had a doughnut
for breakfast, you jerk.
So now we're just waiting for the
data from the ship to be crunched,
but the numbers look
pretty promising.
That's so great.
If you guys prove the existence
of Unruh radiation...
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
My eyes are up here.
Howard, Raj.
Judas.
You know what?
You're a crazy person.
A crazy person with a long memory, and if
all goes according to plan, a robot army.
- Stop it.
- Or a mutant army.
It depends on how
my Kickstarter goes.
I said, stop it!
Now, listen to me.
You two aren't just friends.
You're best friends.
And that's a beautiful thing.
I mean, Leonard, you know
why he's so mad at you?
It's 'cause he missed you!
Yeah, and as his friend, you should
be happy he has love in his life.
As I do.
This man held my breast the other
day, and I love him for it.
A little loud, dude.
So, can we please put aside
these petty differences
and just be glad
we're here together?
- Okay.
- I suppose so.
Thank you.
Uh, it wasn't anything weird. It
was just to see how big they were.
And then Leonard took me
to the barber and the dentist,
and then to cap off
the perfect day,
the Los Angeles Bureau
of Weights and Measures.
I thought the measures were going
to be the stars of the show;
turns out it was the weights.
I'm so glad you guys
are friends again.
And I'm glad you and I
are friends again, too.
- Aw.
- Which reminds me.
This came in the mail,
and I want you to have it.
"50 cents off Vagisil."
Think of me when you apply it.
Uh, can I just say,
I've missed all of us
hanging out together.
- Yeah.
- Me, too.
Um, since when can Koothrappali talk
in front of the girls without a beer?
Oh, that happened
right after you left.
And no one told me?
Can't believe we
forgot to tell him.
Think of Sheldon
when you apply it.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net