Hey, can I ask you a question?
Sure.
You've had this dart board
since I've known you,
but I've never seen you play.
Oh, uh, we played... once.
I broke a window.
What window?
That one over there.
Leonard, where are
the Skee-Ball tickets?
Skee-Ball tickets?
Yeah, from when we went
to the arcade three years ago?
I finally decided
what prize I want.
Hurry up.
Uh, if I still have them,
they're probably
in the junk box.
Ooh, what are you gonna get?
None of your business.
But when you see me
wearing a flower
in my lapel later,
you are most welcome
to sniff it.
Yup, oh... here you go.
Oh, thank you.
Here, get yourself an eraser
for your troubles.
Oh.
Oh-ho.
I forgot about this.
My aunt made it for me
when I started college.
Aw, did she hate you?
Why? Because I got an
ugly, itchy sweater,
and my brother got a car?
No, I was her favorite.
Yeah, I seem to be
a few tickets short.
Are there more in the box?
Hmm, I think I got them all.
Nope, they're not in there.
Well, you barely looked.
Let me see.
No, no, no, I-I looked, and...
(stammers)
No more tickets.
Leonard, let me
look in the box.
Okay, okay!
I'm gonna show you
what's in the box.
but just...
promise not to flip out.
Why would I flip out?
Is it a spider?
(gasps)
It's a spider!
No, if it was a spider,
Lenny would've flipped out.
Okay, Sheldon,
I know I was supposed to return
this DVD a long time ago,
and I know we rented it
on your card.
But it's been, like, seven years
and clearly nothing
bad has happened.
So in-in-in-instead of being
a giant pain in the ass
like you always are,
what if
this one time
you just tried staying calm?
That seems
like a reasonable request.
Although so did,
"Hey, Leonard, would you mind
returning that DVD?"
I'm sorry.
I'll-Ill take care of it.
Okay.
I mean it, I'm going to.
I believe you.
And you're going to stay calm?
I said I would.
How about that?
Sheldon's being reasonable.
Yeah, it's freaking me out.
I'm gonna go.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x08 ♪
The Itchy Brain Simulation
Original Air Date on November 14, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
So... when you say
you're not going to freak
out about the DVD,
here's what that means.
Don't fixate on it.
Don't wake me up
in the middle of the night.
Or nag me through the door
while I'm on the toilet.
Okay, first, talking to you
while you're on the toilet
isn't exactly a picnic
for me either, okay?
Remember...
when you can hear me,
I can hear you.
And second...
you completely disregard
how uncomfortable
unresolved issues are for me.
It's-it's like, a...
an itch in my brain
I can't scratch.
When I broke my arm I used
to stick
a coat hanger down there.
You ever try that?
Maybe go in through the ear?
You wouldn't make jokes if you
could feel the way I feel.
Well, I don't know
how to do that.
How about this?
I promise I won't pester you
about the DVD.
You can defecate in peace.
That's a win for both of us.
But...
until this matter is resolved,
I would like you
to wear this sweater.
With nothing underneath it.
That's stupid.
Why?
You say it's itchy
and uncomfortable.
I say situations like this
make me feel the same way.
I'm telling you, try the hanger.
Put it on.
Let's share the experience.
You got it.
If this sweater
shuts you up,
I'm gonna make a fortune
selling them
to everyone we know.
Now...
all I need to do
is head down to the video store
and return the DVD.
Oh, did I forget to tell you?
That store went
out of business years ago.
Really?
How those nipples feeling,
chief?
Penny, can we please
get our drinks?
Yeah, hang on, just give me sec.
At work today, I did an
in vivo stereotaxic surgery.
Cool. At my lab,
I performed ten laser
capture micro-dissections.
I scraped gum off the
bottom of that table.
Only 'cause my manager
saw me put it there.
Oh, my gosh.
That's the girl that
broke Rajesh's heart.
That's Lucy?
I don't know why but I always
pictured her as Indian.
I think that reason's
called racism.
I'm gonna go talk to her.
Why? What are you gonna say?
I'm not gonna
say anything.
I just want
to check her out.
Because she hurt my friend.
My Indian friend.
Who's racist now?
You because you just called him
your "Indian friend."
Yeah, well, you're short.
We're never getting
our drinks.
No, but we knew that.
Hey, can I start you off
with something to drink?
Oh, water would be great.
Okay.
Um, you're Lucy, right?
I'm a friend
of Raj Koothrappali's.
Actually Amy recognized you.
Wow.
How's he doing?
Oh, you know, he's good.
Great.
Yeah, this is none
of my business.
But why did you break up
with him in an e-mail?
Oh, I don't know.
I guess I thought
it would be easier.
Yeah, I get that.
I'll go get you your water.
When you say "easier,"
you mean easier for you, right?
'Cause it certainly didn't
make it easier for him.
Any chance I can get
a different waitress?
I-I'm sorry, this is rude of me.
I will go get that water.
See, see, see, see.
Just now you expressed
your feelings to my face.
How come you could do that
with me, but not Raj?
I don't know your e-mail.
You know what the worst part is?
You're sitting here,
perfectly happy
and he's at home,
a blubbering mess.
Oh, I thought you said
he was okay.
Well, I also said
I was getting you water,
but look at me
still standing here.
You know, I may be
a bad waitress,
but you are a bad person.
Now, you want
to hear the specials?
So, you can never take it off?
No.
Not even to sleep?
So, you're just an idiot?
It's called proving a point.
Is the point you're an idiot?
Gentlemen, please.
Leonard is trying to walk a mile
in my metaphorical shoes.
He can't walk
in my actual shoes.
He has the feet of a toddler.
So, how are you gonna
return the DVD
if the store went
out of business?
(groans)
Monday morning I'll go downtown
look up the owner's information.
And send him the DVD.
Pay the late fee.
(grunts)
And prove to Sheldon
that you can have
a problem and solve it...
(grunts)
...without acting
like a complete lunatic.
Ah!
And the man impersonating
a bear would like everyone
to know that "Only you can
prevent forest fires."
I don't get it.
You didn't have
Smokey the Bear in India?
No. Oh, is he anything
like, uh, Mun-Mun the Mongoose?
He taught us not
to play with cobras.
You had to be taught
not to play with cobras?
not to burn down the forest?
Hey, if you guys were hungry,
why didn't you order
something at the restaurant?
We did, you never brought it.
Oh, that's right.
Nachos and a turkey club.
Not even close.
Well, I was too busy standing up
for my friend to worry
about your...
I want to say
salmon.
You want to say sorry.
So, how are you gonna
tell Raj abut what you did?
What do you mean "how"?
What's the big deal?
You told Lucy
he was a pathetic mess.
Then you made her cry and leave.
Okay, you guys are overreacting.
Raj is gonna appreciate
how I had his back.
What is wrong
with you, Penny?!
You ruined
any chance I had
of getting back
with Lucy!
(phone chimes) Now she knows
I'm a desperate mess
instead of just
being pretty sure!
It's Lucy.
She wants to meet
for coffee.
I love you, Penny!
Hey, what're you working on?
I'm thinking about
how one could use the fact
that a rapidly
rotating mirror
turns virtual photons
into real ones
as a method of
observing dark energy.
That's a pretty cool idea.
Yeah.
It's great you're here.
I'd love to get
an engineer's opinion.
Sure.
This chair is squeaky.
Now, do I fix it
or get a new one?
Well, Sheldon,
it took me all morning,
but I found the owner
of the video store.
And I am happy to report that
he died peacefully in his sleep,
drunk at the bottom of a pool.
Anyway, there is no one
to return the DVD to,
so this issue is resolved.
Ah...
And I'd just like
to point out that
even though the sweater
was uncomfortable,
I didn't use it as an excuse
to antagonize
everyone around me.
You know,
you could reimburse
the video store owner's
next of kin.
Or it's resolved!
Hey, that next of kin thing
sounds pretty good.
I believe
this is yours.
Can I ask you guys
a question?
So, I'm seeing Lucy
tomorrow night,
and I've never hung out with
someone who broke up with me.
How do you do it?
You can't let her
know you're hurting.
You know, the key
is confidence.
Why is the key
always confidence?
How come it's never
love handles and flop sweat?
If this girl hurt you so much,
are you sure you want
to see her again?
Well, if I may...
he has so little
self-respect
and is so desperate
she could literally sleep
with his own father
in his own bed
and post the video to YouTube,
and he'd still
buy her flowers
and ask her
to be his bride.
He's right.
But in my defense,
if we could survive that,
we could survive anything.
Well, if you're sure
you want to do this,
it's only coffee...
just relax
and see what happens.
Well, can I say
she looks nice?
Sure.
Can I tell her I miss her?
Maybe, if she asks.
Oh, can I show her
an oil painting I made
of us surrounded by our
children and grandchildren?
I'd save that
for the second date.
Good, good.
'Cause no matter how hard I try,
I cannot get the twins
to look alike.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just trying to find
the stupid next of kin
to this stupid video store owner
so I can return the DVD
and see the look
on Sheldon's stupid face
when he sees that
I didn't let this get to me.
(sobbing)
Sheldon's not here.
Why don't you take
the sweater off?
Th-Th-There's a principle
at stake!
Which is?
Oh, I don't know.
Who cares? Look at me!
Oh, my God!
Is that sweater made of bees?
Come on, take it off.
I won't tell.
No, no, honey,
if I take it off, Sheldon wins.
Sweetie...
every night you don't
kill him in his sleep,
he wins.
Nah, i-it's... it's almost done.
I just, I have to find...
(sighs)
the next of kin,
and send 'em the DVD
and then just wait for someone
with my complexion to die
so I can get a skin graft.
(sighs)
Smile.
What-what is that?
What is that for?
So you can send it to Princeton
and get your money back.
AMY:
must say, Sheldon,
you're handling
this DVD business
with an impressive
amount of maturity.
I don't know why
that surprises you.
I'm a grown man.
As should be evident
by this sport coat
and very real flower
in my lapel.
Is there some kind of new coping
mechanism you're employing?
The more interesting question
you should be asking is,
"What does this
flower smell like?"
I'm gonna go with sad.
So what's the story
with you and this DVD?
There's nothing to tell.
Maybe I purchased
a book entitled,
Don't Sweat
the Small Stuff
and I followed
its wise suggestions,
one of which was:
stop and smell the flowers.
Seriously?
Please.
(slight hiss)
Ha-ha!
Oh.
Hi.
Hello.
Oh, it's so good
to see you.
You, too.
Please, sit.
I, uh, I got you
a cappuccino.
I remembered
it was your favorite.
Oh.
I also got crumb cake,
but I remembered it was
my favorite and I ate it.
Anyway, uh,
how are you?
I'm pretty good.
Listen, I just wanted
to apologize
for breaking up
with you in an e-mail.
Well, and I ate all the
crumb cake.
we both made
mistakes.
Okay.
I'm so happy
you asked me here,
and I hope we can
hang out again sometime.
You know,
as friends,
lovemaking partners,
whatever.
Oh, uh...
I'm kind of
seeing someone.
I think I know
the answer to this,
but just to be clear,
it's not me, right?
This is all
your fault!
I should've
listened to Mun-Mun
because I've been
playing with a cobra
and her name is Penny!
Why are you so cruel?
Do you enjoy my pain?
There's a girl at the Cheesecake
Factory I can set you up with.
I love you, Penny!
How is it I can
conceptualize a methodology
of examining dark matter
in the universe
but can't figure out how
to fix a novelty squirt flower?
I think the real
question is,
why do you waste your time with cheap,
childish pranks?
There's probably a deep reason.
Which I'd be happy
to discuss with you
over some peanut brittle
in a can.
Okay, Sheldon,
I am out of options!
(door slams)
Video store owner,
Nursis Manookian,
has no next of kin!
Well, you seem hot
under the collar...
or is that the sweater?
Oh, oh, no, no.
I-It's because
I spent all afternoon
at the Armenian church where
his funeral mass was held.
According to
Father Solakian,
no one attended.
Luckily, my trip
wasn't a complete waste.
I lit a candle and
prayed for your death.
But I'm not Armenian,
so it probably won't work!
This is over, right?
Oh, not necessarily.
I suggest
you look for long-lost relatives
either in Armenia or Lebanon.
Listen to me, Sheldon.
I am not going to Lebanon
to return Super Mario Bros.
the movie!
You know, it might be fun.
You love hummus.
Why isn't this
bothering you?
I-Isn't your brain
getting itchy?
This is
on your card.
This could be ruining
your credit score!
Why isn't this
making you crazy?
Leonard...
I have something
to tell you,
but I want you to promise
not to flip out.
What?
Seven years ago,
I found out
the DVD was late
and I paid for it.
What?
I was going to mention
it at the time,
but then I thought,
some day,
this might be
a teachable moment.
Hah...
I... You...
How can...
What?!
Sheldon...
that was diabolical.
I know.
And it wasn't easy.
Do you have any idea
what it's like
to wait for years and never know
if you're going to finally
get satisfaction?
Wow.
You're even prettier
than Penny said.
I can't believe
a girl like you
doesn't have a boyfriend.
Well, I don't.
I don't believe you,
you're lying to me!
What?
Oh, it's okay.
I have no morals and
I'm desperately lonely.
I'll be the other man
if you want a little
something-something on the side.
What is wrong
with you?!
What is wrong with you?!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net