I got to tell you, the more
I read about the primordial
gravity wave discovery,
the more excited I get.
I know. Being an astrophysicist right
now is like being a rock star.
Only without the sex.
Yeah, literally, none of it.
What do you think
about it, Sheldon?
Meh.
Are you kidding me?
This may be the biggest scientific
breakthrough of our lifetime.
How can you, as a theoretical
physicist, not care about this?
Maybe it's because
I'm not an elitist.
What I'd like to know is:
How does this gravity wave breakthrough
help the man on the street?
You know? Wh-Who's
looking out
for Joe Six-Pack and all his
quantum physics concerns?
Oh, my God,
you're jealous.
Why would I be jealous?
Oh, I don't know. Maybe because the
origin of the universe just got proven,
the Higgs field
just got proven
and you've been working
on string theory
for the last 20 years and you're no closer
to proving it than when you started.
Yeah, well, I've had
a lot on my plate.
We happen to live in a
golden age of television.
Excuse me, fellas.
Sorry for eavesdropping,
but there actually was
some big string theory news today
out of the Hadron Collider.
Really? Did they find evidence to support
extra dimensions or supersymmetry?
No, but they did find evidence
that you'll believe anything.
Why would you do that?
- You're a string theorist as well.
- Incorrect. I am a string pragmatist.
I say I'm gonna prove something that
cannot be proved, I apply for grant money,
and then I spend it
on liquor and broads.
Later.
Do you think he's right?
Am I wasting my life on a theory
that can never be proven?
Maybe. But how great
is Game of Thrones?
♪ Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x20 ♪
The Relationship Diremption
Original Air Date on April 10
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Hey, you're up early.
I couldn't sleep.
I told you those Walking Dead
pillowcases were a bad idea.
No, that's not it.
Is something
bothering you?
Yes, but you
wouldn't understand.
Oh, come on, try me.
All right.
I've devoted the prime
of my life to string theory
and its quest for the
compactification of extra dimensions.
I've got nothing to show for it,
and I feel like a fool.
Okay. I get it.
I mean, not all the jibberjabber
in the middle, but...
I know what it's like to put your
heart and soul into something
and get nothing out of it.
You mean your
acting career?
No.
Your relationship
with Leonard?
No.
- Your failed attempt to
go back to college? - No!
I'm saying you and string theory
sound like a relationship,
and I know what it's
like to be in one
and realize it's never gonna
turn out the way you want.
I said Leonard;
You said no.
I'm talking about
other guys.
Okay.
Well, what do you do?
You have to have the courage
to end the relationship.
You know? Break it off,
shake hands, walk away.
I don't know if I can do that.
I know it's hard, honey, but in
the end, that's how you grow.
Penny, have you seen
my good inhaler?
Break it off, shake
hands, walk away.
Hey, how's dating
two women going?
Um, kind of hit a bump.
When I was honest and told Emily
she wasn't the only person
I was seeing, it went great. So I
tried the same thing with Lucy.
And?
She had mixed feelings.
But when I said,
"Emily was cool with it.
Emily's the best. Why can't
you be more like Emily?"...
...those feelings
became less mixed.
Women. Who knows
what'll set 'em off?
At least now I can focus all
my energies on just one girl.
I hope I get to meet her
as soon as possible.
Why the rush?
She isn't going anywhere.
She is. But I like
that attitude.
Gentlemen, is anybody interested
in my old string theory books?
You're really
going to do this?
I am. Yeah, Penny pointed out that what I'm
going through is essentially a breakup.
And according to
Cosmopolitan magazine,
one of the most effective
techniques for moving on
is to get rid of all reminders
of the relationship.
- You're reading Cosmo?
- Yes.
As it turns out,
there's an article,
on how to get over a breakup
in literally every issue.
Anyway, it suggests that
I set these on fire,
but the smell of burning books reminds
me of church picnics in East Texas.
- What's this?
- Oh,
that's just a doodle of a
hyperelliptic Riemann surface.
Oh, yeah. Wasn't that the basis
of your postdoc fellowship?
It was.
This seemed so
elegant at the time,
but... now I realize I was
just a simple country boy
seduced by a big city theory with
variables in all the right places.
- It's going to be okay.
- I know.
As hard as this is,
I have to move on.
I can't keep postulating multidimensional
entities and get nothing in return.
I have needs, too.
So, you and Emily
still together?
I spoke to Bernadette.
She's free tomorrow night.
Oh, okay, great.
But if we're really
gonna do a double date,
then we have to go over some
ground rules about Emily.
Like when it turns out she's made
of rubber, I don't say anything?
She's very real.
Oh, that's what it
says on the box.
Right next to
"dishwasher safe."
See? This is exactly
the kind of thing
I'm worried about you
saying in front of her.
I promise I'll be on
my best behavior.
You better be. No jokes about
how close I am with my dog.
Or the truth about how
close I am with my dog.
- You got it. - No jokes about
the year I took ballet.
You took ballet?
God, you never listen.
Are you sure you
want to do this?
The magazine articles suggest
that one of the ways
to get over a breakup
is a new look.
Mmm. What about your old look,
well-groomed ventriloquist doll?
- "Oh, my God, I do look like that."
- Stop it!
- So, how do you want
me to cut it? - Oh,
how about Bill Gates
meets Nikola Tesla?
So, business in the front,
science in the back.
Or I don't cut it and maybe
just style it a little.
Oh, I'm in your hands.
Do a good job and I'll tell you Cosmo's
ten dynamite tips to enjoy your PMS.
Can you keep him quiet? Maybe
jangle some keys in front of him?
That doesn't work anymore. He just
thinks I'm taking him to the doctor.
So, now that you're no longer invested in
string theory, what are you gonna pursue?
Oh, there are so
many exciting areas:
- Black holes, dark matter...
- Oh,
Leonard was telling me about dark matter,
but I didn't really understand it.
Don't feel bad.
Neither does he.
Okay...
what do you think?
Have you ever even seen
a picture of Tesla?
It actually looks
good, Sheldon.
- Doesn't it?
- Yeah.
I suppose I could see myself
in a scientific boy band.
Of course, I'd be the dreamy
one and the smart one.
Sorry I'm late.
What did you do?
I gave him a new look.
It's cute, huh?
Yeah, it's cute.
That's the problem.
I don't need other girls to see him
walking around like sex on a stick.
She's right. I'm too hot.
I'm excited to meet Emily.
Me, too. I just hope
he doesn't blow it.
Why would you say that?
Because he's Raj--
that's his thing.
Beckham can bend it, Ralph
can wreck it, Raj can blow it.
Look, I don't want
it to happen,
but odds are he's gonna
find a way to...
Oh, crap, I
know that girl.
- How?
- In a bad way, very bad.
- Hey, guys. - Whatever you hear
tonight, just remember I love you. Hey!
Emily, these are my good
friends, Howard and Bernadette.
- Guys, this is Emily.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Have we met before?
Uh... no.
I-I don't... I don't...
think so.
- You sure? You look familiar.
- Well, you sure don't.
You I know, you
I know, you?
Total stranger.
Even if you had yummy candy,
I would not get in your van.
Did you go to that spin
class on Green Street?
That must be it.
Since when do you
go to spin class?
Wow. Now who
doesn't listen?
Sheldon, your food's getting cold.
What are you doing?
Oh, looking through my textbooks
for a new field of inquiry.
Why do we have a
geology book?
Leonard, did you throw a children's
party while I was in Texas?
Wait. What's wrong
with geology?
Let me put this in a way
you'll understand, Penny.
You remember how you
explained to me
that the Kardashians
aren't real celebrities?
Well, geology is the
Kardashians of science.
Have you considered studying
standard model physics?
You want me to give up string theory
for something that's less advanced?
You know, why don't you break up with
Penny and start dating a brown bear?
Like you could get
a brown bear.
Hey, I've got a good job. I could
buy salmon. You don't know.
Maybe you could make
your new field of study
the calculation of
nuclear matrix elements.
Oh, please.
If I wanted to take up a fad,
I'd get a tramp stamp.
What about loop
quantum gravity?
Oh, Duchess, look at me.
My quantum gravity's
positively loopy.
Who's the duchess?
One of the people that
lives in his head.
I hope he's this distraught
if he ever breaks up with me.
Well, if he does, I'll see
if my bear has a friend.
Sheldon, have you ever considered
not rushing into something new?
I mean, why don't you take
your time, enjoy your freedom?
Maybe something new to
study will find you.
That's actually
not bad advice.
You know, I didn't seek
out string theory.
It just hit me over
the head one day.
How does that happen?
A bully chased me through
the school library
and hit me over the head with
the biggest book he could find.
Okay, how about we toast
your newfound freedom?
Ah, normally I refrain
from alcohol,
but since my cerebral cortex is
twiddling its proverbial thumbs,
why not soak it in grape juice
that's been predigested by a fungus?
And you wonder why other
children beat you with books.
Cheers!
Emily, what do you do?
I'm a dermatology resident
at Huntington Hospital.
Mmm, and you know
what that means.
Someone's skin's about
to be softer than ever.
This is making me crazy. I know
I know you from somewhere.
Oh, uh, Howard was
an astronaut.
- Maybe that's where
you saw him. - Wow!
That's amazing.
What was that like?
It was the most incredible
experience of my life.
Up there in the space
station, you're...
Oh, my God, I remember.
Can I finish my
astronaut story?
It was four years ago.
- Please don't say it.
- We were set up on a blind date.
- You came to my apartment.
You're saying it.
Well, wh-what happened?
- Yeah, what happened?
- Okay, I'll say it.
I was on the way
to pick her up.
My stomach felt
a little funny.
When I got there, I asked if
I could use her bathroom.
Please don't say it.
One roll of toilet paper and 20
minutes later, I was so humiliated,
I snuck out the window
and never saw her again.
You know what else I never saw
again-- my security deposit.
I'm sorry. I tried to unclog it,
but you didn't have a plunger,
- and water was spilling out
everywhere. - Right, just water.
Look, I have felt terrible
about this for years,
and I'm glad I have the opportunity
to tell you just how sorry I am.
It's fine.
All my friends love this story.
They call you Clogzilla.
Get it? Because you clogged up her
bathroom like a radioactive monster!
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
- Howie. - Well, hey, it's not like
cotton candy comes out of you.
Come on, let's get you to bed.
You've had a lot to drink.
- No more than Penny.
- That's what I'm saying.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Empty room.
If somebody says "Come
in," I'm gonna freak out.
So, Emily, why did you decide
to specialize in dermatology?
I like cutting
people with knives,
and all the other jobs where
you get to do that are illegal.
You're kidding, right?
She's scary, but
it's a cute scary.
Can I say just one more thing?
I had some kind of food
poisoning that day.
Sure, in retrospect,
gas station sushi--
maybe not the best choice.
Nor was climbing out your
window and running away.
But I think we can all understand
how humiliating that was,
and I'd really appreciate
it if we could move on.
Howie, we moved on
a long time ago.
- I'm just saying...
- We moved on.
Okay. Fine.
- How's your soup?
- Ah, it's all right.
They could've filled
the bowl a little more.
- Excuse me.
- Where are you going?
I need some fresh air.
Been there.
Oh, no.
What have I done?
How you feeling?
Not so good.
Are you gonna introduce
me to your friend?
It's not my friend.
Nothing happened.
I don't know. I heard you
reading pretty loud last night.
Oh, dear Lord.
- Where's Amy? - After she put
you to bed, she went home.
Oh.
I should call her
and apologize.
Oh.
- Oh, no.
- What?
Apparently, I called Stephen
Hawking last night.
First new message.
Hawkman!
It's your old buddy
Sheldonoscopy!
How come you didn't
pick up the phone?!
Oh, right. My bad.
You're awful quiet.
Everything okay?
Not really.
I had a bit of an
embarrassing evening.
Ugh. Me, too.
What happened?
I drank alcohol and may have left an
unfortunate voice mail for Stephen Hawking.
I wouldn't worry about it. He's
got a pretty good sense of humor.
Oh, I hope so.
What happened to
you last night?
Oh, well, turns out I'd already
met the girl Raj is seeing
when I did a number
on her bathroom.
And that number was two.
Well, you know, I've
always been a fan
of a story told by Attar
of Nishapur, about a king
who assembled a
group of wise men
to create a ring that would
make him happy when he was sad.
And that ring was inscribed with
the phrase, "This too shall pass."
- Hey, Cooper!
- Oh, my God.
I heard you drunk-dialed
Stephen Hawking last night?
- Classic!
- Get out of here, Barry.
Whatever you say...
Clogzilla.
Clogzilla. That's
pretty funny.
I don't think
that's gonna pass.
Next message.
It's me again!
I gave up string theory.
You should give up black holes, and
we can totally solve crimes together!
Next message.
Do you know what's great?!
Geology. Oh!
Look at this geode!
That's fun to say!
Gee... ode! Gee... ode!
Next message.
Gee... ode!
I kiss girls now.
Next message.
Hey, guess who I am!
Beep bop boop bop!
I'm you! Get it?!
Next message.
Are you mad at me?
Oh, no, you're mad at me.
I'm so sorry!
Beep bop boop bop.
Next message.
Thiospinel sulfide.
That's even more fun
than "gee... ode."
Hey, did you see
The Lego Movie?
What a jackass.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net