So, we're about to shoot
this scene in the movie
where the killer ape DNA is
slowly taking over my body.
Okay.
But I realize they're gluing fur
everywhere, except my cleavage.
So, I asked the director
why and he says,
it's important to the story that my
boobs be the last things to turn ape.
It's sweet that he
thinks there's a story.
Oh, and there's not even
a bathroom on set.
I have to go to the gas
station across the street.
I mean, I was dressed
like half an ape
and still not even close to the
most disgusting person in there.
Leonard, I could use
your assistance.
Sure. What's up?
Well, now that I've
given up string theory,
I'm struggling to find
my next area of focus.
So, in your
professional opinion,
which of these areas do you
think is the most promising?
Huh, well, I-I think there's some really
innovative stuff going on in dark matter.
That's helpful.
- Okay. Of these four areas...
- Sheldon!
- What did we say about being
a nicer friend? - Thank you.
Leonard, what did we say about
being a gullible weenie?
It is just so frustrating.
'Cause you're trying too hard. You need to
do something else. Get your mind off it.
Hey. How about we bring back
Anything Can Happen Thursdays?
Hey, that's good. Why'd
you guys stop doing that?
You made fun of us.
Said it was stupid.
Yeah. Sounds like me.
Come on, Sheldon.
What do you say?
All right. I officially reinstate
Anything Can Happen Thursday.
Great! What do, what
do you want to do?
I don't know.
What do you want to do?
I don't know. What
do you want to do?
I'm starting to remember the problem
with Anything Can Happen Thursdays.
♪ Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x21 ♪
The Anything Can Happen Recurrence
Original Air Date on A
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Hmm...
what could we
do that's fun?
What could we do
that's different?
What could we
do that's free?
Got it! We order a pizza.
Are you kidding? That's what
you always do. Think harder.
You're right. You're right.
Got it!
We order calzones, cut them
open, eat them like pizza.
All right! All right! I'll shake the brain
bush one more time, see what falls out.
Got it! There's a live-action
role-playing group
that meets every Thursday
night in Griffith Park
and reenacts battles from
Lord of the Rings.
Uh, tell me more about
this calzone idea.
You know what? Why don't
we just ease into this.
Let-Let's go for a walk and-and-and
see if we find a new restaurant.
Any chance that restaurant
is near Griffith Park?
- No.
- All right.
Raj and Howard are
at Howard's mom's,
but should we call the girls
and see if they want to come?
- No. Bernadette's working late.
- Amy's sick.
- Aw. What's wrong with her?
- Well, she talks a lot.
She always wants to hold hands.
That's not what I meant.
Well, if you were
referring to her illness
your question should have
been, "What ails her?"
- "What ails her?"
- Oh. Who knows?
Come on, anything can happen. We
can push him down the stairs!
Hey. Thanks for
coming to hang out.
No problem. How's
your mom feeling?
Okay, but she'd feel better
if she took her medicine.
You know, when Cinnamon won't take her
medicine, I hide it in a piece of cheese.
Good idea. We can wrap the pill
in cheese, feed it to Cinnamon,
and then my mom
can eat Cinnamon.
What do you feel like doing?
I was thinking we
could watch a DVD.
Well, my mom doesn't have
a lot to choose from.
Unless you want to watch the
video of her colonoscopy.
Spoiler alert: 20 minutes
in, they find a prune pit.
Actually, how do you feel about
watching House of 1000 Corpses?
A straight-up gore-fest?
You hate this stuff.
I do, but for some
reason, Emily loves it
and wants to watch it
with me tomorrow, so...
I thought if I start with you first,
then I could act cool about it with her.
That's actually
not a bad plan.
I can sit through the colonoscopy
now, but that first time I was like,
"Oh, My God, a prune pit!"
Uh, so... you'd watch it?
Sure.
You're a good friend.
I owe you one.
Howard! Help me get
out of the tub!
Not that one.
So, we're just randomly choosing a
restaurant without researching it online?
- Yep.
- Great.
You know, this is how Anything
Can Happen Thursday turns into
It Won't Stop
Coming Up Friday.
Hey, how about that
Asian fusion place?
Fusion and Asians?
I'm trying not to
think about science.
What the hell?
What...? She's not
working late!
And Amy doesn't look sick.
- Why would they lie to us?
- That's a good question.
Amy and Bernadette.
Why did you lie to us?!
Hey. Listen to this:
"Murder... cannibalism and
satanic rituals are just a few
of the thousand plus
horrors that await."
I just helped my mom out of the tub, so,
I'm one slippery horror ahead of you.
You're a good son. I don't
know how you do it.
Beach blankets, my friend.
It's all about beach blankets.
All right, let's get
this over with.
Ew, it's got someone's
hair on it!
Oh, yeah, you're gonna
do great with this movie.
You're not working late.
Why did you lie to me?
And Amy, you told
me you were sick,
but you look just as pale
and tired as always.
I'm sorry. I just
needed a break
from hearing you obsess about
what to do after string theory.
And we kind of just
wanted one night
where we didn't have to hear about how
miserable you are making this movie.
But none of that means
we don't love you.
I haven't been complaining
that much about the movie.
Have I?
I also love you.
You know what? Maybe I need
a break from all of you.
- Come on, Sheldon.
- Where are we going?
We're gonna have Anything Can
Happen Thursday, you're gonna
tell me all about your science
stuff and I'm gonna complain
about my movie, and we're gonna support
each other because that's what friends do.
Okay.
'Cause if I had
to pick now,
- I'd probably go with dark
matter because... - Shut up.
- What's wrong?
- I don't understand my food.
Chinese noodles with
Korean barbecue...
in a taco.
It's fusion.
Well, my mother would
lock her car doors
if she had to drive through
this hodgepodge of ethnicity.
Think I've been complaining
too much about the movie?
- Not at all.
- Thank you.
But to be fair, when you talk,
most of what you say
sounds like, "Wah,
wah, wah, clothes".
Hey, I don't understand why
you're not upset with Amy.
I am. So much so that I'm gonna bring her
here for dinner on our next date night.
Okay.
So, in the last
20 minutes,
we've seen a crazy woman
kissing a fetus in a jar.
We've seen a guy cut in
half and sewn to a fish.
And the brutal dismemberment of a
rotisserie chicken by my mother.
On the bright side, she
didn't even notice the pill.
Why does Emily
like this stuff?
Do you think there's something
psychologically wrong with her?
- What difference does it make?
- What do you mean?
Oh, come on-- she could
have a freezer full of
ex-boyfriend's body parts and
you'd still go out with her.
I do like that the ex-boyfriend's
out of the picture.
I feel so bad about lying to Sheldon.
How am I gonna make it up to him?
I'd tell you what
I do with Howard,
but I don't think dressing up
like a Catholic schoolgirl
is gonna work
with Sheldon.
He'd probably give
you homework.
- Did you lie to Howard about tonight?
- Of course.
And you don't feel
guilty about it?
Between Penny's gorilla movie and
Howard's gorilla mother, I had no choice.
Thankfully Penny and I have
a relationship based on honesty.
What? I don't lie to her.
Oh, we know you
don't lie to her.
Thank you.
Hey, maybe the answer to your
career question is in one of these.
Penny, there's
only one cookie
with something in the middle
that solves life's problems,
and that's an Oreo.
Or a Nutter Butter,
if you're in a pinch.
Come on, open it. I bet
it says something great.
This is Asian fusion.
For all you know, there's
a tiny Chihuahua in here.
Fine, I'll go.
Hmm.
"People turn to you
for guidance and wisdom."
- Yeah, that's a good one.
- No, it's not.
How is that not good?
"Turn to you for wisdom"?
Clearly, that cookie
is mocking you.
You'd never hear that kind of
sass from a Nutter Butter.
Uh, since you're paying for dinner,
I'll let that slide. Open yours.
Have you ever
paid for a meal?
Not with money. Read.
"Your warm and fun-loving nature
delights those around you."
Oh, try again.
Let me get this straight.
So, he kills this girl's father,
cuts off the guy's face,
and is wearing it as a mask
while he makes
out with her.
I'm just gonna say it.
That's not okay.
Why can't I be in a relationship with
a girl who likes The Sound of Music?
Raj, you are the girl in the relationship
who likes The Sound of Music.
Hey, Penny. What's up?
No, Bernie's working late.
Really?
Thanks for telling me.
What?
I'm having sex with a
Catholic schoolgirl tonight.
Oh, I think I see
our next stop.
You can't be serious.
If I wanted to waste
my time on nonsense,
I'd follow Leonard
on Instagram.
No, come on-- tonight,
we are trying new things.
Oh! That's a lot
of incense.
Or someone set a
hippie on fire.
Yeah, honey, I'm
still stuck at work.
Really? Penny said that?
Okay, it's true. I'm sorry.
I'll see you at home.
Yeah, yeah, I'll put it on.
You and I never just hang
out like this. Why is that?
- I know, it's weird, right?
- Yeah. We should do it more often.
Oh, no. I mean, this
is weird right now.
Oh.
- Ah, it's Penny.
- Is she still mad?
Oh, doesn't seem like it. She got
Sheldon to go to a psychic with her.
A psychic?
He considers them not just mumbo
jumbo, but extra-jumbo mumbo jumbo.
Well, Penny can be
pretty persuasive.
She's gotten me to do a lot of
things I wouldn't normally do.
- Because she has sex with you.
- Yeah, she does.
Can I confess something?
Once in a while, I get a little jealous
of how close Penny and Sheldon are.
Really?
I mean, not in a
romantic way.
It's just, she really has some
sort of connection with him.
Well... Well, they've known
each other a long time,
and Penny grew up
around horses,
so she knows how to approach him
without making him skittish.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm glad they're friends.
I just wish he'd be that
comfortable around me already.
Well, it took him a long time to
get comfortable around me, too.
Really? What did you do?
Something terrible in a former life?
I don't know.
I gotta go. Penny
ratted me out.
FYI, she's getting you
a watch for your birthday
with money she took
out of your wallet.
I don't mean to be
rude or discourteous,
but before we begin,
I'd just like to say
there is absolutely no scientific evidence
to support clairvoyance of any kind.
Which means-- and again, no insult
intended-- but you're a fraud...
...your profession
is a swindle,
and, uh, your livelihood is dependent
on the gullibility of stupid people.
Again, no offense.
All right, Sheldon,
just ask your question.
Okay, I just did.
What was it?
Oh, for God's sake. Look, he's a
physicist who's trying to figure out
what his next field
of study should be.
For your information, I was asking
her about the next Star Trek movie.
Okay, I can answer that one:
I'll be bored.
All right, why don't we begin?
Your spirit guides
are telling me that
there's a woman in your life
you're having problems with.
That's an easy guess.
I'm clearly an annoying person and
have problems with both genders.
Yes, you clearly are.
But I'm seeing
a specific woman
that you're in a romantic
relationship with.
Oh, oh, here we go.
Does she have dark hair?
Yes! Yes! Your spirit
guides are on fire!
The majority of people
have dark hair.
Even you, at one time.
Does she work
in a similar field to you?
Ha! The opposite. She's a neurobiologist,
and I'm a theoretical physicist.
My spirit guides can
go suck an egg.
They're telling me that you have
difficulty being close with her.
Oh, he does. He so does.
What should he do?
He should give himself
to this relationship.
Once he does, all his other
pursuits will come into focus.
Sheldon, do you hear that? I mean,
Amy is the key to your happiness.
Exactly.
Personally and professionally.
Everything will fall into place
once you commit to her.
You know what this is?
Yeah, and I reserve this word for those
rare instances when it's truly deserved.
This is malarkey!
Wow, you really
struck a nerve.
I've never heard him use
the "M" word before.
Here we go:
House of a 1,000 Corpses.
Now, just so you know, I was a nanny
for three years, so if you get scared,
I can totally
change your diaper.
Actually, I have to
tell you something.
These kind of movies really
aren't my thing, so,
last night, I watched it just to see
what I was getting myself into.
Okay.
And I have to be honest-- I thought
it was disturbing and weird,
and it made me wonder what it
says about someone who enjoys it.
I wonder that, too.
Then, why do you
watch these things?
Can I tell you something
without you judging me?
Sure.
They kind of turn me on.
And play.
Attention...
Hello.
I didn't expect you
this evening.
Well, I was just feeling so bad
about lying to you the other night,
I wanted to make it up to you.
And how do you
propose to do that?
Unless you have Gravity on
Blu-ray under that skirt,
I don't know where
you're going with this.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net