This is nice, that we all
get to eat together.
- Mm-hmm. - Mm-hmm.
- Absolutely.
Hmm.
Can we maybe put the phones down and
have an actual human conversation?
We can, but thanks to Steve
Jobs, we don't have to.
Guys, guys, you're never
gonna believe this.
- What happened?
- I just got a part on a TV show!
- What? That's great!
- Congratulations!
Guys!
- Oh, yeah!
- Yay, Penny!
- What's the show?
- Um, NC... II...
or, you know, NCSTD...
I don't know,
it's-it's the one with the
letters and I'm gonna be on it!
- That's amazing.
- Yeah.
What's your part?
Um, I play a customer in a diner
and I flirt with Mark Harmon.
Ooh, Mark Harmon,
he's a dreamboat.
So i-it's just flirting?
- Well, yeah. Why?
- Uh, no reason.
I just think it's sexier when
things are left to the imagination.
He's wrong.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x12 ♪
The Hesitation Ramification
Original Air Date on January 2, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
So I-I read a study that
says a man with a dog
is three times more likely to
get a woman's phone number.
Is it true even when the man lets his
dog lick peanut butter off his tongue?
I don't see why not.
If you're really
desperate to meet women
and like having food
eaten out of your mouth,
I could set you up with my mom.
Why is that funny?
That's just unhygienic.
It's a joke.
I don't think so.
I believe that a joke is
a brief oral narrative
with a climactic
humorous twist.
For example, uh, Wolowitz's
mother is so fat
that she decided
to go on a diet...
or exercise, or both.
See? The twist is that
people don't usually change.
Well, they don't.
Hey, guys, don't forget, my
episode's on TV tomorrow night.
- We'll be there.
- Can we bring anything?
Oh, that's so sweet of you, but I
was gonna steal food from here.
You know... my treat.
Wait, if Howard's
mother is coming,
then you should
also steal marbles.
Because she's obese,
and hippos are obese,
and in the popular board game "Hungry
Hungry Hippos," they eat marbles.
Maybe I need to dumb
these down for you.
Leonard, do you
think I'm funny?
No.
Do you?
I think I'm hysterical.
I take it back. That was funny.
The philosopher Henri
Bergson says it's funny
when a human being
behaves like an object.
I bet that bit killed
at The Chuckle Hut.
Oh, he didn't perform stand-up
comedy, he was a philosopher.
You know, I think we're
zeroing in on your problem.
Perhaps I'll spend some time
developing a unified theory of comedy,
which will allow me to elicit
laughter from anyone at any time.
Unless they're German,
'cause that's a tough crowd.
Are you set on people
laughing with you?
'Cause if you're
cool with at you...
I don't get it.
Raj, when you said you were gonna bring
a date to watch Penny's thing tonight,
I didn't think you meant Stuart.
Really? I never for a second
thought it'd be anything else.
I almost met someone
last night, but I blew it.
I was walking Cinnamon and
this girl introduced herself,
but she was so cute I
panicked and said,
"Wouldn't it be easier
if instead of talking
we could just sniff
each other's butts?"
Well, Stuart's cute
in his own way.
When I was a baby, my mother
called me her little possum.
- Are possums cute?
- Not at all.
If you're so intimidated by
talking to attractive girls,
maybe you should practice by
talking to regular people.
You mean like fatties and uggos?
Or maybe just stop talking.
I'm serious. Go to the mall,
talk to anybody, practice--
that way, when you eventually do talk
to a cute girl, it won't be so scary.
Or just keep dating the possum.
Parsa doesn't have those
kind of resources.
No, and that's why he had
Erin Pace rewire it...
I'm so proud of you.
We haven't even gotten
to my scene yet.
I know,
but you're going to be a TV star
and you haven't left me yet.
That takes guts.
I don't know about you, but I'm
very uncomfortable with all this.
Why?
I've never seen this show before and
now I'm starting with episode 246?
It's unnatural.
Just think of the first
245 as the prequel.
All right.
Okay, shh. Guys,
guys, this is it.
I guess it's you and me, kid.
- What are you doing?
- I'm trying to make peace.
- We're good.
- Good.
- Really? Because...
- Are you kidding me?
- What's wrong?
- Well...
the diner scene.
Where's my diner scene?
Well, don't ask me. Until I
see the prequel, I'm lost.
No, there was supposed to be a big
scene with me and Mark Harmon,
but i-it's... gone.
What happened?
They must've cut it.
Oh, Penny...
I'm... I'm sorry.
- That stinks.
- I'm sure you were great.
This doesn't make any sense.
I mean, I...
I thought I did a...
a really good job, I...
Excuse me.
I've been studying how
to make people laugh.
They say that comedy
is tragedy plus time.
Let's tickle some ribs.
No, Dad, I don't think they
cut me out of the show
because I was too pretty.
No, I don't need you to come out
and kick Mark Harmon's ass.
Daddy, I gotta go.
I love you. Bye.
- How you doing?
- Ugh, this is such a disaster.
My parents had all
my relatives over.
They got one of those
six-foot sandwiches,
and got my brother a day
pass out of rehab and...
...now he's missing and the
sandwich is missing, and...
They're probably
in Mexico by now.
So humiliating.
You still got the part.
That's a huge accomplishment.
Yeah, but this was supposed
to be my break, okay?
People were gonna see me in this show
and it was gonna lead to bigger things.
More auditions, more parts...
Now none of that's
gonna happen.
Honey, you only had, like, three lines.
That wasn't gonna happen anyway.
- Unbelievable.
- Oh...
Come on... no, that's
not what I meant.
- Then what did you mean?
- I don't...
Look, you know, words don't
always have to mean things.
- I think you meant that you
don't believe in me. - Nope.
Uh-uh... I might not
know what I-I meant,
but I know that I
didn't mean that.
Not this guy. Oh, no way.
- I want you, right now, to give me
your 100% honest opinion. - Right.
Do you think I have what it takes
to really make it as an actress?
- Yes.
- So you think I'll be on TV
and in movies and win awards.
- Honestly?
- Yes, honestly.
I don't.
- How could you say that?
- I don't know...
I got all confused when
you said "honestly".
Oh!
Look, do I think that you are
talented and that you are beautiful?
Of course I do.
But isn't Los Angeles full of
actresses who are just as talented,
just as beautiful?
All right, look... we'll
come back to that.
No, please.
Don't stop, go on.
Tell me how I'm gonna be a
waitress for the rest of my life.
That is not what I said.
Look, I think
you're really good.
I truly do.
But this is an incredibly hard
thing that you're shooting for.
I mean, the odds of anyone becoming a
successful actor are like a million to one.
Wow, thank you.
Should've let Sheldon come.
This is interesting.
Apparently, a key component
in some forms of humor
is the element of surprise.
Well, that makes sense.
The prefrontal cortex is responsible
for planning and anticipation,
and patients with brain
lesions on their...
Brain lesions!
Sheldon, you scared me.
That wasn't funny.
Or maybe you have a stick
up your prefrontal cortex.
Okay, the notion that you can
read a few books and come up with
a definitive theory
of comedy is absurd.
I mean, humor is a
complex neurological...
- Okay, that's pretty good.
- Excellent.
How about her?
No! No pretty girls!
The point is to talk to regular people
and work our way up to pretty girls.
Fine.
How about that old
lady with the walker?
That depends.
On any level, do you
think she's hot?
We'll find somebody else.
Kumquat?
I guess.
Ointment?
Sure.
Now, would you say ointment
is more, equal to, or
less funny than kumquat?
I don't think I want to
go out with you anymore.
Will you please stop joking around?
I'm trying to figure this out.
Sheldon, how many words
are you gonna go through?
All of them.
You didn't get your part cut.
All right, baby,
here's the deal.
And you didn't get
your part cut.
Yep, bunch of old guys
rocking out in a band,
all with erectile dysfunction,
you didn't get your part cut!
Hey.
Can we talk?
We can, but the part
of Penny might get cut.
That was really crappy of me.
What you're trying to do is
hard, but people do make it,
and I really do believe
you could be one of them.
Thank you.
And...
to show you how much
I believe in you,
I kind of got you an audition.
Are you serious? For what?
- The new Star Wars movie.
- What?!
How did you manage that?!
There's this thing online,
you put yourself on tape
and just send it in--
anyone can do it.
Come on Leonard,
this is just a PR stunt.
So? Even if it is, you
have a huge advantage
because you're an
actual actress.
Most of the people doing this
are just weirdoes and nerds.
Wolowitz sent his in
two days ago.
Really, let it go.
Look, maybe it is a long shot,
but sometimes
long shots happen.
Luke Skywalker was only given one
chance to destroy the Death Star.
He had to get a torpedo into an exhaust
port that was only two meters wide,
but with the help
of The Force, he...
Wow, I can feel you
hating me right now.
How about that lady in the
sweat suit, speed-walking?
Yeah, she seems
friendly and easy to...
Never mind, she's gone.
Yeah, maybe talking
to people is too hard.
We could go over to that department
store, practice on the mannequins.
I don't know. They're
dressed very stylishly.
They're probably stuck-up.
This is ridiculous.
The next person that walks by, no
matter who it is, they're the one.
We're gonna die here.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Where's Sheldon?
He's home trying to use science
to determine the basis of humor.
- That's interesting.
- It's exhausting.
Do you have any
idea how hard it is
to laugh at a knock-knock
joke that starts with,
"Knock-knock-knock, Amy,
knock-knock-knock, Amy,
knock-knock-knock, Amy"?
If you want him to stop, sometimes the
easiest thing to do is just fake a laugh.
Fake a laugh?
Do you ever do that with me?
No, of course not.
Well, I'd be able
to tell anyway.
I don't think you would.
Please, I've made
plenty of girls laugh,
sometimes just by
asking them out.
Yeah? Well, I fake my orgasms.
Yes, how much for a hundred
long-stemmed red roses?
Really?
How much for three?
- Hey.
- Yeah, I'll call you back.
Look, I know you were
just trying to help
with your Star Wars thing. I
didn't mean to call it idiotic.
Well, I don't think
you called it idiotic.
Oh.
Sorry, I meant to.
Anyway, um, I was just
upset with myself.
I wasn't mad at you.
I just feel like everything
is falling apart.
Come on. It's okay.
No, it's not okay!
Look at me, okay?!
I took a temp job as a waitress
forever ago, and I'm still doing it.
I can't quit, because guess what?
I can't do anything else.
And I finally get my big
break, and it goes away!
I'm such a mess.
- No, you're not.
- Really?!
'Cause this morning at Starbucks, a pair
of old underwear fell out of my pant leg!
And it wasn't the
only one in there.
Okay, listen to me, this
is just a minor setback.
No, it's not, okay?! I've been
out here for, like, ten years!
I've nothing to show for it!
Well, you have me.
You're right.
I do have you.
Mm...
Let's get married.
What?
Ooh!
Leonard Hofstadter...
will you marry me?
Um...
Did you seriously
just say, "Um"?!
Look,
you know I love you,
but-but you're-you're drunk
and sad and feeling lost...
Okay, so-so you don't
want to marry me?!
That is not what I said.
No, forget it! I take it back!
Offer's off the table!
Who's in the mood to laugh?!
Really not a good time.
But I used science to
construct the perfect joke.
- I'm gonna go.
- Penny, don't.
No, no, I just need to be alone.
So, a sandwich, a rabbi and
yo mama walk into a bar.
- Where are you going?
- To my room.
- Should I follow you?
- No.
Leonard, wait.
What?
I forgot to tell you the
sandwich is promiscuous.
How about those guys on that bench
over there? They look pathetic.
I bet we could talk to them.
That's a mirror.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, fellas, mall's closing.
- Sorry.
- Yeah. Good night.
Uh, excuse me.
Yeah?
Uh, do-do you like being
a mall security guard?
It's all right.
Okay, nice talking to you.
Smooth...!
Can't sleep?
No.
Would you like
to talk about it?
Penny proposed, and
I didn't say yes.
Why not?
That's a good question.
Does that mean the
relationship is over?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask her?
Because I'm afraid
to know the answer.
Well...
I'm sorry.
That's it?
You're not gonna make some
dumb joke or some
inappropriate comment?
No.
You're my friend, and...
I'm sorry.
Did you just put a "kick me"
sign on my back?
No.
That wouldn't be funny at all.
Star Wars audition, take one...
starring Howard Joel Wolowitz,
real-life astronaut.
Vader is here...
now... on this moon.
I felt his presence.
He's come for me.
He can feel when I'm near...
How many times do I
have to tell you
to replace the toilet
paper when it's empty?!
- I'm in the middle of something!
- So am I!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net