Almost there.
You're doing great.
Thanks for lifting my spirits.
Next time, try lifting the box.
Please hurry.
I don't need a treadmill!
The doctor says you
need to get exercise!
I get plenty of exercise!
Crushing my will to
live isn't exercise!
If she isn't gonna use it,
then why are we doing this?
She'll use it. All I need is to rig it
with a fishing pole and a HoneyBaked Ham.
All right. Now what?
We set it up in
Howie's old room.
Do you know how
to set it up?
Please, I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
I think I can handle...
Ma, look out!
I told you this thing
would kill me!
♪ Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x23 ♪
The Gorilla Dissolution
Original Air Date on May 8, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
So she's gonna be laid up
for at least six weeks.
Poor Mrs. Wolowitz.
Should we do
something for her?
I know. Let's go see
the new Spider-Man movie.
Sheldon, we're talking about your
friend's mother. She got hurt.
I thought that subject had run
its course, so I changed it.
It's called reading
the room, Amy.
- Hi. - Hey, how were
things on the set?
Uh, pretty good, actually.
So the movie's not
as bad as you thought?
Oh, no, it is, but I decided,
instead of complaining about it,
I'm just gonna go in every
day and give it my all.
- Good for you.
- Thanks.
There's no reason why I shouldn't
be the best bisexual go-go dancer
slowly transforming into a killer
gorilla anyone's ever seen.
I don't know.
The bisexual gorilla go-go dancer in
Schindler's List is tough to beat.
Ah, very good.
Because a gorilla go-go dancer
of any sexual preference
would be out of place in a
film about the Holocaust.
It only gets funnier when
you explain it, Sheldon.
I know.
Okay, she's all settled
in the guest room.
Maybe we should get one of those
machines to help her up the stairs.
You mean a forklift?
- Howie... - I'm sorry. I just
can't deal with this right now.
Taking care of your own mother?
How can you say that?
Bernie, she's gonna be off her
feet for six to eight weeks.
Are you prepared to feed her, wash
her and take her to the toilet?
- I would do it for my mother.
- Yeah, of course you would--
you're a loving person. I'm what
my people would call a putz.
Look, I'm not crazy about the idea,
but what other choice do we have?
We get a nurse.
Preferably someone from
a Third World country
who's used to suffering
and unpleasant smells.
You'd hire a total stranger to take care of
the woman who raised you? That's so cruel.
Not if we pay them well and let them
listen to the music of their homeland.
I need to tinkle!
Sounds like a job
for a loving person.
Would you like me to play some Polish
music while you carry her to the toilet?
You are a putz.
As advertised.
Thanks for coming with me.
Thanks for inviting me after
everyone else said no.
Aren't you gonna get
3-D glasses?
I brought my own.
No sense in risking
bridge-of-nose herpes.
Is that a real thing?
Well, until they invent nose
condoms, I'm not finding out.
Emily! Hey!
Oh, hey, Raj.
Uh, this is my friend, Sheldon.
Sheldon, this is Emily.
Oh, yes, you're
the dermatologist.
I went for a walk yesterday
without sunscreen.
Do you see anything on my forehead
that I should be concerned about?
Um, you know what? I better go.
My movie's about to start.
- Are you here alone?
- No, not really.
- What do you mean, "not really"?
- Hey, should we get our seats?
Yeah. It was nice seeing you.
Um, I'll call you later.
Yeah, okay.
That was awkward, right?
Uh-huh.
Is it because she's dating you but
was out with that other fellow?
Yes.
Good. I thought she saw
something on my forehead.
And... action.
Please don't shut me out.
Go away. Just go away.
I swear, I will find a way
to turn you back.
What gave you the right to mix my
DNA with that of a killer gorilla?
I was trying to
save your life.
Life? What life? Look at me!
I'm a monster!
And now I have blood on my
hands, or paws. I don't know.
You can't give up.
I love you.
I love you, too.
But I'm afraid I
love killing more.
Like, one day, I might
actually try and kill you!
- And... cut.
- All right.
All right, let's set
up for the next scene.
Actually, you know what?
Can we do one more?
I think I could do it better.
Let's just move on.
No one cares.
Well, I care. I mean, look,
if we're gonna do this,
why not try and make it something
we're actually proud of?
Look, sweetie, this movie is garbage,
but you should be happy about that,
'cause if it was a good
movie, you wouldn't be in it.
Whoa, whoa, hang on. There's
no need to insult her.
- And who are you?
- I'm her boyfriend.
- Isn't she too hot for you?
- A little, yeah.
Well, boyfriend,
get off my set.
You can't do that.
He's with me.
You know what? You can get off
my set, too. You're fired.
What? You can't fire me.
I'm the star.
I'm the girl that goes bananas.
It says so on the poster.
Yeah, but we just shot the last
scene where we see your face.
So from now own, the star of
the movie is whoever wears this.
Hey, if you're gonna fire her,
then you have to fire me, too.
Wow, that fell
apart really fast.
Thanks for skipping
the movie.
I couldn't sit in that
theater for two hours
wondering about Emily
and that guy.
Oh, quite all right.
After my forehead melanoma scare, I've
learned not to sweat the small stuff.
Well, sorry, I don't have all the
ingredients to make chai tea.
You don't have
to make me anything.
No, I do. You're upset about
Emily and you're Indian.
I need to make
you chai tea.
Now, I have all the ingredients
except cardamom seeds.
Do you happen to
have any on you?
Sorry, I left them
in my turban.
Oh, I'll make English
breakfast tea.
They destroyed your culture.
That's close enough.
You know, I'm curious,
why are you so upset about
seeing Emily with another man?
Wouldn't you be upset if you saw
Amy out with someone else?
Can't happen.
We have an ironclad
relationship agreement
which precludes her from physical
contact with anyone other than me.
But you don't have sex
with her, either.
Slick, huh?
To be truthful, Emily and I
haven't dated that long,
and we never agreed to be
exclusive to each other.
- Have you had intercourse?
- No.
Well, stick to your guns. There
will be a lot of pressure.
I'm hungry again!
It's like the world's
fattest cuckoo clock.
You know, you're always talking
about having a baby someday.
This is exactly what
it's gonna be like.
No, it's not.
Come on. The constant fussing,
eating, pooping, burping, drooling.
We're even waiting for the day when
she can finally walk on her own.
Maybe you're right. Anything she finds
on the floor goes right in her mouth.
I'm just telling you now,
if we do have kids,
don't expect me
to do all the work.
Hey, I'm a very
paternal person.
I'd be excellent at
taking care of a baby.
I'm still hungry!
I'm coming, you big baby!
You know, the only thing
worse than doing a movie
where they glue monkey hair to your
ass is getting fired from a movie
where they glue monkey
hair to your ass.
Forget it, man, it's crap. You
just move on to the next thing.
Yeah, well, it's easy for you to say.
You used to be famous.
Hey. I just lost
a job for you.
You're right, I'm sorry,
you're famous.
Penny, it's not about being famous.
It's about the art.
It's about the passion
we have for our craft.
I have an audition
for Sharknado 2!
If I book this, I am totally gonna
pay you back for this beer.
God, what am I doing
with my life?
You having second
thoughts about acting?
You were on set, you
saw what it was like.
Yeah, but it's not
always that bad.
Oh, really?
What about when you did, uh, Anne
Frank at that cute little theater?
It was over a
bowling alley.
Yeah, but...
there was ample parking.
Are you done?
And you were so good
in the TV commercial.
It was for
hemorrhoid cream.
And I got itchy and swollen
just watching you.
Leonard, you are really
not cheering me up.
Come on.
How can you be sad when you're going
home with all five-foot-six of this?
Hmm. You think you're
five-foot-six, that's funny.
I don't understand it.
I'm a nice guy,
I have a great job,
I'm well-educated,
come from a good family...
Why don't women
want to be with me?
An interesting question.
Well...
good night.
What? Don't send me home. I
can't be alone right now.
That's your problem.
- You can't be alone.
- What do you mean?
How many women have
you had dates with?
Eleven.
How many of those women did you think
would become your perfect companion?
Eleven.
Wait. Do I count the
200-pound Sailor Moon girl
that Howard and I had a
threesome with at Comic Con?
Sure.
I'll stick with 11.
She liked Howard better.
Well, now do you
see the problem?
Maybe. I...
I don't know. You... It's late,
I-I should... I should go.
Look, I-I do get
what you're saying.
Instead of desperately clinging to
any woman who will go out with me,
I need to work on my
fear of being alone.
I was trying to suggest
chemical castration, but...
...it's my bedtime, so whatever
gets you out the door. Good night.
Howie, I'm back!
Shh-shh-shh, I just
got her to sleep.
- Sorry.
- What took you so long?
- The grocery store is a few blocks away.
- They only had regular yogurt.
I had to go to a different store to get
the extra-fat kind your mom likes.
Then why do I smell
coffee on your breath?
So what? After two days
of taking care of her,
excuse me for stopping
to get a mocha.
A mocha? Well, it must
be nice to be queen.
Queen? I've been
killing myself here!
Well, whose fault is that? I wanted
to get a nurse, but you were all,
"I'm nice. I want to
take care of people."
I'm glad I got that mocha.
And you know what
else I'm glad about?
I bought you a brownie
and I ate it in the car!
Howard!
Thanks a lot. Now I have
to go rub her belly again.
Hey.
Thanks for letting
me come over.
Of course.
Please, come in.
I just wanted to say how sorry
I am about tonight, and...
I want to make sure
that we're okay.
Uh, look, you and I haven't made
any commitments to each other.
I know. I just felt like
I needed to explain.
The guy I was with
did my last tattoo,
and he's been asking
me out for months.
I finally said yes just
to get it over with.
It's okay.
Really?
Well, I mean, yeah, it
freaked me out a little,
but that's my
issue, not yours.
Wow.
If I saw you out with another
woman, I'd be pretty upset.
Thank you.
Not just for being upset, but for
believing that could happen.
Just so you know, I'm
not seeing anyone else.
Well, me, neither.
- Okay.
Please. So, uh...
you... you have tattoos?
- Yeah.
- I don't.
I have a hole in my belly button that
may or may not have been a piercing.
- That's cool.
- It's a piercing.
So, uh...
how many tattoos?
One on my shoulder, one
not on my shoulder
and one really not
on my shoulder.
It's, uh... been a long time
since I've seen a girl's...
really not her shoulder.
Well...
how about you show me your piercing
and I show you my tattoos?
But, uh, before I
take my shirt off,
I just need like ten minutes
to do some crunches.
Oh, my God.
What a day.
- Can I get you anything?
- No.
I need to start making
some smart decisions.
- With your career?
- With my life.
Like what?
I don't know.
We could get married.
- Come on, be serious.
- I am.
Why?
Because I'm
a-a "smart decision"?
Well, yeah.
So I'm like a bran muffin.
What... No, that's
not what I'm saying.
No, it's exactly
what you're saying.
I'm the boring thing you're
choosing because I'm good for you.
What does it matter? The
point is, I'm choosing you.
Well, it matters a lot! I don't
want to be a bran muffin.
I-I want to be a...
Cinnabon, you know?
A strawberry Pop-Tart.
Something you're excited about even
though it could give you diabetes.
Sweetie, you can be
any pastry you want.
No, no. No, it's too late.
I-I'm your bran muffin.
Probably fat-free and
good for your colon.
You know what? Forget it. I
never should've brought it up.
You know I want to marry you,
but you're only doing this
because you got fired
and you're feeling
sorry for yourself.
Okay, it may look that
way, but getting fired
from that movie was the best thing
that could have happened to me, okay?
I finally realize I don't need to be
famous or have some big career to be happy.
- Then what do you need?
- You, you stupid Pop-Tart!
Oh.
Then I guess I'm in.
Really? You "guess
you're in"?
Not like, "I guess I'm in."
Like "I guess... I'm in!"
Okay. Cool.
So is that it?
Are... are we engaged?
Yeah, I think so.
All right.
What's wrong?
I'm not sure. Just... feels
a little anticlimactic.
Yeah, it kind
of does, huh?
Oh, I know.
This might help.
- Where did you get a ring?
- I've...
had it for a couple
years, not important.
Penny... will
you marry me?
Oh, my God, yes.
This would have been
so much more romantic
if you didn't have monkey
hair on your finger.
How you feeling?
Last night was a little rough, but I
think we're gonna get through this.
- I'm proud of us.
- Me, too.
Where's my pancakes?!
Coming, Mrs. Wolowitz!
- You were right.
- Welcome to Team Putz.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net