- What are you working on?
- Can't talk. In the zone.
- Do you know what he's doing?
- Could be anything.
Last time he was like this, he figured
out electron transport in graphene.
The time before that, he was
making a list of who's allowed
in his tree fort if
fe ever gets one.
Still can't believe I
didn't make the cut.
Uh, Sheldon, you want
to take a break?
- Your food's ready.
- No, no, what are you doing?
He's both happy and quiet.
It's like seeing a unicorn and
Bigfoot at the same time.
Sorry we're so late.
Bernadette got stuck at work.
Great news! A raccoon virus just
crossed the species barrier
and now can infect humans!
Why is that great news?
In the pharmaceutical business, we have
a saying: "Mo' infections, mo' money."
Wait!
Maybe you want to wash your
little raccoon hands first.
Oh, calm down. If I had
it, I'd be dead already.
- Guys, listen up.
- Can't listen, zone.
Also don't care.
Next week is the anniversary of
my first date with Bernadette.
Really don't care.
I want to do something special, and I was
hoping you guys could be a part of it.
Aw, what horrible thing are
you trying to make up for?
Just putting something in the bank
for what horrible thing I do next.
Ah.
Look, she's gonna be back any
second, so here's the deal:
I'm writing a song, and I was hoping
we could all play it for her together.
- Aw... - Oh, I love that.
- That is so beautiful.
Sheldon?
When did we get to The
Cheesecake Factory?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x06 ♪
The Romance Resonance
Original Air Date on October 24, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
It's really sweet what Howard
wants to do for Bernadette.
Yeah.
Hey, how come you've never done anything
romantic to celebrate our first date?
Well, for starters, you've
broken up with me so many times,
which first date are
we talking about?
Ooh, somebody call
the burn ward.
And back to the zone.
And besides, I do romantic
things for you all the time.
Can you even name one romantic
thing you've done for me?
- I can name tons.
- Sex doesn't count.
Oh.
I know, what about
that bed-and-breakfast?
- Well, I took you there. All you
did was... - I know what I did.
I bet they had to throw
out that rocking chair.
You know, I can be
romantic if I want to.
It's fine.
And also not true.
Okay, just you wait and see. I'm
gonna romance your freakin' ass off.
That's beautiful. Is
that Shakespeare?
- Sheldon?
- Zone.
He'll figure it out when
he falls off the roof.
Sheldon, I know you're in the
zone, but do you want some tea?
All right, I can't believe
I'm gonna say this, but
you haven't spoken in hours and
I'm starting to get worried.
Please say something.
Leonard, prepare to be humbled and
weep at the glory of my genius.
Nope, it was better before.
Look at it.
I feel like my mind
just made a baby.
And it's beautiful.
It's not like human babies, which
are loud and covered in goop.
Holy crap, Sheldon, did you
just figure out a method
for synthesizing a new
stable super-heavy element?
Did I?
Well, that can't be right.
No one's ever done that before.
Except me, because I just did it!
♪ Sheldon and his brain-- yeah! ♪
♪ Sheldon and his brain--
yeah! ♪
♪ Sheldon and
his brain-- yeah! ♪
- ♪ Sheldon and his brain... ♪
- Yeah, definitely better before.
So I'm almost done writing
the song for Bernadette.
Are you cool playing the cello?
If by "cool" you mean
"willing to," yes.
If by "cool" you mean "cool," clearly
you've never seen me play the cello.
Great. Will you
play the ukulele?
Of course. I'd be happy
to shred it on my ax.
Or you could just play
your tiny, ridiculous guitar.
Fine. I will melt her heart.
And her face!
Gentlemen.
Uh, no doubt you heard about
my little breakthrough.
Now, if your plan is to
hoist me on your shoulders
and carry me around the
cafeteria, please refrain.
I don't care for
heights, motion sickness
or the thought of your necks
touching my buttocks.
Seriously,
congratulations, Sheldon.
Yeah, I read your paper online.
That technique for creating
a new heavy element is inspired.
Oh, well, thank you.
Believe it or not,
I just learned
a Chinese research team
at the Hubei Institute for Nuclear
Physics ran a test on a cyclotron,
and the results were
extremely promising.
Sheldon, that's incredible.
Yeah, I know! They called it the greatest
thing since the Communist party.
Although I'm pretty sure that the
Communist party made them say that.
I like China. See, they know
how to keep people in line.
So, what happens next?
Oh, more testing, more
success, more fame.
But don't worry,
I will remain the same down-to-earth
humble Joe I've always been.
- Good to know.
- Yeah.
Now give me that cookie;
I discovered an element.
Thank you so much for coming.
You called the right person.
I believe I have the perfect romantic
evening for you to give Leonard.
Okay, good, 'cause I've been
really struggling with this.
As I'm sure you're aware, the quickest
way to a man's heart is through his...
Pants, but Leonard says
sex doesn't count.
Oh. You poor thing.
You have one arrow in your quiver,
and you just can't use it.
Fortunately, another pathway to a
man's heart is through his stomach.
I don't know if I want to cook for
him; he's kind of a picky eater.
I mean, "It's too salty. It's too dry. It's
too burnt and frozen at the same time."
Wait, come on, what else would
sweep you off your feet?
Well, I've always had this
fantasy that involves dancing.
The sexual chemistry between
my partner and me is electric.
But boy, oh, boy, does
my father not approve
until he sees us in the
big dance competition.
Okay, that's just the
plot for Dirty Dancing.
What else would you love? Other than
being lifted over Patrick Swayze's head.
Oh! Oh, uh, you could, uh, stand outside
his window with a boom box in the air.
That's from Say Anything.
Look, I'm a lonely guy;
I watch a lot of movies.
Look, Penny, if you
truly want to be romantic,
it needs to come from you.
I get that, but why
is this so hard?
Well, you've probably never
had to do this stuff
'cause you're young and beautiful and men
have always thrown themselves at you.
Hmm.
Yeah, I'm trying to be sad about that.
I can't.
Let's see, what's next?
Okay! Here.
This is the Magic Marker I was
using when I made the discovery.
I don't think the Smithsonian's
gonna want your marker.
And that's why you're not
on a list for my tree fort.
Ooh, guess who's getting an article
written about him in Physics Today?
I'll give you a hint. You measured the
diameter of his suspicious mole yesterday.
- Sheldon, I'm so proud of you.
- Well, you should be.
My discovery is
spreading like wildfire.
Unlike my mole, which is holding
steady at the size of a navy bean.
What's next?
This is the very copy of The
Handbook of Chemistry and Physics
in which I looked up the reaction
rates of mendelevium and...
- And what?
- No.
No, no, no, no.
What's wrong?
I've made a horrible mistake.
What are you talking about?
This table-- it's in
square centimeters.
I read it as square meters.
You know what that means?
That Americans can't
handle the metric system?
Amy, I was off by
a factor of 10,000.
But the Chinese team
found the element.
Yeah, well, they shouldn't have.
My calculations were wrong.
There must be some resonance between
the elements I didn't know about.
So you just got lucky?
Sheldon Cooper
does not get lucky!
You and me both, brother.
It doesn't matter. The element was found
because of you, and that's groundbreaking.
What matters is the greatest
scientific achievement
of my life is
based on a blunder.
I'm not a genius, I'm a fraud.
You know, Sheldon,
in neuroscience,
we're forever finding something
in one part of the brain
- that we thought was someplace else.
- Oh, great.
Now I'm worse than a fraud.
I'm practically a biologist.
You got to stop beating
yourself up over this.
I mean, you made a mistake,
but it was a happy mistake.
There's nothing happy about it.
I'm being given credit
that I don't deserve.
Oh, people get things they
don't deserve all the time.
Look at me with you.
No, Leonard, this is going to
haunt me for the rest of my life.
Every science classroom, every
periodic table, every textbook--
this mistake will be
staring back at me
Like that time you let
Koothrappali wax your eyebrows.
I've got to find a way
to stop this thing.
Buddy, I don't think you can. I mean,
once it's out there, it's out there.
This thing is like the science
equivalent of a sex tape.
You know, frankly,
I'd prefer a sex tape.
- You don't know what a sex
tape is, do you? - No.
Make sure you guys get
to the restaurant by 8:00.
Bernadette's meeting me there at 8:30
and I don't want to blow the surprise.
- We'll be there.
- Got it.
Now, uh, I have a
question about the song.
I was thinking at some point I
could bust out a little rap.
N-N-N-No...
Come on, come on, you
haven't even heard it yet.
Leonard, give me a beat.
I will not.
- Please?
- No, I want this to be romantic.
It will be! I don't
call anyone a ho,
and the only time I use the phrase
"my bitch," I'm referring to you.
There he is!
Stop it. Stop celebrating me!
Woo!
And no woos!
Oh, not you, Dr. Woo.
You're fine.
I want you all to know that you
have no reason to applaud me.
My so-called breakthrough
wasn't the result of my genius.
It was nothing more than
a boneheaded mistake.
So please refrain from praising
me for it in the future.
Wh... I don't understand.
They didn't find the element?
Oh, no, they found the element.
No, no, stop it!
I don't need to take this admiration
from the likes of you people!
How do I make them
stop loving me?
Invite them to live with us.
Boy, Bernadette is
gonna love this.
Yeah. It must be nice to have
someone do something so romantic.
Okay, you know what's not romantic?
Rubbing it in someone's face.
Actually, it can be, but I
told you sex doesn't count.
I'm getting worried about Bernadette.
I'm gonna call and check on her.
The National Science Foundation wants
to give me a substantial grant.
- Oh, that's a big deal.
- I know.
When will this nightmare end?
Hey, I get that you feel bad about
all the attention, but still,
what you did is amazing.
We're really proud of you.
I'm not.
You're not?
Sheldon, I've been thinking
about it, and you're right.
You don't deserve any credit.
All you did was misread
some numbers on a table.
A very easy table, too.
Honestly,
I'm embarrassed for you.
That's the most romantic
thing I've ever heard.
Damn it, everyone's
better at this than me.
Congratulations, Dr. Fowler.
You just made the fort.
Guys, there w-was
an accident at Bernie's lab.
Oh, my God, is she okay?
Yeah, but she's at the
hospital in quarantine.
- What? - Poor Bernadette.
- Oh, no.
I hate to pile on the bad
news, but I just got a raise.
Oh, my God, Bernie,
what happened?
Well, let's just say
the next time you move
a dozen vials of raccoon virus
to the fridge, make two trips.
- You're sure you're okay?
- Yeah, it's just a precaution.
If there was a problem, I'd be
throwing up out of my eyeballs by now.
- Sorry I messed up our date.
- No, don't worry about it.
I brought the date here.
Guys, come on in.
What's all this?
Well, tonight is the
anniversary of our first date,
and I wanted to celebrate it
by writing a song for you.
Howie.
Sheldon, get over here!
She might be contagious.
Don't you think I'm having
a rough enough day?
Sheldon!
♪ If I didn't have you ♪
♪ Life would be blue
♪ I'd be Doctor Who
without the TARDIS ♪
- Is it me, or does she not look so good?
- Shh!
♪ A candle without a wick
♪ A Watson without a Crick
♪ I'd be one of my outfits
without a dick-ie ♪
♪ I'd be cheese
without the mac ♪
♪ Jobs without the Wozniak
♪ I'd be solving
exponential equations ♪
♪ That use bases not found on your
calculator making it much harder to crack ♪
♪ I'd be an atom
without a bomb ♪
♪ A dot without the com
♪ And I'd probably still
live with my mom ♪
♪ And he'd probably still
live with his mom ♪
♪ Ever since I met you, you
turned my world around ♪
♪ You supported all my
dreams and all my hopes ♪
♪ You're like uranium-235
and I'm uranium-238 ♪
♪ Almost inseparable isotopes
♪ I couldn't have imagined ♪
♪ How good my life would get
♪ From the moment
♪ That I met you
- ♪ Bernadette
- Oh, Howie.
♪ If I didn't have you ♪
♪ Life would be dreary
♪ I'd be string theory
without any string ♪
♪ I'd be binary code
without a one ♪
♪ A cathode ray tube
without an electron gun ♪
♪ I'd be Firefly, Buffy and
Avengers without Joss Whedon ♪
♪ I'd speak a lot more Klingon ♪
♪ Heghlu'meH QaQ jajvam ♪
♪ And he'd definitely
still live with his mom ♪
♪ Ever since I met you
♪ You turned my world around
♪ You're my best
friend and my lover ♪
♪ We're like changing electric
and magnetic fields ♪
♪ You can't have one ♪
♪ Without the other
♪ I couldn't have imagined ♪
♪ How good my life would get
♪ From the moment
that I met you ♪
♪ Bernadette
♪ Oh, we couldn't
have imagined ♪
♪ How good our lives would get
♪ From the moment
that we met you ♪
♪ Bernadette.
Howie, that was amazing!
Look, I'm shaking.
She's sick, I knew it. Bye!
I have to say, this is the best
Top Ramen you've ever made.
I discovered a
secret ingredient:
the flavor packet.
That sucker is well named.
All right, lover boy.
Get ready, 'cause there is a crap
storm of romance coming your way.
Stop it, you're
gonna make me cry.
All right. You seem
pretty confident.
Oh, I am.
Maybe if you follow this trail,
you'll see why.
Oh, rose petals.
Yes.
The most beautiful and shockingly
expensive of all the flowers.
You made the bed? You really
are pulling out all the stops.
Okay, I gave this
a lot of thought,
and I finally found something to
show you how much I love you.
Oh, wow.
It's a first edition of
Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy.
I remember it was
your favorite book growing up.
This is great.
It... thank you. It's...
so much.
What?
- Nothing. I love it.
- No.
Something's going on.
What's wrong with it?
I remember you saying how great it
would be to have a first edition.
It's true, I-I did.
I did say that...
when we were at the used
bookstore together
and I saw the first
edition and I bought it.
Oh, my God, I am the worst!
No, no, it's okay.
It's really thoughtful.
No, it's not! I mean...
What's thoughtful is
everything you do.
Here, you know what?
Look at this.
Look, here's the... the
plane ticket you bought me
when I was too poor to go
home for the holidays. And...
the rose you left
on my windshield...
just because.
Here's the-the thank-you letter you wrote
me after the first time I slept with you.
All 11 pages of it.
Can't believe you
saved all this stuff.
Of course I did. It's you.
Come here.
Oh.
Is that a pregnancy test?
Oh, yeah, just the first one.
I didn't save them all.
I can't believe I read
this table wrong.
I blame you.
- Me? What did I do?
- You distract me.
I've been distracted since
the moment I met you.
- Sorry.
- Well, you should be.
Because all I can think about
is how much I want to kiss you.
And not just on the
cheek, but on the mouth.
Like mommies and daddies do.
Oh, Sheldon.
Amy?
Amy.
Did you hear what I said?
Can't talk, in the zone.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net