Previously on Mad Men:
You don't have to answer me now,
but I wanna marry you.
Put your nose down and pay attention
to your work,
Because there's not one thing
that you
done here that I couldn't
live without.
I want...To scream at you.
For ruining all of this.
- You are very upset. I understand.
- I don't love you.
You don't owe them anything.
You should start gathering your clients.
Sometimes you're more than a son to me.
I don't think you understand.
This is regarding your contract.
Or lack thereof.
Sign.
- Sterling Cooper is for sale.
- Why?
Ripped: LeapinLar
[Opensubtitles.org]
Transcripted by VeRDiKT, honeybunny & cRaZyMaGgOt
www.addic7ed.com
Sorry I'm late.
That's okay.
I was occupied.
- How are you today, Don?
- I'm well, Connie.
Thank you. How are you?
I'm afraid I have some
serious business to discuss.
Have a seat.
I was at McCann Erickson
yesterday,
and they let me know
that effective January 1,
they're buying
Putnam, Powell & Lowe.
What?
I'm sorry, but that means
I'm going to have to
move my New York
properties elsewhere.
Why?
Because P.P.L. owns
Sterling Cooper.
You're all gonna
be part of McCann.
- So we're all gone.
- Sterling, I don't know.
Cooper will definitely
be put on an ice floe.
But you're a prize pig.
You'll make more money, pick up stock.
You won't have to live
and die with every account.
Bulls---.
It's a sausage factory. I turned
them down three years ago.
This happens
all the time, Don.
It's business.
I'd ask them to put you
on the Caribbean hotels,
but I don't think I'm gonna
stay there much longer.
You come and go
as you please.
Yes, I do.
And you don't give
a crap that my future
is tied up in this
mess because of you?
You wanted my account,
and you were lucky to get it.
And you wanted
to play with me--
Kick me around, knock me down to size
while you called me son.
I get it now, Connie.
It's business.
You know...
I got everything I have
on my own.
It's made me immune to those
who complain and cry because they can't.
I didn't take you
for one of them, Don.
Are you?
- Some other time we'll try again.
- Yes.
Have a nice holiday.
69¢ a bushel.
- That's half last year.
- We ain't gonna make it.
It's as fair a shake
as we could get, considering that
allotment act made
no allotment for wheat.
You were supposed
to get us a good deal.
There's a surplus.
What the hell's he supposed to do?
Well, I ain't
selling at that.
- You've got no choice.
- Sure I do.
I've got a silo.
Store it till winter
when the price goes up.
- How you gonna pay your mortgage?
- That's none of your concern.
- Settle down. We're all in this together.
- No, we ain't, thanks to you.
I take care of mine.
You take care of yours.
Damn it, Whitman,
this is a cooperative.
No more.
Now get out
of my kitchen.
What's so urgent
that you had to wake me?
Conrad Hilton told me P.P.L. is being
sold and us along with it.
- So you knew about this?
- No, but it makes sense--
All that
short-term thinking.
So what do we do?
There's nothing to do.
I have a contract.
You have a contract.
Roger has a contract.
So that's it?
You're losing your business
and you don't care?
- I lost my business last year.
- Well, do something about it.
If Sterling Cooper is for sale,
why don't we buy it from P.P.L.?
We could put everything
back the way it was.
Young men love risk
because they can't imagine
the consequences.
And you old men love
building golden tombs
and sealing the rest
of us in with you.
You're done.
You know that, right?
So I should just
throw away my fortune?
I don't have the rest
of my life to earn it back.
I understand. I'll let you get
back to sleep.
Why do you care?
Because I'm sick
of being batted around
like a ping-pong ball.
Who the hell is
in charge?
A bunch of accountants
trying make $1 into $1.10?
I want to work. I want
to build something of my own.
How do you not
understand that?
You did it yourself
40 years ago.
That's true.
But I'm not sure you have
a stomach for the realities.
Try me.
Well, we're gonna
need accounts.
American Tobacco,
that's most of Sterling Cooper.
But that's Roger.
I understand that.
Did Hilton tell you when this
blessed event is supposed to take place?
New Year's Day.
- We have to talk to Roger now.
- You talk to him.
Do you want
to do this or not?
Honey.
Honey, he probably
feels bad about
the president getting shot on his watch.
Now stop reading the paper.
She's obsessed.
It's the most interest that girl's
ever had in a book depository.
McCann is buying P.P.L.
and is absorbing Sterling Cooper
along with it.
What?
Conrad Hilton told me
this morning.
Christ. From one John's
bed to the next.
What a joke.
Don and I have been discussing the idea
that we buy the company back.
- Really? Why?
- Because we don't want to go to McCann.
And now you're sniffing around because
I have a golden pork chop dangling from my neck.
It's more than that.
- You know Bert's done for.
- Now it's about Bert, huh?
I want to see what you look like
with your tail between your legs.
You sold your birthright
so you could marry that trollop.
Here we go.
This is your pitch?
Well, move along.
I'm not gonna throw it all away because
he doesn't want to work at McCann.
Do you want
to work there?
You don't value what I do
anymore than they do.
I was wrong.
I learned that with Hilton.
I can sell ideas
but I'm not an account man.
You're not good at relationships
because you don't value them.
I value my relationship
with you.
- You do now.
- I do.
I'm sorry.
I've got points, stock.
If I'm useless,
so be it.
There's a deck chair
somewhere with my name on it.
You're right, Roger.
If you've lost your appetite,
you should retire.
Of course, I've seen
that before, so have you.
Men my age,
even younger--
They play golf,
go on vacation,
lose their appetite.
- In three years...
- Join or die?
Jesus, Bert,
he was doing better.
- You know it's true.
- You're still gonna outlive me.
We have to try.
So you do want to be
in advertising after all.
Go upstairs.
- Daddy just got home.
- I'll be up.
Do you want me
to go too?
Please sit down.
I made an appointment
with a divorce attorney
and I suggest
you do the same.
Come on, Betts.
- What are you doing seeing a lawyer?
- I want to be civilized about this.
- Please don't act surprised.
- You haven't been yourself.
Maybe you need to see a doctor--
A good one this time.
Because I'd have to be
sick to want out of this?
You've had a tough
couple of weeks.
We all have.
I've had a tough year.
I felt I should tell you rather than just
let you get a phone call at work.
Well, forget it.
I'm not gonna let you
break up this family.
I didn't break up
this family.
Lane, please shut
the door and have a seat.
Certainly.
We know McCann Erickson
bought P.P.L.,
and we know that makes
Sterling Cooper chattel.
Who told you that?
Someone outside
of this building who knows.
Well, they're wrong.
Lane, we've worked next
to each other for a year.
Don't act like a stranger.
We've got tea.
Well, I suppose you'll
find out soon enough,
but your information
isn't completely correct--
Only Sterling Cooper
is being sold.
- P.P.L., well, will remain p.P.L.
- That doesn't change our plans.
We want to buy back
the company.
We're willing to offer
the purchase price plus 12%.
It's worth more
than that now.
- What did you get?
- I'm not going to say, but more than that.
I apologize you had
to find out this way.
Believe me,
it wasn't my decision.
I've quite
enjoyed it here.
Well, they've only
got me for a year.
You for what, three?
We'll make
another run at it.
The only grounds for
divorce in this state
are absence of a spouse, incurable
insanity, life imprisonment or adultery.
Well, he hasn't
been faithful.
Do you have any witnesses
or corroboration?
Not really.
It wouldn't matter anyway
with both parties at fault.
- N-No. We haven't-- we aren't--
- Ken. Ken, what are you doing?
You think the governor needs
another scandal on the ticket?
I am sorry for presuming,
Mrs. Draper. That was wrong.
So what do I do?
I know it's hard
to understand,
but the state of New York doesn't want
anyone to get divorced.
That's why people
go to Reno.
It's painless.
I met my second wife.
You stay there for six weeks
to establish residency.
Mr. Draper doesn't even need to go,
just consent.
I see.
We need to discuss what you
want in terms of settlement.
Whatever I'm entitled to.
Give us a second.
You don't need
what he can provide.
Henry, I have
three children.
I'll take care of them
and I'll take care of you.
I don't want you
owing him anything.
We want to get this done
as soon as possible.
Saint John,
I'm glad I caught you.
What is it?
Mr. Sterling, Cooper and Draper
have learned of the sale.
What do they know?
It was a mixture of
truth and half truth.
They knew about McCann,
but they were under the belief
that P.P.L.
was being sold as well.
- And what did you tell them?
- That they were wrong.
They even wanted to bid
for Sterling Cooper--
12% above
our purchase price.
Listen,
I apologize, lane.
Obviously the news
is getting out.
- What news?
- P.P.L. is being sold as well.
- What? Why wasn't I told?
- Didn't seem pertinent.
Trying to keep our company
calm as well as theirs.
- Well, where's my place in this?
- With McCann, I suppose.
There there, lane. They know you're
essential to the transition.
- And then what?
- You'll prove yourself irreplaceable.
You always do.
Lane.
Yes?
Don't be disheartened.
I'll put in
a good word for you.
- Thank you.
- No, thank you.
We've got a month till winter,
then we'll be set.
This is what I showed
the man from the bank today.
What are they gonna do,
sell this place?
The bank's gonna get their
payday right after me.
We got nothing and we're about
to have less.
Fine!
I'll sell. I'll sell my crop
for nothing.
Dick.
- What are you doing?
- I'll drive it to Chicago tonight.
You're drunk.
Go.
He can barely stand.
Calm down.
Here.
It ain't gonna rain.
Pa! Daddy! Daddy!
Your guests have arrived.
Close the door.
Have a seat.
- What's he doing here?
- You gonna read us your will?
- I want the Cadillac.
- I couldn't sleep.
And I thought, why don't
we go to McCann directly?
Because you can't. It's done.
- You're not even gonna ask?
- I did, yesterday.
And you were right--
P.P.L. is being sold,
So it seems we're all
going to McCann.
They cut you loose.
I want you to find out what the price was
and give us a shot.
Enough.
I should fire you for even trying
to involve me in this conspiracy.
Go ahead. It's the only thing
you did well here.
- Don, let it go.
- I did a great many things here.
Have another. It's 9:30
for god's sake.
Jes, that's right.
You have absolute authority
to fire anyone.
Fire us.
Fire us. Sever our contracts.
Let us go.
- Can you do that?
- Why would I?
Because once this sale
goes through,
you'll be thrown overboard and you'll be
a corpse knocking against their hull.
Nothing good ever came
from seeking revenge.
Nonsense.
We'll make you a partner.
I should think this
is worth more than that.
So we're negotiating.
We'll put your name on the door.
I don't know.
- Do you know how to do what he does?
- I don't.
It could be done,
But getting you--
us out of here isn't
the difficult part.
- We need accounts.
- Let's say we have Lucky Strike.
And although that's, let's see,
$23 million in Billings--
24.
We'd still need another
third for cash flow.
I can't take anyone else
or Lee Garner sr.
Won't think that he's special.
- What about Hilton?
- No.
Can we get any
of our other accounts?
We'll get them.
If I were to send
a telex in at noon today
That you've all
been sacked,
It's after close
of business in London.
It would remain unnoticed until Monday
morning there--2:00 A.M. here.
That gives us today
and the weekend
To first gather accounts and then
a skeleton staff to service them.
And of course we would have
to obtain all
the materials required for continuity
of service.
Obtain? We he to steal
everything.
Anyone approached
must be a certainty.
If news spreads,
they'll lock us out.
Do we vote
or something?
Well, gentlemen, I suppose you're fired.
We'll, it's official.
Friday,
December 13th, 1963--
Four guys shot
their own legs off.
Allison,
Mr. Pryce has requested
an office-wide memo--
"the office is closed this weekend.
"all work is suspended.
Carpet cleaning."
- Can you get me Mr. Campbell?
- He didn't come in today. He's sick.
Call his house.
It's important.
Peggy, my office.
What do I bring?
Shut the door.
Sit down.
I know we have to roll out
Western Union by New Year's.
I don't have art.
There's no one there.
they're selling
the company.
Again?
I'm starting
a new agency.
I need you here Sunday evening
to get your things
And to help us collect
whatever accounts we end up taking.
- Really?
- Yes.
Who else is going?
Why do you need to know that?
Because it's important.
I can't tell you. Peggy, we are being
bought my McCann.
Do you know
what that means?
You just assume I'll do
whatever you say...
Just follow you
like some nervous poodle.
- I'm not going to beg you.
- Beg me? You didn't even ask me.
Fine, I'm asking you.
I've had other offers,
you know,
that came with a sales pitch
about opportunity.
Everyone thinks
you do all my work.
Even you.
I don't want to make a career
out of being there
so you can kick me
when you fail.
I guess I'll have to talk
to Kurt and Smitty.
I guess so.
- Where the hell are my pajamas?
- Will you please relax?
Trudy, I called in sick today
because I had my interview with Ogilvy.
- I have to look sick.
- You do.
What a pleasant surprise.
Sorry to drop in.
- How are you?
- Better than my husband.
And how are you?
We've been calling all day.
- May I take your coats?
- We're fine.
I'm going to change
the sheets.
- Is everything okay?
- McCann bought P.P.L. and us.
- What? Again?
- We need to talk to you.
- It's serious.
- We're not firing you.
Oh, am I getting a few more
adjectives added to my title?
Don't bother.
I have other plans.
Peter, may I speak
to you for a moment?
Pete, we're starting
a new agency.
We're here to talk
to you about joining us.
Wait a minute.
They're letting you go?
Keep it to yourself,
but I'm taking American Tobacco.
We need another $7-$10 million
in billings for cash flow or something.
What do you have in
your saddlebag so far?
I don't have
a saddlebag.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Pete, I don't blame you for bailing out
the way you've been treated.
- So Kenny turned you down?
- We haven't spoken to Ken... yet.
And yes, we want your accounts,
but we also want your talent.
- Really? And what are my talents?
- You'll do what it takes.
No, I want to hear it
from him.
It's not hard
for me to say, Pete.
You saw this coming,
we didn't.
In fact, you've been ahead
on a lot of things--
Aeronautics, teenagers,
the negro market.
We need you to keep us
looking forward.
I do, anyway.
I want to be a partner
and I want my name in the lobby.
There's not
gonna be a lobby.
North American Aviation,
Secor laxatives,
Gillette, Jai Alai,
maybe Pampers--
That's close to
$8 million already.
I don't think
you get conditions.
We'll make you a partner
if you can deliver by Sunday.
Sunday?
We'll leave the name
and the title as a goal.
Like it or not,
that works with you.
I'd like to say
I'll think about it,
but I don't think
that's an option, is it?
I'm not really sick.
Welcome aboard.
- Good night, Trudy.
- Good night, gentlemen.
- What if I come up short?
- That's not an option.
Good night.
I want you to call
Hubert Adams as Secor.
His number's in my Rolodex.
I threw it under the bed.
Try him at home.
Tell him I'll meet him
at the St. Regis at 7:30
and sound like
a secretary.
I have to get dressed.
I can't believe
he was gonna leave.
That little shit.
Look, they still have
a picture of Kennedy up.
Although, what are
they gonna do,
take it down and put
up Lyndon Johnson?
Not in this place.
I've acted like I've started
a business my whole life,
but I inherited it.
I need an attorney.
Divorce.
So it's true, huh?
- What are you talking about?
- Henry Francis.
- Who?
- Jesus.
Right when things
were almost normal.
I need you to tell me
what you know.
Margaret's friends
with his daughter.
- Are they sleeping together?
- I don't know.
It came
from his daughter.
He talks about her.
It sounds like
it's serious.
I was gonna tell you--
No, I wasn't.
I thought you knew.
I'm sorry I told you.
Believe me.
I'm sorry about that.
- Wake up.
- Shh, he's sleeping.
I don't care.
Who the hell is Henry Francis?
No one.
Stop it.
Stop it!
- Who the hell is he?
- Why do you care?
Because you're good and
everyone else in the world is bad.
You're drunk.
You're so hurt, so brave with
your little white nose in the air.
All along you've been
building a life raft.
Get out.
- You never forgave me.
- Forgave what?
That I've never
been enough?
You got everything
you ever wanted-- Everything!
And you loved it.
And now I'm not good enough for
some spoiled mainline brat?
That's right!
You won't get a nickel.
And I'll take the kids.
God knows
they'll be better off.
I'm going to Reno, you're going
to consent and that's the end of this.
Don't threaten me.
I know all about you.
You're a whore.
You know that?
I want you out
of the house.
Hold the elevator.
- They called you in, too?
- Yes, they did.
- I'll admit it-- I'm a little scared.
- Of what?
- Why are you here?
- I don't know.
Cooper called me.
First they're cleaning the carpets,
now they're not.
- Why are you here?
- Um, work.
Hey, everybody,
Harry Crane is here.
Relax, Pete,
we're expecting him.
- What's going on?
- Why are you here?
I'm sorry,
what's going on?
P.P.L. has been sold to McCann.
We're starting a new agency.
We'd like you to join us
as our new head of media.
- Are you kidding?
- Yes. Yes, we are.
Happy birthday.
We need your answer.
I should really
call my wife.
Mr. Crane-- Harry,
this matter is secret
and time sensitive.
If you turned us down
and elect to be
a mid-level cog
at McCann Erickson,
we'll have to lock you in
the storeroom until morning.
I'm sure you understand.
Pete.
We were hoping you could
decipher these job sheets.
Where exactly
are these materials?
I never look at these.
Can't we just
take everything?
That's good thinking, but
we don't know where anything is.
No one knows
how this works?
Let me make a phone call.
- I'll take care of this.
- No. No more conspirators.
I'll be discreet.
Where's Don?
What did we do?
Nothing.
Then why are we
in the living room?
We want to tell
you something because--
Well, it's going to be
a little bit of a change.
Your father is going
to be moving out.
Now, we'll still be living here
and he'll come to visit.
Then why is he going?
Because...
It'll just be temporary.
Like when you lived
in the hotel?
- Yes.
- It'll be different.
- Is it because I lost your cufflinks?
- No, it has nothing to do with you.
That's not what I mean.
I love you both.
You know that.
Then why are you going?
I'm not going.
I'm just...
living elsewhere.
That's going. You say things
and you don't mean them.
- You can't just do that.
- Sally, sweetheart--
- Go away.
- Sally, stop it.
You said you'd always
come home.
I will.
It's just
a different home.
- Will you be here for Christmas?
- You'll get to have two Christmases.
I only want one.
Did you make him leave?
No. We both decided.
You made him sleep in Gene's room,
and it's scary in there.
Listen to me,
both of you.
I will be here.
You can call me, I will
answer and I will be here.
- Sally. Sally.
- Let her go.
Please don't go.
I don't want you to.
Nobody wants
to do this.
I need you
to be a big boy.
- You look awful.
- Can I come in?
Do you want anything?
Yes, I do.
You were right.
I've taken you for granted
and I've been hard on you,
but only because I think I see you
as an extension of myself.
And you're not.
Well, thank you
for stopping by.
Please. Sit down.
Do you know why I don't
want to go to McCann?
Because you can't work
for anyone else.
No.
Because there are people
out there who buy things,
People like you and me,
And something happened--
Something terrible.
And the way that
they saw themselves...
Is gone.
And nobody
understands that.
But you do.
And that's very valuable.
Is it?
With you or without you,
I'm moving on.
And I don't know
if I can do it alone.
Will you help me?
What if I say no?
You'll never speak
to me again.
No.
I will spend the rest of
my life trying to hire you.
Mrs. Harris, what a
pleasure to see you.
- What is she doing here?
- I said I'd be discreet.
Tell them what to do.
I made a list and I
called some movers.
Can you read these? Do
you know where this stuff is?
Yes. Of course you'll need the
job bags on all these accounts.
We'll also need logo files,
all the film we can find
And negatives which
aren't actually here.
There you go.
- Very good. Now I can pack.
- Sorry I'm late.
Hi.
Joan.
What a good idea.
Well, you're here.
Who did you bring?
North American aviation,
Secor, Jai alai, samsonite.
- Clearasil.
- Really?
I made it.
Where do we start?
Well, I'd start
in the art department.
It's locked.
Great.
I'll start
in my office..
Joanie, I can't read
your writing.
It's perfectly clear--
"correspondence.
Oh, I'm tired.
- Peggy, can you get me some coffee?
- No.
Did you wash your hands?
Hold the elevator.
Greg is going to kill me.
I'm at the Roosevelt, but I'll
need you to find me an apartment.
- Furnished?
- For the time being.
Sorry. Good night.
Go ahead, fellas.
How long do you think it'll take
us to be in a place like this again?
I never saw myself working
in a place like this.
Don't bother.
We've been robbed!
He's waiting on the line.
It's his third attempt.
Saint John, how are you?
What in god's name is
going on over there?
I think at this point
it should be very clear.
You're fired.
You're fired for costing this
company millions of pounds.
You're fired for insubordination!
You're fired
for lack of character!
Very good. Happy Christmas.
Mr. Hooker. I've been sacked.
Please have my office and things
put in storage at this address.
- What's happened?
- You're a sharp boy. You'll figure
it out.
So let's see. I have Peggy
and Pete sharing the desk.
Don, we'll replace
one of these couches
With a table for you, and we're
adding two additional phone lines.
Media will be in the bedroom
with the television.
Accounts gets the bed.
And no one is to come
to this office.
If you have meetings,
please take them elsewhere.
I don't want them in the
lobby or the bar of this hotel.
Well, look at that.
Good morning. Sterling Cooper Draper Pryce. How may I help you?
Yes, Harry, it's room 435.
He didn't leave a note--
Nothing.
Where is he?
I just heard from John Deere--
Pete tried to poach them on Saturday.
He must have gone with Draper.
Damn it.
Sure. Everything is exactly the same.
Don and I will both be on the account.
Thanks, Bill. Okay, bye bye.
- Hello, everybody.
- Lovely, what are you doing here?
I brought lunch. There's every
kind of sandwich imaginable and a cake.
Thank you, Trudy.
- Isn't this exciting?
- It is.
This looks great, Trudy.
- There's food.
- Thank god.
Draper residence.
It's me.
I'm not sure where I'm staying right now,
but I'll be working out of the Pierre.
Okay.
Listen, betts, I want you to know
I'm not going to fight you.
Thank you.
I hope you get what
you always wanted.
You will always be their father.
Okay.
Well, goodbye.
Goodbye.
You know, if you leave your shoes outside the door here, somebody polishes them.
Hello, don.
How was your morning?
Very productive.
Transcripted on Addic7ed.com by VeRDiKT, honeybunny & cRaZyMaGgOt
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net