Previously on Mad Men...
- Do you miss London?
- God, yes.
I don't know what I did
to get under your skin.
I have been watching my life...
Scratching and I'm trying to get into it.
I'm very sorry.
- I started this.
- I don't know what you want.
- ***
- So what?
So I can't stop thinking about you.
Transcripted on Addic7ed.com by cRaZyMaGgOt & honeybunny & Marpessa
Mad Men S03E10
www.addic7ed.com
- Butter.
- And the apples are good now,
but not from the market.
I can go to rodney farms on sunday.
It's near church.
- Can't we go to rodney farms?
- We'll see.
Why don't we go to church?
- We go to church.
- On christmas. Carla goes every sunday.
We don't need to go every week.
- Anything else?
It's early.
- Do you want a drink?
- Yes.
- How was school today?
- Good.
- How come you never ask me?
- I do.
It's just your answer is always longer,
so I thought i'd start with Sally.
- When's halloween?
- Before thanksgiving.
Francine and carlton have invited us, but
I think if we're going to be selling
daddy's house, I don't know,
it might be nice to have it there one last time.
Are you going to sleep here tonight?
No.
You're working too much.
- Betts, I don't have a choice.
- No, that's not what I mean. I just--
I see how hard you're working.
Hello.
Inside.
Were you grading papers?
Why?
I don't know if you're hungry,
but I made date nut bread.
Actually, i made three--
A bake sale.
Oh, your service called.
Mr. Hilton was looking for you,
but he's probably in the air
right now.
Thanks, Miss Farrell.
That's good to know.
I thought so.
I want you to spend the whole night.
- You couldn't possibly
be asleep already.
This eight-year-old, Charlie,
looked up at me
during art today and said:
"How do I know if what I see
as blue is the same
as it is to you?"
And what did you say?
The truth.
I don't know.
I never have,
but I love that he made me
think about that again.
What would you have said?
I would have told Charlie
that my job is about
boiling down communication
to its essentials,
and that I know
that there is a blue
that at least 45% of the population
sees as the same.
Maybe half those people think
they're looking at yellow.
Maybe.
But the truth is people may see
things differently,
but they don't really want to.
Do you feel bad about what you do?
Nobody feels as good about
what they do as you do.
Oh. That's sweet.
I wish I could've known you at eight.
I bet you were serious.
I would've liked you.
Long curly hair--
No one has it anymore.
- Why don't you take her?
- Because I said no.
You'd rather not go than with me?
What do you think Mr. Draper would say
if you showed up at
the sterling cooper 40th with his secretary?
Good morning, Mr. Draper.
- Coffee?
- Morning, Don.
- Morning, fellas. Yes.
- Aqua net, 9:00.
- Get Peggy.
Don, if you could stand over there?
It's Paul Kinsey Theater.
This was my thought:
Aqua net is about hold,
but it is also about beauty.
So we're driving--
Two couples. I call it "Double Date".
The woman in the back's scarf blows off
and her hair starts blowing.
- Her hairdo falls apart.
- Oh no!
And then the woman in front takes off her scarf
and hands it back to the woman in the back.
- Take mine.
- And he says: "Are you sure, Marcia?"
Marcia's hair is perfect.
And then her date gives her
a knowing smile of admiration
on her confident smile.
"Aqua Net. Arrive in style."
Too much story.
Every time I hear "and then" there's
another chance for the ladies at home to misunderstand.
What if it's just the two couples,
the wind is blowing,
the woman in the back has to put on
her kerchief and she just looks longingly
at Miss perfect in front?
"Arrive in style" still works.
And at the end you can see the can
with the kerchief--
Like a see-through one over it
and the wind blows it off
to reveal the aqua net.
A kerchief in a can?
Don't use that,
but very nice.
Well, great then.
What do you have for Western Union?
We don't meet until next week.
Hilton takes precedence, so I need you two
to be ready for me at a moment's notice.
And it has to be TV to compete
with the phone company.
I love getting telegrams, but I never send them.
How is that supposed to help?
I've got it.
My goodness. This is where everyone is.
Allison my dear, do you mind?
- All the paperwork is through on your contract.
It is my pleasure to deliver
your signing bonus personally.
You see, I don't just fire people.
So we finally have an answer to the question:
"What makes Don Draper smile?"
$5,000 seems to be the number.
I wonder why it took two months.
Will your amigo Connie Hilton be attending
the anniversary party friday?
- In his dressiest stetson.
- Splendid.
You will be speaking last.
It's prime time. Please prepare.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Mr. Pryce, your wife is here and
has requested your attention immediately.
- Where?
- Your office.
- What's going on?
- I'll find out.
No, it's okay.
Mr. Kinsey to see you.
- What was that?
Thank you, Olive. What?
I don't need you to put your little
swirl on top of my idea.
- No one's keeping score.
- I am.
And every time we work together,
it looks like you carried the load
because you're spontaneous, you're a girl,
you're his favorite and you use Aqua Net.
- Are you nuts? He hates me.
- That's rich.
Wearing a dress isn't going to help you
with Western Union.
You do your work.
I'll do mine.
Let the chips fall where they may.
Mrs. Pryce, your water.
Thank you ever so much, John.
Will there be anything else?
Oh, he's such a toad.
He is. He is.
Darling, please sit down.
No. I'm not going to let you force me to do anything anymore.
Am I to entertain your ballad of
dissatisfaction or has something
actually happened?
Because I am at work, dear.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I went to pick up my gown.
The queue for my taxi was 10 long
with tose fat ladies in their furs.
Finally I think I'm en route, but I see the park.
I insist it's the wrong direction
and he's obviously running up my fare, which he was.
- I'm so sorry, darling.
- I had to stop here
because I'd already taken a $2.25 tour of harlem and that was all the money I had.
Oh, well, we'll get you home right away.
Do you have enough cash to get me to london?
Because this is not my home.
- These things take time.
- Not for you.
If a superior demands that you be happy,
you say: "Yes, Sir. Right away, Sir."
Go on. Let's have it all, shall we?
Oh, you like it here--
The smells, the noise and the criminals
at every level.
I have made the best of this.
My salary is good. The company is flourishing. My wife has a beautiful gown.
May I see it?
It's not London.
- It's not even England.
- Well, that's true.
I've been here 10 months and no one's ever asked me where I went to school.
Oh. I want to scream.
Don't.
Roll over.
- Just a minute!
Why did you answer?
I had to see you.
I called you from the bus station
in new haven before I started hitching.
I'm so sorry.
Can you give me a minute?
It's my brother.
Get rid of him for 15 minutes.
I'll run out. No, it's okay, Don.
Come outside.
No. So there's a man in here.
He doesn't need to know it's me.
I want you to meet him.
I don't want to ruin this.
It's okay.
I promise.
Danny, I'd like you
to meet my friend Don.
- Sorry to interrupt.
- Danny, be polite.
- I really am sorry.
- What happened there?
- Is it bad under there?
- Are you hungry?
No.
Well, I should be going.
Listen, I know what it looks like,
but I'm not a junkie.
Although apparently I'm too dangerous
to push a cart in a public library.
- He has fits.
I'm sorry.
I interrupted you.
- It's a nice night. I'll see you
in the morning, Suzy.
- Stop it.
- I wish you the best.
- You don't even know me.
- I'll call you.
- Tomorrow.
He could've just stayed inside your bedroom.
I wanted you two to meet.
You're my baby brother.
Well, he knows how to leave a room.
Reminds me of mom.
He's just very private.
He's arrogant.
- His plans were interrupted.
- You don't know him.
I'm going to get you another job,
someplace safe.
Safe.
Other people are the problem.
Name such place.
People are ignorant.
They're scared of things
they don't understand.
I'm really hungry.
1923. We were giddy.
We didn't know the soup was gonna hit the fan,
But we made it through.
All these guys are dead...
Except you, of course...
And Doug Thompson,
But I wish he were.
He left me a whole roll
of bolls laxatives.
I thought they were candies.
I want him to show up and keel over.
Damn it. I don't want to go to another funeral.
Well, I'm not really gonna kill him.
I just would like to, that's all.
40th anniversary.
40 would be an insignificant year
were it not the average lifespan
of a man in this business.
I don't think it's a bad idea to have
a chance to outdrink your clientele.
Who am I kidding?
I don't want to go either.
Have to watch Don Draper accept
an award for his humanity?
- Don is important.
- You know, I found that guy
working in a fur company--
Night school.
And that girl Betty.
I remember Mona said they looked like
they were on top of our wedding cake.
Screw him.
Have the party without me.
I can't do it.
I won't.
Okay. Okay.
It's just a party.
If you don't want to go, you don't have to go.
It's not like it's our company
anymore anyway.
Oh my god.
Remember her?
- Can i?
- If you do it right.
Hello, draper residence.
Hello?
There's nobody there.
They hanged up.
- Hang it up.
Why'd they hang up?
Probably a wrong number.
People do it all the time.
But I could hear somebody
and they heard me.
My goodness, Sally Draper.
Try not to take everything to personally.
Jeez Louise.
WESTERN UNION
What's that, sonny?
The phone is cheap.
It's everday and you can't trust it.
The telegraph is
Honest, solid
and clear. It's old, but it's good...
Traditional.
Sorry about that, Olive.
Peggy.
Peggy!
Hello?
Did you see a girl come through here?
No, Sir.
- I'm Paul, by the way.
- I'm Achilles.
Achilles.
Well, hello, Achilles.
- Are you okay?
- Are you greek?
I'm an american citizen.
No, of course.
It's just that's a mighty big name.
How did that happen?
It's been in my family for generations.
When we have a party and someone says "Achilles,"
all the men turn their heads.
- In fact, one Christmas--
- Hush.
I've got it.
You've got what?
Achilles, I have thought of something
very very good.
- I'm glad to hear it.
- Oh, it's truly great news.
- Yeah, your whole face changed.
- Did it?
Well, I think I shall sleep
very soundly tonight.
I wish you the same.
- Is that taken?
Hey.
I'll only stay for a stop.
I tried to catch you on the platform.
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
Did you call my house last night?
No, I didn't.
- This was a mistake.
- Sit down.
I'm sorry.
You said you'd call me.
Your brother is there.
I don't care about your marriage,
your work
Or any of that,
As long as I know you're with me.
I'm sorry.
I got him a job
At the v.a. Hospital in bedford.
He'll be pushing a broom,
but it has nice grounds.
You can come back tonight.
He'll be gone.
- Are you sure?
- Stop it.
Scarborough!
Briarcliff Manor!
It was nice meeting you.
Mr. Kinsey.
Paul!
Sorry to wake you.
It's 9:00 a.m.
- Good morning, Lois.
- Good morning.
I need you to type something for me.
- Were you in here before?
- No.
- So you haven't touched anything?
- You do that sometimes.
- What was it?
- Does it look like I know?
I wrote it down.
I know I wrote it down.
Did you find it?
It's always the last place you look.
My mother always said to retrace your steps if you lost something.
Would you shut up?
"In conclusion,
With the help of sterling cooper,
Its ingenuity and influence,
America is teaching business
to the world."
Very rousing, Sir.
Churchill rousing or Hitler rousing?
Mr. Pryce's office.
Just a moment, please.
London calling.
Mr. Ford.
- Harold.
- Just calling for a status report on our little party.
All is well, although as of late,
Bert cooper will be in absentia.
- Well, that won't do.
We're flying across the pond.
We expect all the flowers in the vase.
- What does that mean?
Look, Lane,
We've had interest in the company
for some months
And this party is essential to attracting
a second suitor.
For what purpose?
Did we reach you at a bad time?
You seem foggy.
- Saint John here.
- Oh, hello.
Lane, sterling cooper is for sale.
But why?
We've reduced the staff and increased
the revenue by 22%.
I think you've answered your own question.
We need this party to encourage interest.
- Do your best, lad.
- Yes, of course.
- Are you quite all right, sir?
- Yes.
That'll be all.
Henry Francis, please.
It's Betty Draper.
How are you?
What a nice surprise.
I was wondering if you called
my home last night.
No.
No, I didn't.
Oh, well, we had a hang up.
I thought it might be you.
Really?
I'm terribly embarrassed.
Do you want me to call you?
No.
But you thought it was me.
What are you laughing at?
I didn't call you and I'm not going to,
But if you're going to call me, call me.
Don't make up excuses.
I'm not playing a game here.
- Goodbye.
- Goodbye, Betty.
- Do you mind? This is rather serious.
- Go ale forward-slash at the beginning of
It has come to my attention that
You're not attending the
Sterling Cooper 40th anniversary.
I wouldn't have told Roger if I planned on it remaining a secret.
In Great Britain
We have a good deal
Of testimonials and the senior
members are all equally unenthused.
It marks the passage of time.
It's painful, I imagine.
I didn't get to where I am
by dwelling on the past.
So think of the future, hmm?
All of our clients,
all of our staff,
The press, newspapers
and trade publications--
Enjoy the fruit of your longevity.
You really pour the honey on,
then you lick it off.
Well, if you care about Sterling Cooper at all,
Remember that your absence
will make everyone think you are ill.
Who told you I was vain?
Please.
It's obvious.
DECREE OF DIVORCE.
I want to show mommy.
Mommy!
- Maybe she's not here.
- Carla.
- Are you feeling all right?
- I'm fine.
I want you to take
the children to the park.
Don't come home...
Just-- dinner time
Would be perfect.
Take them to the library.
Hello.
- I'm glad to see you.
Sorry again.
We were gonna leave
After school and I am still here, obviously.
You want to wait here for me?
He has to report tomorrow.
Let me do it.
Let me drive him.
Where are you going again?
- Bedford, Massachussets.
- It's a long drive, Don.
And you'll have to come back alone.
Let me do this for you.
I don't want to say goodbye up there.
It's gonna come out ungrateful.
There's $375 in there, okay?
How many times have you done this?
Don't you need to gas up?
No, we're fine.
So you're not gonna stop?
Do you need to stop?
I have some movie in my head where
I give you the slip,
but I might as well tell you:
I'm not going to Bedford.
Well, I am,
So I guess you kind of have to.
Why do you care?
You're just gonna go back and screw her.
I don't know if you're capable
of understanding, but that job is important.
- Did you get me the job?
- No.
So shut up.
I'm not retarded.
Julius Caesar had epilepsy.
- He ran rome.
- Things didn't turn out so well for him.
I know what's waiting for me at that place.
I'm 25 years old, Don.
I don't want to be cleaning toilets
until I die.
Just pull over.
Hold on.
What?
I'm older than you and I'm telling you
It seems bad now, but you can still
change things.
Pull myself up by the bootstraps?
Does that just sound stupid to you?
How do I explain this?
I can't do anything that you can do.
Everyone knows, sooner or later,
that there's something wrong with me.
They're kind and they try,
But then when I come to
With piss in my pants,
They stare at me like i'm from another planet.
I am afflicted, okay?
It's not a question of will.
I can't change that.
Do you need money?
Always.
I swore to myself I would try to do
this right once.
Do what?
I want you to call me if you ever need to.
And I want you to remember
If something happens to you,
Your sister will never forgive herself.
You're not gonna tell her, are you?
That I let you out 20 miles outside
of framingham?
Take care.
I know he thought I was passing him off,
but he means the world to me.
He knows that.
What was the place like?
- Nice.
- Bulls.
He'll be as good as he can be.
Don, I don't want to.
I don't.
It's okay.
Coffee?
No.
Can you get my wife on the phone?
- Betty?
- Where were you last night?
I told you--
I was with Hilton.
Oh, I must have forgotten.
Well, did you remember to pick up my tuxedo?
Yesterday.
It's in the closet.
I'll get home at 5:30.
We should leave within the hour.
I don't know.
I don't know if I'm going to.
What's wrong?
I don't feel well.
Get into bed
And grab a hot-water bottle.
You have seven hours.
It's all the clients
and all the partners,
and they're all expecting me
to show up with the glamorous,
Elegant, stunning Betty Draper.
I want to show you off, Betts.
Okay.
Are you ready? Don's expecting us.
I've got nothing.
What a relief.
Mine's garbage too.
No, I had something,
Something incredible, but I lost it.
I didn't write it down.
I hate that.
It might've been the best idea I ever had.
I did everything: I talked to Achilles;
I spent last night recreating every detail of the evening, hoping it would
Come back. You know how it is.
There was nothing,
then there was it and now it's nothing again.
I'm so sorry.
how do you talk to Achilles?
He is a janitor
with a very bad memory.
You know what the Chinese say?
"The faintest ink is better than the best memory."
Come on.
We've failed before.
Okay, we really looked for advantages.
One of them is, phone calls happen every day.
A Telegram's a big deal.
Something like...
"She's getting married,
are you really just going to give her a call?"
Sounds like you are talking
to her parents.
They should really be at the wedding.
Also...
Old people love them.
"When you care,
send one there."
That's a slogan, not an idea.
Paul?
- Mine aren't any better.
- Damn it, Kinsey. What's your excuse?
- Don't yell at him.
- Excuse me?
- Tell him what happened.
- No.
The dog ate my homework.
I had a great idea and I lost it.
I didn't write it down.
I hate when that happens.
I keep thinking about that Chinese
thing you said. What was it?
"The faintest ink is better than the best memory."
Just makes me think...
You call someone on the phone:
"Hello, I'm getting married",
"Congratulations on the baby" and...
then you hang up.
It's gone.
It's different if you send a telegram.
Telegram is permanent.
Something like:
"A telegram is forever."
You can't frame a phone call.
My God!
That's the way to go.
You keep working on that.
When do you want it?
Party's tonight.
Monday.
See?
It all works out.
Betts, are you ready?
- The car is downstairs.
- The driver is Chinese.
Ready, Betts?
Look how pretty mommy is.
Where are we going?
To Waldorf Astoria, mommy.
Then we passed it,
it's on 5th Avenue.
It moved years ago.
That's right, that's right.
Why did they ever do that?
Enjoy the world as it is, Margaret.
They'll change it...
and never give you a reason.
Mommy, she is not Margaret,
she is Jane. She is my wife.
- Does Mona know?
- Yes, she knows.
You seem surprised that there's traffic.
There's always traffic.
Calm yourself, we'll arrive on time.
They are selling the company.
What?
They are selling Sterling and Cooper.
- When?
- I have no idea.
What happenned to the Americans?
They'll go to the highest bidder.
I know you hate uncertainity
but it complements the fact that
we are returning to England.
I'm gonna keep going on
and make Don Draper wait, because
God knows we've all waited for him.
As if being...
decorated for his services in
Korea were not enough,
his career, has yielded even more awards:
the American Association of
Advertising Agency's
"Arthur Kudner" Award,
"Printer's Ink" Magazine's
Advertising Gold Medal,
The Advertising Writers Association
of New York...
I'm not reading all these.
He is loyal, charming,
quiet, but not modest,
Why should he be?
We have to thank his beautiful wife, Betty,
and his three children,
for sharing him with us.
Because as we all know, sometimes
Sterling Cooper has gotten a large share.
Bert Cooper...
and my father Roger Sterling Senior,
bravely set this in motion
40 years ago.
Now let me introduce the man who
will stand alongside me for the next 40 years
Our creative director, partner,
father, husband and friend.
Don Draper.
Please.
I'm very honored.
Transcripted for Addic7ed.com
by cRaZyMaGgOt & Marpessa
www.addic7ed.cm
www.tvsubtitles.net