/ sent to the encoder
DADDY, DON'T.
IT'S 10:30.
WHY AREN'T YOU ASLEEP?
- I'M AFRAID.
- SALLY.
I KNOW. YOU'RE NOT THOMAS EDISON.
I KNOW.
WHAT ARE
YOU AFRAID OF?
I'M AFRAID OF WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN
WHEN YOU TURN OFF
THE LIGHTS.
I'M HOME NOW.
NOTHING CAN HURT YOU...
EXCEPT MAYBE THIS MESS.
PICK UP YOUR ROOM AND
I'LL GET YOU A NIGHT LIGHT.
OKAY.
GO TO SLEEP.
- WHAT DID YOU FIND OUT?
- NOTHING.
I BET THEY'RE GONNA MAKE
US WORK OVER THE HOLIDAY.
AND COSGROVE'S LATE.
- CAN WE HAVE EVERYONE'S ATTENTION, PLEASE?
- SHH. SHH.
- CAN WE HAVE EVERYONE'S
THIS WILL
ONLY TAKE A MOMENT
AND IT WILL NOT
BE REPEATED.
THAT'S NOT TRUE,
MR. HOOKER.
WE'VE JUST
BEEN INFORMED
THAT THERE WILL BE A VISIT FROM THE
DIRECTOR AND CHAIRMAN OF THE BOARD
OF PUTNAM,
POWELL & LOWE,
THE PURPOSE OF WHICH
IS BOTH FRIENDLY
AND OF COURSE
TO EVALUATE OUR PERFORMANCE.
- MR. HOOKER. - THE VISIT
WILL COMMENCE TOMORROW-
THAT IS TUESDAY-
AT 10:00
AND WILL CONTINUE
INTO THE NEXT DAY.
WE APOLOGIZE. WE REALIZE
WE WERE TO BE CLOSED
- WEDNESDAY JULY 3rd, BUT-
- Man: OH, COME ON.
THEY WERE UNAWARE
OF THE HOLIDAY.
NOW WE MERELY NEED
THAT EVERYONE CONTINUE TO OPERATE
AT THE HEIGHT OF THEIR PRODUCTIVITY
AND TO MAKE SURE THAT
THEIR DESKS AND OFFICES
ARE SHIPSHAPE
AND BRISTOL FASHION.
AND BY NO MEANS SHOULD
THESE PREPARATIONS INTERFERE
WITH OUR WORK TODAY.
VERY GOOD THEN.
DON, MAY WE HAVE A WORD?
WELL, ISN'T THIS PERFECT?
WELL, WE'LL JUST MOVE IT FROM
LUNCH TO THE END OF THE DAY.
I'M HAVING
A CAKE DELIVERED.
- HOW'S THAT GOING TO LOOK?
- A CAKE FOR WHAT?
TOMORROW IS JOAN'S LAST
DAY. I TOLD YOU THAT.
BUT IF WE'RE WORKING ON WEDNESDAY,
WOULDN'T THAT BE HER LAST DAY?
I DON'T KNOW
WHY SHE'D COME IN.
GREG FINDS OUT ABOUT HIS
RESIDENCY TODAY OR TOMORROW-
I'M NOT SURE. I THINK THEY'RE
GOING AWAY TO CELEBRATE.
I'M GOING TO GET SOME MONEY.
WE SHOULD BUY HER SOMETHING.
UMM, HARRY AND PETE,
WE WILL NEED PRESENTATIONS
FOR WEDNESDAY MORNING
ON THE STATE
OF TELEVISION
AND, OF COURSE,
ACCOUNT UPDATES.
- JUST A FEW MINUTES EACH.
- ON EACH ACCOUNT?
NO, A FEW MINUTES
FOR EACH OF YOU.
AND MR. KINSEY,
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO SHAVE YOUR BEARD.
WHAT?! WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU PEOPLE?!
THAT WAS A JOKE.
THERE'S NO NEED
FOR PANIC.
JUST THINK OF THIS AS THE
SAME AS ANY MAJOR CLIENT VISIT.
THEY'RE FLYING ACROSS THE OCEAN
TO HAVE THEIR KNOBS POLISHED?
4th OF JULY-
SUBTLE.
GET THE DOOR,
WILL YOU?
THE BRITISH ARE COMING.
I ASSUME YOU KNOW
I HAVE A THEORY. I BELIEVE
THEY'RE COMING TO SEE YOU.
- WHY?
- THEY'VE SHOWN A GREAT DEAL OF INTEREST IN YOU.
EVER SINCE YOU
SWUNG AROUND YOUR PRIVATES
IN THE BOARDROOM
WITH DUCK LAST YEAR.
Bert: THEY STUDY
AND DISSECT YOUR WORK,
TRYING TO DECIPHER
WHAT IS YOUR PARTICULAR
AMERICAN GENIUS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS?
THE PRESIDENCY?
NO, I THINK IT'LL BE
A CREATIVE UMBRELLA
WITH A DUAL POSITION
- LONDON?
- BYE-BYE, DON.
HOW CONGENIAL
YOU TWO ARE.
I HOPE YOU CAN MAINTAIN THIS
PRETENSE WHEN THEY ARRIVE.
- EXCUSE ME?
- KISS AND MAKE UP
BEFORE YOU COST US
ALL SOMETHING.
YOU'RE BEING
MELODRAMATIC.
MISS BLANKENSHIP,
PLEASE MAKE
AN APPOINTMENT AT ANGELO'S
FOR MR. STERLING
AND DRAPER,
- THE SOONEST AVAILABLE.
- I HAVE MY OWN BARBER.
- THAT'S NOT NECESSARY.
- ENOUGH!
EVERYONE WANTS
MARTIN & LEWIS-
RECONCILE.
DAMN IT!
IT'S DONE!
JOHN DEERE IS DONE.
THE 110 LAWN
AND GARDEN TRACTOR
WITH SNOW THROWER,
TRANSPARENT VINYL ENCLOSURE
AND A KEY.
LOOK AT HIM. HE JUST
BROUGHT IN A MASTODON.
SORRY I'M LATE.
BIG ACCOUNTS MOVE SLOWLY,
BUT THE JOHN DEERE DOESN'T.
LISTEN, MR. CLAMPETT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GET YOUR
IRON HORSE OUT OF RECEPTION.
I WILL...
AFTER EVERYBODY SEES IT.
- NO, P.P.L. IS COMING.
- WHEN?
- TOMORROW MORNING.
- AND WE HAVE TO WORK WEDNESDAY.
- WE HAVE TO GIVE PRESENTATIONS.
- YOU GOT THAT ONE JUST IN TIME.
YEAH, I GUESS I DID.
- SHE'S IN HERE!
- SHH SHH.
I'M RESTING AND YOUR LITTLE
BROTHER'S SLEEPING.
ALL HE DOES IS SLEEP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M BORED.
GO BANG YOUR HEAD
AGAINST A WALL.
- MOM!
- ONLY BORING PEOPLE ARE BORED.
CAN I PET HIM?
DON'T WAKE HIM.
COME OVER HERE.
GO PLAY.
YOU CAN SLEEP ALL YOU WANT,
LITTLE PIG IN A BLANKET.
Roger: THAT IS
QUITE A SHAVE.
I'M THINKING ABOUT
MY TOES RIGHT NOW.
- GO TO TOWN.
- HE'S NEXT.
- I ALREADY HAD ONE.
- SEE, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU THINK THERE'S
SOMETHING FEMININE ABOUT IT?
MY FATHER WAS
THE TALLEST, HANDSOMEST,
VAINEST MAN IN NEW YORK,
AND HE GOT HIS NAILS DONE.
WHOO!
- WHOO!
HE HAD HIS FOURTH CORONARY
BEHIND THE WHEEL
AND THEN HIT A TREE.
WINDSHIELD SEVERED HIS ARM
AND HE WAS DEAD,
SO THEY NEVER PUT IT BACK ON.
IN THE CASKET,
HE HAD ONE HAND-
THE NAILS WERE PERFECT.
I DON'T BELIEVE
THAT STORY.
OKAY, SO HE HIT
ANOTHER CAR AND NOT A TREE.
IT'S MY COMPANY.
WHY SHOULD I BE NERVOUS?
BECAUSE YOU SOLD IT.
SO THAT'S IT?
THAT'S WHAT I DID TO YOU?
I GOT YOU HALF OF A MILLION
DOLLARS? I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- NO ONE SAID
YOU DID ANYTHING.
YOU SOUND
LIKE BURL IVES.
PART OF THE PROBLEM
WITH MONA
IS THAT ONE DAY SHE JUST
STARTED JUDGING PEOPLE.
NEVER GAVE
A CRAP BEFORE.
I'LL TELL YOU
RIGHT NOW, DON,
I DON'T LIKE
BEING JUDGED.
LISTEN, ROGER-
I'M OKAY. I'M OKAY.
WE DON'T NEED TO TALK
ABOUT THIS ANYMORE.
I PROMISE.
I WAS HOLDING OUT
FOR GRATITUDE,
BUT I'LL TAKE THAT.
THANK YOU.
WELL, MAYBE NOW YOU'LL HAVE
THE MONEY AND THE GLORY.
CALL THE PHOTOGRAPHERS,
TYPE SERVICE AND VENDORS
AND TELL THEM ALL DELIVERIES
SHOULD COME BETWEEN 9:30 AND 11:00
SO THE BRITISH CAN SEE LOTS
OF ACTIVITY WHEN THEY ARRIVE.
NOW.
ARE YOU BEING
SHORT WITH ME
BECAUSE YOU THINK
IT'LL MAKE PARTING EASIER?
MY MOTHER USED
TO DO THAT.
I'M NOTICING
FOR THE FIRST TIME
THAT THE LADIES OUT HERE
ARE RATHER PLAIN,
PRESENT COMPANY EXUDED.
WELL, WE COULD HIRE
SOME PROSTITUTES.
I KNOW YOUR PRIME MINISTER
ENJOYS THEIR COMPANY.
THE SECRETARY OF WAR,
AND YOU'D DO BEST NOT
TO BRING THAT UP TOMORROW.
- I APOLOGIZE.
- WELL, I APOLOGIZE
THAT TOMORROW'S VISIT WILL
STEAL FROM YOUR SPOTLIGHT.
PERHAPS WE CAN RESCHEDULE YOUR
SURPRISE PARTY TILL AFTER THE HOLIDAY?
WHY DID
YOU DO THAT?
DO WHAT?
MRS. HARRIS KNOWS EVERYTHING.
I'M SURE SHE WAS EXPECTING IT.
MRS. HARRIS KNOWS
I'M GOING TO GO HOME AND MAKE A
CELEBRATORY DINNER FOR MY HUSBAND.
AND WHEN YOU WAKE UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
AND WONDER WHAT YOU
FORGOT, DON'T CALL ME.
- WELL, THAT'S SMOOTH.
- I GOT A SHAVE.
- WHY?
- THEY ORDERED ME TO DO IT.
WE HAVE AN INSPECTION
TOMORROW- THE BRITISH.
WELL, YOU LOOK
VERY SUCCESSFUL.
HOT OR COLD?
SWEDISH MEATBALLS
OR CHICKEN SALAD?
CHICKEN SALAD.
DID YOU PICK UP
A NIGHTLIGHT?
I DID, AND I READ HER TO SLEEP.
SHE WAS STILL CLINGY.
I DON'T REMEMBER HER BEING THAT
RESENTFUL WHEN BOBBY WAS BORN.
I DON'T KNOW
THAT SHE RESENTS HIM.
WELL, SHE WON'T
GO NEAR HIM.
SHE WON'T EVEN GO IN HIS
ROOM UNLESS I MAKE HER.
SHE WON'T EVEN
- WHY ARE THEY VISITING?
- WE DON'T KNOW.
DELAYED EVERYBODY'S
VACATION PLANS.
HE WAS PERFECT TODAY.
- WHO?
- GENE.
WOULD YOU EVER WANT
TO LIVE IN LONDON?
I'M SERIOUS.
OF COURSE.
I COULD GET A PRAM
AND A REAL NANNY.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
NOTHING.
WHERE THE HELL
WERE YOU?
I TOLD YOU- I WAS GOING
FOR DRINKS WITH THE DOCS.
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME ANYTHING.
YOU DIDN'T CALL ME.
I CALLED YOU
AT WORK.
THAT'S A LIE.
I JUST ATE
DINNER FOR TWO.
GET OVER HERE.
I KNOW
YOU'RE DRUNK.
COME SIT
NEXT TO ME.
SO WHAT HAPPENED?
I, UH...
I DIDN'T GET IT.
WHAT HAPPENED?
IT DOESN'T SAY
ANYTHING EXCEPT
THAT THEY MADE DOUG
HUTCHINSON CHIEF RESIDENT.
AND I FELT THE FLOOR
OPEN UP UNDER ME.
SO YOU'LL GET IT
NEXT YEAR.
YOU KNEW
IT WAS POSSIBLE.
I RAN INTO EDDINGER
ABOUT A HALF HOUR
BEFORE THE LETTER CAME.
I COULD TELL
SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
HE WOULDN'T
LOOK ME IN THE EYE.
I FIGURED HE FELT BAD
AND THAT I'D AT LEAST FIND
OUT WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED.
BUT HE DIDN'T FEEL BAD.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT? HE LOVES YOU.
HE SAT ME DOWN
IN HIS OFFICE,
HE POURED A DRINK
AND HE SAID-
HE SAID I HAD
NO BRAINS IN MY FINGERS.
BUT HE WROTE YOU ALL
THOSE NICE EVALUATIONS.
DAMN IT, JOAN! DOCTORS DON'T
WRITE BAD THINGS ABOUT EACH OTHER.
- SO YOU'LL GO TO ANOTHER HOSPITAL.
- NOT IN NEW YORK.
IF I WANT
TO STAY IN SURGERY,
I CAN GO TO ALABAMA
OR SOMETHING.
SO WHAT HAPPENS?
YOU'RE STILL
A DOCTOR, RIGHT?
I AM.
JUST NOT A SURGEON,
AND I WILL NEVER
BE A SURGEON.
- DID THEY FIRE YOU?
- I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT, JOANIE, OKAY?
I WAS HOPING
YOU WERE ASLEEP.
I HAVE ANOTHER YEAR
OF RESIDENCY.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO LEAVE YOUR JOB.
GREG, THAT'S DONE.
WELL, GET ANOTHER ONE.
HONEY.
LISTEN.
YOU ARE STILL
A DOCTOR.
I MARRIED YOU FOR YOUR
HEART, NOT YOUR HANDS.
THEY ALL WENT OUT
TO CELEBRATE.
I COULDN'T DO IT.
I JUST COULDN'T DO IT.
I COULDN'T FAKE IT.
I'VE BEEN SITTING IN THE
DUBLIN HOUSE SINCE 2:00.
GO LAY DOWN.
I'LL UNDRESS YOU.
JUST LET ME CLOSE
THE LIGHT.
MR. HOOKER, YOU NEGLECTED TO TELL
ME THAT OUR GUESTS HAVE ARRIVED.
- TO WHAT DO I OWE THE PLEASURE?
- THIS IS MRS. HARRIS.
SHE WAS THE OFFICE MANAGER BEFORE ME,
BUT SHE IS OFF
TO GREENER PASTURES.
- WELL, THAT'S A SHAME. GUY MacKENDRICK.
- JOAN HARRIS.
THIS IS
MR. HAROLD FORD
- AND YOU RECALL SAINT JOHN POWELL.
- WE'VE SPOKEN ON THE PHONE.
I BELIEVE THAT'S TRUE.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU
I MADE A RESERVATION
AT LA GRENOUILLE AT 6:00
AND GOT YOU TWO TICKETS TO
"OLIVER." IT'S A WONDERFUL SHOW.
I'VE HEARD THAT
- A TRAGEDY WITH A HAPPY ENDING.
MY FAVORITE KIND.
THANK YOU, JOAN. SHALL I
GIVE YOU THE THREEPENNY TOUR?
- PLEASE LET EVERYONE
KNOW THAT THEY'RE HERE.
WE HAVE YOU
SCHEDULED TO MEET
WITH STERLING, COOPER AND
DRAPER AND THEN WITH MR. PRYCE.
- THEN A LIGHT LUNCH
IN THE CONFERENCE ROOM
WITH THE PERSONNEL
YOU REQUESTED.
TOMORROW, THE PRESENTATIONS
AND CLIENT MEETINGS.
- SAINT JOHN, GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- PETER CAMPBELL.
- THIS IS GUY MacKENDRICK.
- I KNOW EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE A VERY
IMPRESSIVE FELLOW.
I WISH I COULD
RETURN THE COMPLIMENT.
WELL, PERHAPS
ONE DAY YOU SHALL.
GOOD MORNING,
GENTLEMEN.
HELLO.
MISS OLSON,
ONE OF OUR COPYWRITERS.
I KNOW EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU. YOU
ARE A VERY IMPRESSIVE YOUNG WOMAN.
WHY THANK YOU.
I WAS JUST
WRITING COPY.
- AS YOU WERE.
- I HOPE WE CHAT LATER.
MR. DRAPER IS WAITING FOR
YOU IN MR. COOPER'S OFFICE.
THIS WAY.
THAT IS
A VERY HANDSOME MAN.
- GOOD TO SEE ALL OF YOU.
- IT'S A PLEASURE.
DON. NO WORSE
FOR WEAR, I SEE.
WHAT A DELIGHTFUL CUSTOM.
FROM THE FAR EAST I ASSUME?
- JAPAN.
- HOW WAS YOUR TRIP?
GENTLEMEN, I'D LIKE YOU
TO MEET HAROLD FORD
AND THIS YOUNG MAN IS
GUY MacKENDRICK.
MR. COOPER.
- MR. STERLING, WHAT AN HONOR.
- CALL ME ROGER.
- AND YOU MUST BE DON DRAPER.
- I AM.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW EXCITING
IT IS TO FINALLY MEET YOU.
THAT'S VERY FLATTERING.
GUY HERE HAS DONE
A STUDY OF YOUR WORK
AND THAT'S QUITE
A COMPLIMENT.
YOU SEE, IN ADDITION
TO HIS INESTIMABLE CHARM,
GUY HERE HAS DEGREES
FROM CAMBRIDGE UNIVERSITY
AND THE LONDON SCHOOL
OF ECONOMICS.
THREE YEARS AT THE BANK,
TWO YEARS AT McCANN
AND HIS MOST RECENT COUP-
MERCEDES BENZ.
- THAT'S VERY IMPRESSIVE.
- I APOLOGIZE.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
HE WAS GOING TO RECITE
MY ENTIRE
CURRICULUM VITAE.
YOU LEFT OUT "MODEST."
WELL, WE'RE GOING
TO DEBRIEF MR. PRYCE
AND THE PLAN IS FOR YOU
TO JOIN US FOR LUNCHEON.
IN THE CONFERENCE
ROOM AT 1:00.
SOUNDS LIKE
AGATHA CHRISTIE.
WELL, APPARENTLY
OUR TOUR CONTINUES.
I LOOK FORWARD TO- HOW
DO YOU SAY? - CATCHING UP.
I AS WELL.
WELL, THAT WAS STRANGE.
LOOK AT THAT.
- THE SUSPENSE IS KILLING HIM.
- MMM.
YES?
MR. POWELL AND MR. FORD
ARE HERE TO SEE YOU.
- SPECTACLES.
- OH, RIGHT.
SEND THEM IN.
GENTLEMEN.
GREETINGS,
SAINT JOHN.
HAROLD,
WHAT A PLEASURE.
PLEASE SEE TO IT THAT GUY
HAS A SPACE TO PREPARE.
- RIGHT AWAY.
- GENTLEMEN.
THERE'S COFFEE
AND CAKE.
WE'RE VERY
IMPRESSED, LANE.
VERY VERY IMPRESSED
INDEED.
IN NINE MONTHS, YOU'VE
TRIMMED EVERY BIT OF EXCESS,
INCREASED BILLINGS AND WE
HAVEN'T HEARD A WORD OF COMPLAINT.
YES, WELL,
PAX ROMANA AND ALL THAT.
BRAVO. WE'VE DECIDED
TO OFFER YOU SOMETHING
THAT WE HOPE YOU'LL VIEW
AS A REWARD AND A CHALLENGE.
IS IT IN THE BOX?
IN A MANNER
OF SPEAKING.
OPEN IT.
OOH! WHAT IS THAT?
IT LOOKS LIKE
A SNAKE.
FANCY THAT.
IS IT REAL?
- IT WAS.
IT'S FOR
OUR SNAKE CHARMER.
WE'RE SENDING YOU
TO BOMBAY.
BOMBAY?
WHAT WOULD I DO THERE?
WELL, HOPEFULLY THE SAME
THING YOU ACCOMPLISHED HERE.
UH, UMM...
WHERE SHALL
I PUT THIS?
I GUESS I NEEDN'T
FIND A SPOT FOR IT
- IF I'M SIMPLY MOVING AGAIN.
- DON'T POUT.
ONE OF YOUR GREATEST QUALITIES
IS YOU ALWAYS DO AS YOU'RE TOLD.
NO, IT'S JUST THE LOGISTICS
- MY WIFE JUST SETTLED,
MY SON JUST ACCEPTED TO
SCHOOL AND NOW WE'RE MOVING ON.
NONSENSE.
YOU'RE MOVING UP.
- MMM.
- THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
SO WITHOUT FURTHER ADO,
I WILL GIVE THE FLOOR
TO GUY MacKENDRICK.
LET ME BEGIN BY OFFERING
MY WARMEST WISHES
AND ADMIRATION FOR LANE
PRYCE AND HIS EXEMPLARY WORK.
IT'LL BE HARD
TO LOSE HIM,
BUT THERE'S NO DOUBT THAT
OUR LOSS IS INDIA'S GAIN.
NOW LET ME SAY THERE'S
NO CAUSE FOR ANXIETY.
THERE WILL BE NO FURTHER
REDUCTIONS IN THE RANKS.
YES, THAT'S GOOD NEWS
IF I MIGHT, I'D LIKE TO WALK YOU
THROUGH THIS SLIGHT REORGANIZATION.
AS BEFORE, P.P.L. LONDON
WILL BE THE HEAD OF THIS BODY
AND STERLING COOPER,
NOW MORE THAN EVER,
OUR AMERICAN PRESENCE;
OUR BUSINESS MATURITY
WITH YOUR CREATIVE EDGE.
A TRIUMVIRATE OF DON,
MYSELF AND MR. COOPER,
OUR CHAIRMAN EMERITUS,
WILL OVERSEE THREE
STREAMLINED DEPARTMENTS:
CREATIVE ART AND COPY,
ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT-
THAT'S MR. COSGROVE
AND MR. CAMPBELL
FOR THE PRESENT-
AND A COMBINED
TELEVISION MEDIA DEPARTMENT
HEADED BY MR. CRANE.
MR. STERLING'S NOT
ON THAT CHART AT ALL.
THAT'S TRUE.
OH. WELL, THAT WAS
AN OVERSIGHT.
AS YOU CAN SEE, NOTHING
MUCH HAS REALLY CHANGED.
FRANKLY, MY PRESENCE HERE IS JUST
TO ENSURE THOROUGH COMMUNICATION,
THAT WE HELP EACH OTHER
ON BOTH SIDES OF THE POND
WHETHER IT BE A SHARING
OF CREATIVE GENIUS,
MEDIA SAVVY,
OR THE UNBRIDLED ACQUISITION
OF NEW BUSINESS.
I'M SURE YOU ALL HAVE
1,000 QUESTIONS.
BUT FOR THE TIME BEING
I SAY WE INFORM THE TROOPS
SO THAT THE TRANSITION CAN BEGIN
IMMEDIATELY AFTER THE HOLIDAY.
SHALL I HAVE
MR. HOOKER PREPARE A MEMO?
NO. NONSENSE. I DON'T WANT
THIS TO BE THE KIND OF PLACE
WHERE SUCH NEWS IS
DELIVERED THAT WAY.
SHALL WE?
GOSH, WE'RE REALLY
GOING TO MISS YOU.
- WHAT THE HELL JUST HAPPENED?
- THEY REORGANIZED US
AND YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE IN
THIS ROOM WHO GOT A PROMOTION.
- REALLY?
- YES, REALLY.
I APOLOGIZE
FOR MY WILD IMAGINATION.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I WANT
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S FOR YOU.
"FOR MY NEW BIG SISTER,
THE BEST IN THE WORLD."
AND MY GOODNESS,
IT'S FROM BABY GENE.
LOOK.
BABY GENE CAN'T WRITE.
TSK. BABIES GET
FAIRIES TO DO THINGS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
IT'S REALLY FROM HIM.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
I THINK
YOU SHOULD OPEN IT.
- WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S A BARBIE.
I THINK
HE WANTS YOU TO KNOW
THAT HE WANTS
TO BE YOUR FRIEND.
AND YOU ARE
VERY IMPORTANT TO ME TOO.
I'M SURE YOU ALL HAVE
1,000 QUESTIONS,
BUT BEFORE I RAISE A GLASS
TO STERLING COOPER'S FUTURE,
I SHOULD LIKE
TO RECOGNIZE ITS PAST,
MOST RECENTLY,
THE INSPIRED STEWARDSHIP
- OF LANE PRYCE.
- HEAR HEAR!
I'M ALSO AWARE OF A RATHER
SIGNIFICANT MILESTONE.
MRS. HARRIS,
FROM THOSE WHO HAVE
KNOWN YOU ONLY HOURS
TO THOSE WHO HAVE CHERISHED
YOUR NEARLY 10 YEARS OF SERVICE,
I WISH YOU CAVIAR,
CHILDREN
AND ALL THAT IS GOOD
IN YOUR NEW LIFE.
OH, THERE THERE.
THAT WASN'T MY INTENTION.
MRS. HARRIS, PLEASE.
WE'LL HAVE OUR
PRESENTATIONS TOMORROW.
LET THIS AFTERNOON BE
A FETE WORTHY OF JOAN.
ENJOY THE LIQUOR
AND DELICATESSEN.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU ALL.
THIS IS COMPLETELY
UNNECESSARY.
YOU'LL BE
SORELY MISSED.
WE GOT YOU
THE CAKE.
WELL...
SO WHAT NOW? THEY KEEP
ADDING PEOPLE ABOVE US.
ONE MORE PROMOTION AND WE'RE
GOING TO BE ANSWERING PHONES.
WE SHOULD
GO SAY HI.
THIS IS
GOOD CHAMPAGNE.
I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M GOING TO GET
SOMETHING TO EAT.
Allison: MR. DRAPER, CONRAD
HILTON'S OFFICE IS ON THE LINE.
- WHAT?
- CONRAD HILTON,
THE HOTEL OWNER.
- YEAH, I KNOW WHAT HE DOES. WHY IS HE CALLING?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- AND HE'S CALLING FOR ME?
- YES. WELL, HIS OFFICE IS.
PUT HIM THROUGH.
DONALD DRAPER.
Mr. Draper,
this is Miss Wakeman.
Mr. Hilton has expressed
a desire to meet with you.
MAY I ASK WHAT
THIS IS REGARDING?
I just set
his schedule.
When are
you available?
- HOW ABOUT RIGHT NOW?
- "Right now. " Please hold.
How far are you
from the Waldorf Astoria?
15 MINUTES.
It's the Presidential Suite.
I'M ON MY WAY.
MMM. WHERE'S
MISS BLANKENSHIP?
SHE'S DOWN THERE
SALUTING UNION JACK.
WHAT IS THAT?
CHOCOLATE PUDDING.
I WASN'T EVEN
ON THE CHART.
MY NAME'S
ON THE WALL OUT THERE.
- YOU WANT SOME?
- NO.
I LIKE TO THINK, "I'M RICH.
THEY CAN'T HURT ME."
THAT'S A MISTAKE.
I'M BEING PUNISHED
FOR MAKING MY JOB LOOK EASY.
ALTHOUGH
- THAT KID GUY, HE HAS A SPARK.
HE IS
A PURE ACCOUNT MAN.
AND WHAT IS
THAT JOB ALL ABOUT?
I DON'T KNOW. IT'S ABOUT
LISTENING TO PEOPLE
AND NEVER SAYING WHAT'S
REALLY ON YOUR MIND.
NO. IT'S ABOUT
LETTING THINGS GO
SO YOU CAN GET
WHAT YOU WANT.
HAVE A NICE HOLIDAY.
ENJOY THE FIREWORKS.
WE TOOK THEIR MONEY.
WE HAVE TO DO
WHAT THEY SAY.
MY DAD KEEPS TALKING
ABOUT VIETNAM.
LIKE HE WANTS ME
TO GET DRAFTED.
FIRST OF ALL, THEY'RE
HARDLY DRAFTING ANYBODY.
SECOND OF ALL,
YOU'RE TOO OLD.
THIRD OF ALL,
I HAVE A FRIEND
IN THE ARMY,
AND IF YOU'RE SMART,
YOU'RE SET.
HE SITS BEHIND
A DESK AT FORT DIX
AND SCREWS
SECRETARIES ALL DAY.
DOES HE SHOOT
THE PEOPLES?
I DON'T KNOW. I'VE GOTTA TAKE A PISS.
- JOAN.
- YES?
- MAY I SPEAK WITH YOU?
- THANK YOU.
I JUST
- I WANTED TO GET YOU A CARD OR A PRESENT.
IT'D BE NICE IF I GAVE
YOU A GIFT FOR ONCE
AND YOU DIDN'T WONDER
IF I WANTED SOMETHING.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO THINK
I NEVER LISTEN TO YOU.
IT'S JUST-
WE CAN'T ALL BE YOU.
BE THAT AS IT MAY,
I DO TAKE SOME CREDIT
FOR YOUR SUCCESS HERE.
HEY, PUT THAT BACK.
I'M GOING HOME!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M GOING TO MISS THIS!
I'M REALLY HAPPY THAT
YOU GOT WHAT YOU WANTED.
I REMEMBER
ON MY FIRST DAY YOU SAID
THAT COULD HAPPEN TO ME
IF I PLAYED MY CARDS RIGHT.
ARE YOU GETTING
SENTIMENTAL?
OH! OH MY GOD.
DON'T WORRY. I'M SURE WE'LL
SEE EACH OTHER ALL THE TIME.
- IF WE DON'T,
I JUST HAVE TO SAY-
OH, FOR THE LOVE
OF CHRIST!
OH MY GOD.
- OH, MY FOOT!
- CALL AN AMBULANCE!
- HOLY CRAP!
- JESUS!
THERE'S A TOURNIQUET
IN THE FIRST AID KIT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
DEAR GOD.
I CAN'T FEEL
A THING.
OH, GOD!
WHAT DID I DO?!
GET HER OUT OF HERE!
- GET HER OUT OF HERE!
- THE AMBULANCE
IS ON ITS WAY.
- I'M DONALD DRAPER.
- WE'VE MET BEFORE.
WE HAVE,
HAVEN'T WE?
YELLOW ROCK
COUNTRY CLUB.
WE HAD A DRINK.
OF COURSE.
YOU FIXED IT FOR ME.
LET ME RETURN THE FAVOR.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE CONRAD HILTON.
CONNIE.
DON.
FOOD?
BEST KITCHEN IN THE WORLD-
GOT A SALAD NAMED AFTER IT.
I'M FINE. I REALLY
SHOULD HAVE KNOWN THAT.
I DON'T KNOW.
NOW, UH...
AFTER THIS COMES OUT
NEXT WEEK-
WELL, THEY DON'T
DO THAT FOR EVERYONE.
I THINK I LOOK
LIKE AN ARAB.
HOW DID
YOU FIND ME?
I CALLED AROUND, TOLD
PEOPLE I HAD A LONG CHAT
WITH A HANDSOME FELLA
FROM STERLING COOPER
AND YOUR NAME
NEVER CAME UP.
APPARENTLY YOU DON'T HAVE
LONG CHATS WITH PEOPLE.
WELL, HERE I AM.
WHAT CAN
I DO FOR YOU?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK YOU WOULDN'T BE IN THE
PRESIDENTIAL SUITE RIGHT NOW
IF YOU WORKED
FOR FREE.
DON, THIS IS
FRIENDLY.
CONNIE, THIS IS MY PROFESSION.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
I WANT YOU
TO GIVE ME ONE FOR FREE.
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY WANTS TO
THINK ABOUT A MOUSE IN A HOTEL.
WELL, THAT WAS MY IDEA.
YOU GOT SOMETHING BETTER?
I MIGHT.
SO...
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I'M NOT GONNA LIE
- I'D LOVE A CHANCE AT YOUR BUSINESS.
OKAY...
BUT THE NEXT TIME
SOMEBODY LIKE ME ASKS YOU
A QUESTION LIKE THAT,
YOU NEED
TO THINK BIGGER.
WELL, CONNIE,
THERE ARE SNAKES THAT
GO MONTHS WITHOUT EATING
AND THEN THEY FINALLY
CATCH SOMETHING,
BUT THEY'RE SO HUNGRY
THAT THEY SUFFOCATE
WHILE THEY'RE EATING.
ONE OPPORTUNITY
AT A TIME.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
MR. DRAPER, YOU HAVE
AN EMERGENCY CALL.
HOME OR OFFICE?
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S HAPPENED HERE?
- THAT WE'RE NOT TO BE TRUSTED?
- SHE'S AN IDIOT.
- I DIDN'T KNOW SHE COULDN'T DRIVE.
- YOU TOOK THE MACHINE OUT.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE RESPECT
FOR THAT EQUIPMENT.
IT'S VERY SAFE
WHEN OPERATED CORRECTLY.
WE HAD THE WORLD HANDED
TO US ON A PLATE,
AND THEN YOU SWING IN
ON A CHANDELIER,
DROP YOUR PANTS
AND CRAP ON IT.
JESUS, IT'S LIKE
IWO JIMA OUT THERE.
WE SHOULD PUT A RUBBER MAT
DOWN SO COOPER CAN GET AROUND.
THEY'RE CHANGING
THE CARPETING.
ANY NEWS?
HE MIGHT LOSE
HIS FOOT.
RIGHT WHEN HE GOT IT
IN THE DOOR.
OH GOD.
SIT DOWN, SISSY MARY.
YOU'RE PALE.
I TAKE
FULL RESPONSIBILITY.
BELIEVE ME,
SOMEWHERE IN THIS BUSINESS,
THIS HAS
HAPPENED BEFORE.
JOAN- MY GOD.
I KNOW.
IT'S RUINED.
- HOW IS HE?
- I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU TO COME OVER.
I JUST THOUGHT
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
HONESTLY, WHEN I CALLED YOU,
I THOUGHT HE MIGHT DIE.
- BUT HE'S NOT GOING TO?
- MMM.
NO. HE'S LOST
THE FOOT.
JESUS.
THAT'S AWFUL.
LANE WENT TO RETRIEVE
POWE AND FORD FROM DINNER.
THEY'VE ALREADY TALKED
TO THE DOCTOR.
I'LL WAIT.
DESPITE
THE CIRCUS TODAY,
I HOPE YOU KNOW THAT YOU ARE
GOING TO BE TERRIBLY MISSED.
THAT'S NICE TO HEAR,
ESPECIALLY
FROM YOU, DON.
I BET HE FELT GREAT WHEN
HE WOKE UP THIS MORNING.
I'M SURE
YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT THAT'S LIFE.
ONE MINUTE YOU'RE
ON TOP OF THE WORLD,
THE NEXT MINUTE SOME SECRETARY IS
RUNNING YOU OVER WITH A LAWN MOWER.
Lane: OH!
- I'M HEARTBROKEN.
- IT'S A TERRIBLE TRAGEDY.
ONE THAT SURELY
COULD HAVE BEEN AVOIDED,
ALTHOUGH, MRS. HARRIS, THANK
YOU FOR YOUR QUICK THINKING.
- YOU MAY HAVE SAVED HIS LIFE.
- SUCH AS IT IS.
HE WAS A GREAT ACCOUNT MAN
- A PRODIGY.
HE COULD TALK A SCOTSMAN
OUT OF A PENNY.
NOW THAT'S ALL OVER.
I DON'T KNOW
IF THAT'S TRUE.
THE MAN IS
MISSING A FOOT.
HOW IS HE GOING
TO WORK? HE CAN'T WALK.
THE DOCTOR SAID
HE'LL NEVER GOLF AGAIN.
I'M AFRAID WE HAVE TO
REEVALUATE OUR ENTIRE STRATEGY.
LANE WILL REMAIN
HERE INDEFINITELY.
WE'LL CLOSE THE OFFICE
TOMORROW, OBVIOUSLY.
MRS. HARRIS,
PLEASE ALLOW THE COMPANY
TO REIMBURSE YOU
FOR THAT DRESS,
JUST AS A TOKEN
OF OUR GRATITUDE.
I THINK SAINT JOHN AND I
SHOULD SEE HIM IF WE CAN.
OF COURSE.
YOU SHOULD GET HOME
TO THAT LUCKY HUSBAND.
YES.
HUH.
CAN I GET YOU ONE?
SURE.
I'VE BEEN READING A LOT OF
AMERICAN LITERATURE LATELY.
- "TOM SAWYER."
- THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
I FEEL LIKE I JUST WENT
TO MY OWN FUNERAL.
I DIDN'T LIKE
THE EULOGY.
- HEY. HEY HEY HEY HEY. HEY HEY.
- DADDY!
HEY. I'VE GOT YOU.
I'VE GOT YOU.
JUST BREATHE.
SHH.
GET HIM OUT, DADDY!
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
SHH.
- DADDY.
- SHH.
OKAY, CALM DOWN
AND TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON.
GRANDPA GENE-
HE'S NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE ANYMORE.
- HE'S NOT.
- HE'S CALLED GENE,
HE SLEEPS IN HIS ROOM,
HE LOOKS JUST LIKE HIM
AND I BET WHEN
HE STARTS TALKING
HE'S GONNA SOUND
JUST LIKE HIM TOO.
HE'S A BABY.
THAT'S IT.
I WANT YOU
TO GO TO SLEEP.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS GHOSTS.
BETTS,
THIS HAS TO STOP.
THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO.
SHE'S JEALOUS
OF HER LITTLE BROTHER.
NO, SHE'S NOT JEALOUS.
SHE'S SCARED,
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE
HE HAS THAT NAME.
"THAT NAME."
YOU'VE NEVER LIKED IT,
YOU HAVEN'T HIDDEN IT WELL AND
NOW YOU'RE BRINGING HER INTO THIS.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
LET'S TALK ABOUT SALLY.
SHE'S A CHILD.
SHE'LL GET OVER IT.
NOW YOU HAVE TO.
HE WAS MY FATHER
AND THAT WAS HIS NAME.
IT'S WHAT
PEOPLE DO, DON.
IT'S HOW THEY KEEP
THE MEMORY ALIVE.
HE HATED ME
AND I HATED HIM.
- THAT'S THE MEMORY.
- THAT'S HIS NAME.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO WAKE HIM.
THAT'S OKAY, HONEY.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
COME ON.
LET'S GET YOU TO SLEEP.
COME OVER HERE.
YOU SEE?
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS
YOUR LITTLE BROTHER
AND HE'S ONLY A BABY.
WE DON'T KNOW
WHO HE IS YET,
OR WHO HE'S
GOING TO BE.
AND THAT IS
A WONDERFUL THING.
SHH.
YEAH
www.tvsubtitles.net