Previously on Mad Men...
I wanted you to come to me.
- And why is that?
- Because you're married.
- So you're missing here?
- Are you asking if I miss you?
- What's your name?
- It used to be Dick Whitman.
I didn't want to go to her wedding,
but I did.
The least you can do
is not come to mine.
You're not even giving Jane a chance.
I wanna take you in that bedroom,
And give you a go round
like you never had.
I wanted to inform you that
you're now the head of accounts.
Excuse me?
We're making you head of accounts.
Spectacular.
Mr. Campbell.
I've got your hot cocoa.
Wonderful.
I just got back from lunch,
and Mr. Pryce wants to see you.
- It's instant.
- It's from the diner.
I don't know how you can tell.
You can tell because they use
water instead of milk.
It's warmer outside.
It's ridiculous.
The building will take care of it.
They always do.
Sorry about that.
This really is hitting the spot.
Come in.
Have a seat.
I believe I have what is
rather disappointing news.
It's been decided that Mr. Cosgrove
will be made Senior vice president
In charge of account services and
you will
be made head of account management.
Really?
This is not to
ignore that you've
Distinguished yourself and been
of great service to the company.
What is it based on?
Our billings are neck and neck.
In fact, i think I've done a lot
With what i was given
in this arbitrary scheme.
It's become apparent that you are
excellent at making the clients feel
Their needs are being met,
but mr. Cosgrove has the rare gift
Of making them feel as
if they haven't any needs.
- I see.
- I improved your title.
And you tell your clients there'll
be no need to be deprecating.
- Bert and Toger know about this?
- This is under my authority.
And i have to commend you
on taking it as well as you have.
I hope this was
a difficult decision.
It was.
There you go.
- Where are you going?
- I don't feel well.
Why did you pick that place?
I don't know why a lunch counter is
- any better than eating at your desk.
- Well, you could've joined me for a drink.
I can drink at my desk if i
want to, and i'm not out $1.25.
I'm sorry I'm not asstimulating
a lunch companion as doug,
It's duck, and i work most lunches.
Well, i don't like his aftershave.
I can smell it on you and i can smell
it in the bathroom in the morning.
What's wrong with him?
Nothing. I don't even know why i'm
weighing in on men right now.
I think it's good that
you're being picky, finally.
Well, there's nothing around but married ones, I
mean, we can't all throw caution to the wind.
Duck's not married.
Oh. Then why are you with him=
Well, this is me.
- Are you working late tonight?
- I don't know yet.
Bye.
Wow. Van Cleef.
How very Janie Siegel-Sterling.
They're blue and they're new.
- She's trying.
- You always take her side.
- I do not.
- She started giving me advice--
"Don't go to bed angry.
Let them do what they want.
Dress sexy"--
And all i kept thinking
about was daddy.
It's disgusting doesn't
she know that?
That she ruined my life?
Your father had a part in it.
You don't think I know that?
Brooks is different
than your father.
I don't want to get married.
Everything's pointing to the fact that
I Shouldn't and everybody knows.
Brooks knows.
His mother knows.
Do you know what she said to me?
She said in India if the wedding
doesn't take place at the appointed hour,
- They burn the bride.
- Just because she went to India,
Doesn't mean she's not an idiot.
And jane--
If she's coming,
I'm not going.
She's coming because your father's
coming and he paid for everything.
You're having the wedding.
The bride will not be burned.
Turn those earrings into
a tea service or something.
- Aren't you listening to me?
- I am and you're babbling like a little fool.
- Go to your room.
- What?
You heard me. You want to act like
a child I'll treat you like one.
Would somebody get that?
- Hello.
- Daddy.
Are you alone?
- Yes, what's wrong?
- Nothing's right.
My bridesmaids are supposed to give me
something blue and something new--
Or mommy. She should know that.
Who?
I don't like her, daddy, and i've told
you I don't want her to be there.
- Honey, put your mother on the phone.
- He wants to talk to you.
You have to keep Jane under control.
Well, first of all, tell the
bride that everything is copacetic.
We both agree that she's
nuts and she should shut up.
Your father said that he's sorry,
that Jane will stay
Out of your way And that
we're both tired of the drama.
- He said all that?
- I'm not playing chicken anymore.
If she wants to cancel the wedding,
I'll take the deposit out of her inheritance.
He said the wedding's off.
- Fine.
- You mean that? You're not
worried about India?
- Why are you doing this?
- Do you want to cancel it or not?
No.
Then go eat something.
I'm not taking that dress in again.
Why did Jane get her
such an expensive gift?
I didn't even know they saw each other.
Of course you didn't.
- I forbid it.
- I can't wait to get her out of here.
Is everything okay?
Goodbye.
Yeah, goodbye.
Jane!
Get in here now.
I didn't know you were home.
You were home. I overdid it at lunch,
as did you, i heard.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I just wanted to make amends.
- I got her a beautiful present.
- Why the hell are you even talking to her?
You're screwing things up!
I'm tired of the awkwardness
And i'm trying to be nice.
I don't know what kind of world you live
in, but i am the good person here.
You're not good because you didn't
listen to me and you really upset her.
Everything you do is for her.
I'm your wife. And guess what--
I live here and i get to do what i want to do,
So stop trying to tell me
that you know better.
You'd better not have
locked that door.
Go away!
Or what? You'll commit suicide?
Peter, what are you doing home?
I got fired.
What happened?
Lane told me Kenny
is senior something
Of something accounts and i'm not.
I'm account something.
I couldn't even hear him.
All i saw was his
froglike mouth flapping.
- So did he ask you to leave?
- No.
I have to ask this, but
did you lose your temper?
No, i didn't.
That's good.
That's verygood.
Do you remember if he said anything
about how much they want you to stay?
- No.
- That's good too. So it didn't come up.
Trudy, stop it with
the ellery queen.
I'm going to call Duck.
No, you're not. They would have
fired you if they wanted to fire you.
You need to wait and see how it goes.
He basically said I care too much
about my clients and they notice it.
How could that be bad?
Peter, you hold all the cards.
It's going to be fine.
I thought you had left.
I'm here.
I see.
Well, thank you.
I've done it before.
Go back to bed.
Do you want anything?
No. I'll be in in a bit.
Oh, it's got to be 100 in here.
You ask the building
for heat, you get heat.
Mr. Herman on line one.
Hello. Can you give me a minute?
No.
I'm right around the corner
at the elysee, room 531.
I'm in the middle of something.
Peewee sweetheart, it's been three weeks.
You can get room service.
I think they have a Monte
Cristo sandwich. You love that.
I'm having lunch with Kurt and Smitty.
They're a couple of homos.
Tell them you have plans.
It's kind of short notice.
Come on, creative, be creative.
I have to go to the printer.
I know a nooner when I hear one.
You're disgusting.
No, Bob did.
Bob?
I was hoping to catch you on your way to lunch.
Too late.
I must say I'm surprised.
Frankly, I was a little suspicious... I found out yesterday
that  head of accounts is going to Kenny and his haircut.
I heard.
Can you turn that off?
Not really.
Did you ask him why he invited her?
He said something about not wanting her
to actually have to get involved.
What does it mean?
It's not good.
I know it's not good.
There's no future for me her
How did you do it?
You made your job u
I didn't. I looked at other agencies,
saw that they had Tv departments
and wondered why we didn't.
Oh. There's no such thing in the accounts field.
There's marketing.
That's a research job.
Is this official?
Yes.
I'm afraid we can't hire Mr. Charcot.
Well, at least you had the guts
to send me a memo.
He's far too expensive.
Salvatore Romano is gone.
There is no one in charge
of the art department.
I haven't heard a complaint
from any of the clients.
Jesus! It's hotter in here than in my office.
That's because you're overexcited.
Do you want me to walk you
through a delivery schedule?
This is Walter Cronkite in our newsroom
and there has been an attempt,
as perhaps you know now,
on the life of President Kennedy.
He was wounded in an automobile
driving from Dallas airport
into downtown Dallas along with
governor Connally of Texas.
They've been taken to Parkland
Hospital there where their condition
is as yet unkn...
My God, how much have
you been smoking in here?
Sorry about that.
I'm, uh, glad you ran over.
Me too.
I don't understand.
I can't run my department
without an art director.
Do you want to call Saint John?
Bert Cooper still has a say around here.
Hello. What?
If they wanted to fire you,
they would've fired you.
I'm gonna die at this desk, unnoticed.
Do you have any idea what
I've done for this company?
- What are you doing??
- They shot the president.
What?
... top of the President's car
was down they drew their pistols,
but the damage was done. The
President was slumped over
in the back seat of the car, face down.
Then Governor Connally, after
slumping to the left for a moment,
lay on the floor of the rear seats.
Oh my God.
- Dear God.
- Is he dead?
What the hell is going on?
Every person listening at this
moment has flashed back
to that day in April, 1945,
when Franklin Delano Roosevelt...
Excuse me, Chet, here is a flash
from the Associated Press,
Dateline Dallas.
Two priests who were with
President Kennedy say he is dead
of bullet wounds.
There is no further confirmation,
but this is what we have...
Is he okay?
They just said he died.
Two priests in Dallas who were
with President Kennedy
say he is dead of bullet wounds.
- Oh, lord.
- There is no further confirmation.
This is the only word we have
indicating the President may,
in fact, have lost his life.
It has just moved on the Associated
Press wires from Dallas.
The two priests were called to the
hospital to administer the last rites...
- Oh my goodness.
- I know.
And it is from them we get the word
that the President has died,
that the bullet wounds
inflicted on him as he rode
in a motorcade through downtown
Dallas have been fatal.
We would remind you there is no official confirmation of this from
any source as yet.
Bill, just moments before
you brought the flash, I had
word from the hospital
that the vice President, Lyndon Johnson,
and his wife had just left the hospital,
been rushed away into a motor...
Did you give me a hickey?
- I don't think so.
- I told you I don't like that.
I get questions from my mother.
Listen. There was a news story that
was on right before you came in.
It's been distracting me.
You didn't seem distracted.
I just want to see what's going on.
What's going on?
... It was only on October the
24th that our ambassador
to the United Nations, Adlai Stevenson,
was assaulted in Dallas leaving
a dinner meeting there.
From Dallas, Texas, the
flash, apparently official:
President Kennedy died at
1:00 p.m. Central standard time,
2:00 eastern...
- Jesus.
- Oh my God.
What happened
Vice President Lyndon Johnson has
left the hospital in Dallas.
I've gotta call my kids.
We do not know to where he has proceed.
Presumably, he will be taking
the oath of office shortly
and become the 36th President of the United...
President Johnson is under heavy guard...
it's ruined.
It's over.
It's gonna be ruined.
Five-year- old boy and myself were by
ourselves on the grass there on Palmer Street.
and I asked Joe to wave to him.
Betts?
Where's your mother?
She's not feeling well.
I can't stop crying.
Why are the kids watching this?
What am I supposed to do, Don?
Am I supposed to keep it from them?
Take a pill and lie down.
I can handle the kids.
Turn this off. I'll make us some dinner.
A polaroid picture taken
by another witness,
Mary Norman of Dallas, showing the
President slumped over in the car.
Just as Mary started to take
the picture, the President came
right even with us, two shots...
You two, look at me.
Two shots rang out and he grabbed his chest.
Everything is going to be okay.
We have a new President and we're
all gonna be sad for a little bit.
And then on Monday there's gonna be a funeral.
Are we going to the funeral?
... shots rang out, but by that time
the motorcade had sped away.
... Fair play for Cuba,
a pro-Castro organization,
where he had been arrested
on disturbance of the peace charges.
He denied he was a communist,
said he was a Marxist and claimed there was quite a difference
between the two. Police in Dallas
have just announced...
you should get ready. It's almost 2:00.
Really, Don?
... Gunpowder traces on both hands,
indicating he'd recently used a rifle...
the type of weapon that killed
Mr. Kennedy yesterday.
As we told you a short time ago,
Oswald has refused...
He's 24 years old.
In Washington, the body
of the late President
lies in the east room of the White House...
Come on, Betts.
Are you sure they haven't canceled it?
It said in "The Times"
they were doing that.
I'm not gonna call Roger to find out.
If we go in and it's off,
we'll grab dinner or something.
I can't sit in front of the tv all day.
Fine.
Just stay here until Carla comes.
After the terrible news had reached us...
Can you see bags?
I don't understand this.
And here we are...
Lyndon Johnson, more of the same.
Nobody voted for him.
It felt for a second like everything
was about to change.
You should get your coat and your scarf.
I know it's far, but I
really feel like walking.
Why are we going?
Because it's your boss's daughter's wedding.
It's business, Pete, and there
a system. You always say that.
It's one thing to go to this wedding
and act like I don't hate them.
It's another thing to go and act
like the President hasn't been murdered.
Maybe they'll cancel it,
but we have to show.
- Have you been drinking?
- The whole country's drinking,
and not to celebrate some
spoiled brat's wedding.
We are mourning together with his widow...
They'll never cancel.
You know why?
Because they're happy.
You should've heard some of
the things people said yesterday.
Like what? What did they say?
"The man made a lot of enemies," things like that.
That's awful.
I don't care what your politics
are, this is America.
You don't just shoot the President.
Chet Huntley was talking about
Jackie and those kids,
how she just lost that baby, and Harry Crane was
looking at his paperwork, calculating how many
commercials weren't going to be aired.
I'm not going.
You can go and say I'm sick
if you think it's that important.
"... Demonstrates the internal threat
that can never be underestimated."
No, you're right.
"Our sympathy for the Kennedy family
is no less that it is for the millions
of people who have sustained
equal losses in the fight for freedom."
I got a call from Leona, this girl I used
to work with at the phone company.
My friend Francine called me.
Don couldn't get through.
The system was completely overloaded.
It's annoying that people think the
operators were watching tv.
They were as frustrated as anyone.
The maitre d' has reorganized the seating.
If you are at an even-numbered
table, take these first six.
If you are at an odd-numbered table,
the left side of the room.
Maestro, do you mind?
Thank you.
Look, everybody, grab your plate
and come on up to the front here,
sit wherever you feel like.
And please feel free to have the
prime rib and the fillet of sole.
Help yourself.
I mean that. There are no waiters.
Three months after Roosevelt
died, we bombed Hiroshima.
That's how we got over it.
I say we hang Lee Oswald and
then we take care of Texas...
Hell, the whole south.
What did everyone think of the sweetbreads?
You were right, mommy. Okay?
Problem solved.
Hardly.
They just told me the cake's not coming.
Shit.
I have to say on some level Harry has a point.
I think he wanted attention.
He obviously didn't fit in.
Congratulations.
You are so beautiful, like Natalie Wood or something.
Daddy, I really wish you could've
gotten to see the ceremony.
It's okay. We understand.
We're honored you're here.
I heard the church was packed.
Those weren't our guests.
Have a seat.
Just sit anywhere.
I'm so happy for you.
I would like some legal representation,
but these police officers
have not allowed me to have any.
I don't know what this is all about.
- Did you kill the President?
- No, sir, I didn't.
People keep asking me that.
How would you know that's
what a monster looks like?
Naturally, if I work in that building, yes, sir.
Did you see "The Times"?
He lived in Russia.
I thought he just visited.
Would you visit?
I'm just a patsy.
There you are. What are you doing here?
They're about to interview Oswald.
Hey, somebody go buy a cake.
Has the gentleman been identified?
I need you out there. I'm about to give my toast.
I've heard your toast a million times.
The President is dead.
And I'll tell you... something else...
our table has no one at it.
I consolidated the tables.
Would you keep an eye on her?
Absolutely.
We'd better get back in there.
Jane.
That this investigation has
been carried on jointly...
This toast is going to be much
shorter than it was supposed to be.
Obviously, we're all in a different mood.
Can someone please get my
wife out of the kitchen?
I have something very nice
to say about her.
But while we're alone...
...I want to say something
nice about my ex-wife.
Mona, you're a lioness.
And thank you for resisting
the urge to eat your cub.
This could've been an awful
day, but here we are...
Not watching tv but, together,
watching the two of you.
To Margaret and Brooks Hargrove.
The adults... we all wanted to be
strong for you, but your spirit
your love, your hope is giving us strength.
And I promise you now...
if you can make it
through a day like today,
marriage is a cakewalk.
To many years of happiness.
Cheers.
We invite the father of the bride and
the bride to share the dance floor.
Sorry about that.
Now if there are any other
fathers and daughters...
You know what? Everyone, please, join them.
Do you want to dance?
I don't know.
Want me to teach him how to dance?
He's a great dancer.
She's happy.
That's because she doesn't know his
net worth just dropped by half.
Stop it, daddy.
Everything's gonna be fine.
How do you know that?
You'll see.
Why do you keep
looking at that woman?
What are you talking about?
- are you ready?
- did jennifer fall in?
- she'll be right out.
- see you tuesday.
He was so handsome, and now i'll never get
to vote for him.
You want me to cut you out
of that dress?
I'm making a phone call.
- hello.
- so what's new?
It's incredible, isn't it?
Yes.
Margaret got married today.
That's right. I forgot.
Poor thing.
Joanie, i wish you could've seen it.
Oh my god, what a disaster.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, she pulled through.
They pulled through.
I pulled through.
I can't believe how
quiet it is out there.
Not everywhere.
Greg just called. He's working the night shift at the E.R.
People are still getting sick.
Car accidents are happening.
Babies are are being born.
Well, i'm glad he's not home.
I had to talk to you.
Nobody else is saying the
right thing about this.
My god, you're really upset.
What's that about?
Because there's nothing
funny about this.
Well...
Hang in there, red.
You too.
Bye-Bye.
Goodbye.
Put him on a standby of
indeterminate length, will you?
Clearers are pushing.
There is Lee Oswald.
He's been shot.
- Oh my god. Oh my god.
- What happened?
Lee Oswald has been shot.
They shot him.
The police were walking him
through the building
And some man ran up and shot him.
What?
What is going on?!
Oswald has been shot.
There is no question about it.
Don, please leave me alone.
Betts?
Pandemonium has broken loose  here in the
basement of dallas police headquarters.
What happened?
Nothing.
Go upstairs.
The family, incidentally, asked
that there be no flowers
But there nevertheless
have been flowers.
And one room or two rooms
in the white house
Have had to be set aside to--
To host.
I'm going out.
Where?
For a drive.
Let me drive.
I'll get the kids. We'll all go somewhere.
- That's a good idea.
- No.
I need to clear my head.
I'm so glad you could see me.
Where does your husband think you are?
I don't care.
He's been lying to me for years.
I couldn't be in that house.
Then I saw you yesterday.
I didn't know you were going to be there.
I hoped you would be there.
Derby day...
It seems like 100 years ago.
And then this morning, seeing that
man shot to death...
what is going on?
It will be okay.
We've lost a lot of presidents
and we're still standing.
I wish I could believe you.
I can't believe anything right now.
Have you thought that there are
other ways to live?
Listen. I'm not in love with
the tragedy of this thing.
It's not "Romeo and juliet."
I want it to happen.
I have three children.
I'll know more when the primaries
start to shake out in spring,
But i can leave the campaign right now.
I don't want you to do that.
You don't have to answer me now...
But i want to marry you.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
I told you.
But if you search your heart,
You'll know that I
can make you happy.
I should go.
I wish i could take you to the movies right now,
Some theater that's playing
your favorite movie.
"Singing in the rain."
Well, just think about that.
...it was made possible
by a special equipment,
it will move at one fourth speed,
so we would like to show you in slow
motion the shooting of Lee Harvey Oswald now.
They just stood there.
No security for the most wanted man
in America.
He didn't even have a trial.
Just throw him over the mob.
You can see the two detectives,
one in a light suit, one in a dark,
bringing Oswald out.
The camera changes its length,
for a close up of Oswald.
The shot has been fired, you cannot
hear it in this version of the tape.
Oswald falls and the man with the hat moves in
on him and he's grabbed by the man in light.
Do not go in to work tomorrow.
No, of course not.
It's a national day of mourning.
You're going to go on Tuesday.
That's another happy thought.
Those people don't care about you.
And honestly, what's the difference?
What are you saying?
You did everything they asked you to do,
but...
You don't owe them anything.
You should start gathering your clients.
They'll follow you
wherever you go.
The only other president buried there
is William Howard Taft.
Though of course, there are many
other heroes of perhaps lesser renown.
Francine has the kids.
I don't know where to begin.
What?
I want...
To scream at you.
For ruining all of this.
But...
Then you try to fix it and...
There's no point.
There's no point, Don.
You're very upset, I understand.
I know it's painful.
But it's going to pass.
I don't love you.
Betts, don't.
You're distraught.
It's true.
But I don't love you anymore.
I know that.
Stop it.
I kissed you yesterday.
And I didn't feel a thing.
You'll feel better tomorrow.
You'll see.
You can't even hear me
right now.
You're right.
Morning.
- Morning, daddy.
- Morning.
Where are you going?
I have to go to work, I'm sorry.
It's cold outside.
I'm fine.
Peggy.
What are you doing here?
I don't know. Aqua Net.
It doesn't shoot till after
Thanksgiving.
We'll be ok.
What do you have?
What are you doing here?
The bars are closed.
My roommate invited over half the
building so they can watch TV
and write condolence letters
to Jackie.
Then I went to my sister's and
my mother was crying...
and praying so hard.
There wasn't room for anyone else
to feel anything.
The funeral has already started.
I was gonna watch it in Cooper's office.
Is it ok?
Yeah.
Are you coming?
www.tvsubtitles.net