You know how hard I've prayed?
Why does he make me suffer?
God will give you a child.
Let me see her.
So you killed another one?
'cause you had nothing to do with this.
Maybe you oughta stay off her once in awhile.
Get out you witch!
I've got eighty-five and my boots are off.
You don't have a sheet.
I'll get one...
But that'll be another quarter
And this is all I have.
Go wash yourself.
You get me in trouble
And I'm gonna cut your dick off
And boil it in hog fat.
I'm gonna cut his dick off
What was that, sweetheart?
I'm cold.
You wanna hold him?
I'm gonna cut his dick
off and boil it in hog fat.
It's midnight.
What do you want?
I told you god would give you a child.
Whose is it?
Is your husband home?
God is giving you a child.
His name is dick...
After a wish his mother
should've lived to see.
Come on, drink this.
There's no point
In both of us not sleeping.
She wakes up at night when I drop off.
Are you so sure it's a girl?
Oh, believe me, she knows what she wants.
I packed her valise.
I could've done that.
Well, you'll get a chance...
The clasp is broken.
Carla says she saw sally
hitting it with a hammer.
She's taken to your tools
like a little lesbian.
Am I ever going to sleep again?
At least you don't look tired.
I just want everything to be perfect.
I want her to come into our home at its best.
Close your eyes.
You're on a warm, sandy beach.
Because I'm a whale.
Shh.
You're on a warm, sandy beach...
You can smell the faint
scent of coconut oil...
And as you slide your hands
Through that cool patch of sand
Underneath that shadow
of your deck chair--
You're good at this.
Lola?
Hello?
Yes, but on occasion,
You have to resign yourself
To sleeping where you are.
That's why they sell subway tokens, silly.
Lola.
You're looking lovely today.
Thank you.
Are you here to see me?
No, I'm just verifying some information.
Thank you, lola.
He just always stops by
Concerning the strangest things.
Yesterday, it was my engagement ring.
Enough, lola!
You know there's something
about the way he talks.
I could listen to him read the phone book.
Well, when he gets to "s",
I need harold sullivan at lever brothers.
Remarkable!
I picked it for its sensuality
But it also in some way
reminds me of our business.
Who is the man who imagined her ecstasy?
Who indeed?
We were just talking about you.
Burt's on his way.
Where's roger?
Probably taking another grecian treasure
Out of its crate!
I apologize for baltimore.
It has to be done.
Well, it's a sales call.
Isn't there more I can do here?
It's not a sales call.
You're the face of our business.
They need someone they can trust.
London fog...
How ludicrous.
Really, I have one.
So do I.
No, of course, uh, it's just the name.
There's no fog in london...
There is no london fog?
Are you sure about that?
Quite!
Never was.
It was the coal dust from the industrial era.
Charles dickens and what not.
Mr. Cooper?
Mr. Peterson is here to see you.
Good morning, burt.
Hey, don.
Bert.
Wayne.
We need you to have a seat, burt.
Okay.
You got a blindfold, too?
This isn't easy.
It really isn't.
Oh, god!
I really thought I'd made it.
I know it's unkind but it's generous
And it's fair.
So why the hell'd you wait so long?
It was brought to our attention
That your wife was undergoing radiation.
We thought it decent to wait.
That was decent.
Sorry I'm late!
Did I miss anything?
Oh, sad meeting...
Sorry about that.
Wasn't easy.
We'll see how you do without my rolodex.
We're gonna take that risk.
You make me sick!
You're the dying empire!
We're the future!
Burt, control yourself.
I'm the head of accounts dammit!
I'm sure we'll regret it.
I'm serious!
See ya on the bread lines, fellas.
Is that the last of it?
Because I don't like how much
I'm getting used to these.
I don't know anything you don't know.
Do you understand there's not point ever
In making over forty thousand dollars
When you'll be taxed 69%?
You're working for them!
And god forbid, you really make it...
Everything over seventy grand is 81%.
Even if you're married?
Fellow comrades in mediocrity,
I want you to listen very carefully.
You can all go straight to hell!
Heard he's going in house at nabisco.
You're sure it's not starting again?
Mr. Campbell's office.
The fire incident? What?
Mr. Campbell, mr. Price wants to see you.
I'm at lunch.
Bring your doggie bag.
Holy crap!
You couldn't have pulled
me aside to say that?
I'm sure it's nothing.
How the hell am I supposed to live like this?
Drop dead you limey vulture!
Son of a bitch!
I assume you can continue
to handle this beautifully
While I dispense psycho-therapy
To the girls in the pool?
You americans don't know
How to handle you're emotions...
It's unbecoming.
His wife is sick...
And if you would have talked to his girl,
She would have informed him.
So, he would've had a
longer walk to mr. Cooper's?
And if you would talk to me,
I would have been waiting with his coat
And his rolodex.
While we're on the topic of decorum,
I'd like to speak with you
About the way I'm being addressed.
Could you be more specific?
The switchboard, I'm not john.
I'm mr. Hooker.
That's the way they've been taught
To address the secretaries.
Yes, well, as I've
explained in great britain--
A truck is a laurie and
an elevator is a lift.
I've got it, mr. Hooker.
Despite your title...
You are not a secretary.
I'm mr. Price's right arm.
I'm not his typist.
Of course.
Good luck everybody!
Good luck!
I assume you will let him know
When mr. Peterson has left the building.
How are we today?
Very well--
thank you.
Burt peterson has left the agency.
Really?
Yes.
I can't speak for everyone here but, um...
I like you.
And, I like you.
But you don't know me.
But I will make that effort
If given the opportunity.
Pardon?
I apologize that I haven't
been more welcoming socially.
It seemed until your wife arrived...
I didn't want to make it
awkward with a threesome.
Although, now that I think of it,
Perhaps your being alone is all the reason
I should have offered my hospitality.
Do have a seat.
Why?
Is-is something wrong?
I don't know...
You just removed the head of my department,
Now you're offering me a chair.
How cruel of me.
I wanted to inform you
That you're now head of accounts.
Excuse me?
It seemed like the right thing to do
Despite your lack of hospitality.
The, uh, specifics are pending
As is the announcement.
Is this really happening?
I need to know it's certain.
Yes, but, um, shh.
Wonderful!
Thank you.
Splendid.
Well, it turns out things are splendid.
That's good.
Could you get my wife on the phone?
I have mrs. Campbell for you.
How are you, sweetheart?
What are you doing?
I know, I told you this morning.
I'm having luncheon
With the dosins committee from the met.
How are they?
Since when do you care?
Since I was made "head of accounts."
Yes! No!
Oh, my goodness!
It really is. Peter, that's wonderful!
I knew it would happen one day for real.
I love the sound of your voice, right now.
That's because I'm already drunk.
Good for you!
Just one
more minute--
My husband got some good news.
Make a reservation.
Surprise me. Okay.
I should call my mother.
Oh, peter...
Don't go to the well.
There's no water there.
I don't even know if I'm getting a raise.
I didn't
ask-- I forgot!
That's very nobel.
You see, one doesn't need
money to be fulfilled.
Don't let those ladies from the met
Hear you say that.
I should go.
Bye.
Sorry to interrupt your lunch.
I heard you wanted to see me,
So I grabbed a sandwich.
What can I do for you?
Mr. Peterson's left the agency.
If that's your news,
I think you've been scooped.
So you've heard.
Let's just say, he did not go gentle
Into that good night.
So you're probably wondering
Where that leaves you.
Should I be worried?
No, I should say not.
We're making you head of accounts.
Spectacular!
Thanks a lot!
We're charting the course
of transition, right now.
There are many details to come.
I wouldn't be much an account man
If I didn't ask what it pays.
I wouldn't be much of a financial officer
If I wasn't prepared to disappoint you.
It's 21, but we'll reevaluate this year.
Ken, this is not for broadcast.
They'll be a formal announcement.
Great!
Can you believe this?
What's the world coming to?
That is a big bottle.
That's not a bottle that's his date.
My-oh-my, what a
big bottle you have.
I'm sorry, honey but I'm taken.
I just pawned my typewriter
So we can be together all weekend.
The captain's about to announce our decent
Into friendship.
Quick refill?
I don't know,
Need something to run the plane.
And what about you, mr. Hoffstat?
Excuse me?
I took a look at your luggage.
You're william hoffstat.
Uh, bill.
Call me bill and, uh, this is my associate,
Uh, mr. Fleishman.
S-sam.
Shelly.
Are you headed to baltimore or d.C.?
Baltimore.
Well, how 'bout that.
We're heading to hausner's for dinner.
We should've been in line two hours ago
If we wanted to eat by eight.
Lorelei has made some
inroads with the maitre d'.
Well, we have to check-in
And we have an early meeting.
Where you stayin'?
The belvedere.
Well, this is too
much-- us, too!
7:30...
It'll be a hoot and a half.
Now you have to take
someone else's luggage...
Bill hoffman's.
Hoffstat-- my
brother-in-law.
He borrowed a suitcase to go to puerto rico
But he never tires of putting his name
On other people's things.
I've flown a few times...
But I've never actually seen a stewardess
That game.
Really?
This is your captain speaking.
Hello, kenny.
Any plans tonight?
All I know is to avoid grand central.
I heard burt peterson's still at the bar.
Now-now.
It had to happen, I guess.
He didn't put up much of a fight.
Not counting today I mean.
It's a tough job.
No doubt about that.
I just wanna let you know,
I've always been a big fan of your work
And I've been very vocal about it.
I appreciate that.
Maybe now things will finally settle down.
That's true.
Listen, I just wanna say
that through all of this
I know that you were there reminding me
That I can do this job.
Well, you're welcome.
I guess it's because I think you can.
Have a good night. You, too!
And my friend and I were listening
To some radio program
And we had this huge bag of fritos.
Oh, we're not allowed in uniform.
So at some point, my friend stops eating
But I can't.
And I ate all of them and I got so...
It was quite unladylike.
And I still can't eat them to today.
Too much of a good
thing-- it happens.
I think accounting sounds fascinating.
Going through other peoples bank accounts...
It sounds sexy.
Jesus, lorelei.
How deep did you have to
dig to come up with that?
Why would you insult a man's profession?
No, it's okay, uh, I
don't usually tell people
I'm an accountant.
Listen, billy, sam,
I didn't mean to insult your profession.
Don't sweat it.
'course you do know there are different kinds
Of accountants.
Are there?
Tell them what we do.
I don't know, bill.
I'm gonna have to swear you all to secrecy.
You can't guarantee that.
You're right.
Well someone just brought everything
To a screeching halt.
We'll be good.
You ever heard of james hoffa?
You know, I don't just throw
away newspapers everyday.
I also read them.
There is a lot of money missing
And they don't really keep receipts.
So you're a couple of g-men.
No, we're accountants.
Isn't the service exquisite?
I'm based in new york.
I'd always rather be there,
But it's my job to be outta town.
I don't know, I... are you a pilot?
Keep going a lot of places andnding up
Somewhere I've already been.
How 'bout a night cap?
I don't know.
You're face is red.
Order for us!
Felt self-conscious there for a moment.
We're the only one's without a uniform.
Good night, bill.
Sam.
Shelly, it's been a swell evening.
Well, this is me.
Let me see if it's different than my floor.
What are we doin'?
I don't know.
I'm engaged.
On the other hand, you
might be my last chance.
I've been married a long time.
You get plenty of chances.
It's my birthday.
Really?
Is it?
Really is.
Let me see your drivers license.
That's not gonna help.
Oh, happy birthday.
Hello?
My air conditioner does not work.
It is stagnant in here.
Take your hand out.
I can't breathe!
Stand up.
Lorelei thinks you look like tye power.
Remember him?
Go on.
And why you're distracted
I'm gonna take off my shoes.
Is that okay?
Your turn.
Not yet.
Do you like?
Everyone's always asking
me if I was a model...
But I wasn't.
The one I have at home is different.
Hope I didn't break it.
Nope--
it's fine.
Just a minute.
Hmm, thank you.
Airplane.
Oh, god!
Oh!
Oh, jesus!
Fire alarm! What is that?
Come on, let's go!
Come on, forget your shoes.
Let's go!
Come on!
Do you have another cigarette?
Everything's okay, folks.
Morning. Morning.
You ever get nervous
wearing that on the subway?
I don't ride the subway.
I do worry about being followed though.
I think lola takes a horse and buggy.
She's never on time.
I'm not at work yet.
I don't wanna sit in my office
And listen to someone talk
about their water retention.
Peggy, brides are very self-conscious.
If she's so worried about getting married,
Then why is she shamelessly
flirting with money penny
Don't call him that. All the time?
He hates that.
Are you defending him?
He's repellent.
Reminds me of a door man.
And the typing she does for him...
Oh, god, I'm so glad
I'm gonna be out of here soon.
That's very comforting, joan.
There's nothing I can do.
Congratulations.
Oh, thank you.
Mr. Price just called.
There's a meeting for the heads of accounts
Immediately.
Excuse me?
Mr. Price called a big meeting for you
And mr. Cosgrove.
What are you talking about?
Whatever the circumstance
is it's nice to see you.
I'm just here to show you the continuity
Of our service.
That with or without burt peterson,
You're on our mind.
I apologize.
Morris, you remember salvatore romano.
I don't know how but I left my plane ticket
At the hotel.
He's the guy with the marker
Who always does what I say.
Words, pictures.
Sal this is howard.
Pleasure.
I don't remember...
Do you have a family?
Uh, not yet.
I have a wife.
Well, howard is my son.
He's going to be a part of this from now on.
Starting with taking you
two gentlemen on a tour.
That's it?
You're not gonna say anything?
My father's extremely concerned
About the business, right now.
What was it about our work?
I mean, we don't want to
take credit for everything
But, uh, two of every three
raincoats sold last year
Had london fog stitched on the inside pocket.
Dad was worried that everyone
who's ever going to buy
A raincoat already has one.
Because a business has to
get bigger every year...
That's capitalism.
Well, our worst fears lye in anticipation.
That's not me--
that's balzac.
Balzac, huh?
You are not burt peterson.
I've been investigating
umbrellas, bags, hats--
There are companies that
all they do is make hats.
London fog is a
40-year-old brand
That sounds like it's existed forever
And you've established with our help
That it means one
thing-- raincoats.
New products aside...
There will be fat years
And there will be lean years...
But it is going to rain.
That's true.
Let's see if we can find you some ear plugs.
Bacardi, bel jolie, birds eye, cadbury,
Campbell soup international,
Cartwright double-sided aluminum,
Chevron oil, dunkin' donuts,
General foods europe, kodak, lever brothers,
Martinsons, popsicle, relaxacizor,
Rio de janerio--
which is dormant.
United fruits, warner brothers.
And now for mr. Campbell.
Admiral television, alpine real estate,
Bethlehem steel, con-ed, gillette, gordon's,
Liberty capital savings,
lucky strike, maytag,
North american aviation,
P&G, pampers, playtex, samsonite,
Secor laxatives, snyder's ketchup, utz.
Why does he have utz?
Some of this was done based on accounts
And some of this was done
based on relationship's
And you figure out what happened with utz.
So you decided all of this?
Forty-cents of every dollar at this agency
Is spent in the television
department but no-- we did.
What are these others for?
Olson.
She's all over the place.
You know that's not true.
You're each taking half the company.
'course it's possible someone
could distinguish themselves.
Could be easier that way.
Can you believe this?
If you're upset, you seem to be hiding it.
I'm excited.
I mean, I feel badly about burt peterson.
Three kids, wife
with cancer--
But you greased up the
shoot and shoved him down it.
What could possibly be the matter?
Why did you even accept this?
You have no interest in this.
Why wouldn't I want this?
Because you're no good.
They want us to hate each other.
I refuse to participate in that.
Very nice.
Very-very nice.
Look at you, never break a sweat.
You're right-- I
should just lay down
And we should run together holding hands.
What time is it?
1:15.
We should be back in the office by three.
We're going back to the office?
I'm gonna ask you something and I want you
To be completely honest with me.
London fog.
It's a subway car...
And there's a commuter looking up.
There's a girl with her back to us.
She's wearing one of those short, tan one's
But it's open.
Her legs are bare.
We know what he's seeing...
Limit your exposure.
That's it?
Good?
Mr. Hooker, may I speak with you?
I thought it was a good
idea that ppl had an office
For when visitors come.
'course it would make since for someone
To be occupying it in the meantime.
I wrestled up an office for you.
I hope you find it
appropriate to your status.
My position?
Steer mr. Price-- not
exactly in the thick of things
But you will have someone
to attend to your typing
To avoid you siphoning off the man hours.
My own girl of my choosing?
I will have a lineup.
Did he take the ant farm?
No, it's actually mr. Cooper's.
Oh. It just lives there.
Hello, sweetheart.
Now, don't be cross.
I'll only be a minute.
You have a fever?
No.
"peter campbell, the buck stops here."
Huh, the buck stops here...
Unless it stops over there.
What's the matter?
There's two heads of accounts.
Kenny cosgrove and I are sharing it.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I was sitting there and they just...
Read off a list of names.
A list of companies...
That's my life.
I know you won't like hearing this
But you're a lot like my father.
You're an ambitious man and an ambitious man
Is never happy with what he has.
Why does it always have to be like this?
Why can't I get anything good all at once?
This is an amazing opportunity!
They believe in you.
Don't turn it sour.
It's a test.
Why not just cut it short
and tell them I want it.
You can do whatever you want
But they do not want to hear your outrage.
They want you to beat ken.
I know what they want, trudy.
And honestly, I don't know...
I can't live with this.
But you'll try.
It's great!
It's a great ad!
So, how was everything in baltimore?
Out of town, don draper...
First class.
Go on.
Two old married men.
Oh, there was a fire in the hotel
Buno casualties.
That's too bad.
For casting this lucky fellow in the subway.
What's he look like?
I don't know, a little excited...
A little shocked.
No, what's he look like?
Oh, handsome.
The girl's gone.
I have stolichnaya
and cuban cigars--
Sent them from greece.
Should've tried a pound of opium.
Help yourself.
So, cosgrove versus campbell.
Is cooper playing god or darwin?
I know it sounds japanese
but it's not cooper.
What'd lane read about it
in some management book?
I think it came from the home office.
When he told me about it,
I thought he was joking.
I told him it was a stupid idea
But they don't always get our inflection.
Can I speak with you for a moment?
Come in.
Oh...
What?
I, um...
I just wanted to let you both know
How honored I am with this promotion.
Help yourself.
Not the stoli.
Hello.
Oh, mr. Campbell, I was going to tell don
But I can tell you myself.
I have an old pal at the mayors office
That wants to do a small campaign for...
I don't know, something about penn station.
It'd be my pleasure, bert.
Is there any brandy?
Any glass will do.
I told him that despite
life under british rule,
We still had a real yankee.
I don't care what they say...
London fog is a great name.
I like the ants.
There's no shortage of distractions here.
Now if we can find a proper pub,
We'll have everything.
Why do you have this office?
I thought it was necessary
that we have a place
For when superior's visit.
Of course, it would make sense
For someone to occupy it in the meantime.
That's a hair-brained idea.
We just fired one-third of their workforce.
It's unseemly to go through
their pockets, as well.
A visitors office is good
but you sit out front.
Of course, it was presumptuous.
This place is a ginocracy.
Hadn't noticed.
My only point is if you decide
to take the train tomorrow
And you run into carlton,
I told him you were busy.
Our stories are straight.
Sally has something to tell you.
Sally!
I got it out of her.
Out!
Go ahead.
I'm sorry I broke your suitcase.
Find out how much it is to repair
And it'll come out of your allowance.
I don't have an allowance.
Then don't break things.
I just thought-- I just
didn't want you to go.
Come here.
I will always come home.
You'll always be my girl.
Your eyes look tired.
I don't sleep well when I'm not here.
You squint too much.
You need reading glasses.
Daddy-daddy!
Are these for me?
Yes.
Give me that--
it's a stick-pin.
There ya go.
Was I really in there?
Nine months.
Tell me about the day I was born.
Well, it was, uh, the middle of the night...
And it was raining very hard...
And I had just got home from work.
He did not feel like
getting back in the car...
But he did.
I took my suitcase
And my little stuffed eeyore
That I knew I was going to give you.
muter for bierdopje.eu
www.tvsubtitles.net