Betty: DON?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- NOW IT MAY TAKE A MOMENT TO GET USED TO.
I TOLD YOU-
MEN DON'T LIKE CHANGE.
WELL, IT'S HARD FOR ME TO JUDGE
WHEN I CAN'T SEE A PRICE TAG.
Woman: OH.
A MODERN
CHINOISERIE BREAKFRONT,
A DUNBAR
JAPANESE-INFLUENCED SOFA,
SILK DUPIONI DRAPES,
MURANO VASES
AND A CLASSIC
DREXEL END TABLE.
- AND WHAT GOES HERE?
- WHERE?
RIGHT WHERE
WE'RE STANDING.
WELL, THAT'S YOUR HEARTH,
DARLING.
THAT'S THE SOUL
OF YOUR HOME.
PEOPLE GATHER AROUND A FIRE
EVEN IF THERE ISN'T ONE.
PEOPLE GATHER
AROUND A FIRE EVEN
- SO, DON?
- I THINK IT'S FINE, BETTS.
ALL YOU DO ALL DAY AT
WORK IS EVALUATE OBJECTS.
I WOULD LIKE
THE BENEFIT OF YOUR EYE.
MOVE THE END TABLE AND THE LAMP
TO THE OTHER END OF THE COUCH.
I THINK
HE'S RIGHT.
- HOT AS HELL ALREADY.
- YES, IT IS.
I WATCHED THE SUNRISE TODAY
- I COULDN'T SLEEP.
- HOW WAS IT?
- AVERAGE.
OGILVY WROTE
A BOOK.
I GOT
THE GALLEYS.
THEY WANT A QUOTE
OR SOMETHING.
ADVERTISING'S ALREADY
UP THERE WITH LAWYERS
AS THE MOST REVILED.
THIS IS NOT GOING TO HELP.
IT'LL HELP HIM.
IT'S CALLED "CONFESSIONS OF AN AD MAN."
- I LIKE THE TITLE.
- PLEASE.
IT'S A BOOK EVERYBODY WRITES,
ONLY HE GOT IT PUBLISHED.
IT SHOULD BE CALLED
"1,000 REASONS I'M SO GREAT."
- IS HE PUBLISHING IT HIMSELF?
- NO, ATHENEUM.
I'LL SEND IT OVER.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO BUY IT.
Allison: I DON'T KNOW
WHERE TO PUT IT
AND YOU KNOW I WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO TELL YOU.
- THERE YOU ARE.
- WHEN DO YOU WANT US TO MOVE THE MEETING TO?
- MR. DRAPER?
- MOVE IT?
I'M 15 MINUTES LATE.
I TOLD YOU I DON'T WANT THEM HOVERING.
IF I'M LATE, SEND HEM AWAY
AND CALL THEM WHEN I GET HERE.
MR. DRAPER, CONRAD
HILTON IS IN YOUR OFFICE.
- RIGHT NOW?
- HE JUST WALKED RIGHT IN.
- WE WERE WAITING AND HE BLEW RIGHT PAST US.
- HOLD ON.
COME BACK
IN 20 MINUTES.
- DID YOU OFFER HIM COFFEE?
- Allison: I DID. HE'S ALL SET.
- YOU LOOK GREAT.
- 20 MINUTES.
- YOU CAN TAKE AN HOUR IF YOU NEED IT.
- HE WANTS TO LOOK BUSY.
MOVE IT.
ALLISON,
HOLD ALL MY CALLS.
CONNIE.
WHAT A GREAT WAY
TO START THE DAY.
9:30?
IT'S PRACTICALLY LUNCH.
WELL, CAN I GET
YOU SOMETHING?
I'VE GOT
A PERSONAL MATTER
THAT'S NOT FIT
FOR THE PHONE.
- WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU? - I DON'T
KNOW WHAT I'M MORE DISTURBED BY-
THE FACT THAT
YOU DON'T HAVE A BIBLE
OR THAT THERE'S NOT
A SINGLE FAMILY PHOTO.
- I'M EASILY DISTRACTED.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE THOSE THINGS.
THEY'LL MAKE YOU FEEL
BETTER ABOUT WHAT YOU DO.
START SHOWING UP
ON TIME.
MAYBE I'M LATE BECAUSE
I WAS SPENDING TIME
WITH MY FAMILY
READING THE BIBLE.
ARE YOU NERVOUS, DON? I'M
FINDING YOU HARD TO TALK TO.
WELL, YOU CAUGHT ME
BY SURPRISE, CONNIE.
I THINK
YOU KNOW THAT.
NOW YOU'RE
A MARRIED MAN,
SO YOU'LL HAVE TO USE
YOUR IMAGINATION, BUT...
I HAVE THIS...
INVOLVEMENT.
I CAN'T SAY
IT'S PERFECT
AND MY NEEDS ARE
BEING MET,
BUT I HAVE
SIGNIFICANT NEEDS, DON.
- DO YOU CATCH MY DRIFT?
- YES.
SO WHAT DO I DO WHEN
MY EYE STARTS TO WANDER?
DON'T YOU HAVE
A COTERIE
OF TRUSTED
ADVISORS, FRIENDS,
KINGS THAT MIGHT
COUNSEL YOU BETTER?
I WANT YOU TO HANDLE
THE WALDORF ASTORIA,
THE NEW YORK HILTON
AND THE STATLER HILTON.
IT'S JUST NEW YORK,
BUT MY EYE HAS DEFINITELY
STARTED TO WANDER.
I THINK THAT'S
A GOOD START.
RETAINER, ET CETERA-
THAT'S FOR LAWYERS.
EVERYTHING ELSE
WILL BE LIKE THIS.
HAVING ME IN YOUR LIFE
IS GONNA CHANGE THINGS.
- I LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
- THEY ALWAYS SAY THAT.
- A HAPPY BUNCH.
- IF YOU SAY SO.
YOUNG PEOPLE GIVE US ENERGY.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
IT'S NOT MUCH
TO START WITH,
BUT I LOOK FORWARD TO
SHARING MY DREAMS WITH YOU.
SPEAK TO YOU SOON.
I CANNOT BELIEVE YOU JUST HAD
A BABY AND YOU REDID YOUR HOUSE.
ARE YOU SUICIDAL?
- THEY WERE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE SIMULTANEOUS,
AND THE BABY WASN'T THE ONE
THAT COULDN'T KEEP A SCHEDULE.
I ASSUME THIS MEETING
MEANS YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN REPLACING FRANCINE
AS SECRETARY?
- I AM.
- GOOD,
BECAUSE WE WAITED FOR YOU FOR
OUR MOST PRESSING BUSINESS.
THE PROPOSED
3- MILLION-GALLON WATER TANK
WILL NOT ONLY DRAIN THE
PLEASANTVILLE ROAD RESERVOIR,
BUT ALSO BLEMISH THE NATURAL AND
FINANCIAL HEALTH OF OUR COMMUNITY.
WELL SAID.
THE JUNIOR LEAGUE NEEDS
TO TAKE OVER THIS EFFORT
AND EXPLAIN THE ISSUES.
CONSERVATION-
THE "SILENT SPRING,"
THE MAJESTIC BEAUTY
OF THE HUDSON RIVER VALLEY.
WORTHLESS REAL ESTATE
SECOND:
ON BOTH SIDES
OF THE RIVER
BECAUSE SOME INDUSTRIAL PARK
ON ROUTE 9 NEEDS OUR WATER.
WE NEED TO GO OVER THE VILLAGE
BOARD'S HEAD, APPEAL TO THE GOVERNOR.
THE ROCKEFELLERS OWN
HALF THE LAND HERE.
REAL ESTATE-
THAT'S SCARY.
I MAY KNOW SOMEONE
IN THE GOVERNOR'S OFFICE.
WHO?
UMM, HIS NAME IS HENRY.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
HENRY FRANCIS.
HE'S IN THE PAPER
SOMETIMES,
ALWAYS RIGHT
BEHIND ROCKY.
WHAT DOES HE DO?
I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
HOW DO
YOU KNOW HIM?
I MET HIM AT A PARTY FOR DON'S WORK.
OH, HERE HE IS. OH MY.
IT JUST SAYS "ADVISOR."
OH. YES, I KNOW
WHO HE IS.
HE USED TO BE
THE REPUBLICAN PARTY CHAIR
FOR WESTCHESTER COUNTY.
I KNOW HIM.
WELL, CALL HIM THEN.
I THINK WE HAVE
A BETTER CHANCE
IF BETTY CALLS.
IT'S NOT ADORABLE TO PRETEND
LIKE YOU'RE NOT ADORABLE.
HMM.
CALL HIM.
Woman:
HE'S A BIG DEAL.
MIAMI IS WHERE WE SHOULD
START, LET IT GROW FROM THERE.
HO-HO WANTS IT
EVERYWHERE.
HE JUST BOUGHT LAND IN
SEATTLE. IT'S AN INDOOR CITY.
- AS LONG AS
HE KEEPS WRITING CHECKS.
LOOK, DO YOU WANT TO KILL
THIS THING IN ONE BLOW
OR DO YOU WANT TO SHEAR
THE SHEEP EVERY YEAR?
WHATEVER YOU WANT, DON.
YOU MADE IT CLEAR YOU
DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT,
BUT AT LEAST TELL US
HOW YOU KNOW HIM.
WE RAN INTO EACH OTHER
AT A PARTY.
THAT'LL BE ALL.
I KNOW ROGER WILL BE
THE FACE OF THIS THING,
BUT I WOULDN'T MIND
DOING THE LEGWORK.
PETE, I THINK YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BRING IN THE ACCOUNT
AND I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE TO BE ON IT.
WHAT HAPPENED WITH
NORTH AMERICAN AVIATION?
IT'S GOING WELL,
MY FRIEND RUSS WHO DEALS
WITH McNAMARA'S OFFICE
SAID THE ORDERS ARE
THROUGH THE ROOF
FOR HELICOPTERS, CARBINES AND
ESPECIALLY JETS FOR VIETNAM.
I THINK I'VE CONVINCED
NORTH AMERICAN
THEY'RE GOING
TO NEED TO SPEND MORE
IF THEY WANT TO GET OUT OF
NASA AND INTO THE PENTAGON.
WHEN THEY DO,
WE CAN TALK
ABOUT HILTON.
UNDERSTOOD.
Betty: OH. NO. YES, OF COURSE.
HE'S BUSY.
IT'S WILSON-4-8-0-3-8.
BETTY DRAPER.
HE CAN CALL ME
ANYTIME.
IT'S A CIVIC MATTER
REGARDING OSSINING.
THANK YOU.
LUNCH!
WASH YOUR HANDS,
BOBBY.
DRAPER RESIDENCE.
MRS. DRAPER,
IT'S HENRY FRANCIS.
YES, OF COURSE.
I APPRECIATE YOU GETTING
BACK TO ME SO QUICKLY.
STOP IT.
COULD YOU HOLD
JUST A MOMENT?
- I'M GOING TO GET ON THE EXTENSION.
- Of course.
I'M GOING IN THE STUDY.
HANG UP THE PHONE.
DAMN IT!
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- YOU SAID TO HANG UP THE PHONE.
AFTER I PICK UP
THE PHONE.
FREEZE.
- DRAPER RESIDENCE.
- IT'S HENRY AGAIN.
- WE WERE DISCONNECTED.
- I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT-
MY SON.
I KNOW HOW THAT GOES.
HOW ARE YOU?
YOU MUST HAVE HAD
YOUR BABY BY NOW.
YES, I DID.
YOU REMEMBERED.
- What did you have?
- A LITTLE BOY.
CAN YOU GET HIM
REGISTERED BY NOVEMBER?
I JUST REALIZED EVERYONE WHO
CALLS YOU MUST WANT SOMETHING.
ACTUALLY, I'VE BEEN DOING
MOST OF THE CALLING LATELY.
WHAT CAN
I DO FOR YOU?
WELL, WE WERE
HOPING YOU COULD STOP
THE DESTRUCTION OF THE
PLEASANTVILLE ROAD RESERVOIR.
- WHO'S "WE"?
- I'm representing the Junior League
OF TARRYTOWN.
THEY WANT TO BUILD
A 3-MILLION-GALLON WATER TANK
- AND IT'S A VERY SCENIC AREA.
- I know the area.
WELL, IT'S PRACTICALLY
THE GOVERNOR'S BACKYARD.
THAT'S TRUE, BUT I
GREW UP THERE AS WELL.
- Really? Where?
- MOUNT SALEM.
I'M HEADING UPSTATE
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
MAYBE I COULD STOP BY
AND TAKE A LOOK.
WELL, TOMORROW IS
SATURDAY.
OF COURSE.
WORK EVERY DAY.
I FORGET
OTHER PEOPLE DON'T.
NO.
THIS IS
VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
I THINK I COULD
FIND THE TIME.
IS SWENSON'S BAKERY
STILL THERE?
IT IS AND IT HAS
AN AIR CONDITIONER.
I'LL BUY YOU
A CUP OF COFFEE
AND THEN WE CAN TAKE
A HIKE TO THE RESERVOIR.
- Is 3:00 too late for you?
- NO, IT'S PERFECT.
- I'LL MAKE IT WORK.
- Well, I'll see you then, Mrs. Draper.
I CAN SAVE YOU
THE TROUBLE-
IT'S FROM HIM
AND IT'S EXPENSIVE.
I'M GOING
TO FIRE HER.
WHAT DID
YOU PROMISE HIM?
- WHO?
- YOU'RE THICK, DO YOU KNOW THAT?
THAT PRESENT-
IT'S FROM DUCK.
HERMES. NICE.
I HOPE YOURS IS
A DIFFERENT COLOR.
"ELEGANCE
AND SUCCESS. DUCK."
I WONDER WHO WROTE
THAT FOR HIM.
- I DON'T TRUST HIM.
- WHY?
BECAUSE HE WANTS US?
WE'RE VERY IMPORTANT HERE.
WHO IS?
DID HE PUT YOU
ON HILTON?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
STOP BARGING IN HERE AND
INFECTING ME WITH YOUR ANXIETY.
THIS IS
REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
HE SENT ME
A BOX OF CUBAN CIGARS...
ALTHOUGH I'M STARTING TO THINK
THEY'RE NOT THAT HARD TO COME BY.
HILTON HOTELS?
DID WE GET THAT?
DO YOU LIVE
IN A CAVE?
CONRAD HILTON CAME
TO SEE DON THIS MORNING.
- HE WAS RIGHT THERE.
- REALLY?
- WHAT WAS HE LIKE?
- I ONLY GOT A QUICK LOOK AT HIM.
HE WAS SKINNY,
LIKE A COWBOY.
MY MOTHER GAVE ME
HIS BOOK.
HE'S CATHOLIC.
IT'S GOING TO BE
A HUGE ACCOUNT.
NOT AS BIG
AS LUCKY STRIKE,
BUT IT WOULD BE NICE TO BE
PLANNING A LITTLE OFFENSE FOR ONCE
INSTEAD OF HIDING
FROM THE F.T.C.
- HE HAS A BOOK?
- I REALLY LIKE THIS.
LOOK, I'M KEEPING THIS.
DUCK SAID WE'RE
NOT TIED TOGETHER.
I'LL KEEP MY MOUTH SHUT
AND YOU DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
DO YOU KNOW WHY DUCK
DOESN'T WORK HERE ANYMORE?
BECAUSE DON SQUEEZED HIM OUT
WHEN THE BRITISH TOOK OVER.
SO WHAT?
DON DIDN'T LIKE HIM.
IT'S THE WORLD AGAINST DON
AND NOW IT'S SOMEONE ELSE.
TRUE, BUT DUCK WOULD LOVE
TO HIT DON WHERE IT HURTS.
WELL, I'M NOT
GOING ANYWHERE
AND I'M NOT
GOING TO TELL DON.
I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT DUCK.
SEND IT BACK.
WHEN WERE YOU GOING
TO TELL US ABOUT THIS?
I THOUGHT I'D LET IT BE
AN INCOMING PHONE CALL
AND THEN WAIT AND SEE
WHO TOOK CREDIT FOR IT.
THIS IS
VERY EXCITING.
DESPITE ITS
MODEST BILLINGS,
LONDON IS THRILLED
WITH HILTON'S POTENTIAL
FOR INTERNATIONAL GROWTH.
- FINALLY.
- HUZZAH.
IF YOU DON'T MIND MY ASKING,
HOW DID YOU MAKE THIS HAPPEN?
WE TRAVEL
IN THE SAME CIRCLES.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
IF WE SHOULD CELEBRATE YET.
HIS LAWYERS CALLED AND THERE'S
A LITTLE MATTER OF THE CONTRACT.
WELL, DON'T BE AFRAID
TO PUSH BACK.
I AGREED
TO THE NEW YORK HOTELS,
BUT EVERYTHING ELSE SHOULD
BE UNDER OUR TERMS.
I DON'T THINK
YOU UNDERSTAND.
THIS IS REGARDING
YOUR CONTRACT.
OR LACK THEREOF.
Lane: IT MAY SEEM LIKE
A FORMALITY TO YOU,
BUT TO MR. HILTON
IT'S A NECESSITY THAT
ALL THE PRINCIPALS
IN THE FIRM BE SECURED.
AND HONESTLY,
I CAN'T BLAME HIM.
I'LL GIVE HIM
MY WORD.
AND HE'LL TAKE IT,
BUT HIS LAWYERS WON'T.
OBVIOUSLY,
YOU'LL WANT
YOUR ATTORNEY
TO LOOK IT OVER.
THAT'S BEN MICHELSON, HMM?
IT'S FAIRLY STANDARD-
THREE YEARS, A NON-COMPETE
CLAUSE, A HEALTHY RAISE.
THAT'S VERY GENEROUS.
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
I'M CONFUSED.
IF SOMEONE HANDED ME THAT
CONTRACT, I'D BE FILLED WITH GLEE.
A THREE-YEAR GUARANTEE,
A $5,000 SIGNING BONUS-
I- I'VE NEVER SEEN
THAT BEFORE.
WELL, WE WANT
TO TAKE CARE OF HIM.
LOOK, I'VE GOTTEN TO KNOW
CONRAD HILTON A LITTLE BIT
AND I THINK HE'LL ENJOY
SOMETHING HE CAN'T HAVE,
AND YOU SHOULD TELL HIM
THAT IT MATTERS TO ME.
IT MATTERS TO HIM.
STILL, I DON'T THINK ANYONE
TOLD HIM THAT IT MATTERS TO ME.
WELL, THIS IS
THE WAY IT HAS TO BE
AND NOT JUST FOR CONRAD
HILTON, BUT FOR STERLING COOPER.
I'D LIKE YOU TO TAKE THOSE
PAPERS HOME FOR THE WEEKEND
AND THINK ABOUT THAT.
I'D BE HAPPY TO.
AH.
I MET HIM ONCE. HE'S A BIT
OF AN ECCENTRIC, ISN'T HE?
YES.
OH.
OH, JESUS.
- MRS. DRAPER.
- MR. FRANCIS.
I'M ALONE.
I HOPE THAT'S OKAY.
OH WELL. ACTUALLY, MY FRIEND
COULDN'T GET AWAY EITHER.
I APPRECIATE
YOUR COMING UP.
PLEASE. I LOVE
COMING BACK HERE.
SO MUCH CHANGES,
SO MUCH DOESN'T.
LIKE WHAT?
I'M INTERESTED.
- Woman: CAN I HELP YOU?
- JUST AN ICE TEA, PLEASE.
THAT'S FINE FOR NOW.
- WHAT WAS I SAYING?
- YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT COMING BACK HERE.
OSSINING HAS ALWAYS BEEN
A REAL MIX OF PEOPLE.
WELL, AFTER LIVING IN MANHATTAN,
IT WASN'T MY FIRST CHOICE,
BUT IT'S GROWN ON ME.
I LIVED IN MANHATTAN
WHEN I WAS MARRIED.
IT'S OKAY FOR WORK,
BUT I CAN'T SLEEP WITH ALL
THOSE PEOPLE ON TOP OF ME.
LIKE IN A SKYSCRAPER.
MAY I HAVE
A STRAW?
SO YOU HAVE YOUR FOLDER.
I THOUGHT I'D JUST
GIVE YOU THE LITERATURE
AND A COPY OF THE PETITION.
I DON'T KNOW THAT
I'M A GREAT SPOKESMAN.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME HOW
BEAUTIFUL THE RESERVOIR IS.
I USED TO DO
JACKKNIVES INTO IT.
WE DRINK THAT WATER.
I'VE LOOKED
INTO THIS FOR YOU
AND I'M AFRAID
ITS UNDERWAY.
OH NO.
WE'RE TOO LATE.
MAYBE IF YOU KNEW
SOMEBODY WITH SOME CLOUT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT YOU DO.
I'M A CLASSIC STRATEGIST,
FUNDRAISER,
MAYBE CAMPAIGN MANAGER.
I'M WAITING ON THAT.
AND HOW DO YOU
BECOME THAT?
GIVE A LOT
OF MONEY?
NO.
NO, I'M A LAWYER,
BUT I DON'T USE IT MUCH.
WE ALL HAVE SKILLS
WE DON'T USE.
I WAS
AN ANTHROPOLOGY MAJOR.
IMAGINE THAT.
WHERE?
BRYN MAWR.
WELL, YOU MAY BE SAVING
YOUR COMMUNITY RIGHT NOW.
I'M HUNGRY.
DO YOU MIND?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- FINE.
YOU CAN READ FROM YOUR
FOLDER AND WATCH ME EAT.
I'LL HAVE
APPLE PIE AND-
ICE CREAM
OR CHEDDAR CHEESE?
ONE OF EACH.
CAN WE JUST GET
ONE THING OUT OF THE WAY?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I CAN
DO ABOUT THE WATER TANK.
OH.
DON'T GIVE UP
SO EASILY.
Suzanne: WHAT THIS REALLY
IS IS A CAMERA OBSCURA.
WE CALL IT
A SUN SCOPE
AND IT ALLOWS US
TO LOOK AT THE ECLIPSE
WITHOUT INJURY
TO OUR EYES.
- I DIDN'T BRING A SCISSOR.
- I HAVE SCISSORS.
AND SQUARES OF CARDBOARD THAT
ALREADY HAVE PINHOLES IN THEM.
AND IF YOU REALLY
NEED SOME HELP,
ASK YOUR DADS.
THE ECLIPSE IS
22 MINUTES AWAY.
- GENTLEMEN,
START YOUR ENGINES.
I COULD HAVE
GONE GOLFING.
I HAD NO IDEA THIS IS
WHAT WE'D BE IN FOR.
GO AHEAD.
I'LL TAKE ERNIE HOME.
YOU KNOW, FRANCINE TAUGHT SCHOOL
WHEN WE WERE FIRST MARRIED.
I USED TO LOVE SEEING HER STANDING
IN THE MIDDLE OF THOSE LITTLE KIDS
LIKE A TELEPHONE POLE.
HEY.
THERE YOU GO.
SALLY HAS A CRUSH ON HER.
WHY CAN'T YOU STARE
INTO THE ECLIPSE?
WHAT'S IT GOING
TO DO, REALLY?
I STARE
AT THE SUN EVERY DAY.
YOU STARE
AT THE SUN EVERY DAY?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
LOOK AT IT.
YOU KNOW, I SEE HER SOMETIMES WHEN
I'M OUT RUNNING IN THE MORNING.
YOU RUN?
YEAH, OVER BY
THE HIGH SCHOOL TRACK.
- DO YOU TALK? - NO. NO,
THERE'S AN ETIQUETTE TO IT-
YOU KEEP TO YOURSELF.
AND HONESTLY, THAT'S ONE OF
THE THINGS I LOVE ABOUT MY RUN-
IS BEING ALONE.
THAT'S HARD
TO COME BY, YOU KNOW?
LISTEN.
I HATE TO DISAPPOINT YOU,
BUT I HAVE TO BE ON MY WAY.
OH, THAT'S TOO BAD.
I HAVE TO BE
IN ALBANY FOR DINNER.
HIS MASTER'S VOICE-
THE GOVERNOR.
IT'S AN OLD AD.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- IT'S THE ECLIPSE.
HE MADE
A CONTRAPTION.
DON'T LOOK AT IT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I THINK SO.
I FEEL
A LITTLE DIZZY.
TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
IS THAT BETTER?
SO YOU NEVER HAD TIME TO
GO TO THE RESERVOIR ANYWAY.
I ONLY HAD AN HOUR,
BUT I FIGURED-
THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED-
- A FAINTING COUCH.
- WHAT'S THAT?
VICTORIAN LADIES WOULD
GET OVERWHELMED
FROM CORSETS
AND THINGS.
THEY'D NEED A PLACE
TO LIE DOWN.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
I USED TO MOVE
FURNITURE.
MAY I WALK YOU
TO YOUR CAR?
I DON'T KNOW. THIS
IS STILL A SMALL TOWN.
NO, OF COURSE.
- MRS. DRAPER.
- BETTY.
HENRY.
SO THAT'S A RAIN CHECK
FOR THE HIKE.
I'LL CONTACT YOU
AS SOON AS I KNOW ANYTHING.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO WATCH IT?
OH, I WILL ONCE IT GETS
A LITTLE FURTHER ALONG.
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU HEARD ME BEFORE,
BUT IT ONLY HAPPENS
ONCE EVERY 10 YEARS.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO MISS IT.
- HOW'S YOUR SUMMER GOING?
- IT'S GOOD.
ARE YOU GONNA TAKE
A VACATION?
I DON'T THINK SO.
I'LL GET AUGUST OFF
THEN SEPTEMBER
I'M BACK AT IT.
IT'S ALL
FAIRLY PRESCRIBED.
- HAVE YOU BEEN HERE
IN AUGUST?
IT'S A GHOST TOWN.
WHERE ARE
YOU GOING?
OH, WE'LL BE HERE.
SO NOW I KNOW THAT.
MOST JUST COME RIGHT OUT AND
ASK IF I'M GOING TO BE AROUND.
I WAS JUST MAKING CONVERSATION.
YOU CAN CHANGE IT IF YOU WANT TO.
YOU'RE ALL THE SAME-
THE DRINKING,
THE PHILANDERING.
THEY DON'T KNOW
THAT WORD.
DO YOU WANT ME TO LEAVE
YOU ALONE? JUST SAY SO.
IT'S HARD BECAUSE
THIS HAPPENS A LOT.
NOTHING IS HAPPENING.
WE'RE JUST TALKING.
OKAY.
AND WHERE I COME FROM,
SCHOOLTEACHERS
ESPECIALLY USED TO SAY
YOU SHOULDN'T JUDGE
A BOOK BY ITS COVER.
SO YOU'RE
DIFFERENT, HUH?
IS THAT IMPOSSIBLE?
YOU'RE ALL WEARING
THE SAME SHIRT.
SO HOW DO
PEOPLE LIVE ELSEWHERE?
THEY DON'T HAVE
AS MUCH.
THEY DON'T GET
AS BORED.
I'M NOT BORED.
Sally: MISS FARRELL! MISS FARRELL!
I CAN SEE IT! LOOK!
YES, IS HE IN?
TELL HIM IT'S PEGGY OLSON
REGARDING CLOROX.
OF COURSE.
HELLO.
MISS OLSON,
WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
I HAVEN'T
CHANGED MY MIND,
AND I'D APPRECIATE
YOU NOT SENDING THINGS.
THINGS YOU WANT
TO KEEP?
I'M SENDING IT BACK
AND I HOPE YOU TAKE THAT
AS A DEFINITIVE ANSWER.
I WOULD IF YOU HAD
ALREADY SENT IT.
LISTEN. I'VE BEEN
HAVING MEETINGS
AT THE PIERRE ALL DAY,
SUITE 600.
AT 4:30 HERMES COMES BY.
GIVE IT BACK IN PERSON.
WHY ARE YOU MEETING
AT THE PIERRE?
HAVE YOU BEEN
TO GREY?
IT'S A PENN STATION TOILET
WITH VENETIAN BLINDS.
- I CAN'T DO THAT.
- You can and you will, then I'll leave you alone.
SUITE 600 AT 4:30,
NOT THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
PLEASE DON'T
CONTACT ME AGAIN.
HOW WAS
YOUR WEEKEND?
SHORT.
WHAT DID MICHELSON THINK
OF THE CONTRACT?
HE HASN'T
GOTTEN BACK TO ME.
THAT'S BECAUSE
HE DIDN'T GET IT.
I CALLED HIM.
ARE YOU AFRAID YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE A BOSS?
YOU WILL-
THE CLIENT.
- IT'S NOT THAT.
- WHAT IS THE PROBLEM?
YOU THINK YOU'RE MORE
DANGEROUS WITHOUT A CONTRACT?
YOU ARE, AND IT'S
AFFECTING OUR BUSINESS.
YOU'RE OUR DAVID OGILVY,
AND IF YOU LET ALL THE BLOKES
AT PUTNAM, POWELL & LOWE
RELAX FOR THREE YEARS,
MAYBE WE COULD PUT
YOUR NAME OUT FRONT...
AFTER MINE...
AND COOPER PROBABLY.
WELL, I'LL LET
YOU GET BACK TO WORK.
ALL I NEED IS
A LETTER OF INTENT.
BEN MICHELSON CAN
RAPE US LATER.
GRUNT ONCE FOR YES.
THE PROBLEM IS
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU WANT
TO DO THIS HERE
OR YOU DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS AT ALL.
DIDN'T WE GIVE YOU
AN OFFICE?
I JUST NEED
A MINUTE.
I NEED TO SEND
MARTINSON'S TO THE PRINTER.
COME ON IN.
SO DO YOU KNOW WHO YOU'RE
GONNA PUT ON HILTON YET?
NO.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW IF THEY
WANT A WOMAN'S POINT OF VIEW.
- BUT I READ HIS BOOK- - WHO TOLD
YOU WE WERE GOING TO LAND HILTON?
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT,
AND I RESENT YOU BRINGING
WORK IN HERE UNDER PRETENSE.
- OH, I DIDN'T- - I DIDN'T
NEED TO SIGN OFF ON THIS.
I'M SORRY IF-
I WAS EXCITED
AND I HEARD THERE WAS
AN AMAZING ASSIGNMENT.
AND YOU THOUGHT YOU'D
COME IN HERE AND ASK FOR IT
- BECAUSE I NEVER SAY NO.
- YOU SAY "NO" ALL THE TIME.
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO
FOR YOU? PEGGY, TELL ME.
YOU WERE
MY SECRETARY
AND NOW YOU HAVE
AN OFFICE AND A JOB
THAT A LOT OF FULL-GROWN
MEN WOULD KILL FOR.
EVERY TIME
I TURN AROUND,
YOU'VE GOT
YOUR HAND IN MY POCKET.
YOU WANT A RAISE.
YOU WANT THIS ACCOUNT.
PUT YOUR NOSE DOWN AND
PAY ATTENTION TO YOUR WORK,
BECAUSE THERE'S NOT ONE
THING THAT YOU'VE DONE HERE
THAT I COULDN'T
LIVE WITHOUT.
I'M-
I'M SORRY, DON.
YOU'RE GOOD.
GET BETTER,
STOP ASKING FOR THINGS.
CLOSE THE DOOR.
DRAPER RESIDENCE.
BETTY. ROGER STERLING.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M WELL, THANK YOU.
- Is Don about?
- NO, HE'S NOT HOME YET. SHALL I LEAVE WORD?
ACTUALLY, BETTY, IF I COULD
BE FRANK, IT'S IMPORTANT.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- Well, it's a little touchy.
I DON'T WANT TO PUT YOU
IN A STRANGE POSITION.
WHAT'S WRONG, ROGER?
WELL, IT'S ABOUT
HIS CONTRACT.
WHAT ABOUT IT?
LOOK, I KNOW YOU HAVE TO BE
ON THE SAME PAGE AS HIM-
HE'S YOUR HUSBAND-
BUT IT'S A LOT
OF MONEY, BETTY.
It's a lot of money.
THREE YEARS ISN'T
THAT LONG, YOU KNOW.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I WANT YOU TO SEE WHAT YOU
CAN DO TO GET HIM TO SIGN IT.
I KNOW YOU'RE
THE WOMAN BEHIND THE MAN.
DON IS GOING TO DO
WHATEVER HE'S GOING TO DO.
AND HONESTLY, I FIND IT
TERRIBLY DISRESPECTFUL
- THAT YOU WOULD GO BEHIND HIS BACK.
- EASY, BETTY,
- that's not-
- I HAVE TO GO.
YOU MISSED HERMES.
I WAS GOING TO GIVE YOU
10 MORE MINUTES.
YOU CAME ALL THIS WAY,
HAVE A DRINK.
WHAT ARE YOU HAVING?
WHATEVER YOU'RE HAVING.
I'M NOT HAVING ANYTHING.
A WHISKEY.
YOU ARE DON'S GIRL,
AREN'T YOU?
I WAS RAISED
ON WHISKEY.
SIT DOWN.
A FEW MINUTES OF ADULT
CONVERSATION AND WE BOTH GO HOME.
GREY HAS
HERMES, MACY'S,
H.J. HEINZ BABY FOOD
AND REVLON.
- YOU NEED SOMEONE IN A SKIRT.
- EVERYBODY DOES.
- COPY CHIEF?
- MAYBE ONCE THEY GET USED TO YOU,
BUT DEFINITELY
MORE MONEY.
WOULD I GET TO GO
TO PARIS FOR HERMES?
THEY COME HERE,
BUT YOU'RE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE WHERE YOU ARE.
- I CAN'T.
- OKAY.
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
THAT'S WHAT
OPPORTUNITY LOOKS LIKE.
I'M JUST SORRY I WON'T
BE SEEING YOU EVERY DAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT
ALL THE TIMES I WALKED BY YOU
AND DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE.
OH.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
WHAT DO
YOU WANT FROM ME?
I WANT TO TAKE YOU
IN THAT BEDROOM,
LOCK THE DOOR, TAKE YOUR
CLOTHES OFF WITH MY TEETH,
THROW YOU ON THE BED AND GIVE YOU
A GO-AROUND LIKE YOU'VE NEVER HAD.
BOBBY, SALLY, TURN OFF
THE TV AND GO UPSTAIRS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
ROGER STERLING CALLED.
HE PRETENDED TO BE
CALLING FOR YOU
AND THEN HE STARTED ON ME
ABOUT YOUR CONTRACT.
- WHAT?
- YOUR CONTRACT, DON.
IT WAS
VERY UNCOMFORTABLE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- I'M CALLING HIM.
- DON'T.
BETTS, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT MY JOB.
WHY WOULD I? I DON'T
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
THEY OFFERED YOU A CONTRACT AND
YOU DIDN'T SAY A DAMN THING TO ME.
I HAD TO HEAR
ABOUT IT FROM HIM.
AND WHY THE HELL
WON'T YOU SIGN IT?
IT DOESN'T CONCERN YOU.
YOU'RE TAKEN CARE OF.
WHY WON'T YOU SIGN IT?
LET ME EXPLAIN SOMETHING
TO YOU ABOUT BUSINESS,
SINCE AS USUAL YOU'RE TURNING
THIS INTO SOMETHING ABOUT YOURSELF.
NO CONTRACT MEANS
I HAVE ALL THE POWER.
THEY WANT ME,
BUT THEY CAN'T HAVE ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHY WOULD I THINK THAT
HAS ANYTHING TO DO WITH ME?
IT'S THREE YEARS, DON.
WHAT'S THE MATTER? YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE GOING TO BE IN THREE YEARS?
GOOD NIGHT.
I LOVE THE TASTE
OF LIQUOR ON YOUR BREATH.
- WHERE YOU HEADED?
- NIAGARA FALLS.
BUT WE'LL SETTLE
FOR THE NEAREST MOTEL.
HOP IN.
THANK YOU.
I'M DOUG.
THIS IS SANDY.
Don:
NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HOW FAR ARE WE?
- A COUPLE OF MILES.
YOU WANNA KNOW WHY WE'RE
GOING TO NIAGARA FALLS?
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED.
AT NIAGARA FALLS.
FANCY THAT.
PEOPLE KEEP TRYING
TO TALK US OUT OF IT.
WHY'S THAT?
WELL, WE DON'T REALLY KNOW
EACH OTHER THAT WELL.
WELL, WE KNEW EACH OTHER
A LITTLE BIT IN HIGH SCHOOL
AND WE'RE NOT REALLY
IN LOVE OR ANYTHING.
I'M SURE YOU HAVE
A GOOD REASON,
NOT THAT IT'S
ANY OF MY BUSINESS.
OH, I'M NOT KNOCKED UP.
THEY'RE PASSING A LAW
THAT IF YOU'RE MARRIED,
THEY CAN'T SEND YOU
TO VIETNAM.
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'VE SERVED, MISTER.
I DON'T WANT
TO OFFEND YOU.
AGAIN,
NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
IT'S JUST I'M 1A, 22.
I CAN'T GET INTO SCHOOL.
I KIND OF HAVE A TARGET
ON MY BACK, AND FOR WHAT?
I THINK THEY'RE REALLY
GONNA START SENDING PEOPLE.
I HAVE IT ON GOOD AUTHORITY
THAT YOU'RE RIGHT.
GOOD AUTHORITY?
ARE YOU A SPOOK?
NOPE.
I'M IN ADVERTISING.
NOAY.
NOW THAT'S PRICELESS.
BUT YOU SEEM OKAY.
THANK YOU.
Sandy:
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL NIGHT.
IT SMELLS GOOD...
BUT EVERYTHING SMELLS GOOD
WHEN YOU'RE HIGH.
THAT'S TRUE.
LISTEN, CADILLAC,
WE DON'T HAVE
GAS MONEY, BUT...
THEY'RE REDS.
YOU EVER HAVE THEM?
WHAT ARE THEY?
PHENOBARBITAL.
THEY'RE MY DAD'S.
GIVE ME ONE.
MAKE IT TWO.
- AH.
Please come to me
When other lips
no longer kiss
When other arms don't...
DOES HE KNOW
HOW TO DANCE?
WHO CARES?
To kiss again
To love again
-  Please...
- HOW OLD ARE YOU?
- 19.
Please come to me
When darkness brings
you loneliness...
- WHY CAN'T YOU GO TO SCHOOL?
- BECAUSE IT'S A WASTE OF TIME, MAN.
YOU LIKE
TO WATCH US DANCE?
YEAH, YOU WANT
TO WATCH US?
To love again
Please come to me...
A HILLBILLY KNOCKS ON THE DOOR
OF HIS NEW NEIGHBOR'S HOUSE.
"HOWDY, NEIGHBOR,"
HE SAYS.
"IN HONOR OF YOU MOVING
INTO THE HOLLER,
I'M GONNA THROW
A PARTY.
THERE'S GONNA BE
A WHOLE LOT OF DRINKING,
A WHOLE LOT OF DANCING AND
A WHOLE LOT OF SCREWING."
"SOUNDS LIKE FUN,"
THE NEIGHBOR SAYS.
"WHAT CAN I BRING?"
THE HILLBILLY REPLIES,
"YOU CAN BRING
ANYTHING YOU WANT-
IT'S JUST GONNA BE
YOU AND ME."
- WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING AT, CADILLAC?
Archie:
LOOK AT YOU.
UP TO YOUR OLD TRICKS.
YOU'RE A BUM.
YOU KNOW THAT?
NO, I'M NOT.
CONRAD HILTON?
YOU WOULDN'T EXPECT HIM
TO BE TAKEN SO EASILY.
SHUT UP.
YOU CAN'T
BE TIED DOWN.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- Archie: LOOK AT YOUR HANDS.
THEY'RE AS SOFT
AS A WOMAN'S.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
WHAT DO YOU MAKE?
YOU GROW BULLSHIT.
Oh, baby
Please, baby
Oh, baby,
come to me...
- I GAVE HIM TWO.
- HOW THE HELL IS HE STILL AWAKE?
( faucet squeaks,
EVERYTHING OKAY?
I'M WORRIED THAT HOUSEKEEPING
IS GOING TO COME IN.
I PUT OUT THE SIGN.
I'LL CALL THEM
WHEN WE'RE DONE.
I DON'T KNOW.
COME ON.
I LOVE THE MORNING.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
- IT'S AWFUL.
- IT'S AN ANTIQUE.
WE DISCUSSED THIS
FOR MONTHS
AND WE DECIDED
ANTIQUES WERE EXPECTED.
LOOK AROUND! YOU HAVE
RUINED THE WHOLE ROOM.
IF YOU WANT
TO KEEP IT,
PLEASE DO NOT
TELL PEOPLE I DID THIS.
- MORNING.
- FENDER BENDER.
OH. I'M GOING TO GET
COFFEE. DO YOU WANT SOME?
NO, THANK YOU.
GOOD MORNING,
MR. DRAPER.
- FENDER BENDER.
- I'M SORRY.
MR. COOPER'S
WAITING FOR YOU.
THANK YOU.
GOOD MORNING.
SIT DOWN.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
SACAJAWEA CARRIED A BABY
ON HER BACK ALL THE WAY
TO THE PACIFIC OCEAN,
AND SOMEWHERE THAT BABY
THINKS HE DISCOVERED AMERICA.
YOU, DON, HAVE BEEN STANDING
ON SOMEONE'S SHOULDERS.
WE BROUGHT YOU IN,
WE NURTURED YOU LIKE FAMILY
AND NOW'S THE TIME
TO PAY US BACK.
YOU CAN'T GO ANY FURTHER
ON YOUR OWN, DON.
WOULD YOU SAY I KNOW
SOMETHING ABOUT YOU, DON?
I WOULD.
THEN SIGN.
AFTER ALL,
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
WHO IS REALLY SIGNING
THIS CONTRACT ANYWAY?
I DON'T WANT ANYMORE
CONTACT WITH ROGER STERLING.
I DON'T WANT
DON?
SOME PEOPLE SAY A MAN
IS MADE OUT OF MUD
A POOR MAN'S MADE
OUT OF MUSCLE AND BLOOD
www.tvsubtitles.net