Oh, hey, Stuart,
I got you
a little souvenir
from my trip to space.
Well, Howard,
that's very nice of you.
Yeah, maybe. Open it first.
It's my official
NASA portrait.
"To Stuart, your comic book
store is out of this world.
Just like the guy
in this picture was."
For the record, he also thinks
the Walgreens
and the dry cleaners
are out of this world.
That's not true.
At the Walgreens,
I was "over the moon"
for their store-brand antacids.
Hey, Stuart, I see
you're getting ready
for your Halloween party.
Yeah, it's my annual attempt
to meet women.
Ninth time's the charm.
Would you like me to help?
I do have a certain je ne sais
quois when it comes to soirees.
Thanks, but I can't afford
je ne sais quois.
How much for just quois?
You know,
you don't worry about money.
I'll take care of everything.
Really?
Yeah, you'll love it. Ain't no
party like a Koothra-party.
But you know
what wasn't a party?
That hotel in Kazakhstan
they put you up in
before the launch.
I mean,
it's your last night on Earth.
You'd think you'd get
one porn channel.
Have you noticed
that Howard can take any topic
and use it to remind you
that he went to space?
Interesting hypothesis.
Let's apply the
scientific method,
perform an experiment.
Okay.
Hey, Howard, any thoughts on
where we should get dinner?
Anywhere but the Space Station.
On a good day, dinner was
a bag full of meat loaf.
But, hey, you don't go there
for the food,
you go there for the view.
It's fascinating.
Let me see if I can
duplicate the result.
Howard, I've
always thought
the lemon was an
underrated fruit.
Care to weigh in?
Not really.
Oh, well.
You know, people say the Soyuz
capsule was a lemon.
But, hey, that baby got me
to space and back.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x05 ♪
The Re-Entry Minimization
Original Air Date on October 25, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Ladies night
at the Cheesecake Factory.
Does it get any better
than this?
I hope so.
Question. Do you think your
husband's fondness
for turtlenecks is an
expression of longing
for his
missing foreskin?
It's not getting any better.
Uch. It's Leonard.
He wants to go costume
shopping later.
I thought you liked Halloween.
I do, it's just
he wants to go to that party
at the comic book store.
A lot of the guys that hang out
there are kind of creepy.
Like my husband?
And my boyfriend?
I'm, I'm sorry, Amy.
You were saying something
about Howard's foreskin?
Nice try, but you have
to go to that party
'cause we're going.
Yeah, I'm gonna go.
It's just not my idea
of a good time.
Leonard does thing he doesn't
like to make you happy.
Yeah, he's my boyfriend.
Isn't that, like, his job?
Then what's your job?
Letting him make me happy.
I just think in relationships
you get back
what you put into them.
That's not always true.
Last night I gave Sheldon
my best come-hither look,
and he responded
by explaining how
wheat came
to be cultivated.
I guess I could probably try
a little harder.
You could start by taking
an interest in his work.
Yeah, that's kind of a problem.
Why?
Not really clear on
what he does.
He's an experimental
physicist.
Yeah, I'm not really clear on
what that means.
He takes hypotheses
and designs protocols
to determine
their accuracy.
Yeah, you're really
just making it worse.
What kind of tea
would you like?
I think I'm gonna try
green tea
mixed with lemon zinger.
Two tea bags in one cup?
You're not at a rave.
So, listen, Sheldon,
I was thinking,
since this is gonna be
our first
Halloween party
as boyfriend and girlfriend,
I thought it might be fun for us
to go in a couples costume.
I couldn't agree more.
Really? I find that inconsistent
with everything I know
about you.
Oh, oh, on the contrary.
Couples costumes are one
of the few benefits
of being in a relationship.
Now imagine this:
you and I entering
Stuart's party
and all eyes turn to see
America's most beloved
and glamorous couple.
Yeah?
R2-D2 and C-3PO!
Dibs on 3PO.
Sheldon, when I said
couples costume,
I meant like Romeo and Juliet
or Cinderella
and Prince Charming,
not two robots from some
silly movie I don't even like.
Okay!
I'm gonna let that slide
because I kn you're hopped up
on tea bags.
I make compromises
for you all the time.
Just this once,
can't we find something
that we're both happy with?
Fine. How about one
of the most beguiling
and influential couples
of the 20th century?
Hewlett and Packard.
Dibs on Hewlett.
What, you want to be Hewlett?
Anybody home?
Hey-hey-hey,
what are you doing here?
I just thought I'd
stop by and say hello.
Oh, what a nice surprise.
Oh.
I don't think you've
ever seen my lab before.
No, I know.
It's long overdue.
So, what ya doing?
Better not be building
a robot girlfriend.
No. Although Howard was
making some real strides
in that area until
he met Bernadette.
You're kidding.
Nope.
Now the Lisatronic 3000
just sits in a box
waiting for the phone to ring.
Ooh! What's going on in here?
Oh, no, no, no,
don't look in there.
What, is it secret?
No, it's a nitrogen laser.
It'll cook your eyeball
like a soft-boiled egg.
Oh. You might want
to put a sign on it.
Sign right there.
Ah. "Danger," sure, sure.
Yeah. What's, what's that?
Uh, that is an
integrated ion trap
and time-of-flight
mass spectrometer.
Wow. High-techie-techie.
What's this little box?
That is a pencil
sharpener.
Ooh, low-techie-techie.
So, what are you
working on right now?
It's actually pretty neat.
Yeah?
Yeah. It's a front-projected
holographic display
combined with laser-based
finger tracking.
Here, I'll show you.
We'll just put this
pencil over here.
Sharp. Thanks to the machine
we saw earlier.
Very good.
And then a laser will map
the reflective surface...
and voilà.
Wow. That is amazing.
You know, there's a foundational
idea in string theory
that the whole universe
may be a hologram.
What do you mean?
Oh!
Wow.
Uh-huh.
Well, the holographic principle
suggests
that what we all experience
every day in three dimensions
may really just be information
on a surface located
at the farthest reaches
of our cosmos.
So it's possible
that our lives are
really just acting
out a painting
on the largest canvas
in the universe.
Hmm.
What?
Sometimes I forget
how smart you are.
You should visit
more often.
What are you doing?
Take off your clothes.
What? Here? Now?
Yeah. You got a problem
with that?
No, no. It's kind of crazy.
I've never fooled around
in the lab before.
Really? Never?
No. I did have a shot
with the Lisatronic,
but the extension cord
wasn't long enough.
Before I forget, I'd like
your opinion on the menus
I've prepared
for the Halloween party.
The theme is "food
that goes bump in the night."
"Creature from
the Black Forest Ham Lagoon."
On Sesame seed Bunzillas.
"Night of the Living
Garlic Bread"?
It's funny because "bread"
sounds like "dead".
I'm sorry, but these
are just ordinary foods
with the names bent
into tortured puns.
The dishes themselves
are in no way Halloweenie.
Ooh, Hallow-weenies!
That's a good one.
They'll pair nicely
with my "Draculoni and Cheese."
How do I do it?!
That reminds me, I was thinking
about wearing my NASA jumpsuit
as a costume.
But then I realized everyone
would be, like,
"Where's your costume?
Why are you wearing your work
clothes, you nut?"
Hello, boys.
What are you smiling at?
Nothing.
You know where's there's
a lot of nothing.
Space.
Boy, it's nice to sleep in
a bed with gravity again.
Did I tell you
about the night
my retainer floated out
of my mouth
and into the air lock?
Yeah, you mentioned it
once or twice.
So, here we are,
just a couple
of young newlyweds.
What to do?
What to do to you?
Astronaut Wolowitz,
reporting for booty.
Preparing thrusters.
We have liftoff.
Are we clear to jettison
that nightgown?
Okay, we need to talk.
What?
Howie, I know you
went to space.
I'm incredibly
proud of you.
But you might want to try
and not bring it up
every minute.
I don't talk about it
Tonight at dinner you went on
about it for an hour straight.
What was I supposed
to talk about?
We were eating
at Johnny Rockets.
I'm just saying,
people are getting
a little tired of it.
So, I did this
amazing thing
and I'm never allowed
to mention it?
Of course you can.
But maybe a good
rule would be
to wait for people
to bring it up.
Okay, no problem.
It won't happen again.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I can't tell you how
many times I dreamed
I was in bed here
with you when I was...
you know.
What, I can't even point?
So, basically, this is what's
called mag-lev technology.
It uses very powerful
electromagnets
to create a force strong
enough to overcome gravity.
Here, you hold this.
Whoa! That's heavy.
Yeah. Oh, uh, you don't have
on any jewelry, do you?
No. Why?
A grad student forgot to take
out one of his piercings.
Now he's on a
transplant list
waiting for a
nipple his size.
Now watch this.
Whoa!
That is very cool.
Sometimes I like
to turn this on
and pretend I'm the
super villain Magneto.
It's getting a little
less cool, Leonard.
But what I really am is
a very smart scientist
who understands the
mechanics of the universe
and is wearing the sexy black
underwear you bought him.
There we go.
So, I thought the photo
booth for the party could
either be creepy like
a mummy's tomb,
or they also have the Tardis
from Doctor Who.
A Tardis makes no sense.
It's a time machine
from a science-fiction show.
It has nothing to do
with Halloween.
That being said,
if you don't get a Tardis,
you stink
and your party stinks.
Do you have a preference?
I don't care. Get the Tardis.
Yes! This party just
became a major rager.
Oh, by the way,
can I borrow your
bullwhip and fedora?
Yeah, sure, whatever.
I was thinking of dressing up
as Indiana Jones'
mocha-skinned love child.
"Indian" Jones.
Clever.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Oh, Howard, I've got
a party to plan.
Don't make me
pull it out of you.
Okay, here it is.
Bernadette said you guys are
all sick of me
talking about my trip to space.
Is that true?
No.
Yes.
We seem to have
different approaches here.
I was going
for helpful honesty.
I have no idea
what you're doing.
It's called being nice.
Okay. If you think
being nice
will get him to shut up,
I'll try it.
You know what, guys? Never mind.
I just won't talk
about the greatest achievement
of my life ever again.
Look at that,
the problem solved itself.
Hello, boys.
What if we were to go
as dinner table favorites
salt and pepper?
You know salt makes me retain
water and my cousin William
was ground to death
in a pepper factory accident.
How about
Raggedy Ann and Andy?
I loved them
growing up.
No, I don't think so.
Those dolls represent
three things I do not care for:
clowns, children
and raggediness.
I think it's a lost cause.
No. There are certain things
that say to the world,
"I have a boyfriend,
and he's not made up."
Matching costumes,
hickeys and sex tapes.
Pick one.
What's a hickey?
How do I look?
Fine.
Uh-oh, is someone a little blue?
Come on, Howie,
that's like the funniest thing
I've ever said in my life.
What do you say?
You ready to go?
To tell you the truth,
I'm not really in the mood.
What are you talking about?
It'll be fun.
All your friends'll be there.
Yeah, some friends.
They all think I'm boring.
Maybe you should go
without me.
No, if I'm there alone,
people might think
I'm just a really short
person from Avatar.
I'm sorry.
I just don't want to go.
Hey, I just spent the last three
hours coloring myself blue.
I'm gonna be
washing paint out
of my Smurf for a month!
Fine.
Two weeks ago
I was an astronaut.
Yeah, well, now you're a Smurf.
Keep walking.
♪
Oh, my God,
you guys look adorable!
Thanks, so do you.
Slutty cop?
No, sexy cop.
Slutty cop only came
with a skirt and two badges.
And Albert Einstein?
Ja, und later
she's going to arrest me
for goink fashter
zen da shpeed of light.
I thought we said
in the car, no accents?
Sorry, Officer.
Hello!
It's a great party!
Thank you!
The monster foods,
they're really fun.
Oh, yes, thank you.
I like to think of fun things
like that because I'm fun.
I'm not clinically depressed
at all.
Sheldon, get in here!
I should've picked hickey.
Hey, hey,
look at you guys!
I'm Raggedy Ann, and
he's Raggedy C-3PO.
It was a compromise.
I lost.
Can you believe
Stuart's walking around
taking credit
for this party?
Who cares?
What do you mean "who cares"?
Look at what I pulled off here.
The deejay's on fire, there's
a Tardis photo booth in the back room,
and, oh, my God, the food!
Stuart wanted Kraft
Draculoni and cheese.
You're right, the party's
fantastic. Please, tell me more.
I haven't heard enough
about it all week
because hearing about that
never gets old!
Is this about the
space thing again?
Well, I'm not allowed
to talk about it,
but since you brought it up,
I went to space!
Space, space, space!
Whoa, Drinky Smurf.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Great, now I'm in trouble.
You happy?!
You, out!
You are being very rude!
No, I'm not.
They're all being rude.
And you're being rude.
Me? What did I do?
"Oh, Howie...
"stop talking
about space so much.
Nobody likes it."
I don't sound like that.
You're my wife.
You're supposed
to be on my side.
I'm always on your side.
Then why are you trying
to take this away from me?
Being an astronaut is
the coolest thing
I'm ever gonna do.
If I stop talking about it,
then I'm just...
Just what?
Just plain old
Howard Wolowitz again.
Plain old Howard Wolowitz
is the best guy I know.
You're just saying that.
No, I'm not.
I married him.
On purpose.
Come here.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Nothing to see here.
Just sexy police business.
Just explaining
the theory of relativity.
Twice.
Hey, what you watching?
I don't know.
Raj sent me some video
of Buzz Aldrin.
Here you go.
It's a Milky Way.
The Milky Way's
a galaxy in space.
I've been in space.
Here's a Mars bar.
I'm an astronaut.
And this one's a Moon Pie.
I walked on the Moon.
What have you done?
Okay, I get it.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net