Previously
on The Big Bang Theory...
Can I have your attention,
please?
We're all here tonight because
we have no one to be with.
We've got to stop defining
our self-worth by whether or not
we're in a relationship.
We are a community, and as long
as we have each other,
we're never truly alone.
That was cool.
What you said.
Thank you.
Uh... would you like
to, uh...
get a cup...
a cup of coffee...?
Okay.
Later, losers!
So then I went to Cambridge,
which was wonderful
not only because
it's a good school
but because it totally
looks like Hogwarts.
That's where I fell in
love with astronomy,
and now I'm an
astrophysicist at Caltech,
so I guess you could say, uh,
Raj is my name and
stars are my game.
And rhyming is also my game.
So, uh, two games.
Uh, anyway, that-that's
enough about me.
I want to hear
everything about you.
I have to go
to the bathroom.
I go to the
bathroom, too.
Sometimes more frequently
than I care to admit.
Oh, I've had it checked out,
it's nothing.
Hmm! This is going great!
Mmm... can I have a refill
on my chai tea?
Yes...
I have a good feeling
about this.
I should have bought condoms.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Welcome to Sheldon Cooper
Presents: Fun with Flags.
My apologies that this episode
is coming late.
I did shoot one last week,
in honor of Black History Month,
but I was informed
by my roommate
that my spot-on portrayal
of George Washington Carver
could be considered
"wildly racist."
My heart goes out to the members
of the African-American
community,
who, like me,
have been kept down by The Man.
Now, Fun with Flags is not just
for the flag aficionado;
it's also for the flag novice,
so, to help me with that,
please welcome my friend,
neighbor, and flag virgin--
yeah, not a real virgin.
She's had coitus many times.
Sometimes within earshot
of this flag enthusiast.
Once while he was trying
to watch The Incredibles.
Penny.
Hello.
So, Penny, I understand
you would like to learn
more about flags.
Yeah, I can't tell you
how many times
I've been at a party where
everyone's talking about flags
and I just couldn't join in.
Yeah.
Well, you came to
the right place.
Uh, I'm sorry, can we
just pause for a minute?
What's wrong?
I just think
it might look more natural
if you talked to me
instead of the camera,
you know, like,
like a real conversation.
It's something we work on
in my acting class.
Interesting.
A few people in the
comments section have said
that my delivery
is robotic.
Perhaps that isn't the
compliment it sounds like.
Yeah, let's try it again,
and maybe, this time,
you could work
on your body language a bit.
You know, when you're
all hunched like that,
you're shutting
the audience out,
but when you're relaxed
and open,
you're inviting them in.
Right.
And which one do I want?
Let's try open.
If our friend, the flag,
has taught me anything,
it's to go where
the wind takes you.
As long as you remain firmly
attached to a rigid pole.
And... action.
So, Penny...
what sort of flag questions
keep you awake at night?
Um, well, I'm from Nebraska.
So what can you tell me
about the state flag?
Gosh, Penny...
what'd you have
for breakfast?
A big glass of
good question juice?
The Nebraska state flag
is simply the state seal
on a field of blue.
Spread your legs;
invite them in.
I'm telling you,
something's wrong.
I can always feel it
when Raj is in trouble.
Geez, how close were you guys
before we got married?
Don't look under that rock.
Raj, you okay?
You in there?
Go away!
Come on, buddy, open up.
We're worried about you.
Oh, just because I
stopped going to work
and answering my phone you
think something bad happened?
Maybe something
good happened.
Did something good happen?
Of course not!
Nothing good ever happens!
Whoa.
What?
Nope, just-just... whoa.
It smells pretty ripe in here.
You kind feel it in your eyes.
Raj, what's going on?
I was humiliated
by yet another woman.
You didn't kill her
and chop her up--
that's not what we're
smelling, right?
No.
I took her for coffee,
and she snuck
out the bathroom window
to get away from me.
Oh, you poor baby.
I went and looked.
It was a high and tiny window.
She must have been
very motivated.
I'm sorry.
That's awful, but come on.
you got to shake it off.
Yeah, you can't stay
in your apartment
for the rest of your life.
Why not?
With online shopping
and overnight delivery,
I can get anything I want.
Look,
I just ordered a case
of Dinty Moore beef stew
and two live lobsters on Amazon.
Lobsters overnight?
Oh, you're kidding.
Let me see.
Well, I'll be.
Look, you can throw
in a couple steaks
and have a surf and turf.
The surf and turf sounds good.
See if they corn on the cob.
Guys!
We're trying to get him
out of here,
not you in.
You're wasting
your time.
Just please,
leave me alone.
Now what?
I don't know.
We could go to Red Lobster
and talk about it.
We're all thinking it.
I just had the decency to wait
for him to leave.
Hello, Sheldon.
Hello.
How's the final stage
of your nicotine
addiction study going?
Fine.
Just hold on.
Mommy's on the phone!
Sorry.
We've cut the monkeys down
to one cigarette a day,
so things are a little intense.
Makes me miss
my marijuana-abusing flatworms.
Those guys were mellow.
Good news.
Uh, the latest episode
of Fun with Flags is online.
Oh, that's right.
How'd it go with Penny?
Much better than I expected.
She even gave me
some helpful tips
about acting and body language.
Watch.
Welcome to my world.
Not welcome to my world.
Welcome.
Not welcome.
Subtle, but powerful.
I know.
I'm still learning
to control it.
Did you tell Penny
how helpful she was?
Why would I do that?
Because she's your friend,
and she did a nice job.
I'm sure she'd like to hear it.
All right.
I didn't mean now. Hello?
Yeah, yeah,
you want a cigarette.
Well,
I'd like a normal boyfriend.
Deal with it.
Oh, hi. What's up?
Um...
You need me to shut the door
so you can do
your knocking thing?
No.
I didn't start yet; it's fine.
Okay. So, what do you need?
Well, I was thinking
about you helping me
out last night...
Penny.
And I just wanted to tell you...
...that the answer
to the question,
"Who did a great job?" is you.
Penny.
Really?
Yes, you were very natural
in front of the camera,
and I found your suggestions
extremely helpful.
Aw, sweetie,
you just made my day.
Okay.
Hey, my acting class is putting
on a play Friday night.
I could put you and Amy
on the guest list.
Oh, that sounds terrible.
Why would I want to do that?
That's right.
They're no good
without the lighter.
Well, so much for your advice
on complimenting Penny.
Why? What happened?
She tried to rope us into going
to her acting class
to see a play.
Don't worry.
Luckily, I had the good sense
to drown that kitten
in the river.
Sheldon, that's very rude.
She helped you with your show.
The right thing to do
is reciprocate
by going to see her play.
Oh, so many crazy rules.
That better be Tootsie Rolls
you're throwing at me!
Penny. Penny.
Penny.
Oh yeah, much better.
What?
Amy pointed out to me
that since you did
something nice for me,
I'm obligated to do
something nice for you.
So...
yes, I'll go
to your dopey play.
Hey, I don't want you
to go anymore.
Why not?
You should go 'cause
you want to go,
not because you have to.
Oh, Dear Lord, more rules?
Where does it stop?
Can I want to go
because I have to want to go?
Okay. Do whatever you want.
Yeah, but now, wait.
Do whatever I want...
or whatever I have to want?
Oh, for God's sake,
just come to the play.
All right.
I don't want to, but
at least that makes sense.
You know, I haven't seen
Raj in several days.
Is he no longer a part
of our social group?
And if so, should we be
interviewing for a replacement?
Perhaps, this time, we go Latin.
He's just decided he's never
leaving his apartment again.
Oh, brilliant.
I've been itching
to pull that trigger.
He's upset because he can't
get anywhere with women.
Would it help if I gave
him some pointers?
I'm just funnin' ya.
Hi.
I don't know if you remember me,
but I was here the other night
at your party.
Oh, yeah, you left with Raj.
Uh, yeah.
You're the one?
Okay, let me tell you something.
That guy you blew off
happens to be my best friend.
Okay?
He was devastated.
Sorry.
Can you just give him this?
Okay.
But I gotta warn you,
Raj is a proud, passionate man.
If you go running out
on him again,
you're only gonna get, like,
three or four more chances
before you are history.
Come on, she came back.
This is good news.
You should celebrate.
I don't want to celebrate.
Not even a little?
I mean... we could have
a pants party.
Go put some on.
Why would I want her number?
I don't want anything to do
with this woman.
Oh, come on, Raj...
No, you don't get it.
I want nothing to
do with any woman.
My heart is stone.
From now on, I'm a monk.
I renounce
all worldly pleasures.
Except for lobster.
And garlic butter.
Boy, I want to tell you
it's her loss,
but you are not making it easy.
You're-you're a good friend
for trying to help, but...
I've made my choice.
All right.
Well, I'll see you around.
See you.
Oh, wait--
take her number.
I don't want the temptation.
Okay.
I must be strong
so I don't stray
from my true purpose:
the study of the universe.
All right.
Thanks for
ruining lobster for me.
Wait!
Give me the number!
Give me
the number!
Give me the number!
So, Amy, what's going on
with your addiction study?
Sadly, I'm no longer associated
with that project.
Why? What happened?
Typical bureaucratic nonsense.
You can get animals addicted
to a harmful substance,
you can dissect their brains,
but you throw their own feces
back at them
and suddenly you're
"unprofessional."
I'm sorry...
...that I asked.
All right, let's get
this stupid play over with.
Uh, hang on.
Empty your pockets.
Why?
You know why.
The Nintendo DS.
And the PSP.
Now the Gameboy.
Aw, for Pete's sake.
Can we go now?
Well, is that all of it?
Just set it down.
Just so you know, this is
not a stupid play.
A Streetcar Named Desire
is an American classic.
It's about streetcars?
Oh, great. I won't need this.
Just a sec.
Oh, who says "just a sec"?
I hate myself!
Hello.
Hi.
Uh, would you like to come in?
Oh, no, I can't stay.
Oh.
I just wanted to say...
I'm sorry for running
out of the coffee shop.
That wasn't cool.
So, uh...
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Can you at least tell me
what went wrong?
It's okay.
I can take anything.
Unless it's something I did,
or said, or am.
'Cause those are,
like, my buttons.
No, it's not any of that.
It's just...
I kind of have a hard time
around people I don't know.
Really?
Then what were you doing
at the comic book store
that night?
I've been trying to force myself
into situations
that I'm not comfortable with.
I saw the flyer
in the store window,
and I made myself go in.
I don't even like comic books.
Yeah, me neither.
Then what were you doing there?
I lied. I love them.
I only said that
so you'd go out with me.
Oh, you don't want to do that.
I'm kind of broken.
That's great.
I'm broken, too.
Oh, no, you're not.
Oh, I totally am.
If it wasn't
for this beer,
I couldn't even talk
to you right now.
I'm a wreck.
There are many things
seriously wrong with me.
And not quirks, either.
Like... diagnosable
psychological problems.
Maybe brain damage.
Well, how do I know
you're not just saying that?
Go out with me on one date,
and I promise you, you'll see.
Okay.
Text me.
Bye.
You won't regret it.
I'm the most pathetic
guy you've ever met.
And that, boys and girls...
is how it's done.
You love her very much,
don't you?
Yes.
I think you have
a great capacity for devotion.
You'll be lonely when
she passes on, won't you?
I understand
what that is.
To be lonely?
She's
pretty good, huh?
She is.
But when do they get
to the part about streetcars?
...when I was a very young girl.
When I was 16 years old,
I made the discovery...
love.
All at once,
and much, much too completely.
It was like you suddenly turned
a blinding light
on something that had always
been half a shadow.
That's how it struck
the world for me.
But I was unlucky.
Deluded.
She's remarkable.
She really is.
Our Penny's a star.
...and softness and
tenderness which...
How can she remember
all those lines,
but as a waitress,
she can't remember
"no tomato" on my hamburger?
www.tvsubtitles.net