Look, I know you guys don't want
to do this,
but we have no choice.
So, you can either
bitch and whine
or we can
just get it over with.
I got "whine."
I got the "b word."
Yeah, well,
it's in our contract
to serve on a
university committee.
And frankly,
this is one I believe in.
Okay, here we go.
Encouraging more women to
pursue a career in the sciences.
Come on,
if I was any good
at convincing women to do stuff,
I wouldn't have spent so much of
my 20s in the shower.
If you ask me,
this whole thing is a waste of
our time.
Helping women?
Yeah, helping anyone.
People should take care
of themselves.
Oh, like yesterday,
when you made me drive you
to the dry cleaners,
the pharmacy
and the post office?
I'm not saying people
can't use tools.
Even an otter picks up a rock
when he wants a clam.
You don't think it's worthwhile
to try to get more women
working in science.
I think
that's incredibly sexist of you.
I believe in a
gender-blind society
like in Star Trek,
where women and men
of all races and creeds
work side by side as equals.
You mean
where they were advanced enough
to invent
an interstellar warp drive,
but a black lady still answered
the space phone?
Oh, I did spend a lot of my
shower time
with Lieutenant Uhura.
Howard's
disturbing recollections aside,
I don't appreciate
being forced to do
banal committee work.
Yes, I know,
you're too smart for this.
Exactly.
It's like
asking the Human Torch
to heat up your frozen burrito.
Got it.
All right,
I'm thinking one way
to counter bias
in the peer-review process,
is for papers to be submitted
under gender-neutral names.
Like S. Smith
instead of Samantha Smith.
I suppose there is a history of
professional women
using their initials,
so as not to be pre-judged.
Harry Potter's J.K. Rowling,
uh, Star Trek's D.C. Fontana.
Van Nuys pole-dancer
D.D. Melons.
All right, I think we've
really helped women today.
Let's fire
up the old Xbox.
Guys, please don't make this
a school project
where I'm the smart kid doing
all the work
while the slackers
sit back and watch.
No, we're not.
This time you're the smart
kid doing all the work
while the even smarter kids
sit back and watch.
So, you think I'm
one of the smarter kids?
No, you're a tool I was
using to make my point.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x87 ♪
The Contractual Obligation Implementation
Original Air Date on March 7, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Guys, our topic is "Encouraging
Women in Science."
Can you at least play
a less sexist game
How is it sexist?
My character wields a
battle axe as well as any man.
Not to mention she
has mammary glands
that could
nurse a family of 30.
And have enough milk left over
to open a Baskin Robbins.
Mother, warrior-princess,
franchise owner--
I hear glass ceilings
shattering all over town.
Sheldon,
you're always saying
how much smarter
you are than me.
Spend five seconds
and come up with one idea
on how to get more women
into science.
All your ideas address the issue
at a university level.
By then it's too late.
You need to
design an outreach program
that targets girls
at the middle school level
and sets them on an
academic track
towards the hard sciences.
That's actually good.
Why didn't I
think of that?
Some people are otters,
some people are rocks.
I wonder if there's a way
we could give the idea
a trial run.
Maybe I could call my old
middle school,
see if we can talk to some of
the female students.
That's great--
try to set up something
for the three of us
to go over there.
Oh, hold on.
While I'm comfortable speaking
about science,
I'm not sure I know how to spark
the interest of schoolchildren.
Better Google it.
What exactly are you looking up?
"How do I get
12-year-old girls excited."
No!
Thanks again for letting
me crash "girls' night."
Are you kidding?
You brought fancy
wine and made fondue.
I've slept
with guys for less.
It's a joke.
Based on real events.
Anyway,
I was hoping I could, uh,
pick your brains a little.
I'm supposed to take
Lucy out Friday
and I need a killer first date.
Well, evolutionary biology
says that women are attracted
to a man who is steady
in the face of danger,
so I recommend an
unsafe environment.
Seedy bar on the wrong
side of the tracks...
picnic near
a lunatic asylum...
a wine tasting on Skid Row.
Eh, Lucy has some,
uh, social anxiety issues.
Maybe we could start
with something simpler.
Why don't you take
her to Disneyland?
You go on Space Mountain,
you're in the dark,
she's holding onto you.
Yeah, but you
just have to remember,
that ride is
shorter than you think
and they take a
picture of you at the end,
so make sure
you got your clothes back on.
It's a joke.
Based on real events.
Mm, Disneyland?
I don't know.
With all the crowds and the
weird characters walking around,
just reminds me
too much of India.
I haven't been to Disneyland
since I was a kid.
We should
definitely go one weekend.
Weekends are too crowded.
So, blow off work,
go on a weekday.
Hooky?
I've never
played hooky in my life.
My mom said
that's how girls end up
addicted to
reefer and jazz music.
It's more like how girls end up
at a Best Western hotel
with a 34-year-old guy
named Luther.
Joke?
I can laugh about it now.
So, what do you say?
This Friday we ditch work
and go to Disneyland?
I'm in.
Me, too.
Excuse me,
I thought we were trying to
solve my problem?
Oh, yeah, right.
Wait, what was your problem
again?
I am a man
who can't talk to women,
trying to figure out how to go
on a romantic date
with a girl who suffers
from such crippling
social anxiety she can't be
around other people.
Yeah, that's a toughie.
Let's think.
Hmm.
We doing just Disney
or California Adventure, too?
It's nice
of your old school
to let us try out our science
talk on some female students.
Well, they're
actually pretty excited.
I'm their
most famous alum.
If you don't
count the serial killer
who ate all
those prostitutes.
This must feel
pretty good for you,
coming back to your
alma mater as an astronaut.
Yeah, last time I was here, I
was just a scrawny little nerd.
And now
you're also an astronaut.
So many memories.
I mean, how many
times in these hallways
was I tripped,
punched and spit on?
Oh, look,
here's my old locker.
I have a
masters in engineering
and I still can't figure out
how Scott Kapinski
got me and my briefcase
to fit in there.
Hey.
What?
Nothing.
Smart. We don't
want any problems.
I can't believe I ditched work
for Disneyland.
What did you
tell your boss?
Oh, I was very clever,
I did it in stages.
At 7:00 last night,
I called about
a problem at the lab
and casually mentioned
I was going out for seafood.
At 9:30,
I called and told him that
one of my scallops tasted weird.
At 11:30, I called and said
I was
throwing up like a fire hose.
At 12:45, I called and made
nothing but dry heaving sounds,
and now I'm
going to Disneyland.
Penny, what did you say?
I work at the
Cheesecake Factory,
I said "bye."
So, what are we
gonna do first?
I don't know
about you guys,
but I'm gonna make
a beeline for the place
that gives you
a princess makeover.
Ooh, that sounds like fun.
You're
kidding, right?
We're not just gonna get drunk
and go on rides?
Come on, do it with us.
All right, whatever.
How does it work?
Okay, so,
you pick your princess--
Sleeping Beauty, Snow White
Cinderella--
they give you
hair, makeup, the works.
Guess it would be fun
to be Cinderella.
Oh, I want to be Cinderella, too.
Yeah.
We can't all be Cinderella.
Then how do we decide?
Well, it's simple.
This was my idea.
I'm driving.
I'm Cinderella.
You bitches
got a problem with that,
we could stop the car right now.
Excuse me,
I'm meeting a girl here.
It's kind of our first date.
In a library?
She and I
are both a little awkward
in social situations,
so this seemed like a good idea.
People say
I'm a little awkward, too.
May I join you?
No, you can't join us.
Just go-go climb back up
whatever beanstalk you came
down from.
You can do better.
Oh, we're eating here?
We're having
a texting date?
I love that.
As you're reading,
it will help to remember
I have an adorable accent.
Okay,
who's ready for some science?
Me, too.
Okay, I am
Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
I am here with my friends
Dr. Cooper
and real-life astronaut
Howard Wolowitz,
and we are going
to show you girls
how cool a job
in science can be.
How cool, you ask?
Well, how about
negative 273 degrees,
'cause that's the temperature
at which entropy reaches
its minimum value.
Did I just learn something new
and have fun doing it?
What?
All right!
So now let's bring out
theoretical physicist
Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Hello, female children.
Allow me to inspire you
with a story
about a great female scientist.
Polish-born, French-educated
Madame Curie.
Codiscoverer of
radioactivity,
she was a hero
of science...
until her hair fell out;
her vomit and stool became
filled with blood...
and she was poisoned
to death by her own discovery.
With a little hard work,
I see no reason why
that can't happen to any of you.
Are we done?
Can we go?
The thing to remember is
you can go to outer space, too.
I mean, look at me.
I went to this very school.
Those desks you're sitting in,
I was once superglued
to one of them.
Did you go to the moon?
No, but I did go
to the
International Space Station.
Did you fly the rocket?
No,
but I was in the rocket.
I didn't actually...
So you just flew around?
That's kind of like my uncle.
He's a flight attendant.
No...
I'm an American hero.
Your uncle
brings people nuts, okay?
Boy, we are learning
a lot here, huh?
Thank you, astronaut Howard.
Um, I am what's called
an experimental physicist,
which is super-fun,
because I get to test theories
and work with lasers.
Yes?
How did you decide
to become a scientist?
Uh, excellent question.
Um, I suppose I've always been
into science, you know...
My mother and father
are scientists,
so I was kind of led
in that direction.
Eh, pushed might be
a better way to describe it.
To be honest
with you guys,
when I was your age,
I wanted to be a rap star.
Like Snoop Dogg,
but with a healthy respect
for the police.
Yeah, no, sure, you laugh.
Just like my mother did.
After I confided,
I was derided
and chided,
my moms and I collided.
She said my dreams
were misguided.
That's just a little freestyle.
My dad's a gynecologist
in India,
so if you're over there
and need a check up,
as he likes to say,
he's "at your cervix."
That's terrible.
Your dad should be sent
to the pun-itentiary.
That's a fitting
pun-ishment.
I still don't know
what you do for a living.
Web design.
Anything I might have seen?
I don't know.
You ever look
at porn Web sites?
No, never.
What is porn?
Sorry. Autocorrect.
That was supposed to say
"prom Web sites."
Ooh, fun. I love prom.
The romance, the gowns,
it's like a fairy tale come
to life.
Sorry. Autocorrect.
That was supposed to say,
"I like sports."
I never wanted to play
the cello.
How do you meet girls
playing the cello?
"Hey, you want
to come over to my house
"and listen to me play
an instrument
that sounds like
a suicidal bumblebee?"
Quick,
pull the fire alarm.
Let's get out of here.
Uh, hello again.
Um, yeah, I don't know
if women in general
have been actively discouraged
from pursuing the sciences,
but it's clear you young women
here, today, have been.
While I was listening to
my colleagues waste your time,
it occurred to me that it
might be much more meaningful
to hear about women in science
from actual women in science,
and, uh, I happen to know
two brilliant examples
who have agreed to speak
to you on the phone right now.
Uh, Dr. Rostenkowski,
Dr. Fowler, are you there?
We're here.
Thank you for taking time
out of your very busy schedule
to enlighten these young women.
It's our pleasure.
I'm Dr. Fowler, and
I'm a neuroscientist.
And I'm
Dr. Rostenkowski Wolowitz,
and I'm a microbiologist.
The world of science
needs more women,
but from a young age, we
girls are encouraged to care
more about the way we look
than about the
power of our minds.
That's true.
Every one of you has
the capacity
to be anything you want to be.
Unless you want
to be Cinderella.
Come at me.
See what happens.
This was really fun.
My battery's dying,
so I'm just gonna talk.
Thanks for today.
I've been trying to do
more things that scare me,
and coming here
was definitely one of them.
But it was also really nice.
So thanks, and, um,
I'm gonna go.
Maybe I could do
one more scary thing
before I go
and give you a kiss good-bye?
You know,
if that's okay.
Okay.
Panic attack!
Maybe next time.
I'm counting that as foreplay.
Bernie,
I'm home.
You have fun today?
Yes, and I have a
surprise for you.
Please be Cinderella.
Well, hello, Prince Charming.
Milady.
Hey, how was your... what?
I can explain.
I played hooky with the girls,
then we all went to Disneyland
and got...
What are you doing?
Disneyland. Go on,
I'm listening.
Sheldon, all Snow White needs
is one little kiss to wake up.
Heard you the first time.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net