Howard's capsule
should be reentering
the atmosphere
any minute.
It'll be good to have him back.
The Fantastic Four reunited!
Yeah, you had a good
run, Fake Wolowitz.
We'll remember you
with nostalgic fondness.
The way we do the dial-up modem,
the VHS tape, or...
or Leonard's gym membership.
We're not kicking him out.
Stuart and I have
become good friends.
Okay, one vote for,
one vote against.
Leonard, you're
the tiebreaker.
I don't have a problem
with Stuart.
Besides, he gives us
a 20% discount
at his comic book store.
Well, I don't sell my
friendship that cheaply.
I can go 30.
Welcome aboard,
old chum.
Okay, the NASA Web site says
Howard's final
descent has begun.
He left a boy,
he returns a boy-sized hero.
Loops, calm down!
♪ Baruch atah,
Adonai, Eloheinu ♪
♪ Melech haolam,
hamotzi ♪
♪ Lechem min haaretz... ♪
What's that?
The Jewish prayer
for eating bread!
We don't have one
for falling out of space!
We did it!
We're on the ground!
We survived!
That was just
the parachute.
We still have another
six miles to go.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x04 ♪
The Re-Entry Minimization
Original Air Date on October 18, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Waiting for my husband.
That's nice.
He's coming back
from outer space.
I think this flight's
coming from Houston.
No, I mean, he...
Never mind.
There he is! Howie!
Howie!
Whoa, thank you.
Great to be
back on Earth.
Uh, I think they're
here for me, Ringo.
Howie!
Mr. Mandel, I'm your driver.
Oh, thanks.
Here you go.
That nut job was telling
everybody on the plane
he's an astronaut.
I missed you so much!
I missed you, too.
Oh...
Where are the guys?
Oh, it's just me.
Oh, I get it.
They're waiting back home
with a big surprise party.
Don't worry, I can
act surprised.
No, I told them they could
have you tomorrow night.
Tonight, you belong to me.
Gesundheit.
You okay?
I am now that you're back.
Come on, let's go home
so I can tear off
those little pants.
Great. Just keep in mind
astronauts lose a lot of
muscle tone in space,
so you might have to do
most of the heavy lifting.
You know, I am
very disappointed
that I won't be able
to celebrate
Howard's accomplishment tonight.
Me, too.
But we'll see him tomorrow.
Yes, it's just that
in all the years I've known him,
he's never had the opportunity
to receive my admiration.
I was excited to see
the look on his face
when it finally happened.
You're unbelievable.
I know.
All right,
Pictionary-- what are the teams?
How about
boys versus girls?
Oh!
That hardly seems fair.
But I guess
any team that I'm not on
has a decided disadvantage.
Once again, unbelievable.
Yeah,
once again, I know.
All right, round one.
Here.
Got it.
Okay.
Ready, set,
go.
Uh, box?
Uh,
window?
Batman.
Batman and Robin.
Uh, Wonder Twins
plus the monkey.
Wonder Twins plus
the monkey and Batman.
A gift? Present!
Present! Yeah!
Oh...
Leonard.
Now, how can you not get that?
In what universe
is that a present?
It's not a present,
it's the present. Look.
There's you and me.
It's Penny and Amy.
We're playing Pictionary.
In the present.
Oh, my God, we're
gonna kill them.
It's a quark-gluon plasma.
No.
It's asymptotically free partons
inside a quark-gluon plasma.
Nothing with quarks.
It's an observational rebuttal
of the Lambda-CDM model
of the universe!
No!
It's a chocolate chip cookie!
Yes!
How could you miss that?
Hey, if you want someone to
guess "chocolate chip cookie,"
you draw a glass of milk
next to it.
Penny got it.
Yeah, only after
I eliminated
all the obvious answers.
You're welcome.
Oh, uh, uh, uh, sausage.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, bratwurst?
Oh, oh, a hot dog.
Penny, aren't you gonna
draw something?
Relax, we got time,
this is so fun.
There.
A solar system.
Uh, uh, uh,
uh, um, unidentified
flying liverwurst? I don't...
Now?
Soon.
Come on, Leonard,
I am spoon-feeding this to you.
I don't know,
uh...
Casper the alcoholic ghost?
All right,
that's enough.
Uh, hand.
Uh, nail...
polish?
Yep!
Wait, no, no!
No!
The word is "Polish."
See, look.
Polish sausage.
And the-the model
of the solar system developed
by Nicolaus Copernicus,
a Polish astronomer.
And then, finally,
if that wasn't enough--
which it should've been--
this is Madame Curie
killing herself
by discovering radium, who,
although she was
a naturalized French citizen,
was Polish by birth!
Excuse me,
the word is "polish."
See? Small "P."
Ah!
So it is.
I guess we both
share blame on this one.
Bernie, you okay?
Yeah, I'll be
right there.
Did you get a sea lion
while I was gone?
It's just allergies.
Okay.
Took some Benadryl.
I'll be fine.
So...
did you miss me?
Oh.
Are you kidding?
Every minute of every...
Ew.
Excuse me.
Sweetie, we don't have
to do this now.
Yes, we do.
You left right after
we got married.
This is like
our honeymoon.
Now,
hold on to your hat.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
You okay?
A little dizzy.
Must be the Benadryl.
Switch places with me.
Okay.
Now...
...kiss me!
Bernadette?
Bernie?
That was amazing.
You made me feel things
I never...
Well, that was quick
and a little gross.
Now, I know how she feels.
Hey, Sheldon, you're always
full of fun little facts.
Where did the expression
"got your ass handed to you"
come from?
Don't know.
I wonder if it's from,
like, ancient Rome
where they'd actually
chop somebody's ass off
and then go, "Here."
You know, to appease
Loseroneous, the god of losers.
I am not a loser.
Pictionary is not a true test of
any real intelligence or skill.
Mmm, in all
fairness,
Pictionary has verbal
skills, visual skills.
It's a pretty well-rounded game.
Lot of big talk
from a man
who can't draw
a chocolate chip cookie.
All right, fine,
pick another game.
Amy and I will beat
you at anything.
All right.
Let's play...
Physics Fiesta.
Oh, come on, what is that?
It's a game
that I just invented,
in which the participants
answer physics questions
in remedial Spanish.
Um...
¿Dónde está el boson de Higgs?
En el acelerador
de particulares.
Bueno, mi amigo.
No, no, we're not playing
some dumb made-up game.
All games
are made up.
They're not found in nature.
You don't just dig in
the ground, come across
a rich vein
of Rock'em Sock'em Robots.
Just pick
another game.
Why don't we do
something athletic
like go over to the university
pool and play water polo?
No good--
Sheldon doesn't float.
That is true.
I have a higher than
normal body density.
If I run too deep a bath,
I drown.
All right,
let's keep it simple.
How about darts?
Oh, that's not fair either.
Why not?
Darts is a bar game.
You've been frequenting
drinking establishments
since you were of legal age.
Yeah, that's
when it started.
Well, regardless, she
has a distinct advantage
in all tavern-
based competitions.
Pool, beer pong, wet T-shirt
contests-- they're all out.
Okay.
Just for the record,
I have never entered
a wet T-shirt contest.
I've won a few, but that's just
because I spill when I'm drunk,
so...
We could go
to the cadaver lab at UCLA
and play real-life Operation.
Uh-uh.  No.
I don't think so.
Are you sure? I mean,
the nose doesn't light up,
but if the corpse
is fresh enough,
sometimes you can get
the leg to jerk.
Hey, Ma, twinkle, twinkle,
your little star is home!
Ma, the chain's on the door!
Howard?
I thought I wasn't going
to see you till tomorrow!
Yeah, well,
Bernie's not feeling well,
so I thought I'd stop by,
tell you about the greatest
adventure of my life,
see if you can make me feel bad
about it.
Uh, uh, okay, hold
on, I'm not decent!
All right.
Woman hasn't tied her robe
in 20 years.
Suddenly she's not decent?
You want me to hide in the
closet or go out the back?!
Shh, you need to whisper.
Ma, who is in there?
Uh, nobody!
The TV is on!
I only got one sock.
Where's my
other sock?
Who is that?
I told you, it's the TV.
Jay Leno lost a sock;
it's hilarious.
If you're busy, I can come back.
Just give me
a second!
Go, go, go, go.
Dr. Schneider?
Oh, hello, Howard.
What are you doing here?
Um, house call.
You're a dentist.
Yes, yes, I am.
I think he's
on to us!
Okay, glasses off.
Find Waldo.
Hurry up,
find him, find him.
I'm trying!
Don't yell at me!
For goodness' sake,
he's wearing
a hat, glasses,
and a red striped shirt.
I know what he looks like.
Oh, there he
is, I got him.
Yes, we
win again!
How could you not find him?
Because he's hard to find.
If he was easy to find,
the books would be called
There's Waldo.
57, 58, 59,
that's one minute.
Long division,
long division.
Go, go, go.
Remember,
show your work.
I'm okay.
I'm not okay.
Get up, we can't lose in math.
37!
Yes!
Aah!
Ready, set, wrestle.
One, two, three, pin.
Mwah!
Stop that.
Amy, do something.
Mwah.
Amy, help.
W-- Amy, stop that.
Amy, Penny,
both of you, stop it.
One to beam aboard?
Oh, my God, you're back.
Oh, look at you.
You, you look
like you grew.
Yeah.
The lack of gravity
did decompress my spine,
so I'm like
an inch and a half taller.
I'm going to the DMV tomorrow
to get my license changed
before I shrink back.
Oh, uh, come in, come in.
Oh, I, uh, I didn't think
I was going to get
to see you until tomorrow.
Yeah, well,
Bernadette's a little
under the weather
and my mom's
kind of under my dentist.
Wait, your, your mother
is sleeping with your dentist?
Former dentist.
I need a new one now that I know
where his hands have been.
So you're wandering
all around by yourself?
That's not the kind
of hero's welcome
an astronaut should
come home to.
It's okay, you know,
we space cowboys
don't do what we do
for glory and fame.
We leave that to your rock stars
and your athletes
and your Howie Mandels.
Oh, hey, man, welcome back.
Oh, Stuart, thanks.
What are you doing here?
I, I kind of live here now.
Just until he gets
back on his feet,
which are looking pretty good
in the boots I bought him
for his birthday.
Ah, he's spoiling
me and I love it.
Wow, so you guys
are like buds now?
Oh, yeah, we hang out
all the time.
Plus, he doesn't
have a girlfriend,
I don't have
a girlfriend.
It's like we both had
these holes
in our lives, but now we fill
each other's holes.
Uh...
that sounds a little
funny to an American ear.
Which part?
Just all of it.
Okay,
so w-what do you guys
got going on tonight?
Raj is taking me to the
Sound of Music sing-along.
Sound of Music sing-along?
That used to be our thing,
but that's cool.
Oh, Howard,
it's still our thing.
Come with us, we'll, we'll
get you a scalped ticket.
So I'd be sitting by myself?
We'll switch.
You'll come sit with me
after intermission.
So I-I-I'd be sitting by myself
during "Edelweiss"?
No, no,
you guys go.
Have fun.
Okay, uh, will I get
to see you tomorrow?
Absolutely.
See you, Stuart.
Yeah, yeah.
Is he taller?
At least my mother made her
boyfriend climb out the window.
All right, standard state fair
pie-eating contest rules are:
no hands, first one
to clean the pan wins.
On the count of three.
One, two...
Wait.
I'm a little concerned.
Blueberries are rich
in antioxidants.
So?
So, with all those antioxidants,
what if I run out of oxidants?
Sheldon, we haven't won
a game all night.
Now, you either stick
your face in that pie
or I'm gonna stick
that pie in your face.
That's rude.
One, two, three, eat.
Hey, guys,
guess who's back from space.
Not now!
Oh, ow, blueberry
in my nose,
blueberry in my nose!
Snort it down
and keep eating!
You look familiar.
I don't think so.
Yeah, I just saw you
on the news.
You're an astronaut.
Yes.
Yes, I am.
Good for you.
How about a piece
of cheesecake on the house?
Oh, thank you so much.
I've been having
the worst night.
I just got back,
and my friends don't care,
my wife's sick,
I went to my mom...
You want
the cheesecake or not?
Yes, please.
♪ And I think it's gonna be
a long, long time ♪
♪ Till touchdown brings me
'round again to find ♪
♪ I'm not the man
they think I am at home ♪
♪ Oh, no, oh, no ♪
♪ I'm a rocket man. ♪
Perfect.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net