I was reading about this
jellyfish that never dies.
Instead, it reverts
to its asexual state
and then grows up again.
We thought my 90-year-old
grandfather had reverted
to an asexual state,
but the lawsuit
from his Jamaican caregiver
proved us all wrong.
My point is, immortality is not
only a possibility, it is real.
Only if you're this
jellyfish which periodically
reverts to a mass of
undifferentiated protoplasm.
If I could keep
my Gmail account,
I'd be okay with that.
- Hello, fellas.
- Hey.
Remember when we were trying
to figure out what that smell
coming from Professor
Tupperman's office was?
Yeah?
Turns out it was Tupperman.
Dead at his desk for two weeks.
Oh, my God.
That's terrible.
In lieu of flowers,
the department chair
is asking that everyone donate
a bottle of Febreze.
If we're going to change
the topic from jellyfish,
I'd be okay with brine shrimp
or the history of the unicycle.
Show a little compassion--
a man died.
And turned into a puddle of goo.
Now, we can either
sit around and cry
over spilt professor, or...
we can rejoice in the knowledge
that a tenured position
has just opened up.
I choose to do
the latter.
Excuse me, the whole tenure
system is ridiculous.
A guaranteed job for life
only encourages the faculty
to become complacent.
If we really
want science
to advance, people should have
chips implanted in their skulls
that explode when they say
something stupid.
Well, I believe people
do their best work
when they feel
safe and secure.
If you need my nose,
you'll find it firmly lodged
up the rectum of the
tenure committee.
You Ph.D's gonna go
suck up like Kripke?
No.
I mean, I'll apply,
but I'm not gonna stoop
to playing politics.
Yeah, me neither.
It should be about the work.
And if I can't get tenure,
I'd like to see you
or Sheldon get it.
Raj, don't dangle
false hope
in front of Leonard like that.
Excuse me, but I think I'm
just as qualified as you are.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x20 ♪
The Tenure Turbulence
Original Air Date on April 4, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
So "tenured" means
a job for life?
Yup.
And you can't get fired
even if you're bad at it?
Mm, not really.
Wow, sounds a lot like being
a pretty waitress
at the Cheesecake Factory.
While I disagree
with the premise of tenure,
if they gave it to me,
it wouldn't diminish my output.
You know, I'm like the sun.
Can't turn this off.
Are Rajesh and Leonard
competing for it as well?
Mm-hmm.
Do they know they
don't stand a chance
'cause you're so great?
Well put.
You know, I must say
I go back and forth
on this boyfriend-girlfriend
thing, but those moments
when you worship me
really keep you in the running.
It would be nice to have
the increased income.
Stop taking money
from my parents.
Money from family does come
with strings attached.
You have no idea.
They buy me a new BMW
for my birthday
but can I get seat warmers?
No.
"Rajesh, if you
want a warm butt,
you're gonna have
to pay for it yourself."
Well, maybe I will, old man!
I think that's
enough wine for now.
I just keep thinking
about how cool it would be
if I called my mom and told her
that I got tenure at Caltech.
She'd be proud, huh?
Oh, very.
Assuming she takes my call.
My primary concern
with being granted tenure
is living with an insanely
jealous roommate after the fact.
I might need to sleep
with a gun under my pillow.
Or a chainsaw.
Or you take advantage of your
newfound economic stability
and move out...
buy a house...
get married...
start a family.
Yeah, or...
the chainsaw.
And I will return
to New Delhi in triumph
atop a bejeweled white elephant!
And you know
what will be
on that elephant's back?
A seat warmer.
"No, Father, you may not
have a ride!"
I'm gonna make some coffee.
So, who do you have to schmooze
to get this deal?
I'm not gonna schmooze anybody.
I'm gonna let my work
speak for itself.
That's great.
That shows a lot of integrity.
Thank you.
I'm a naive idiot, right?
Oh, good, you heard me.
You know, if you
really want tenure,
maybe you should cozy up to
the people making the decision.
Sheldon Cooper
does not do "cozy."
You don't say.
But I suppose
it wouldn't hurt
to know who's
on the committee.
Let's see...
Oh, Janine Davis.
Oh, dear.
Is that a problem?
Well...
Yeah, even you.
You're a slave.
I'm a what?
I'm not sure;
it could go either way.
Hey. Mrs. Davis.
Hey.
Dr. Hofstadter.
Yeah.
Just thought I'd come down
and start getting ready
for swimsuit season.
Good for you.
Eh.
Not that you need it.
I bet you look great
in a swimsuit.
Thank you.
I've got what my father used
to call "furniture disease."
My chest is falling
into my drawers.
I'm not, uh, familiar
with this model.
How do I make it start?
You push start.
Right.
This one might be broken.
You have to move.
Got it.
Oh.
There.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, now I'm feeling it.
Oh, this is great.
I could do this
for the rest of my life.
Hey, speaking...
speaking of things you do
for the rest of your life...
uh, did I read that you're
on that-that tenure committee?
Yep.
I got to get a home gym.
Well, I'm sure you have
a lot of good applicants, I just
wanted to say hi and...
let you know that I'll be...
throwing my hat in the...
...ring.
All right, I'll keep
an eye out for that.
Yeah.
Hey, Hofstadter.
Funny seeing you here
for the first time in...
ever.
Go... away.
Janine the Machine,
let's do this!
Hey, Barry.
Well, look at that.
Burned a whole calorie.
I guess you got here
early to burn off that
banana bread I baked you.
Yeah, it was delicious.
Thank you.
No, my pleasure.
Oh, if you... if you
like banana bread...
I've got a-a great recipe.
The trick
is in... in fresh ground...
I'll e-mail it to you.
All right, I'm warm.
Ready to kick it up a notch?
Let's go.
That's enough cardio for me.
I'm just... gonna stretch out
before I hit the weights.
You okay?
Call someone!
Good day, Mrs. Davis.
This is Dr. Rajesh
Koothrappali
from the astrophysics
department.
Don't be alarmed,
I'm not really in space.
Anyhoo...
I'd like to take
this opportunity
to tell you about myself,
so sit back, relax and enjoy
the following 90-minute video.
Oh, come on.
Born in New Delhi,
the third son
of an itinerant gynecologist,
I showed early
signs of genius.
At the age of five,
I discovered a celestial object
which later turned out
to be the moon.
Mrs. Davis?
Mrs. Davis? Mrs. Davis?
God, they're everywhere.
Come in.
Dr. Cooper,
how can I help you?
Yes, hello. I'm fine. Um...
I understand you may have
a bad impression of me,
so I bought you a gift.
Uh, Dr. Cooper,
that's not necessary.
It's too late.
Get ready to like me.
Roots?
The tragic history
of slavery in America.
Fun for the whole family.
Why would you think
this is an appropriate gift?
Um...
Well...
You are black, right?
This meeting has come to an end.
Because you want to start
watching it right now.
Copy that.
Let's see.
Up next
on the tenure committee is...
Professor Wu.
Well, get ready for the complete
works of Jackie Chan.
Gentlemen.
Where have
you been?
Nurse's office.
Asthma attack?
Asthma, heart--
some kind of attack.
I'm fine, though.
You guys going
to Professor Tupperman's
memorial?
I don't know.
Probably not.
Barely knew him.
Yeah, you wouldn't want to look
like you guys are brown-nosing
the tenure committee,
who will all be there.
Oh, yeah, that's what
I was hoping for-- meerkats.
I won't be able to make our
date night this Thursday, so...
bad news for you.
You better have a
good excuse this time,
because "trimming Q-tips
to fit your ears right"
is obvious nonsense.
First of all,
when you say things like that,
people think you're crazy.
Second, the reason
I'm cancelling is because
I have to attend a memorial
service for Professor Tupperman.
It sounds like a long
and tedious evening.
Eh, it will be.
Honestly, if I must endure
a long and tedious evening,
I'd rather it be
with you on date night.
But I have no choice.
The tenure committee's
going to be there.
Oh! Well, in that case,
perhaps I should come along.
Well, now that I think about it,
that would be most helpful.
Of course it would.
I'm well-versed in
academic politics,
and as a respected scientist,
I can only raise your
stock as a candidate.
Actually, I meant
you could drive me.
But if it makes you happy,
that other stuff, too.
Do anything
interesting today?
Oh, not really.
I was out shopping with Amy.
She wanted me
to help her find something
for this memorial thing.
Wait--
Sheldon's going to be there?
We all promised
we weren't going to go.
Oh, what a jerk.
I know.
I was hoping to go
without anyone finding out.
Well, since Amy's going,
do you want me there?
You know, to support you?
Oh...
that's nice,
but it-it's just gonna be
a room full of boring old men
and I'm not sure
how much help you'd be.
Okay.
I'm just gonna tie my shoe
while you think about that.
Oh, yeah. No.
Thanks, that would
be great help.
You realize
you might kill some of them.
Oh, then you all can get tenure.
Come on, Daddy.
All the other scientists
have seat warmers.
This is so humiliating.
I've got to get tenure.
Okay, l-let's meet halfway.
How about I cut my cleaning
lady down to twice a week?
Looks like we're both going
to be living like animals.
Let's go over our emotional
responses one last time.
Okay.
Professor Tupperman is dead,
and that makes us...?
Sad.
The fact that there
are so many people
here tonight doesn't make us
cranky and claustrophobic.
It makes us...?
Glad.
Giving Mrs. Davis the box set
of Roots was...?
Bad.
However...
No.
Fine. Bad.
Unbelievable.
You have some nerve
showing up here
just to schmooze
with the tenure committee.
You're here.
Excuse me.
I'm here to pay my respects
to Professor... Tupperware,
or whatever his name is.
So am I.
His passing makes
me feel... bad.
Well, well, well, Sheldon,
fancy meeting you here.
I guess the train store
in Glendale
wasn't having a cotillion
after all.
And you-- you said
you weren't coming here, either.
I have a thick accent.
You don't know what I said.
I'd like to know
why Penny's here.
I'm here to support
my man, just like you.
What are you going to do?
Take people's drink orders
and get them wrong?
Do it.
What? Did she do it yet?
She plans on flirting with
members of the tenure committee
to further
Leonard's cause.
Well, that's a fine
how-do-you-do.
Don't just stand there.
Take your breasts out.
Ooh, meerkat fight!
You're all
wasting your time.
Sheldon is the most
qualified for the job,
and no amount of gravity-defying
bosom's going to change that.
Seriously, is that tape?
Like, how are they
staying up like that?
Way to hit 'em
with both barrels.
You two should be
ashamed of yourselves.
Using women to advance
your cause with sexuality,
and whatever Amy plans on doing.
Are you implying
that my girlfriend has
no sexuality to exploit?
Yes!
Okay, because
that was not clear.
Sheldon!
What?
That was ambiguous.
Well, now it's biguous.
What are you gonna do about it?
Um...
You could talk some smack
about his mother.
Well, yes, of course,
he wouldn't like that at all.
Last night,
I was feeling in need
of sexual release
when I happened
to come across your mother.
Okay, okay.
Guys, what are we doing here?
I don't know what you're doing,
but I was about to insinuate
that I had coitus
with Raj's mother for a dollar.
Oh, you do
what you want,
but I don't want to lose
my friends over tenure.
Friends are forever.
So is tenure.
Walk!
I'm just gonna go home and
let my work speak for itself.
You're right.
This is beneath me.
Like your mother was last night.
How about it, Sheldon?
What do you think
I should do?
Well, you'll always be
an academic success,
but...
I seriously question
whether you'll make
any more friends.
I don't want any more,
but let's go.
Are you kidding? I would
"wove" to baby-sit for you.
I could not ask
you to do that.
Nonsense.
Children "wove" me.
Something about me just makes
them "waugh" and "waugh."
No. We cannot lose
to that jerk.
Yeah, screw it.
I'm going in.
You... Wait. Hold on.
I believe "Screw it,
I'm going in" is what
I said to your
mother last night.
Don't worry, I didn't
really say that.
I-I find the concept
of coitus ridiculous
and off-putting.
Should have taken my breasts out
while I had the chance.
Mrs. Davis?
I know you're in there.
I saw your car
in the parking lot.
What?
I just found out
that you recommended myself,
Dr. Hofstadter
and Dr. Koothrappali
to be on the short list
for tenure.
Well, despite your quirks,
the three of you
are very accomplished
in your respective fields.
I don't know what you mean
by "quirks," but, um...
...I do want
to express my gratitude.
You didn't bring
another gift, did you?
No, no.
No, I learned my lesson.
I understand
that was inappropriate.
Good.
Anyway, thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm gonna pretend
that didn't happen.
Yeah, right on, sister.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net