Burbank Airport, please.
Vegas, here we come!
No husbands,
no boyfriends, no rules.
No rules?
We're not gonna get drunk
and have a six-way
with the Blue Man Group, are we?
No.
So there are some rules.
Fine.
No husbands, no boyfriends,
some rules.
Thank you.
Vegas!
The ladies are away,
the boys will play.
Anything can happen.
It's gonna get crazy.
Dungeons & Dragons!
I got a brand-new bikini,
so drinks at the pool
are on these.
I got a sexy new tube top
that says "Come hither"
and a can of pepper spray
that says "Close enough, Jack."
I got some old underwear
I'm gonna throw on stage
at the Garth Brooks concert.
I'm sorry, why old?
'Cause last time I saw him,
I threw new ones
and it got me nothing.
I've got a brand-new
seven piece set
of polyhedral dice.
Hello, new dice smell.
I've got my helm
of lordly might,
my boots of speed,
and if things get too exciting,
my inhaler of asthma.
I got my new bloodthirsty
savage warrior
who will lay waste to all
who stand before him.
And I had a sensible salad
for lunch,
so I can eat
all the pizza I want.
Come on, are we
gonna sit around
chatting like a bunch
of teenage girls,
or are we gonna play D & D
like a bunch of teenage boys
who are never gonna have sex
with those teenage girls?!
Vegas! Vegas! Vegas!
The Dungeon
of Mofooskay-Heeko!
The Dungeon of
Mofooskay-Heeko!
The Dungeon
of Mofooskay-Heeko!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x23 ♪
The Love Spell Potential
Original Air Date on May 9, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
I'm actually glad
Lucy had to work tonight.
Saved me the awkward
conversation about how I was
gonna be hanging with my bros.
Isn't every conversation
you two have awkward?
Eh?
Painfully so.
We have this rule on the phone
that if no one talks
for three minutes,
you can just hang up.
So into her.
Ready whenever
you guys are.
Yeah, yeah, we'll
be right there.
Yeah, Leonard...
Yeah?
I'm not sure how I feel
about Howard being
dungeon master instead of you.
Oh, that's nice.
But relax,
sometimes change is good.
Uh, you were worried
about Zachary Quinto
being the new Spock,
but you wound up liking him.
Oh, please.
Every time the topic
of change comes up,
you throw Zachary
Quinto in my face.
I'm upset the mailman
has a new haircut:
Zachary Quinto.
I'm upset that daylight
saving time started:
Zachary Quinto.
I'm upset daylight saving time
ended: Zachary Quinto.
I'm saying this
for the last time:
Zachary Quinto was
a weird, wonderful,
unrepeatable event.
So stop using
him against me.
Okay, here we go.
You find yourselves in
an overgrown old forest.
Before you is a giant oak tree
with a face on it that looks
a lot like Nicolas Cage.
He says,
"Travel with caution.
"These woods are home
to the bones
"of many a fallen...
hero!"
See, Howard's just as good
a dungeon master as I am.
As good?
You just got pantsed
in the schoolyard, four-eyes.
Hey, come on, guys, focus.
Um, uh...
Oh, mighty Nicolas Cage tree,
we thank you
for your warning,
but we are brave warriors,
and nothing short of death
will keep us from our goal.
Oh, Lucy's free after all.
See ya.
Hey, hey, hey,
you can't leave.
We just started.
You're right,
I should finish the game.
I take my plus-one long sword,
stab myself in the face with it.
I'm dead, I've got
a date with a girl.
Bye.
We'll be fine, watch.
Suddenly, a spectral shape
rises from Koothrappali's
bloody corpse, and says,
"Don't worry, buddies,
"Ghost Raj will help
guide you through the forest."
"Well, I'm just
"a tree, but if I were you,
I'd listen to your
ghost friend!"
Go on, give him
your lunch money.
I'm very happy you were able
to hang out tonight.
Me, too.
Not that it's up to you
to make me happy.
Uh, well, unless
you find neediness sexy.
In which case,
you're about to have dinner
with the hottest man
on the planet.
Can I tell you something?
I was so nervous
about seeing you,
before I left my apartment,
I put roll-on antiperspirant
all over my body.
Really?
Yeah.
If sweat starts squirting
out the top of my head,
you'll know why.
I, uh, I'm sorry
to put you through that.
Oh, it's okay.
I've been trying
to force myself
to do things that
make me scared.
What else have you been
thinking about doing?
Well, let's see.
I'd love to be able to tell
the lady who cuts my hair
that I don't like bangs.
I like your bangs.
Oh, thanks, I
like 'em, too.
What else?
Mm...
it's kind of a tie
between sending food back
in a restaurant and
saying no to those kids
who sell magazines
door-to-door.
Mm, yeah.
Those are both toughies.
I know.
I have a two-year
subscription to Guns & Ammo.
I push my shoulder
against the secret door
to see if it gives way.
Uh...
it does.
He does sound
effects, too!
Hey, I always did sound effects.
A-A swarm of bloodthirsty bats
fly through the dungeon.
Uh, uh, they attack
a nearby unicorn.
Okay, well, I have a sound
effect for those sound effects.
Guess who!
What are you doing back?
That's an excellent
question. Amy?
Uh, well...
when we were going
through security,
I got pulled
out of line for a pat-down.
The, uh,
TSA agent got
a little handsy...
I may have broken
her nose with my elbow.
Long story short,
she's on the No Fly List
and we might have been
followed here by a drone.
I'm sorry.
I feel like such an idiot.
Oh, it's not so bad.
You lost money, you're
filled with shame
and you got groped
by a stranger.
I mean, that's Vegas,
you nailed it.
You guys enjoy your evening.
I'm gonna go before I ruin
anybody else's weekend.
That's my girl.
No, no.
Amy, wait. Uh, uh,
I know it's not
the night you had in mind,
but why don't you guys stay
and play with us?
It'll be fun.
It would-- fun?
Yeah, okay,
three weeks ago,
you bought crunchy
peanut butter,
but now you want the
girls to play D & D--
do you have a
drug problem?
What's the big deal?
Raj bailed, so we could
use some extra players.
Well, I've just never
played Dungeons & Dragons
with girls before.
Oh, don't worry, sweetie.
No one has.
So, what do you say?
I'll leave it up to
the dungeon master.
Yeah, a... satanic fungus
that looks suspiciously
like Al Pacino
rises from the forest floor
and says,
"You're playing D & D.
"You're playing
D & D.
"This whole apartment...
...is playing D & D."
Okay, who wants a drink?
Yeah, we-- now, Penny,
we don't consume alcohol
during Dungeons & Dragons.
It impairs our judgment.
Oh, this isn't alcohol.
It's a magic potion
that makes me like you.
Double potion, please.
Okay, here we go.
You find yourselves
face-to-face
with two hulking ogres.
"What are you doing
"in our dungeon?
You shall die!"
Okay, literal
goose bumps.
Look.
What do you do?
I draw my broadsword.
I ready my
quarter-staff.
I drink my potion.
- I say we attack the big one.
- You know what?
Give me the dice,
I want to roll.
Well, the dungeon master's
supposed to roll.
Yeah, well I'm supposed
to be in Vegas
throwing up on a shrimp buffet.
Now give it.
All right,
what do I need?
Uh, 15 or higher.
15's the point, the point is 15.
Give the little lady some room,
here it is, coming out.
Sixteen!
Yes!
Oh, please tell me
we're playing for money.
Oh, even better than money.
You gained experience points.
More potion, please.
Yeah.
How are
your crab cakes?
Kind of funky.
That's great.
It is?
Does "funky" mean
something different in India?
No, no. Uh, you've always
wanted to send your food back
in a restaurant;
here's your chance.
Mm.
It's okay. I just won't eat 'em.
Don't be ridiculous. Waiter?
Everything all right?
Uh... yeah.
Everything all right with you?
Yes.
'Kay, thanks, bye.
Hold on.
Isn't there something else
you wanted to tell him?
N-No, it-it's fine. Uh...
He's from a different country;
he doesn't understand our ways.
Don't be silly. Just tell him.
I have to go to the bathroom.
And it's not because
the crab cakes are funky.
So you're okay here?
Uh, yeah, sorry.
She's just a little shy.
The-the first time we met,
she was so nervous,
she climbed out a bathroom
window to get away from me.
Uh-oh.
Hey, Raj.
Funny story.
Come on, mama wants a
pair of dead ogres!
17! The larger ogre is dead!
The-the other ogre says,
"You killed my brother.
Now Ogre Thanksgiving
is ruined."
That is amazing.
He made me care
about the ogre!
All right, Amy,
there's one ogre left.
Take him out!
Okay.
Pretend he's that
TSA agent. Come on.
Nineteen!
Yes!
This is turning out to be
even better than Vegas!
No, it's not!
Lucy?
Oh, hey.
Long time no see.
You don't know me very well,
but each time you crawl out
a bathroom window
to escape my company,
it chips away at my masculinity.
I'm sorry.
Why would you leave like that?
You were pushing me;
I clearly didn't want
to send my food back, and you
tried to make me do it anyway.
Okay, if I upset you, then why
didn't you just say something?
Well, how can I tell you I'm
upset if I can't tell the woman
at Supercuts that my forehead's
my best feature?
It's scary.
Yeah, well, I like you a lot,
and that's scary for me.
Mostly because
you're a proven flight risk.
How could you like me a lot?
Well, uh, for one thing,
you have bigger
emotional problems than I do,
and I find that
very attractive in a woman!
I-I don't know. I just...
I think you're wonderful.
I'm sweating out of my head.
The dragon falls from the sky,
crashing into the volcano!
But wait!
He's not dead.
He crawls out,
spreads his wings
and prepares to attack.
Yeah, uh, wait!
Doesn't he say
something first?
You know, maybe in the voice
of a beloved celebrity?
Fine.
"You'd think, after all these years,
"I'd know not to fly
over volcanoes.
I'm a freaking idiot."
The dragon's
Christopher Walken!
That's perfect.
All right, Amy,
it's your turn.
We need one more hit.
Finish him off!
Here we go.
Fifteen?
It's a hit. The dragon collapses
to the ground!
Wait.
And says...
"Mother?
"Is that you?
Your little boy is coming home."
Oh, I don't know about you
guys, but I have been through
the emotional
wringer tonight.
This may be the potion
talking, but you are
one fine-ass dungeon master.
Oh, yeah?
Well, when we get home,
I'm gonna take you
on a whole different adventure.
Another quest
by Wolowitz?
Count me in.
Sheldon, they're talking
about sex.
Oh, then I'm out.
Ooh! I have an idea.
Since it's not happening
anytime soon,
why don't your character
and your character
do it in the game?
Ooh!
Come on, back
me up here.
Oh.
Ooh!
Okay, I cast a love spell
on Sheldon and Amy.
Oo... Sorry, I thought
you were gonna do that...
The love spell takes effect.
When Sheldon looks
at Amy, she is the most
beautiful half-orc
he's ever seen,
and he's overcome
with a desire
to rip her armor off
and gaze fondly
at her four hairy breasts.
When Amy sees Sheldon,
he looks...
well, just like Sheldon, 'cause
apparently she's into that.
What do you do?
I don't like this.
You see what happens
when you let girls play D & D?
Amy.
What?
I've never knocked
on my own door before.
That was a wild ride.
You don't have to come in here
and cheer me up.
Thank you.
Would you go tell
everyone else that?
Because they sure think
otherwise.
I'll tell you what they think.
They think our relationship
is a joke.
Well, I don't think
our relationship is a joke.
I think
"a horse goes into a bar,
bartender says,
'Why the long face?'"
That's a joke.
It's a good one, too,
because a horse has a long face.
Sheldon,
are we ever going to have
an intimate relationship?
Oh, my.
That's an uncomfortable topic.
Amy...
fore I met you,
I never had any interest
in being intimate with anyone.
And now?
And now what?
Do you have any interest now?
I have not ruled it out.
Wow.
Talk dirty to me.
I know it doesn't seem
like it to you, but,
for me, what we have
is extremely intimate.
I guess I know that.
It's just...
part of me wants more.
More?
I mean, look at us.
It's only been three years;
here we are in bed together.
Come on.
Let's go back out there.
Y... Well, no.
Hold on.
My Elven magic-user
and your half-orc warrior
did have a love spell
cast on them.
We wouldn't really
be playing the game right
if we didn't see that through.
Okay.
I believe that, uh,
we just killed a dragon.
While the others
pillage the corpse,
I lead you
to a secluded area
where I attempt
to remove your leather armor.
It comes off.
Oh.
What do you do?
I...
...kiss you... on the lips.
I kiss you back on the...
...lips as well.
Your turn.
I... remove your armor.
What do you do?
I... erotically caress your...
...nose.
Keep rolling.
Hey, you guys have been
in there for a while.
- You doing okay?
- We're fine, thank you.
Okay, we just want to say,
we feel really bad about...
Go away! Sheldon
is nibbling on my...
14! Yes!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net