Oh, dear.
Penny, have you been
recording shows
on our DVR again?
No.
Answer honestly.
This is not a trial.
That'll come later.
Absolutely not.
Help me out here.
I can't afford another demerit.
Yeah.
Uh... maybe we were hacked.
You know, the Chinese have been
hacking everything lately.
Why would the Chinese make our
DVR record Paul Blart: Mall Cop?
I don't know.
It's a fat guy on a Segway.
That's funny everywhere.
I'm deleting it.
Well, hang on.
Maybe the Chinese haven't
finished watching it yet.
You know, if you're trying
to make space on the DVR,
why don't you just get rid of
some of the stuff
you've already watched?
Like, um... Alphas.
No, that's
the season two finale.
That was quite the cliffhanger.
I'm going to re-watch it
before season three starts.
There is no season three.
They canceled that show.
Well, they can't cancel it.
It ended on a cliffhanger.
- They did.
- Uh, Sheldon,
there are two dumplings left.
Do you want them?
Dumplings?
Don't you understand
what's going on here?
As a rule, no.
That show ended with all
the residents of New York
either dead or unconscious.
Now I'll never know
what happened.
Well, why don't you
make up your own ending?
Oh, sure, what a wonderful idea.
And after that,
I'll make up my own rules
of oral hygiene.
You know, instead of flossing,
I'll rub pudding on my gums.
I'm going to get the number
of the SyFy Channel
and give them what for.
Oh, please, don't do that.
No. They can't just cancel
a show like Alphas.
You know? They have to help
the viewers let go.
Firefly did a movie
to wrap things up.
Buffy the Vampire Slayer
continued on as a comic book.
Heroes gradually lowered
the quality season by season
till we were grateful it ended.
I feel bad for whoever
gets that phone call.
Ah, don't.
If they didn't want to be
yelled at by crazy nerds,
they shouldn't have started
a sci-fi channel.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x21 ♪
The Closure Alternative
Original Air Date on April 25, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
I think you're gonna
be really happy
with this security camera.
The optics are great,
it's got infrared technology,
and there's even
a backup battery
when the power goes out.
Whatever.
I can see my little princess
while I'm at work, right?
Why can't you just watch porn
like a regular guy?
I need your laptop so I can
configure the software.
Wait, hold on.
This is weird.
What?
I was Googling that girl
I've been dating,
and I found her blog.
Cool.
Anything juicy?
She said she recently
went on a date
with a guy named Roger?
And he's Indian?
And he's an astrophysicist, too?
You know what's going on,
don't you?
Yes.
Mummy was right.
American girls are
sexually voracious devils.
I can't believe
I have to explain this.
People change names on blogs
to protect their privacy.
Roger is Raj.
Oh.
I always thought,
if I had a white name,
it would be Gavin.
Keep reading.
What does it say?
No, no, I don't know
if I should.
If she wanted me to know about
her blog, she would've told me.
It's almost like
I'm reading her diary.
That's exactly what it's like.
Keep reading.
No, this is creepy.
Oh, I think we were looking
at creepy in the rearview mirror
when I put up that camera.
It's not creepy.
Don't listen to him.
Oh, look who's got
the sweetest kisses.
Should I go?
With all the TV Sheldon
was talking about,
I had the greatest idea ever.
It even blows away my idea
for a Star Wars themed coffee
shop called "Brewbacca's."
You need to watch
Buffy the Vampire Slayer.
It is the perfect show
for the two of us.
It's got action and jokes
and hot vampires and romance.
I cannot oversell this!
What do you say?
It's 6:30 in the morning.
I thought you
grew up on a farm.
Hello, SyFy Network?
Yeah, this is your
vice president of programming.
Now, we have made a horrible
mistake regarding Alphas.
Yeah, we need to uncancel it
immediately.
Well, you just put me through
to the people who handle that,
you tell them it's me,
and I don't want to answer
a lot of questions
about if I really am
who I say I am, you know?
I just... I want this done.
No, I am not the person
who just called.
That man was clearly a cowboy.
Yeah, who was plumb concerned
about y'all canceling
his favorite show.
Why do they keep
hanging up on me?
I'm sorry you're upset.
You know, Sheldon, sometimes
people seek the comfort
of physical contact
in moments like this.
I am not flying
back to Texas
just so my mom
can give me a hug.
Okay.
Well, what I think
is going on here
is you have a pathological
need for closure.
Oh, that's nonsense.
I mean, you tell me stories
about your day all the time.
I don't care how they end.
You know, I might be able
to help you with this.
There's a whole field
of behavioral neuroscience
that examines ways to retrain
your neural pathways
so stuff like this
bothers you less.
Yeah, but I just told you,
I don't have a problem
with closure.
You sure about that?
Oh, quite sure.
That proves nothing.
Ready to go to lunch?
Do you think I'm feminine?
Yeah. Let's go.
Thanks a lot.
What's going on?
I broke down,
and I read Lucy's blog.
And in one
of the entries,
she said, when we first met,
I struck her
as a little feminine.
Just a little?
That's great.
I have to talk to her
about this.
Oh, geez, why do you girls
always want to talk
about things?
Listen to me,
if she's writing
about your relationship,
use it to your advantage.
Rig the game.
Well, that doesn't seem fair.
Is it fair that girls
like confident, normal guys
more than nervous weirdos?
No, it's not.
I've always thought
that was unfair.
So take what's
in that blog
and use it to get
her pants off.
Why do you have to make
everything so filthy?
Why couldn't you just say
the blog is like
her giving me
the key to her heart?
"The key to her heart."
That's nice.
Were you quoting someone
or is it tattooed
on the small of your back?
I was quoting a man
who knows a thing or two
about women:
Sir Elton John.
So, did you love it?
Of course you loved it.
How could you not love it?
Tell me how much you loved it.
It was cute.
Oh, don't say cute.
That's the worst.
W's wrong with cute?
It just makes things seem small.
It diminishes them.
So you want me to stop calling
your little tushy cute?
You can try,
but nobody's gonna believe you.
I just... I don't understand how
you can watch a show that great
and not be excited by it.
I liked it. I'm excited.
Well, then, tell your face.
What do you want from me?
You know what?
Never mind.
We gave it a shot.
Let's just see
what else is on.
Oh, come on,
don't be like that.
Well...
I'm sorry I called it cute.
Let's watch another one.
Really?
Yeah, it was fun.
Kind of reminded me
of my high school.
But instead of vampires,
we had meth heads.
But both came out at night
and had messed up teeth.
All right, cool.
I-I think you'll like
the next one better.
All the cheerleaders are
suffering from an evil curse.
Oh. Well, that's like
my high school, too.
But instead of a curse,
it was crabs.
I've come up with
a series of exercises
to help with your
compulsive need for closure.
I take issue with
the word "compulsive."
All I'm saying is,
we live in a world where
closure isn't always an op...
...tion. Okay.
For the sake of argument,
let's say I have a problem.
What would be your plan
for addressing it?
I'm going to recondition
your brain
so that the need for completion
isn't so overwhelming.
By playing tic-tac-toe?
Yep. Your turn.
Oh, Amy.
And you wonder why people
think neuroscience
is nothing but a goofy game
for diaper babies.
Tic-tac-toe can only end
in win, lose or draw...
none of which will
deny me closure.
Especially since
I'm about to win.
B-But we didn't finish.
Exactly.
How does that make you feel?
The same way any
normal person would.
Feel like I want to
peel off my own face
and tear it in two
and then again and again
until I have a handful
of Sheldon-face confetti.
And that's exactly the feeling
we want to address
with this course of treatment.
Yeah, or you could pitch in,
grab a nostril
and help me get this face off.
Come on, you can do this.
You don't know what it's like
to feel completely frustrated.
To have a-a desire
build up within you
and be denied
any opportunity for release.
Yeah, sounds like a drag.
Okay, help me out here.
Why does he love
this show so much?
Well, there was action,
it was funny.
I mean, you do get
that usually the monster
chases the pretty girl,
but this time the pretty girl
chases the monsters?
Yippee, it's backwards.
I get it.
Why does this
bother you so much?
I don't know.
It's just, he's so passionate
about so many different things.
I just don't get that way.
Do you?
Well, sure. I'm pretty
passionate about science.
I remember the first time
I looked through a microscope
and saw millions
of tiny microorganisms.
It was like
a whole other universe.
If I wanted to, I could wipe
it out with my thumb like a god.
See? I wish I had some
of that fire in my life.
I mean, I want
to care about things
and get excited
like you guys.
Well, there's no
reason you can't.
You think?
Absolutely.
All we need to do is spend
a little time and find something
you're passionate about.
That sounds
like a lot of work.
Hey, what's up?
Uh, Lucy's coming over.
I need some advice.
However long you think the
foreplay should be, triple it.
Just tell me which one you think
is more manly.
This hockey jersey or...
this football jersey.
I don't know. Go with hockey.
Good-- black is more slimming.
Oh, that's her.
I got to go be butch.
Toodles.
Hey.
Hi.
Come in.
Oh, look how cute
your little doggy is.
Yeah, well,
I wouldn't get too close.
If I give the right command
in German,
she'll rip your face off.
♪ O'er the land
of the free ♪
♪ And the home
♪ Of the...
Next.
That's quite an impressive
layout, isn't it?
Yes.
Let's box it up.
"Let's box it up."
That's enough.
Sheldon, Sheldon, give it!
Okay, Sheldon, make a wish
and blow out the candles.
Oops, missed one.
Now your wish can't come true.
Lucky for you,
'cause I wished you were dead.
I like your jersey.
Thanks. I love hockey.
Oh, cool. So does my dad.
We watched it
all the time growing up.
Who's your favorite player?
Not Brian Boitano,
that's for sure.
How's your burrito?
It's still a little frozen
in the middle.
Probably because I didn't read
the instructions.
No wrapper's
going to tell me what to do.
Unless his name is Jay-Z.
Is something going on?
What do you mean?
Well, you're acting all weird.
And I'm pretty weird,
so I think I know
what I'm talking about.
I don't know. Maybe it's all
those steroids I've been taking.
I think I'm gonna go.
Thank you for the burrito
and the pork rinds
and the 20-minute lecture
on why monster trucks
are better than regular trucks.
Wait, wait.
I-I found your blog
where you wrote about me.
Oh. I kind of just write that
for myself.
I didn't think anybody
actually read it.
No kidding. You didn't make it
easy to find.
I spent hours
digging around online.
For the record, you have
excellent credit scores.
And your diabetic aunt seems
to be adjusting
to her new leg just fine.
Why were you acting
so strange tonight?
You called me feminine.
And I...
I wanted you to think
I was more manly.
Raj, I didn't say "feminine"
was a bad thing.
I meant that you're sweet
and thoughtful
and your skin looks so much
like caramel,
I just want to dip
an apple in your face.
I do have a pretty
balls-to-the-wall
moisturizing regimen.
So, are you okay?
Yeah.
Good.
Do you even like hockey?
No.
Bought this
at the Staples Center
when I went
to see Taylor Swift.
So, I was thinking
how excited you get
about stuff like Buffy
or science
or which TV remote
you and Sheldon should buy.
The "Harmony One" was fine.
We didn't need to upgrade
to the 1100,
which he knows
is too big for my hand.
See, that's the kind of passion
I didn't think I had.
But then I realized
I'm passionate about you.
Oh... my cute little tushy
strikes again.
No, I'm serious.
Look, I've always had
these plans.
I was gonna be in movies
and live this glamorous life,
and anything less than that
just wasn't worth
getting excited about.
Those things can still happen.
Oh, obviously it's gonna happen.
Yeah, a psychic at a
bachelorette party told me so.
Anyway, what I meant was...
I shouldn't wait, you know?
I've got you, I've got Sheldon,
all these wonderful friends.
My life is exciting right now.
That's a big deal.
It is, isn't it?
So, does that mean
we get to do stuff
like talk about cool shows
or get dressed up
in matching costumes
and go to Comic-Con?
Leonard, I had an epiphany,
not a stroke.
Amy, I must say,
I was skeptical at first,
but this has truly been
a transformative evening.
I'm a little surprised to hear
you feeling so positive.
Well, you're an excellent
neuroscientist,
you're a wonderful
girlfriend, and...
And?
Doesn't matter, does it?
I'm proud of you, Sheldon.
And a complete sucker.
Oh, yeah.
There he is.
♪ And the home of the brave...
Don't stop. Yes, keep going.
Just like that.
Almost there, almost there.
Sheldon, you big weirdo,
I want you to know that I love
that you're in my life.
I love you, too.
Hello. Uh, is this
the Bruce Miller who wrote
the season finale of Alphas?
Oh, smashing.
Yeah, you already sound nicer
than the last Bruce Miller
who suggested
I have sexual relations
with myself.
Yeah, now, down to business.
Um, your show ended
on a cliffhanger.
Could you please tell me
how you planned to resolve it?
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
I see.
Well, that all stinks.
No wonder you got canceled.
Bye.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net