So, anyway, last night on
video chat, I spent, like,
20 minutes just staring
into Lucy's eyes.
Oh, that sounds romantic.
It was until I realized
the screen had frozen.
Still one of my top three dates
of all time.
So, are we ever gonna
hang out with this girl?
I'd love that,
but she's not really comfortable
around people.
Yeah, I used to be
uncomfortable around people,
but then I learned a trick.
I pretend everyone I meet
is a beloved character
from Star Trek.
How's that been working
for you?
Oh, like a charm, unnamed
crewman in a red shirt.
Leonard, I may have
gotten you a job.
I have a job.
Yes, he does.
He caters to
my every whim.
No, in a couple of weeks,
Stephen Hawking's team
is sending an expedition
to the North Sea
to test hydrodynamic
simulations of black holes.
One of their experimental
physicists dropped out,
and I recommended you.
Well, do you really think
I have a shot?
Yeah, I've worked with Hawking.
I talked you up.
He knows your research.
I think this could happen.
He knows-- Wow!
Well, now, but do you
think that's a good idea?
Uh, you know Star Trek.
Should a guy
with no name
and a red shirt really
go on an expedition?
Hey, don't discourage him.
This is a fantastic opportunity.
No one asked you, Uhura.
Would you like to hear a classic
Sheldon Cooper factoid?
What do you think?
Great.
I've been doing some reading
about vehicular safety.
Did you know
that the highest number
of drowning accidents happen
on or around boats?
Interesting that you would
bring that up
when I might go work on a boat.
Well, that's the thing
about factoids--
they're interesting.
I know what
you're doing.
You don't want me going
on this research trip
because you're afraid
to be alone.
I'm not afraid to be alone.
On land.
On the sea,
it would be terrifying.
Because of all the drowning.
Sheldon.
Fine, no more drowning talk.
I'll change the subject.
Oh. Who do you think
would win in a fight--
you or a shark?
Look, I appreciate
your signature blend
of concern for me
and incredible selfishness.
If I get the chance to do this,
there is nothing you can say
that's going to stop me.
Very well.
Things between you and Penny
have never been better.
I hope four months apart
doesn't change anything.
I should have opened
with that, huh?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x24 ♪
The Bon Voyage Reaction
Original Air Date on May 16, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
If you look
carefully at Venus,
you should be
able to see
the International
Space Station pass by.
Wow.
Your friend
was actually up there?
Yeah. He brought me back
a T-shirt that said,
"My Friend Went to
the Space Station
and All I Got Was
This Lousy T-Shirt""
Did he take the
T-shirt to space?
Nope. It's exactly
as lousy as advertised.
Speaking of friends,
they have been
asking to meet you.
I was thinking
maybe we could all
hang out sometime?
I don't know.
How many are there?
Let's see. Six.
That's pretty cool;
I have six friends!
Kind of like Sinatra.
Six strangers?
That's a lot of pressure.
Staring at me,
asking me personal questions.
Like, "What do you do""
"Where are you from?"
"Why did you lock yourself
in the bathroom?"
Okay, how about
you just dip your toe in
and meet one of them?
Will you be there?
Of course.
Well, that's two.
Three if you count me.
Oh, this is getting out of hand.
So, then, during
my afternoon shift,
I spilled an entire tray
of drinks on myself.
Oh, that's awful.
Not really.
My shirt was soaking wet.
I got, like, the biggest tip of my life.
Oh.
So, listen, do you remember
when I said
the similarities
of the equations
of general relativity
and hydrodynamics suggest
you could find the equivalent
of Unruh radiation
in a large body of water?
I thought I said that to you.
Anyway,
Stephen Hawking's team
is looking into that,
and I've been invited
to join them.
Wow, Hawking!
Good for you!
Well, it is.
Just-- you know,
I'd be gone for a while.
Well, how long?
Three, four months.
Whoa.
When would you leave?
Couple weeks.
Wow.
O-Okay, well,
I'll just come visit you.
That's the thing-- you can't.
I'll be on a ship
in the North Sea.
On a ship?
Aren't they afraid Hawking will
just roll overboard?
Uh, he's not gonna be there.
He's just sending a team
to research his theory.
Oh, sure.
Like when you send me
to kill spiders in your bathtub.
Wow. Okay.
Four months.
Yeah.
And I'm a little worried
because things
between us have been so great,
and I'd hate to do anything
that screws that up.
Oh, sweetie,
if you're gonna screw things up,
it's gonna be while you're here,
not while you're away.
Oh.
No. I mean, look,
you have to go.
It sounds like
an amazing opportunity.
And I'm just basing that
on how much I didn't understand
what you said about it.
Okay.
I'll confirm the travel
arrangements in the morning.
Okay. Good.
I do have to ask
you one favor.
Sure.
Sheldon's nervous
about me leaving.
Just keep an eye on him
while I'm gone.
Oh, I don't know.
Remember what happened when
I took care of your goldfish?
Well, flush Sheldon down
the toilet and get me a new one.
Really, you guys do not need
to throw me a going-away party.
Are you kidding me?
How often can you say
"Bon voyage" to somebody
when they're actually going
on a voyage?
Hello, Rajesh.
Hello, Amy. Nice to see you.
What can I say?
It's funnier with the accent.
There's beer in the fridge.
Anyway, you guys really don't
need to make a big deal.
Leonard, you're being selfish.
We need to give you a proper
send-off so we'll have closure
when you die at sea
and crabs eat your face.
Sheldon, sweetie, shut up.
You know, one of the things
that helped me get through
Howard being in space
for so long was getting
married before he left.
Bernadette, sweetie, shut up.
Okay.
I have a request to make.
And now he can talk.
I want to cut open your brain
and see what the heck's
going on in there.
The only person allowed
inside this head is Dr. Phil.
Anyway,
I-I spoke to my new lady friend
about meeting you all,
and she thought
it would be easier for her
to start with just one.
Oh, gee, I don't know.
My schedule's a little busy.
Actually,
I was thinking Leonard.
Oh. Thank you, Raj.
I'd be honored.
What the hell?
I thought
I was your best friend.
You are, but you've got
kind of a big personality,
with your flashy clothes and
your Woody Allen swagger.
You know,
maybe she'd be more comfortable
meeting a girl first.
Good idea. Bernadette?
What the hell?!
Well, you're very pretty.
That could be intimidating
to another woman.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, you don't think I'm pretty
enough to scare your girlfriend?
Calm down, Bernie.
You're very scary.
It should be me.
Why?
So you can make jokes
about cutting open my brain?
A, that was not a joke.
That was a sincere request.
And B, more
importantly,
I was the outsider
to this group,
and I know how frightening
that can be.
But you guys took me in
and made me feel loved,
like I was family.
Fine, I'll do it.
So, after I started
dating Sheldon,
I met Leonard,
and then everybody else,
and they've all been
so wonderful to me.
That's really nice to hear.
Maybe next week,
we could all get together.
Oh, Lucy, you don't
have to answer that.
Don't put her on the
spot. She hates that.
Am I right? Tell her
how much you hate
being put on the spot.
Go ahead, tell her.
Ignore him. He's a little
nervous 'cause he doesn't think
I understand the severity
of your social anxiety.
What the...?
Are you crazy?
You can't talk
about social anxiety
to someone who has
social anxiety.
It makes them
socially anxious!
Excuse me, but I'm
a neurobiologist.
I think I'm a little
more qualified than you
to understand what's not working
in your girlfriend's brain!
Don't call her my girlfriend.
We haven't discussed
whether or not
we're girlfriend
or boyfriend yet.
Now that it's
out there...
...are you my girlfriend?
By the way,
if you say no,
I'll never be happy again.
Not to put you on the spot.
I think I have to go
to the bathroom.
We might as well
go ahead and eat.
She's not coming back
anytime soon.
This is ridiculous.
We're shopping
for a party.
This store doesn't even
have a party section.
Yeah, it does,
and here we are.
You know, I have to say, Penny,
I don't understand
why you of all people
are encouraging Leonard
to do this.
Well, I'm his girlfriend;
of course I'm gonna support him.
Yeah, well,
you're his girlfriend for now.
You know, maybe
you're not aware of this,
but there is
a rich tradition
of men at sea finding comfort in
each other's arms and britches.
Honey, this is a big
deal for Leonard, okay?
He gets to work with
Stephen Hawking.
Who, by the way,
will not be on the boat.
I checked it out.
It's not that big
of an opportunity.
And even if Hawking's theories
are correct,
all they prove is
where the universe came from,
why everything exists and
what its ultimate end will be.
I mean, me?
I'm interested
in the big questions.
Oh, my God, Sheldon the genius
is jealous of Leonard.
I'm not jealous.
I'm just very unhappy
that good things
are happening for him
and not happening for me.
Look, sweetie, this is
a natural thing to feel, okay?
But just because good things
are happening to Leonard
doesn't take anything
away from you.
You know what? Let me
tell you a little story.
Once there was a girl who worked
at the Cheesecake Factory,
and she wasn't very good
at her job.
It was you.
It wasn't me.
But she was also an actress,
and we were both up
for the same part
in a toothpaste commercial.
She got it. Look,
I was so jealous.
But instead of ripping out
her fake blonde hair...
You ripped out
your own fake blonde hair.
I...
looked her in the eye,
smiled and said,
"I'm happy for you."
Because that's what friends do.
They lie
so they don't look petty.
Yeah.
How?
Like this.
I am so happy for you.
Wow.
No wonder you didn't get
that toothpaste commercial.
Hey.
Hi.
I want to apologize
for Amy last night.
She was completely out of line.
Are you... are you
not speaking to me
or did the screen freeze again?
Amy wasn't the problem.
Okay. I know.
It was me.
I-I pushed too hard. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
You know,
I-I've been thinking that...
maybe meeting somebody
one-on-one is too intense,
so...
Friday night, my friends
are having a party.
A party?
A little one!
It's-it's a farewell
for Leonard,
so all the attention
will be on him.
If you wear something brown
and sit on the couch,
they won't even know
you're there.
I'm not sure.
Oh, please?
Raj.
Come on.
Don't make me beg.
And I'm from India,
so I know how to do it.
Okay.
Y... Thank you!
Th-This means a lot to me.
My friends are like my family.
Unless you don't like them;
in which case,
they're dead to me.
So, have you ever spent
a long time on a boat before?
Yeah.
Are you referring to the time
we got stuck on the Small World
ride at Disneyland?
Yeah.
I'm proud of you, Leonard.
Working out
on the North Sea
for months--
that's really something.
I know. As far as science goes,
this is the adventure
of a lifetime.
Maybe your lifetime.
I went to space.
It's not a competition.
You're right, you're right.
I'm really proud of you, and...
I'm gonna miss you
when you're gone.
And space beats water.
Rajesh, I thought
Lucy was coming.
She is. She's just running
a little late.
You know how it is--
girls always fussing about
their hair, their makeup.
She'll be here.
Just give it a rest, okay?
Um, can I have
your attention, everyone?
That's, uh, B-flat, for those
who don't have perfect pitch.
I would like
to propose a toast
to my best friend,
Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
He has been presented with
a wonderful opportunity,
and I couldn't
be happier for him.
Thank you, Sheldon.
That must've been
very hard for you to say.
Well, I mean it.
I'm really happy
for you.
And that's how you get
a toothpaste commercial. Cheers.
Cheers.
It was really nice of you
to try to be happy for Leonard.
Mm. Thank you.
It must've killed you
when I went to space.
Oh, no.
Buddy, you okay?
Oh, man.
What's going on?
Uh, go ahead. Read it.
"Raj, I can't come
to the party.
"This is all just
"too much for me.
"I don't think
we should see
"each other anymore.
Sorry.
Lucy."
Excuse me.
Raj, I'm so sorry.
Me, too.
It did not kill me
when you went to space.
Monkeys went to space.
Well, here we are.
Yep.
I'm really gonna miss you.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Penny, we're
in the red zone.
The white zone
is for loading and unloading.
We're breaking the law.
Okay, there's no space
in the white zone, so...
Anyway,
we can e-mail, and I-I think
the phone connections
are pretty good.
All right, you have to get
out of the car right now.
I'm not going
to jail for you.
Would you just relax?
Oh, I see a space
in the white zone.
Quick, circle the airport.
Did you bring enough inhalers?
Yeah.
And, uh, extra Dramamine?
You remember what happened
on It's a Small World.
I'm covered.
Okay.
Oh, dear Lord,
a police officer's
glancing in our direction.
We've been made.
Calm down.
I'm getting out.
I have something
I want to give you.
Oh, Leonard.
It's just a heart-shaped
locket with a picture of
Leonard's face in it. He got
it at the mall on clearance.
Now move, move, move!
I love you.
I love you, too.
Don't worry, Officer.
They just love each other.
We're not smuggling drugs.
Raj, it's Penny.
Are you in there?
Hang on.
Hey. I'm just coming back
from the airport.
I wanted to see
how you're doing.
That's-that's very nice of you.
Uh, come, come. Come on in.
Can't stay long.
I left Sheldon in the car
with the window cracked open.
He's gonna go through
that activity book
in, like, 30 seconds, so...
Are you okay?
No.
Oh.
I'm so sorry.
No.
It's my fault.
You know, I finally found
someone who was right for me,
and I-I drove her away.
Oh, Raj.
Penny, I...
I miss her already.
I know how you feel.
I miss Leonard, too.
What's... what is
wrong with me?
Why-why can't I
ever have love?
You will.
No, I... I won't.
I'm-I'm unlovable.
That's just
the booze talking.
No, it's not.
I haven't had a drink
since last night.
You're talking to me.
I am.
And now I'm crying for
a whole different reason!
Me, too!
So I-I guess
what I'm saying is.
I get where Lucy's
coming from.
That's great.
Do you want some wine?
Uh, no, water's fine.
Anyhow, I-I've been
thinking about it a lot,
and-and I totally see
why Lucy did what she did.
I pushed too hard.
But you know what?
If I back off
and give her enough space,
maybe there's still
a future for us.
Yeah, the funny thing about life
is that, you know, sometimes...
Does he ever shut up?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
...at least
my heart is starting to heal.
Slowly but surely.
And  how I cried.
It was like a little, uh,
thunderstorm on my face.
But I'm a man, okay?
So I need to pull myself
together, pick up a pen
and get it all out
in my journal.
I mean,
it's not all bad, right?
Having my heart broken
has allowed me to finally speak
in front of you...
so, you know,
it was a silver lining.
www.tvsubtitles.net