Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Welcome to Sheldon Cooper
Presents: Fun with Flags.
Before we get started,
I'd like to announce
the winner of our design
your own flag competition.
But I can't.
The only entry
was from GameyGamer75,
and I know that was a jpeg
of your buttocks.
Now this week we have
a very special episode
where we explore the flags
of the popular entertainment
franchise, Star Trek.
And to help me,
I'm pleased to introduce
Internet personality,
former star of Star Trek:
The Next Generation,
and the only guy I know lucky
enough to be immortalized
in 1/16 scale--
set phasers to "fun"...
...for my friend, Wil Wheaton.
Hi, Sheldon.
Thanks for having me.
I'm happy to be here.
Cut.
What's wrong?
Sorry, Sheldon, you were
brilliant as always.
Wil, that was
a little wooden.
Wooden?
Don't worry,
it wasn't terrible.
Just, this time, try to say it
the way people sound.
And action.
My friend, Wil Wheaton.
Hi, Sheldon.
Thanks for having me.
I'm excited to be here.
So, Wil, what do you
have for us first?
Well, this is
an exciting one.
This is the flag of the
United Federation of Planets.
Now what's interesting about this flag...
Cut.
What was wrong with that?
It's called "Fun with Flags."
They're not at half-mast,
nobody died.
Let's try and keep it upbeat.
Um, no offense,
but I've been acting
since I was a kid.
I think I can
handle a Web show
without a lot
of direction.
It's true.
In 1982, Wil
played the voice
of Martin the mouse
in The Secret of NIMH.
You moved me.
You'll have to forgive me.
This is my first time directing,
I just want it to be good.
So do I.
Great. So, this time let's try
more real boy, less Pinocchio.
And action.
And cut.
You realize that I'm doing this
for free, right?
Yes. And so far, we're still
not getting our money's worth.
Let's try it again.
Everybody's having fun.
And action.
So, Wil...
...what do you have
for us first?
Well, this is
an exciting one.
This is the flag
of the United
Federation of Planets.
Cut.
Problem,
first-time director?
Oh, none that I could see.
I saw a man who loved flags
almost as much as I do.
I got goose bumps.
He was overacting on purpose.
Really?
He reminded me of a
young William Shatner.
Listen, Sheldon,
I'm really happy
to do this for you,
but not if she's gonna be
a huge pain in the ass
the whole time.
You gonna let him
speak to me like that?
Well...
you're my girlfriend
and I don't want
you to be upset.
Then again,
Wil Wheaton's my friend
and I don't want
him to be upset.
Hmm...
This is a sticky wicket.
What do you think?
Can I speak to you
for a second?
I'll be right back.
Feel free to play
with yourself.
I don't care for your friend,
he's being rude to me.
You need to ask him to leave.
Amy, I can't just ask
Wil Wheaton to leave.
He's a minor celebrity.
Once you explain who he is,
many people recognize him.
Fine. Then maybe I should go.
Could you?
That would solve everything.
You are the best.
I'll see you at dinner tonight?
You sure you wouldn't rather
have dinner
with your friend Wil Wheaton?
Come to think of it, I would!
You, little lady, are on fire.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x07 ♪
The Habitation Configuration
Original Air Date on November 8, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Every time we eat
dinner here,
your mother refuses to let me
help with the dishes.
Don't take it personally.
She likes doing them by herself
so she can lick the plates
with no one looking.
You ready to go?
Yeah, let me just grab a couple
of fresh turtlenecks.
I don't understand
why you keep your stuff here
when there's plenty
of room at home.
What are you
talking about?
All I have here
is a few sweaters,
books, bank stuff,
computers,
mail, collectibles, medicine
and my electric body groomer.
Ooh, there's my plaid dickie.
Oh, got this at the Goodwill
store for 50 cents.
Can you believe it?
50 cents sounds right.
Let's go.
You know, it's kinda late.
Why don't we just spend
the night here?
Because we don't live here.
I know.
Do you? You said when you got
back from space
you were gonna move into
my apartment,
but half the time we stay here.
That's not true.
Howard, I'm doing laundry!
You want me to put
anything in for you?!
There's some underwear
in the hamper!
Oh, good! I got that new
stain stick to try out!
Thank you! I only put it
on the list two weeks ago!
Okay, I see what
you're getting at.
How about this weekend
I'll box up all my things
and move them to our place.
Thank you.
The lightsabers are gonna
look great in the living room.
Or in the closet.
We can decide later.
Howard, help!
My hand's stuck
in the garbage disposal!
Let go of whatever piece of food
you're holding!
Are you kidding?!
It's a perfectly good
chicken leg!
Hey, look who's out
after dark, like a big boy.
I was out raising heck
with Mr. Wil Wheaton.
Four hours more
and we would have
closed down the
HomeTown Buffet.
I thought you had plans
with Amy.
Yeah, I did, but then Wil called
Amy a pain in the A-S-S.
She got huffy and left,
then Wil and I headed out
to dinner.
That place really did remind me
of my hometown.
Because there we also have
a HomeTown Buffet.
Hold on.
Wil and Amy had an argument?
Yes, quite the kerfuffle.
Then Amy got mad and left?
Walked right out the door.
And you...?
Enjoyed a delightful dinner
at a reasonable price.
The manager recognized Wil
and let us sit right next
to the frozen yogurt machine.
Right next to it!
I was closer to it than
I am to you right now.
Buddy, I think Amy
might be upset.
Why's that?
Because your friend
was rude to her,
and then you went
to dinner with him.
You're just repeating
what I said.
It's like living with
a lactose-intolerant parrot.
Trust me, call her.
Fine. It's a shame you didn't
go to dinner with us,
because the buffet
you're about to enjoy
only serves humble pie,
a dessert much less tasty
than frozen yogurt.
I was this close.
What?
You'll appreciate this.
Leonard has some ridiculous
notion that you're mad at me.
Tell him you're
not mad at me.
Go ahead, set
him straight.
I'm mad at you, Sheldon.
Hmm. Eat one of
your Luna bars.
Very often when women
think they're angry,
they're really just hungry.
I'm not hungry.
Your friend insulted me,
and you didn't do anything.
Precisely, I didn't
do anything.
Now does someone feel like
checking her emotional math?
Keep going, buddy,
you're doing great.
Sheldon, I'm your girlfriend,
and you should have
taken my side.
That's it. End of story.
Good night.
Wow, Amy's mad
and Leonard was right.
What a weird day.
Hey. Sorry this took so long.
But you used to work here,
you know how it is.
Kitchen slammed again?
No, I'm a terrible waitress,
remember?
So, is there anything I can do
to help you with the move
tomorrow?
Now that you mention it,
I was thinking tomorrow
might not be great.
What's your excuse this time?
No excuse. It's just, you know,
I'm Jewish, and technically,
we're not supposed to drive or
carry anything on the Sabbath.
So this one's on God.
That might be
a little more convincing
if you didn't have a mouthful
of bacon cheeseburger.
My religion's kinda
loosey-goosey.
Basically, as long as you got
your schmekel clipped
and don't wear a cross,
you're good.
Howie, you promised you'd move.
And I will.
Yeah, right.
I will. I'm obviously not going
to live in my mother's house
for the rest of my life.
I'm not a child.
I've seen her burp you.
She did not burp me.
She was patting me on the back,
and I happened to burp.
Don't you have other tables
you should be waiting on?
Yeah, but I told you,
I'm not good at my job.
Bernadette,
listen to me.
He is never gonna leave.
I'm starting to think
you're right.
All right,
I've had enough of this.
I'm a grown man,
I have a successful career.
For the love of God,
I've been to space!
I will move out when I'm ready,
and I don't need anyone
badgering me into it!
Wow, excuse me.
That was just for her benefit.
I'll move tomorrow. I love you.
Don't leave me.
Amy.
Angry Amy.
What?
I've been thinking about
what happened,
and I hope this gift
will make things better.
Star Trek DVDs?
Why would I want this?
First of all, you're welcome.
Furthermore, not being familiar
with Wil Wheaton's body of work,
there was no way for you to know
you were being rude
to a national treasure.
Get ready for 130 hours
of "I told you so."
Fine.
I'll just tell you what happens.
Episode one,
"Encounter at Farpoint."
Fade in.
The new Enterprise heads out
on its maiden voyage
to contact the Bandi people
of Deneb IV.
Enter Wesley Crusher,
played by my buddy...
She's hooked.
Wow.
An end of an era.
Boy, if these walls could talk.
They'd say, "Why does he
touch himself so much?"
Yeah.
I can't believe I'm not going
to live here anymore.
This has always been my bedroom.
Right here is where my mom
used to mark my height.
Oh, yeah.
Fifth grade.
Sixth grade.
Seventh grade.
Eighth grade.
Ninth grade.
I remember when I was five,
hiding under this desk
with all my Halloween candy.
Had some Peanut M&M'S,
went into my first
anaphylactic shock
and had to be rushed
to the hospital.
Came home,
celebrated with a Snickers,
went into my second
anaphylactic shock.
When did you figure out
you were allergic to nuts?
Sometime
around the third Almond Joy.
Okay.
You want to start loading
this stuff into the truck?
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, would you do me a favor?
Go on ahead.
I just want one last moment
alone in my old room.
We're not standing outside
by the U-Haul
while you fondle yourself.
Fine, let's go.
Hey.
What brings you in?
Penny, if you wouldn't mind,
I'd like to have a conversation
about girls.
I had a feeling we'd have a
talk like this sooner or later.
Are you finally getting
fuzz in weird places?
Penny, please,
I'm on the horns
of a relationship dilemma.
And for the record,
I had a full pubis of hair
by the time I was 19.
And for the record...
So what are you drinking?
Well, it's been a rough day.
I usually go chamomile tea,
but I don't think
that's going to cut it.
You could have a
Long Island Iced Tea.
Will that calm my nerves?
It's calmed the pants
off me a couple of times.
Sold.
Oh.
So, the heart you got from
the wizard giving you trouble?
The trouble isn't with me,
Penny,
it's with your gender.
Someday,
scientists will discover
that second X chromosome
contains nothing
but nonsense and twaddle.
Yeah, Amy told me what happened.
Look, just apologize.
It'll warm her twaddle.
It's a Band-Aid at best.
The core problem is that Amy
and Wil do not like each other.
Which is baffling because
they're both crazy about me.
And I like them,
which indicates
they're bright and interesting
and/or were on Star Trek.
Honey, you can't make
people like each other.
Not true.
Leonard made me like you.
And let me tell you,
that was a hard row to hoe.
Cheers, pal.
Ooh.
Boy, that is a treat
that's hard to beat.
Get the Mad Hatter on the horn,
I'm having a tea party.
You might want to pace yourself.
I drink tea all the time.
I think I know what I'm doing.
Far be it from me to criticize
a man with a full pubis.
Look, Sheldon, your problem
is not Wil Wheaton, okay?
Your problem is the way
you treated Amy.
My problem is I'm out of tea.
Come on, someone insulted
your girlfriend and
you just let him do it.
I thought you Texas guys
stood up for your womenfolk.
Penny, please,
I think I've evolved beyond
my simple rustic upbringing.
Sorry.
On the other hand, that low-down
polecat done wronged my woman.
Welcome to Long Island, Tex.
Amy deserves better.
You know, when we buy
the Planter's deluxe mix,
she eats all the Brazil nuts
so I don't have to look at them.
She's a unique blend
of saint and squirrel.
Yeah, that she is.
Here you go.
I'm a callous egomaniac.
She's gonna leave me.
No, she won't.
No, she won't. I'm great.
Okay, I have now
officially moved
out of my mother's house.
You are now the only woman
in my life
who I'll see naked
in the bathroom.
I know this wasn't easy.
You doing okay?
Oh, I'm fine.
It's just her I'm worried about.
Aw, she'll be okay.
She's a grown woman.
I know.
It's just
ever since my dad left,
I've felt responsible for her.
That's a lot for a
kid to deal with.
She was just so sad
all the time.
Yeah, I was the only person
who could cheer her up.
Well, me and Ben and Jerry.
She's lucky you were there.
You know, she's why
I first got into magic.
I would do little shows
for her,
hang up a bedsheet
like it was a curtain,
put on a top hat and cape.
And part way through the act,
I would say I needed a volunteer
from the audience
to be my beautiful assistant
and invite her up on stage.
I can still remember
the way she'd smile.
For a few minutes,
she'd...
forget how lonely she was.
Aw, crap.
Let's go.
Where we going?
Grab a box.
We'll sleep
at your mother's place tonight.
No, but I want to live here.
Well, you should've
thought of that
before you told me
the stupid magic trick story.
Can't we talk about this?
No husband of mine is gonna
break his mother's heart!
Wil Wheaton!
Wait, how many was that?
Hey, Sheldon, what's up?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Have you been drinking?
Just tea.
The best tea I've ever had.
Why are you here?
I'll tell you.
I'm from Texas.
Need I say more?
Yeah, actually, a little more
would be helpful.
You insulted my woman.
I'm here to defend her honor.
Two! It was two.
Wil Wheaton!
Now prepare yourself
for what may come.
Oh, Sheldon, do you really
think we're gonna fight?
My fists are not up here
because I'm milking a
giant invisible cow.
They're up to beat an
apology out of you.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Well, that was a long bus
ride for not very much.
Are you okay?
You're asking a lot of
questions, Wil Wheaton.
As a matter of
idle curiosity,
which of your
shrubberies do you feel
would benefit from
a thorough vomiting?
Never mind, I'll choose.
You were so good in Stand by Me.
Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Welcome to Sheldon Cooper
Presents: Fun with Flags.
Get ready
for a very special episode
where we explore the flags
of the popular
entertainment franchise,
Star Trek.
And to help us, I'm pleased
to introduce a special guest--
surprisingly,
it only took gas money
and the promise of free food
to get him here--
Mr. LeVar Burton.
Hey, Sheldon,
it's a pleasure to be here.
- Well, we've got some interesting flags for...
- Cut!
Yikes, this guy is worse
than Wil Wheaton.
I don't know what
she's talking about,
but I'm obligated
to agree with her.
She's my girlfriend.
Ah, I hear you, brother.
I still get lunch, right?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net