WOLOWITZ:
Hey, Bernie.
Hey, how's my little
astronautie hottie?
Okay, I guess.
It's just,
being cooped up in this...
tin can for weeks on end
is starting to get to me.
Well, hang in there.
You just have a couple more
days to go,
and then you'll be home.
I know.
I got to get back to work.
I love you.
Love you too.
Hey, Bernie?
Before you go, can you
do something for me?
What do you want me to do?
Okay, here it is.
I really miss gravity.
Can you drop something
so I can watch it fall?
Really, you're serious?
Okay.
Oh, baby, you're killing me.
Ugh.
Hey, Sheldon?
Hi. This came
for you today.
It's from your mom.
Oh!
Thank you, Penny.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, w... here.
For your troubles.
Oh, boy, a whole dollar.
Now, I can quit my paper route.
So, what's in it?
Mmm, doesn't matter.
Half the time, he just ends up
playing with the box.
Yeah, it's journals and research
papers I wrote as a child.
Aw, how cute.
Is this like a diary?
No, that's my
potty training journal.
Really, your
potty training journal?
Yeah.
And forgive my crude penmanship.
I didn't start typing
until I was six.
"August 7, 8:42 a.m.
This is humiliating.
What was wrong with diapers?"
(giggles)
There are some charts
in the back
where I kept track
of shape, color
and consistency.
Oh!
Disgusting.
No, what's disgusting
is he's still keeping track.
Why do you need
all this stuff...?
No, no, no, no...
Sorry!
I am glad you asked.
Oh!
Yeah, are you familiar
with the Higgs boson?
Of course, it is...
it's been in the news.
And it's a very famous boson.
Nice try.
Now, in 1964, Dr. Peter Higgs,
accomplished self-promoter
and physicist,
he wrote a paper
postulating the existence
of a subatomic particle
called the Higgs boson.
Now, initially,
the paper was rejected, but
recently, he was proven right.
And now he's on the fast
track to win a Nobel prize.
Yeah, that's basically what I said.
Yeah...
The point is Higgs
is being celebrated for work
he did 50 years ago, so that
got me thinking,
perhaps I've already hit
upon the idea
that will win me my Nobel prize.
I didn't know
they gave Nobel prizes
for making boom-boom
in the potty.
You really think
there's some kind
of scientific discovery in here?
Well, this box only covers
my work through nursery school.
There's a good deal
more to come.
I didn't really hit my academic
stride until I cut out
that time-suck
known as "playing outdoors."
LEONARD:
So, you're going to spend
hours and hours combing
through all this stuff?
(gasps) That's a good point.
My time is much too valuable.
You know, perhaps I should
find someone to do it for me.
You know, someone with
a rudimentary understanding
of science, but whose real
talents lie in menial labor.
Not gonna happen.
Yeah, well, if I didn't
think you could handle it,
I wouldn't be asking.
If you want help,
just hire a grad student.
Maybe I could do it.
You, really?
You can assess
the quality of my work?
Okay, um, here.
I wrote this
when I was five years old.
"A proof that algebraic topology
can never have a non-self
contradictory set
of abelion groups."
I'm just a blonde monkey
to you, aren't I?
You said it, not me.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x03 ♪
The Higgs Boson Observation
Original Air Date on October 11, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Watch Online in HD for free with subtitles
www.jimmyleaks.tv
All right, Ms. Jenson.
Uh, before we begin,
may I offer you a refreshment?
Water, coffee, tea,
a marijuana cigarette?
No, thanks. I'm fine.
Now, are you sure?
Everyone's smoking them.
I think they're the best.
I don't do drugs.
Excellent, yeah.
That was a ruse.
They're not the best.
Physics is the best.
And by the way,
coffee was also
an unacceptable choice.
All right, so I see here
you're from Des Moines, Iowa.
Uh, you're summa cum laude
in theoretical physics
from Stanford University.
Oh, and two years ago, you had
a persistent ear infection.
I hope that didn't
cause any hearing loss.
No, of course not.
How did you know about that?
I did a comprehensive
background check.
Medical records, credit reports,
criminal history.
(muffled): I trust you paid off
those parking tickets.
Yes, I did.
Hearing unimpaired, good.
Look, Dr. Cooper,
I really want this position.
It would be
an incredible honor to work
for a man of your brilliance.
Flattery will not get you
this job, Ms. Jenson.
It's not flattery
if it's the truth.
Oh, well, thank you.
Welcome aboard.
You talk to Howard lately?
Uh, yeah, last night.
He kept making me
drop pencils for him.
I got uncomfortable.
Hey, Sheldon,
hope you're hungry.
They're serving
macaroni and...
(voice deepens):
cheese.
(mocking):
Smooth.
Hi.
Hello.
Sheldon, aren't you
going to introduce us?
No. I have people
for that now.
You're up.
I'm Alex,
Dr. Cooper's new assistant.
Ah, congratulations and may God
have mercy on your soul.
I'm Leonard. This is Raj.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm so excited
to be working with Dr...
Yeah, please reserve
chitchat for your breaks,
Ms. Jenson.
Yeah, FYI,
there will be no breaks.
I should probably get to work.
She seems nice.
Hey, you already
got a girlfriend.
I call dibs.
All I said was,
"She seems nice."
Yeah, well, I love her.
(phone rings)
Hey, I wasn't expecting
to hear from you today.
Everything okay?
Uh, no, not really.
What's wrong?
Well, remember the...
Soyuz capsule
they were sending
to bring us home?
Uh-huh.
It's delayed.
We're gonna be here
at least another week.
Maybe ten days.
It's the Russians,
so you don't know.
They left dogs up here
in the '60s.
Come on, Howard.
No one's leaving you up there.
I don't know how much longer
I can take this.
I can't sleep, and zero gravity
is giving me crazy acid reflux.
(inhales)
I'm down to my last three Tums.
You're going to be fine.
You survived that Weight
Watchers cruise with your mom.
And they ran out
of low-fat ice cream on day two.
Just calm down and take
a few deep breaths.
Okay, okay.
(breathing deeply)
What am I doing?
I'm using up all the oxygen.
If I die, promise you'll never
have sex with another man.
Oh, yeah.
I'm a man-eater now.
Okay, for the final touch,
this is an eyelash curler.
You just place it on your lashes
and squeeze it closed.
Oh, I don't know.
Looks like something used
by Tinker Bell's gynecologist.
Who I hope for her sake
is not Captain Hook, so...
Who are you calling?
I'm going to
video-chat Sheldon.
Mmm.
If my new look
leads to phone sex,
I'm going to have to ask you
to leave the room.
ALEX:
Dr. Cooper's office.
Oh, hello. Who are you?
I'm Alex,
Dr. Cooper's assistant.
Can I help you?
I'd like to speak to Sheldon.
I'm sorry. He's asked me
to hold all calls
unless you're Stephen Hawking,
his mother
or himself from the future.
All right.
Well, tell him Amy called.
Last name?
He knows my last name.
I'm his girlfriend.
We have a contract
and everything.
I'll send you a PDF.
All right, I will
tell him you called.
Hmm, that's weird.
What?
Sheldon told me he had
a new assistant named Alex.
He didn't mention
that Alex was a girl.
Maybe he didn't notice.
You're right.
I don't have to worry
about Sheldon.
(laughing):
No, you do not.
It's her I have to worry about.
Oh, Amy, really?
She is not going to come on
to Sheldon.
Oh, really?
Look at this face.
How can any woman
spend eight hours a day
alone with this face
and not fall in love with it?
Well, for starters,
at some point,
that face starts talking.
Amy, this is crazy.
You have nothing
to be suspicious about.
I'm not suspicious.
I just want to stop in,
say hi to my boyfriend
and meet his new assistant.
Aha!
Can we go now?
Hang on.
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm spreading my scent
to mark my territory.
Come on, Amy.
That is not gonna work.
Really? Because just before you
became my best friend,
I did this
all over your apartment.
Has your, uh, assistant
said anything about me?
In fact, she has.
Uh, her exact words were,
"What is that guy's problem?"
I'm in her head.
Let the dance begin.
Here's your frozen yogurt,
Dr. Cooper.
This should be fun.
Half chocolate,
half vanilla,
side by side, not swirled?
Yes.
Half a teaspoon of sprinkles?
Rainbow, not chocolate.
Two cherries?
One on top, one on the bottom.
Stems removed?
Um...
top one, yes.
I didn't check the one
on the bottom.
Oh...!
I'm so sorry, Dr. Cooper.
It's all right, Alex.
I'm not mad at you;
I'm just disappointed.
Wait, Alex.
Do you want to join us?
Um...
Uh, Alex, a moment.
I need a word with
Dr. Hofstadter.
Do you think it's appropriate
for her to sit with us,
given her station?
Given her what?
If I've learned anything from
British television shows on PBS,
it's that servants dine
downstairs with their own kind.
What?
It's a kindness, Leonard.
Otherwise, you're cruelly
tempting them with a glimpse
of a world that's just beyond
their soot-stained fingertips.
Oh, sure.
Please join us.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
So, Alex, what's the topic
of your dissertation?
I'm looking
for Trojan asteroids
at Earth's L-Five
Lagrange point.
Oh, that happens to be
Dr. Koothrappali's
field of expertise.
You two have a lot
to talk about.
Is that true?
Is he all right?
No.
But compared to your boss,
he's the poster boy for sanity.
It's okay, I've been around
scientists all my life.
My dad's an astronomer at SETI.
Oh, SETI-- the Search for
Extraterrestrial Intelligence.
You should introduce him
to Sheldon. The search is over.
So, what kind of research
are you doing?
High-energy lasers.
Ooh. Military?
Not yet, but I can remove
unwanted hair
from two miles away.
(both chuckle)
You were right.
I had nothing
to worry about.
That skank's your
problem, not mine.
You're very funny,
Dr. Hofstadter.
LEONARD:
Thank you.
Aah! Cherry stem!
Cherry stem!
(coughing, gagging)
How you doing, Howie?
You feeling a little better?
Oh, a lot better, thanks.
One sec.
Listen close.
I don't have a lot of time.
I need you to go to my house.
In my bedroom, you'll find
a model rocket.
I want you to take it
and bring it back to your place.
Okay...
Step two: Build a version
roughly 14 stories high.
Fill it full of rocket fuel
and come get me.
(whispers):
I'll leave the door unlocked.
Howie, honey, maybe you should
talk to someone,
let them know you're having
a little anxiety.
No, no, I'm fine.
No anxiety!
(quietly):
We should probably talk in code.
From now on, "frog" is me,
"sandwich" means you
and "lemon" means rocket.
So, come on, sandwich,
build me a lemon 'cause froggy
wants to come home!
Look at you,
putting on a brave face.
There's nothing
to be brave about.
Everything's fine.
Really?
I don't know how much you know
about primate behavior,
but Sheldon's assistant
was clearly courting Leonard.
Were she a mandrill,
she would have bent over
and displayed her brightly
colored hindquarters
like a big red welcome mat.
By the way, you try that
at the junior prom,
you get kicked out.
Okay, maybe she was flirting
with him, but who cares?
Look, I don't even know
where my relationship is
with Leonard is right now.
So says your
prefrontal cortex.
But meanwhile, the limbic system
of your brain is calculating
that if another woman
is attracted to Leonard,
it must be because
he's desirable.
Well, of course
I mean, he's great.
He's smart, he's sweet,
and, ooh, in the bedroom, whew,
let me tell you,
he really tries.
So it does bother you.
Fine, it bothers
me a little.
No. You know what?
This is stupid.
It doesn't bother me.
Okay, it bothers me.
But only because she
wouldn't stop laughing.
Leonard is not that funny.
And there you have it;
prefrontal cortex reasoning
versus limbic lust.
If this were a boxing match,
they might call it
"The thrilla adjacent
to the amygdala."
(laughs)
If you were
a brain scientist,
you would be busting
a gut right now!
So, how was work today?
Ah, it was
all right, I guess.
Got to Heimlich a
cherry stem out of Sheldon.
Caught Raj right in the eye.
Oh!
You're kidding.
No, Raj had to go to the nurse.
Wow. Anything else?
Mmm, the nurse is a woman,
so he couldn't talk to her.
She had to bring him
a Grover puppet
so he could point at what hurt.
Is that it?
Isn't that enough?
It had the weaponized fruit
and a puppet.
What more do you want?
Oh, good, Leonard, you're here.
Science news.
This will interest you.
And, Penny, feel free
to paint your nails.
What do you got?
I believe Alex may
have unearthed
the grade school
science project
that could be my ticket
to the Nobel Prize.
Behold.
"Magnets: What Do
They Stick To?"
If the answer is "metal,"
it's not exactly groundbreaking.
The original title was
"A Rederivation
of Maxwell's Equations
Regarding Electromagnetism""
I dumbed it down because some
of the more religious people
in town were starting
to say I was a witch.
Sheldon thinks the approach in
this paper might change the way
we calculate ferromagnetic
hysteresis.
Oh, it's about time.
I hated the old way.
Hi. I'm Penny.
Alex.
Uh, do you work
with Dr. Hofstadter?
In a way.
We've kind of been involved
in a five-year experiment.
Oh. Well, you're lucky.
He seems very talented.
And I'm sure a lot of people
want to work with him.
Well, a lot of people can't.
Uh, hey.
Where are we going?
My limbic system wants
to take your pants off.
She seems nice.
Notice people on your own time.
We're working.
Hey, Howie, how you feeling?
Better. Much better.
The other astronauts
held me down,
gave me a shot.
Oh...
Attention, people of Earth:
Tonight, there will be two moons
in the sky.
Howie, stop that.
NASA's watching this!
Put your pants back on!
Whee! Whee!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net