Okay, now holding sides
of hearth in position,
lower mantelpiece assembly
onto top tabs.
Look at that, I built a
fireplace with my own two hands.
You're so butch.
Aw, I got a little paper cut.
Of course you did.
Your hands are
softer than veal.
Oh, before I forget,
Saturday I'm planning a little
Dungeons and Dragons night
with the guys.
Really? That's how you're gonna
spend your Saturday night?
Oh, come on, I hardly ever get
a chance to play anymore.
Oh, you poor thing.
Is having a real-life girlfriend
who has sex with you
getting in the way
of your board games?
Little bit, yeah.
Oh, great! I've always wanted
to play Dungeons and Dragons.
Yeah, oh, I'm sorry.
I should've mentioned
this earlier.
You're not invited.
Why not?
Amy,
from time to time,
we men need to break free
from the shackles
of civility and get in touch
with our primal
animalistic selves.
By rolling dice
and playing make-believe
with little figurines?
Yeah, like a bunch of savages.
Saturday night?
But I've been working
late all week.
That was gonna be our night.
But I have to go.
We play as a group.
If-if I'm not there,
then everyone will blame you.
They'll be all,
"Bernadette ruined everything.
She's the worst."
So, you see?
I have to play
Dungeons and Dragons...
for the marriage.
You're an idiot.
I'm your idiot.
Forever.
So, listen, I know we talked
about getting a bite to eat
in Silver Lake, and then seeing
the Christmas lights
in Griffith Park,
but Leonard's talking about
a big D and D game at his place.
Saturday night just went
from crazy to epic!
Woo-hoo!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 6x11 ♪
The Santa Simulation
Original Air Date on December 13, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
All right, Sheldon,
to start our quest,
you need to open this little
Christmas gift I got you.
A Christmas gift?
You know I don't
enjoy Christmas.
What's wrong
with Christmas?
Oh, where to begin?
Trees indoors.
Overuse of the words
"'tis" and "'twas."
And the absurd custom
of one stocking.
Everyone knows socks
belong in pas.
Who uses one sock?
Pirate with a peg leg?
Actually that helps,
thank you.
Would you just look inside?
Oh, a scroll.
I like scrolls.
They're my third
favorite system of transmitting
the written word.
After stone tablets
and skywriting.
"You have all been
summoned to join
"a thrilling Dungeons
and Dragons adventure.
"Your quest begins
"in a secret northern
village of elves
who have all been massacred."
I like
where this is heading.
"Your task
is to rescue their leader
from a dungeon of ogres."
Oh, that's a saucy twist.
"That leader's name:
Santa Claus""
No, no, no!
It's actually, "Ho, ho, ho,"
but you'll get the hang of it.
Thought it'd be fun to make
a quest with a holiday theme.
Fun?
Mixing Dungeons and Dragons
with Christmas is
like making a sandwich
of grape jelly,
the best-tasting jelly,
and petroleum jelly,
the worst-tasting jelly.
Okay, here we go.
"You find yourselves
"in the smoking remains
of Santa's village.
Clearly, a great battle
has taken place."
Oh, man, the first
monster I see,
I'm gonna sneak up behind
him, whip out my wand,
and shoot my magic
all over his ass.
Do you hear yourself
when you say these things?
Okay,
there are ogre
tracks and a trail
of broken candy
canes in the snow.
Sheldon, what do you do?
I signal my contempt
for your cruel plan
to shove Christmas joy
down my throat
by making a gesture that says,
"Get a load of this guy."
Fine. Howard, what do you do?
I follow the ogre tracks,
checking for secret doors
along the way.
And you discover a secret door
leading to a dark corridor.
Okay, guys, let's make a plan:
spell casters in the back,
warriors in the front...
No, screw that noise,
I'm going in.
Hang on, Santa,
I'm coming for you!
Okay, you run into
a room full of weapons,
hit a trip wire...
...a cannon blows your face off,
you die, you're out of the game.
But... a canon?
Am I really out of the game?
Lucky.
Okay, come on, moving on.
Wait, doesn't anyone have
a roof resurrection?
Because if you've got
one, I need it bad.
Get in here with your rod
and give it to me.
Okay, you need
to say these things
in your head before
you say them out loud.
Hey, guys.
I don't mean to interrupt
your little game,
but I thought you'd like to see
what you're missing out on.
So...
Bernadette?
Bernadette's wearing
leopard-print pumps
and a rack-tastic red dress
from Forever 21.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
And there's Amy,
showing all kinds of ankle.
In an outfit I'm assuming is
from Forever 63.
And I, myself...
...am wearing a little
number that got me
out of two speeding
tickets and jury duty.
I know they're making
a rhetorical point,
I just don't know what it is.
See you, boys. We
are going drinking.
Uh, wait,
can I come with you?
My character died.
Sorry, Raj,
it's girls' night out.
Maybe another time.
Okay...
Come on.
Ooh!
Girls' night, girls' night!
How does he not hear that?
So, what's the plan?
Are we gonna teach
our fellas a lesson
by getting stinking drunk,
luring strange men
into the bathroom,
and turning the toilet stall
into a temple of the senses?
No!
Geez, who's Forever 63 now?
Can we get another bottle of
champagne for the table?
Don't worry.
It's my treat.
Thanks.
Wow!
You should come
to girls' night more often.
And not just because
if you weren't here,
this would be a can of Pabst.
My pleasure; nothing
makes me happier
than the chance
to spoil a lady.
Just ask my dog.
My vet says if I give her
any more foie gras,
she's going to die of gout.
Hey, let's help Raj
meet a girl tonight.
No, no, no, I'm fine.
Okay, wait, are we talking
one-night stand or do we want
to get him into a relationship?
Let's get him laid!
Stop it.
You're ruining girls' night.
Raj, you're a great guy,
you're in a bar full of
single women; let us help you.
Yeah, you're
a real catch.
I know you're shy,
but that doesn't mean
you shouldn't have someone
wonderful in your life.
That's sweet of you.
But what can you do to help?
We'll nose around,
see if we can find a nice girl,
and then introduce you.
Okay.
Well, a couple of things.
Don't tell them
I come from money.
I want them to love me for me.
They must be insanely hot.
Like, nines or tens.
Nines or tens?
Okay, an eight is acceptable
if she's willing to bring
another eight to the hot tub.
Bottom line:
you'll take
any woman who'll
have you, right?
In a New Delhi minute.
I don't remember you buying
these miniatures in my store.
Oh, uh, yeah.
I got 'em on Amazon.
Sure. I get it.
Why support a friend
when you can support
a multinational conglomerate
that is crushing the life
out of that friend?
I know, but when I shop online,
I can do it on the toilet.
Have you seen my store?
The whole place is a toilet.
C-Can we please move this along?
Yeah, sorry.
Uh, you come to the
end of the tunnel
and find a large chest.
What do you do?
And, Howard, do not say,
"I feel up the large chest."
Excuse me,
I'm a married man now.
I wasn't going to say
anything so juvenile.
Great. What do you do?
I walk up
to the large chest,
bury my face in it
and go.
I open the chest.
It's locked, but suddenly
the door behind you slams shut
and now the walls of the room
start closing in.
That's not good.
My character and I
both have claustrophobia.
Glowing letters appear
on the chest that read,
"If squashed to death
you wish not to be,
sing of Svaty Vaclav
and his victory."
Who the hell is Svaty Vaclav?
Walls are getting closer.
Oh, boy, happy place,
happy place.
Wait, Svaty Vaclav was
the Duke of Bohemia.
You're ten seconds away
from getting crushed!
Nine, eight...
What are we supposed to do?
...seven, six...
Wait, wait.
Svaty Vaclav is better known
as Good King Wenceslas
from the beloved
Victorian Christmas carol.
Never heard of it.
Must be the one Christmas song
not written by a Jewish guy.
...three, two...
Somebody sing the damn song!
♪ Good King Wenceslas
looked out ♪
♪ On the feast of Stephen
♪ When the snow lay
'round about ♪
♪ Deep and crisp and even
The walls are getting slower.
♪ Brightly shone the moon
that night ♪
♪ Though the frost
was cru-el ♪
♪ When a poor man
came in sight ♪
♪ Gath'ring winter fu-el
The walls stop! You're safe!
That was amazing, Sheldon.
How did you know that?
It was simple.
I combined a well-known,
historical fact
about Bohemia with the memory
of my grandparents,
Mee-Maw and Pop-Pop,
singing Christmas carols
while I sat in front of the fire
and tried to build
a high-energy particle
accelerator out of Legos.
Okay, continuing
our quest.
W-W-Wait.
There's still four more verses.
You don't sing a song
and not finish it.
♪ Hither, page,
and stand by me ♪
♪ If thou know'st it,
telling ♪
♪ Yonder peasant, who is he?
♪ Where and what his dwelling?
♪ Brightly shone the moon that
night, though the frost... ♪
Looks like he's
doing pretty good.
Of course he is.
Look, that girl just got
dumped by her boyfriend.
She's angry, she's drunk,
and her favorite movie
is Slumdog Millionaire.
I mean...
That is some low-hanging fruit.
Oh, here he comes.
So, how'd it go?
Great.
I bought her a couple
of drinks,
and she gave me
her e-mail address.
Ooh!
"Jennifer@not-even-if-you-were-
the-last-guy-on-earth.loser""
What?
I'm sorry, Raj.
Why can't I find someone?
I'm smart, I've got a cool job,
and my naturally
bronzed complexion
means I can pull off
mustard yellow
in a way most guys can't.
Oh, honey,
it's not you, it's them.
No, it's not.
She was too beautiful for me.
Why would you say that?
It's true.
I'm always attracted
to women I can't have.
I do it all the time.
I did the same thing
with the two of you.
The two of them?
I don't understand.
Well, uh, there was a time
when I had a thing for Penny,
and I thought she
was into me, too,
because she got drunk and naked
and climbed into bed with me.
But apparently
I misread those signals.
And you liked Bernadette also?
That was before Penny.
I make it a rule
to only fall for
one of my friends'
girlfriends at a time.
I'm very old-fashioned that way.
So at, uh, some point,
you probably had
a thing for me, too.
No, not really.
Oh, come on, Raj,
not even a little bit?
Not that I can think of.
Think harder.
Nope.
I guess the heart wants
what the heart wants.
Or in this case, doesn't.
I mean, at all.
What?
♪ Ye who now will
bless the poor ♪
♪ Shall yourselves
find blessing ♪
♪ Ba-da-bum.
Done?
I think the word you're
looking for is "bravo."
Okay, you leave the room
and find yourself
standing before a pool
of melted snowmen.
Melted snowmen?
Are there carrots
and lumps of coal in the water?
I don't know.
What's the difference?
It's a game of
the imagination, Leonard.
Paint a picture.
Fine.
You leave the room
and find yourself
standing before a pool
of melted snowmen.
There are carrots and
lumps of coal in the water.
What happened to the
top hats and the corncob pipes?
You see those, too.
Oh, it's like I'm really there.
I gotta tell you, this-this is
the most holiday fun I've had
since my therapist changed
my anxiety medication
and I stopped caring about
the blood in my stool.
Good story.
What are you drinking there?
Little eggnog?
Yes.
What, is there a problem?
No, it's nice to see you
enjoying a holiday beverage.
Pretty Christmasy.
Since when is eggnog
a Christmas drink?
Eggs are available
all year 'round.
I've been known to
enjoy this poolside.
Come on, Sheldon.
You know all the Christmas
stories, and the carols,
you've got an eggnog
mustache going on there.
Just admit it.
You're getting
a little Yuletide spirit.
Oh, don't be silly.
Christmas is a bunch of baloney
created by the tinsel industry.
Why is this so important to you?
Honestly, because I had enough
crappy Christmases as a kid
and I'm tired of you
sucking the joy out of them now.
What was so bad
about them?
I grew up in a house
full of crazy academics.
Instead of leaving Santa
milk and cookies,
we had to leave him
a research paper.
And in the morning,
you could tell he'd been there
because the paper
would be graded.
No wonder you love Christmas.
That sounds amazing.
It wasn't amazing.
I got a C-minus
four years in a row.
Yeah, I'm familiar
with your work.
C-minus was your gift.
Amy, I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you.
It's fine.
I'm used to being the girl
who never gets looked at twice.
I didn't have my first kiss
till I was 22,
and the guy only did it so
I'd give him back his insulin.
Sometimes the pancreas wants
what the pancreas wants.
Forget it.
I don't expect
you guys to understand.
I understand.
In seventh grade,
I played Spin the Bottle
and it landed on Alina Shankar.
She said if I came near her,
she would break
the bottle and cut me.
You think that's bad?
In college, I passed out
at a frat party
and woke up with
more clothes on.
Sometimes I get so lonely,
I sit on my left hand
until it goes numb,
then I put it in
my right hand and pretend
I'm holding hands
with another person.
I do that, too.
Sometimes the left hand
tries to cop a feel.
And I let it.
It's kind of nice
to talk to someone
who understands what
it feels like to be alone.
It is, isn't it?
But you're not alone anymore.
Now you've got Sheldon.
I do.
And don't worry, someday
you'll have somebody, too.
Thank you.
I hope she's half as
lovely and amazing as you are.
Thank you, Rajesh.
He wants me, I'm good.
We can go now.
Damn it.
What?
Now that I know
she doesn't like me,
I'm kind of into her.
All right.
I think I cracked the code
to lower the drawbridge.
Great.
Let's do it.
The drawbridge is lowering.
My carpal tunnel's acting up.
Play through
the pain!
You did it!
The drawbridge is down.
You cross the chasm
and find yourself in
a small dungeon room.
And in the corner,
chained to the wall,
you see a bloodied and beaten
Santa Claus.
He says, "Ho, ho, help me."
Yes, we found Santa!
Christmas is saved!
Don't ever tell
my mother I said that.
I take out
my skeleton key
and run to Santa
to unchain him.
But first, I cast
a spell of paralysis
on Stuart and Howard.
Wait, what are you doing?
You can't talk;
you're paralyzed.
I get right up in Santa's
big, fat face and say...
Well, well, well,
jolly old Saint Nick,
we meet again.
Yeah, I believe
the last time we spoke
was in the Baybrook Mall
in Galveston, Texas,
when I was five years old,
isn't that right?
Uh, okay.
My mother
dragged me there
and she plopped me
down on your lap
and you asked me
what I wanted for Christmas.
And I told you "my Pop-Pop,"
because that was the year
my grandfather died.
I missed him
and I wanted him back.
This is weird, right?
Pop-Pop was the only one
in my family
who encouraged me
to pursue science.
But you didn't bring
him back, did you?
Instead, I got Lincoln Logs.
Well, you can build a lot of
neat things out of Lincoln Logs,
but Pop-Pop ain't one of 'em.
And now you're here
asking me for something--
to save you.
Well, sorry, Mr. Kringle,
but today's not your day.
I'm leaving you here to rot,
and I hope the ogres
feast on your bones.
I take the skeleton key,
and I toss it into the chasm,
and on the way out, I give Santa
a swift kick in his
bowl full of jelly!
Okay.
So Wolowitz and Stuart
are paralyzed, Santa's dead,
and I picked this over
having sex with my girlfriend.
Santa?
Oh, hello, Sheldon.
You should be asleep.
Well, then, you shouldn't have
jingle bells on your boots.
Oh...
I've been wanting
to talk to you.
I'm sorry I disappointed you
when you were a little boy.
I-I can do a lot
of magical things,
but unfortunately bringing your
Pop-Pop back isn't one of them.
I understand.
But I-I do have
something special for you.
Close your eyes.
Oh, I hope it's a train.
Oh, it's better than a train.
Two trains?
Better.
I'm getting three trains.
Okay, open 'em.
This is for leaving me
in the dungeon
to be eaten alive by ogres!
Wait, uh, uh, hang on.
I-In my defense...
Ho, ho, ho, ya big dork!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player
www.tvsubtitles.net