Mad Men
Season 2
Ep 11
I lay on my pillow
at the Sherry-Netherland Hotel.
Delicious and destroyed.
Inhaling the fragrance
of the sheets.
Feeling the warmth of where
you were just laying.
You make me new
with laughter.
You make me old
with wisdom.
You make wine taste sweeter.
Who wrote that?
I write a lot of poetry
when I'm inspired.
I guess I shouldn't be
surprised by anything you do.
You shouldn't.
It's insulting.
I have to keep you in line,
or I'll lose you.
Yes, you will.
I don't like the idea
of making you older.
I just meant...
I don't know.
It doesn't matter
how old I am.
Our souls are the same age.
Oh, God.
You're getting to me.
How do I know I'm not just
going to eat another mushroom and
this room will disappear
and I'll be back on a train to Trenton?
and this room will disappear
Because I love you, Jane.
This is hard for you.
I know it.
You don't want me
to talk about it, but...
Margaret and Mona have been in
your life for the last 40 years.
30.
Listen,
I'm not being impulsive,
because I've been thinking
about this all the time.
I want you to be my wife.
What?
Marry me.
Roger, are you serious?
Will you do that for me?
90% of Right Guard users
say they play sports.
60% wear it
for their girls as well.
Most impressive, 80% of the fellas
saying yes to the question
"Does Right Guard make you
feel more confident at work?"
Did anyone watch
Loretta Young last night?
I was supposed to.
What happened?
I can't even describe it,
it was so awful.
Creative, you think
old Donny Draper will mind
if we think better
on a full stomach?
Well, if you'll all swear
Gillette dropped in.
- Are you kidding?
- Absolutely.
I'll pretend they're here
if you give me some actual ideas.
Right Guard already
has a great campaign...
"men being men."
You know, women
smell bad, too.
Not you, of course.
Women have perfume.
"Perfume does not
fight wetness. "
Loretta Young.
She's my dad's favorite.
The aprons.
The nauseating upholstery
on the couch.
Strangers who drop by.
- Hear from Kinsey?
- What do you mean?
Did you read what's
going on down there?
In this day and age.
The papers said it's going to
be Little Rock all over again.
I don't know why people
keep stirring up trouble.
It's bad for business.
Just another reason
not to watch TV.
Kurt doesn't
even have one.
You have to have one.
It's your job.
You're going to miss
the playoff.
It's a different life
for single men.
What do you do
with your spare time?
I like concerts.
I like park.
He saw Bob Dylan
at Carnegie Hall.
I heard him on the radio.
So we're not going
to work at all.
Tell Right Guard, short of
a new product just for women,
we need more research
and time.
And lunch.
Can we split a lobster?
Does he sound
like the album?
When you hear him,
he plays it himself.
It must be
something to see.
I'd love to go sometime.
- So go.
- Yes, I should.
You will go with me.
- What?
- You would go with me?
Oh, no. I... I don't want
to impose if you have plans.
When you hear him,
you will smile like this.
Pick you up at 8.
I live in Brooklyn.
It's a hike.
Neighbors.
Joey says that Duck's
in the blind.
It's now or never.
This is why I booked
a day early.
What did Ricardo
in there say?
He's an hourly contact
with TWA,
and they've offered
to buy you new luggage.
And fill it
with my things?
Ricardo recommended
a tailor.
Chinese.
And they said they've got
a whole shop full of swim trunks.
I brought mine.
There's not going
to be any swimming.
The convention doesn't
start for another day.
You want to be the hundredth person to
shake someone's hand at some convention?
For what, a free pen?
We'll follow-up
face to face.
Forget Santa Monica.
Take your list,target some of these guys,
and make them feel special.
Didn't Roger
give you leads?
He did.
I'm going to need
sunglasses.
Come on.
You wanna be on vacation, Pete?
'Cause I can make that happen.
Old-fashioned.
Excuse me.
My friends and I have
been speculating about you,
trying to decide
who you are and what you do.
- Why?
- Are you an actor?
- No.
- Are you an astronaut?
No.
Someone over there
would like to meet you...
a young woman...
only if you were
none of these things.
I'm Vicompte Monteforte
d'Alsace.
- Willy.
- Don.
This is Don.
She's been staring
at you all day.
Can't stop talking
about you.
I'm Joy.
Oh, and this is Rocci.
You look so comfortable
alone by the pool all day.
I wonder if you're
waiting for someone.
I am.
Do you smell that jasmine?
Mmm.
Dine with us.
Maybe another time.
Well. That never happens.
Hello.
Pete, this is Joy and Rocci
and Vicompte Monteforte.
Very good.
D'Alsace. Willy.
That's quite a name.
Peter Dykeman Campbell.
Have we met somewhere?
Newport?
I have a terrible memory
for faces.
- Nice meeting you.
- Yes.
A pleasure to meet you.
Look for us.
Everybody here
is late for everything.
Oh. I just saw Tony Curtis
in the men's room.
Handing out towels?
Tony Curtis, Don.
A thing like that.
Who's for dinner?
Rodney Barnes.
Classic salesman turned executive.
And this interesting
scientist, Caleb Sawyer.
He has this "optiman" thesis.
In addition to rockets,
they're going to start engineering man...
you know,
for travel in space.
Uh, new organs,
super strength.
You know the Soviets
are working on it.
Are all of our meetings
like this?
It's American Aviation
and Rocketdyne.
It's not a joke.
Can I get a drink here
or what?
Raphael was a little tired.
But the Fifth Arrondissement
has most of your good restaurants.
Of course, we kept getting lost,
and every time Sherry asked for directions,
it turned out to be another American.
Well, there you go. I'll take Jane
to Paris, and I'll send Mona to Reno.
You don't have to
marry her, do you?
No.
Maybe you and Mona could work out
one of those modern arrangements.
George, stop.
It is possible
that you'll get tired of her,
and then where will you be?
Mona doesn't have
a right to anything...
not my company money,
not my family money.
She's lucky
I'm giving her anything.
You know what? We've been
miserable for years.
I don't want to die
with that woman.
Calm down.
I didn't know that.
This is the life I was
always meant to have.
Congratulations.
Mona has the marriage license,
and she was to hurt you.
If you want to be with
this 20-year-old girl,
you're going to have
to buy it from her.
And I have to warn you.
Women in this situation
become extra irrational.
Well, how badly
does she want to hurt me?
I have a list of conditions
and an alimony that could
support Rita Hayworth.
Think of all the good things
in life and cut them in half.
I want you to push
as hard as you can,
but I want it done.
- Mr. Phillips is here.
- In a minute.
I'll proceed.
But I want you
to think about it.
Duck Phillips,
this is George Rothman.
Actually,
we know each other.
Roger.
It's good to see you, Duck.
Was he for you or against you?
He's supposed to be the best.
Him or Marvin Hughes.
That's who Mona has.
He's her cousin.
How bad was it?
Do I want to know?
I don't think my circumstances
were the same as yours.
What can I do for you?
Actually, this might not be
the best time to talk about this.
Can't you tell I'd welcome
a change in subject?
Well, good, then.
What the hell, right?
Listen, we're coming up
on two years together here.
Did you get me something?
I think we're
at a point in time...
where I need to know
what your plans are.
A partnership.
I think I've earned it.
Right.
I'll bring it up at the next
meeting of the partners.
Thank you.
Of course you might have to come in
and be an advocate for yourself.
I'd be proud to present
my accomplishments.
Good.
Because I'm at a loss.
What is that
supposed to mean?
You haven't exactly delivered
on that 30% you promised.
I think we've really performed
in a very dismal year.
These things are cyclical.
You know that.
Is there some question about
my value to Sterling Cooper?
Just think about the board.
Bert Cooper hates everyone,
and his sister...
well, she does whatever he says.
Don... he's only 12 1/2%, but...
I can't say he's
your biggest cheerleader.
What are you saying?
Everyone thinks
you're a fine fellow.
But if I were you,
I'd go out there
and make rain.
Thank you
for being so candid.
This year we have seen an historic
collaboration in American aerospace.
Building on Lockheed's
new Polaris A3,
Bell Aerosystems,
Areojet General, and NASA
have developed
a restartable rocket engine.
Can we get the lights, please?
We at Space Technology
Laboratories
have set our minds to
the challenges of the future.
In July, Khrushchev said
the Soviet Union now has an anti-missile
that can hit a fly
in outer space.
Space Technology Laboratories
is leading a coordinated effort
to create an invulnerable warhead...
multiple, independently targetable
re-entry vehicles - M.I.R.V.s.
And North American
Aviation's vernier thruster
allows the primary missile
to correct its trajectory
before shooting off several warheads
hidden inside its nose cone.
The M.I.R.V. can be launched from
a submarine or land into the stratosphere.
Then it splits off
into 14 individual warheads.
That's 14 different targets.
14 different cities.
14 individual warheads, each with
ten times the payload of Nagasaki.
Even if Khrushchev hits 35%,
that's 5 out of 14.
Secondary strike capabilities
will be extremely limited...
...due to the decrease
in infrastructure and population.
(U.S.S.R.
Moscow)
Total annihilation.
Do you realize that one of these
companies spends more annually on media
than three Lucky Strikes?
It's a gold rush.
Where are the valets?
So much for cheap labor.
Go see if General Dynamics
beat us here.
Drop these
by the front desk.
You don't want them
under your arm.
Hello.
I think you're happy
to see me.
Well, take a good look.
I have to be on my way.
Are you working?
Yes.
That's too bad.
I'm going to Palm Springs.
You should come with me.
I don't know about that.
Why would you deny yourself
something you want?
You want to get
your things?
No.
Well. Why don't we give it
a few more minutes?
Enjoy the scenery.
Order some drinks.
I think Don needed
to make a phone call.
Hello?
Just leave the bags there.
Who lives here?
Friends.
They're in Sardinia.
I'm supposed to be
in Edward's room.
That's Stephanie
in the swimming pool.
And Willy and Rocci you've met.
And there's Greta
and her friend Carlos.
I'm surprised to see them
in the same place.
Come with me.
Hello, Greta.
Hello, Joy, darling.
Who's this?
This is my friend Don.
I'm Carlos Villa Declan.
It's medicinal.
importante?
Good-bye, Carlos.
Come for a swim with me?
You can go inside and ask for
some trunks, or you can go au naturel.
I think I should...
go inside.
You're white as a sheet.
Don, are you okay?
Where am I?
You're with me, remember?
You have heat exhaustion.
- What are you doing?
- It's fine. It's medicine.
Klaus is a doctor.
No. It's okay.
I just need some water
and some aspirin.
Everybody out.
I thought you were
going to break your neck.
Next time you feel faint,
lean towards the pool.
See you at dinner.
Little girl,
don't get any ideas.
This man needs rest.
I found you
some clothes upstairs.
Who are these people?
They're friends.
We're nomads together.
What are you all doing here?
There's an open door policy.
You should rest up
for dinner.
Have you ever
had Mexican food?
No.
You're going to like it.
Come out when you're ready.
You're spoiled.
This is great food.
This is Mexican.
- It's not...
- I don't like Mexican.
- I wanted the French again.
- We are in Califor...
- Sweetheart.
- Mexican does pig. I don't eat pig.
I've already told you.
Okay, well.
Oh, he's here.
Oh. Ah! Don!
Klaus, will you
let Don sit here?
Would you like
some wine, Don?
Klaus, is that okay?
Hmm, he looks
healthy enough.
You must be hungry.
Everyone,
to our guest.
To not being
carried out in a box.
So, Don,
what's your story?
I don't know how
to answer that.
Where are you from?
New York.
Try this. It's a pepper
filled with cheese.
- Darling.
- And there's the sauce.
Joy and Willy think
that you're a spy.
But your wallet fell out
when they carried you inside.
You're in advertising.
Or I'm a really good spy.
You'll never meet a group of people
more interested in professions,
and yet there is not
one of us here who has one.
I'm a physician.
But you don't work.
So I assume
you're all well off.
I should take something up.
I'm smarter than I've
ever been in my life.
Not only do I know so much,
but my brain is more agile.
I didn't know
that was possible.
And my muscles are
remembering their skills.
Are you an athlete, Don?
I've played some football
in high school.
Willy was
a champion fencer.
I made the Olympic team twice.
1948 London,
1952 Helsinki.
Foils.
It's hardly a sport.
Let's play places.
I start.
You have to name a place
that starts with the last letter
of the place that's named.
Guarnavaca.
Alaska.
It's not a city.
Amalfi.
Ir
Naples.
- Stockholm.
- Malaga.
Athens.
Sarajevo.
Oslo.
O is impossible.
Odessa.
Orezzo.
Osaka.
Oakland.
Dunkirk.
Kabul.
London.
- Nice.
- Essen.
Nairobi.
Itanbul.
Lisbon.
Negril.
Lausanne.
How old are you?
I'm 21.
I'm 36.
You're still warm.
Who are you?
I'm Joy.
There's glazed.
Coconut, crullers.
Oh, Bismarcks.
Who brought these
in, Cosgrove?
I haven't seen contracts,
but this is certainly a good sign.
Gosh, Joan,
thank him for me.
We're going to be getting
a delivery like this every week,
with all the varieties.
Hmm, Lemonaires.
Are these for us?
The spoils of victory.
8:00 in this evening.
- Excuse me?
- Our destination.
Oh. Okay.
- Where are you two going?
- To the Bob Dylan.
Isn't that interesting?
Peggy and Kurt
in the Village, oh, my.
Oh, don't be shy.
I think you two
are adorable.
What is with this?
- You think Peggy and I?
- We do.
I'm homosexual.
I don't think that means
what you think it means.
Kurt.
No. I make love
with the man,
not the woman.
What?
Eight?
Of course. Absolutely.
Enjoy the dancing beans.
Did you know about this?
He's from Europe.
It's different there.
More for me.
So Kurt is a pervert.
How about that?
He certainly
had me fooled.
Mr. Cosgrove, do you want me
to invite the girls in?
I knew queers existed.
I just don't want
to work with them.
What, he's the first homo
you ever met in advertising?
You think Smitty's in love?
Which bathroom does he use?
Joan, get the girls in here.
What are you reading?
William Faulkner.
I took a survey
of American literature.
So you're in school?
I was at Pembroke.
Willy has a house in Rhode Island,
so it seemed convenient.
Didn't fit.
Is it good?
Sex is good.
This book is just okay.
I like sex.
You do, too,
I can tell.
Greta and Carlos
are arguing.
I knew they had problems.
Greta has.
Carlos never had any.
Good morning.
Do you hear them
in there?
Oh, the humiliations
have been spectacular.
Christien is coming with the children.
I hope you don't mind.
No matter how late I show up,
I'm never later than Christien.
Look at him.
You are so beautiful.
Papa, ne touche pas.
You are a brat.
She has her mother's
temperament.
That's why you love me.
I make beautiful
babies, don't I?
I'll see you outside.
That's your father?
He doesn't want people
to think he's old.
Yes, it's Peter Campbell from
Sterling Cooper for Clarence Hastings.
Is there any way
we can meet here?
I can't drive, and there doesn't seem
to be a taxi
that will take me
to Pasadena.
We can meet by the pool.
Thank you.
How are you two today?
Duck Phillips.
St. John Powell, how are you?
Capital, capital.
This is Alec Barton.
Duck Phillips.
By Jove, man,
catch up.
I have a bit of a cold.
Well, it's warm already.
It'll open up the passages.
Oh, it's warm or he would have drunk it.
So, how are you
finding New York?
Brief.
We're going to visit
a candy plant, the Cadbury.
Then it's fate
that I caught you here.
You say fate.
I say another round, gar
Have mine.
If y're not drinking,
what's this about?
I keep thinking how I miss
doing things your way.
Two years ago, you said you wanted
to come here and be with your children.
They're grown.
It's not a good time.
I'm not going to take "no"
for an answer.
I wouldn't expect you to.
You know, if we were hiring,
you would be at the top of our list.
That's too bad.
I love you New York ad men.
To our noble profession.
Cin-cin.
How old are your children?
Alec's wife is about
to have their first.
Do you think that I have
nothing to offer you?
No, of course not.
You represent
over 20 American companies,
doing business in Europe.
I know you want
a U.S. presence.
You're wasting your time doing things
like digging around here for Cadbury.
And you could make
a difference?
What if I were to bring you
every account at Sterling Cooper?
Fully serviced
and completely satisfied?
What are you
talking about?
I'm suggesting that you
buy Sterling Cooper.
There are very few client conflicts.
All you have to do is change the welcome mat.
I didn't know
it was for sale.
Roger Sterling has
a 20-year-old fianc¨¦
and his wife's lawyer's not going
to leave him a pot to piss in.
Alec, would you excuse us?
Did he send you here
with a price?
Send me here?
51% will cost you
a lot less than you think,
plus a finder's fee.
2%.
I want to be in charge
of all international business,
and I have to be president.
Creative reports to me,
or the whole thing falls apart.
Thank you for thinking of us.
To old friends.
Hello.
Did you have
any trouble finding me?
- Neighbors.
- Right.
Would you like some wine?
Very much.
Listen, in the office,
I hope you weren't embarrassed.
No. It's okay.
It's good.
Well, if you have a man that you'd
like to go to the concert with tonight,
I completely understand.
Are you not
on the trip tonight?
I don't know why I pick
the wrong boys.
You're drinking sad.
I don't know.
What's wrong with me?
You are old style.
No, I'm not.
This is not modern office,
a working woman.
What are you talking about?
I fix you.
We should leave.
Each time, Bob Dylan is late.
He will not miss us a half hour.
Sit.
Look at me.
I'm very good.
- Just a trim.
- Yes. Yes.
- For you.
- Oh, my God.
It's OK.
It's good.
We're headed
to Lyford Cay, Nassau.
Why?
It's what we do.
Something about taxes.
It's very different
than here.
I think you'd like it.
You'll need a tuxedo.
Will I?
You don't need a passport, unless
you want to follow us to Capri after.
Stephanie's uncle's
an ambassador.
Joy.
My father
will take care of you.
He likes having you around.
You're beautiful,
and you don't talk too much.
I'm not possessive.
You can be
with anyone you want.
Hello, Joy.
Who is this?
Christien, this is Don.
Bernard and Amelia.
Hello.
Hello there.
Did Isabel ring?
Why would she?
Because I'm sick
of her attorneys.
These are my children.
They should be with me.
Are you in Edward's room?
You can have it.
Thank you.
As you can see,
we're very tired.
Come, Bernard.
You gave away our room?
Looks like someone
doesn't want to sleep.
Come in.
Joyce seems
to have stepped away.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Crane
accidentally opened this.
Thank you, Joan.
My, oh, my. A case.
They're all there.
I checked.
All the card says
is that it's for you.
Well, thank you,
Miss Holway.
Why don't you
just take this?
As a finder's fee.
A whole bottle?
It's the good stuff.
I know. Thank you.
Anything else?
No, thank you.
"The town of Oxford
is an armed camp,
"following riots that accompanied
the registration of the first Negro
"in the university's
118-year history.
"James H. Meredith
was formally enrolled
- "in the University of Mississippi..."
- Hello, all.
How the hell
was California?
Looks like Draper
let you off the leash.
Did you see this?
Yes, I did.
Strange, isn't it?
"Americans are free,
in short,
"to disagree with the law,
but not to disobey it."
For any government
of laws...
So how was it?
Spectacular, business-wise,
but I don't know that
I'd want to live there.
Here. These are for everybody.
I'd like to see it
for myself.
What's wrong with it?
The people.
I don't know.
I'm glad to be home.
Has Don checked in?
Is he here?
No. I don't think so.
"...by force, or threat of force,
could long deny that man..."
You look different.
It's my hair.
Right.
Kurt's a homo.
"No judge would be
sure of his..."
So...
are you leaving us?
No.
So? What, then?
What if I told you that
the international divisions
of General Foods, Bird's Eye,
Campbell's Soup, Chevron Oil,
Lever Brothers, Hoover,
Warner Brothers, Eastern Airlines,
and Chrysler can all
be part of Sterling Cooper?
How is that possible?
St. John Powell, of Putnam, Powell,
and Lowe, called me the other day.
They want to open up a New York office
to deal with their American clients.
They love the idea of just sticking a key
in the door at Sterling Cooper.
Really?
Is this as solid
as American Airlines?
I guess you're happy having to scramble
on the third tier of this industry...
waiting for minor divisions of
major companies to drop in your lap.
On the table will be
mountains of money,
international prestige,
a chance at going public,
and we don't have
to change our name.
I guess we could
think about it.
No. I need to know
that you're open to this.
If so, I'm giving them
five business days to try to impress us
with a price for controlling
interest in the agency.
There he is.
There's the man
I heard so much about.
Five days to make an offer.
Or you can give me a price
and I'll pass it on.
No.
Let them open the kimono.
Daddy! Daddy!
Over here!
This water hole full.
Stop splashing!
Don't do it, darling.
Yay!
Hello. It's Dick Whitman.
Yeah.
I'd love to see you.
Soon.
No. I didn't bring it
with me. Hold on.
I'll see you soon.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
* What'll I do
* When you
* Are far away
* And I am blue?
* What'll I do?
* What'll I do
* When I
* Am wondering who
* Is kissing you?
* What'll I do?
* What'll I do
* With just
* A photograph
* To tell
* My troubles to?
* When I'm alone
* With only Dreams of you **
www.tvsubtitles.net