Previously on Mad Men...
- Let's get out of here.
- No!
They'll knock the door...
- What time is it?
- Shut up.
- You want it so bad...
- I don't want you!
I'm really sorry about that.
Please!
This is a process.
I just want to be
a part of this place.
I think it's on the way up.
I got the job.
You don't say...
I can't stay that long...
I have to go back and
redo the Heinz speech.
( Theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
( Radio playing )
Did you eat my pack
of violet candy?
What?
It's purple and silver.
Don gave it to me
before a presentation once.
- No.
- I need it.
- So you'll buy another one.
- That's not the same.
Don't be such
a strict catholic.
I'll buy one for you
and I'll say a brucha.
How about tonight we go
see that stupid movie
about the guy being
hunted in Africa?
- "The Naked Prey."
- I don't know, Abe.
You're gonna resist the chance
to see Cornel Wilde naked?
I heard he wrestles a boa constrictor.
Sounds pretty dirty.
I can't think beyond
my presentation.
There's always special
circumstances.
That's not true.
I've been working
on Heinz for months.
You know what you want?
You want to take me to work with you
and stick me in a drawer and
open it whenever you get bored.
Fine. You don't want to
see each other anymore?
Jesus!
You always want to push the
button on the whole thing.
I come all the way
up here to make love.
Half the time you don't want to and then
you just do it to get it over with.
It's just hard when I come
right from work.
I need a second
when I walk in the door.
- You sound like my dad.
- ( Sighs ) Fine.
We'll go to the movies. I just can't
promise that my mind won't be elsewhere.
Your mind is always elsewhere.
Why are you doing
this right now?
Most men wouldn't even have
this conversation. They'd just leave.
And why would they do that?
I'm your boyfriend,
not a focus group.
Have a shitty day.
( Door closes )
I don't know.
Can't you make it till Friday?
Because today
is not a good day.
This conversation went in a circle
and we're back where we started.
The answer is no.
Yeah, me, too.
I just had the same
conversation.
No, I think they were different
because yours was private.
( Sighs ) Sorry I'm late.
There's no place
to pee in this city.
- She just got here.
- Then why are you giving me a hard time?
We had the funniest thing
outside our building.
A bunch of students with backpacks
asked us how to get to Broadway.
What's so funny
about that, Jethro?
It's like the campaign.
We could have cast it right there and then.
Stan:
Mmm.
- Megan, can I have a moment?
- Oh, uh, sure.
- She goes to casting now?
- I guess so.
She's kind of been
my junior on this.
I was buying dinner last night
for this large-breasted girl
who calls herself salome,
and she's looking at the menu,
ridiculing this Grandma Moses drawing
and she's bas-out funny.
But I ignore her
because all I can think of
is I'll never be able to draw
as well as a photograph.
Oh, thank God.
I couldn't take
one more omen of doom.
I'm sorry. We're gonna have
to miss the presentation.
We have to head upstate
for Howard Johnson's.
- Really?
- You're running the show.
How does me sitting there
change anything?
Howard Johnson's, huh?
I love the colors,
the atmosphere,
- the clams.
- She's never been to one.
I'm really sorry.
No, we have all
your work, I guess.
I'll check in from the road.
Get your stuff.
Um, break a leg.
- Well, that's a disaster.
- Don't listen to him.
That's a vote of confidence.
Give me one of those.
The fire is primal.
These kids, they all
come there alone,
and gathered in a circle,
they suddenly feel
included.
They're safe from
whatever is out there
in the night, in the darkness.
It's the beans
that brought them together
on that cool night
at the end of the summer.
"Home is where
the Heinz is."
I wish someone
was eating beans.
That guy is.
I did ask for college students.
I know that, Raymond.
And we want you to have
everything you asked for.
Well, stop writing down
what I asked for
and try to figure out
what I want.
Raymond, I saw you
when she was talking.
- You were off somewhere.
- It's very sentimental.
I have that memory.
That's for me.
That's not for kids.
Kids have memories.
And so do the homemakers
who make a home with Heinz.
Raymond, can you see
how passionate she is?
Photography will really capture
the fun on their faces.
- And the glow.
- Did Don sign off on this?
Don loves this work.
Maybe Don doesn't understand
what you wanted either.
Let's not speak for Don.
I'm sorry. I'm not a word
person like you people.
Sure, you are.
And your words are always
"I don't like it."
And I think you're right.
We don't understand you.
Because you do like it.
I think you just like fighting.
Peggy, you're being
oversensitive.
Do you know how often
people come in here
and look at work
and feel something?
Almost never.
You have to run with this.
It's young and it's beautiful.
And no one else is gonna figure
out how to say that about beans.
Can you believe this girl?
I don't know.
Can you?
Miss, you're lucky
that I have a daughter
or I wouldn't be
so understanding.
Raymond, they're frustrated,
but they're not through.
I'm frustrated, too.
- It's close, I guess.
- It's damn close.
Why don't just you and I
have dinner tonight?
Maybe take in a show?
Take your mind off things?
You can try.
Stan:
I've got to admire you.
That was a completely
suicidal move.
Women usually want to please.
Give me sketches
of the talking beans.
I'll write new dialog.
- You're off the business.
- What'd he say?
He said you're off
the business.
Everyone has
somewhere to go today.
I'm going to the movies.
Very good.
Man: One of them gave Sam
a first-class scratch.
Not very good-tempered,
are they?
Woman: Well, neither are
you when you're hungry.
I don't suppose
you've fed them.
No, I can't say I have.
You didn't pack any lion's
milk for me before I left.
You didn't ask me.
You're going to get in trouble.
Want some?
Sure.
What the hell.
Come on.
- Hello.
- Hi.
But why don't they?
It's at least two days
since they've eaten.
- They'll just die.
- Yes, I know.
It must be the formula.
We haven't hit on it yet.
We'll just have try again.
Right, back to
the drawing board.
Formula...
- 13.
Oh, George, I've just been
thinking about the cod-liver oil.
( Growling )
She's not gonna make it
out there on her own.
- Woman: Shh.
- You've got to keep it down.
( Giggling ) Okay.
Aren't you worried?
It'll turn out all right.
Woman: That evening, we suffered
all the agony of parents
whose teenage daughter
is out on her first date.
No.
Just watch the movie.
We returned the next day
only to find Elsa
minus both the young
lion and her food.
( Lion roaring )
( Water running )
Morris: I told you a dozen
sometimes I was coming in.
And I said no,
you're not coming in.
'Cause you don't want
I should see you?
You see me at home,
for Christ's sake.
You stare at me
when I'm sleeping.
Eh, I don't want
to see you anyway.
- I just want to use the photocopy.
- For what?
I'm building my case.
Again?
Who's this?
I'm Peggy Olson.
I work with Ginsberg.
Well, I'm the original.
Okay. Ahem.
It's bedtime.
Miss Olson.
- What time is it?
- It's 8:30.
Mr. Draper's on the phone.
I'll take it in here.
You can go.
Good night.
- Hello. - Dawn didn't get any
calls. Did you get any calls?
- About what?
- Has anyone called you?
I don't think so.
Oh, okay.
Listen, it didn't go well.
- I've got to go.
- I take full responsibility.
( Hangs up )
Hello?
( Sighs )
Why didn't you tell me
you had a family?
- Your father's nice.
- He's not my real father.
People don't understand.
- Are you adopted?
- Actually, I'm from Mars.
( Laughs )
It's fine if you don't believe
me, but that's where I'm from.
I'm a full-blooded martian.
( Laughs )
Don't worry.
There's no plot to take over Earth.
We're just displaced.
Okay.
I can tell
you don't believe me.
That's okay.
We're a big secret.
They even tried
to hide it from me.
That man, my father,
told me a story I was born
in a concentration camp,
but you know that's impossible.
And I never met my mother because
she supposedly died there.
That's convenient.
Next thing I know, Morris there finds
me in a Swedish orphanage.
I was five.
I remember it.
That's incredible.
Yeah.
And then I got
this one communication.
A simple order.
Stay where you are.
Are there others like you?
I don't know.
I haven't been able
to find any.
( Phone ringing )
- Hello?
- Hi. It's me.
You at work?
No, I'm home.
Come up here.
You need me, huh?
I always need you.
What happened?
This guy told me the strangest
thing at work today.
Yeah?
He said he was born
in a concentration camp.
But that's impossible, right?
It happened.
- Come up here.
- Okay.
Hurry.
I'm going to go in there and
sit down with the door closed.
And I want you to buzz me
when he comes in.
One buzz for Don, two
buzzes for Mr. and Mrs.
( One buzz )
- Who died?
- Let's play hooky.
Should I close the door?
Remember when we used to
represent double-sided aluminum?
I remember twins
and a hospital.
Not that part.
Bob Whozit's moved over
to Howard Johnson's
to help them with
their new models.
So how about a completely
debauched and unnecessary
fact-finding boondoggle
to the flagship in...
Plattsburgh, New York?
Just an hour from
scenic lake placid.
- Are you kidding me? - Did you ever hear
the one about the farmer's daughter?
This is where
it all takes place.
- No.
- Don, come on.
Alone, I'm an escapee from some
expensive mental institution.
But the two of us, we're a couple
of rich, handsome perverts.
- I love Howard Johnson's.
- We'll try and stop by.
I think Montreal
is an hour away.
Look, the whole point of going
is to forget about her.
I mean, I'm supposed to have
dinner with Jane's snooty friends,
sit around talking about
Frank Lloyd rice.
I always say it that way.
They hate it.
- ( Laughs )
- You know what?
- I'm gonna take Megan.
- Really?
You can bring Jane.
Megan gets along with everyone.
You're very funny.
Forget it.
Newlyweds.
I'll give Dawn the guy's name.
Dawn, I need you to get
me out of everything
through the weekend.
( Phone rings )
It was a dumb idea.
Don:
Megan, can I have a moment?
Sure.
- You're not gonna say anything?
- What?
I said you look nice and I
said I don't want to do this.
Well, what do you want to do?
Go home, open your vest
and yell at the TV
for the next 20 years?
Go ahead.
God.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I don't know these people.
I do.
And it's not about them.
It's very important to me.
I don't know how many ways to say it.
I should have worn
something more comfortable.
You really do look great.
It's the study of the ways the
things are true or false.
Some things are possibly true.
Some are necessarily true.
Some used to be true.
Some will be true.
Some are true on this planet,
but not necessarily others.
So there's no good and bad
because the truth is relative?
Even if the truth is what
you would call relative,
good and bad are not relative.
Your mistake is
that you're assuming
That because something
is true that it's good.
- Professor's got you there.
- ( All laugh )
I think the truth is good
because it's always real
on any planet.
I have patients who spend years
reasoning out their
motivation for a mistake.
And when they find it out, they
think they've found the truth.
They probably have.
- And then they go and make
the same mistake. - Like who?
Catherine has been the
psychiatrist to some celebrities.
- Wow.
- So they never get better?
I didn't say that.
I just said that it's a myth
that tracing logic all the
way down to the truth
is a cure for neurosis
or for anything else.
Is there a cure for neurosis?
Love works.
I say we postpone this conversation
until after we turn on.
- Shall we?
- Or after we turn in.
Jane, honey, you ready?
What do you think you're doing?
I took your college course.
I say it's time to hit the sack.
- No, we're gonna do this.
- Do what?
I told you, we're going
to take LSD with them.
You were supposed to
clear your schedule.
LSD?
Really?
You really are never
listening, are you?
- How long does it last?
- Please.
I don't want to do this alone.
It'll be good for us.
Okay.
Just copy what they're doing.
I think we are going to go.
- Oh, no.
- We had a lovely time.
No one has to stay.
All I'll say is
that I have taken it
now four times
and every experience was more
beautiful than the last.
And I'm not gonna take it.
I'll be here to guide you.
I'm excited.
I'm not gonna lie;
I'm a little nervous.
This is an experience
of self-fulfilling prophecy.
You have to enter into it
with a spirit of optimism.
It's like a boat trip.
You don't cast off thinking about sinking.
And this boat is perfect.
And the water is calm.
No, you hold on to that.
Go ahead.
Just let it melt
on your tongue.
You always say
I never take you anywhere.
( Traffic noise )
Well, Dr. Leary,
I find your product boring.
( Opera playing )
( Music stops )
( Music resumes )
Leary: Only awareness
can make reality.
And only what's real
can become a dream.
And only from a dream
can you wake to the light.
Okey-dokey.
He's not making this up.
It's from the Tibetan
book of the damned.
The dead, my dear.
"Bardo Thodol" is a guide to dying.
Oh, my God.
Look at my arm.
- I don't want to die.
- Man: Some party.
( Honks )
All absence is death
if we let ourselves know it.
Man: Weren't you the one who said we
were supposed to think positive?
Yes.
I feel like that
when Roger goes to work.
A mere change
is incremental and shallow.
Roger's voice: I'm sitting here listening
to these people have a conversation.
It has nothing to do with me.
( Laughs )
It's incredible.
♪ I keep looking for
a place to fit in ♪
♪ where I can speak my mind ♪
♪ and I've been trying hard
to find the people ♪
♪ that I won't leave behind ♪
♪ they say I've got brains ♪
♪ but they ain't
doing me no good ♪
♪ I wish they could... ♪
Don's voice:
Don't look in the mirror.
What?
- Why didn't you tell me that?
- I did.
I already looked.
Look at me.
Everything's okay.
You are okay.
Now go to your wife.
Why?
Because she wants to be alone
in the truth with you.
Just go already.
♪ I guess I just wasn't ♪
( Songs overlapping )
You're crying.
It's so...
It's perfect here.
Let's go home.
♪ You and I together ♪
♪ I should not want to
be around you ♪
♪ nor should you ♪
♪ want to be around me... ♪
( Baseball game playing )
( Crowd cheering )
( Laughing )
Why are you laughing?
Are you laughing at me?
What's wrong with me?
It's the World Series.
1919.
The Black Sox.
- ( Laughing )
- Were you there?
No, but I'm there.
( Bat cracks )
Look at the cars--
Model T, model T,
model A, model T.
I can't see it.
( Laughing )
What time is it?
How could a few numbers
contain all of time?
I can feel your lips.
- I'm still here.
- I can see you.
- You're beautiful.
- You always say that.
It's all you ever say.
Now I know why
your friends are so smart.
Catherine is not my friend.
She's my doctor.
I knew that,
but I didn't know it.
Sometimes I think she knows
me better than you do.
Do I want to know?
Probably not.
Because it's over?
She's just waiting
for me to say it.
And what does she think of me?
She thinks I'm waiting
for you to say it.
But instead you wrote me
this poem tonight, didn't you?
I knew we were going somewhere
and I didn't want
it to be here.
Do you feel
as relieved as I do?
All I think about
is having an affair.
I see them everywhere.
You never cheated on me?
There was a kiss.
I stopped it.
And then I was mad at you,
that you didn't appreciate it
even though you
didn't know about it.
A younger man?
No, Roger.
That's always been real.
And I won't even ask about you.
I just know for a fact that
you did not fall in love.
So what was wrong again?
You don't like me.
I did.
I really did.
- Is it morning?
- Yes.
I'm sorry I always say it,
but you are so beautiful.
Last night was beautiful.
It was, wasn't it?
Where are you going?
Out the door
and into the elevator,
I suppose.
What about me?
You can take
your time, obviously.
I figured I'd just check
into a hotel for a while.
I don't want to displace you.
What are you talking about?
I imagined all the screaming
and fighting and lawyers.
It's just so beautiful
how we were able
to be there together
in the truth like you wanted.
- Are you leaving me?
- No.
We're leaving each other
just like you said.
- I didn't say that.
- You did.
You said so many
amazing things.
- You were speaking German.
- I don't know German.
You were quoting your father.
It must have been yiddish.
But I was on drugs.
I obviously didn't mean any of it.
So your psychiatrist
didn't tell you that you knew
is was over, but you were
waiting for me to say it?
I did say that.
It's good that you did
because we both know it.
No.
I don't know.
It's going to be
very expensive.
I know.
Dawn, I need you to get
me out of everything
through the weekend.
It was a dumb idea.
- Megan, can I have a moment?
- Oh, uh, sure.
Listen, there's
a Howard Johnson's upstate
I thought we'd go and make
a long weekend of it.
- What about Heinz?
- What about it?
It'll be fine.
Remember California?
- Two hotel rooms.
- Of course.
- But we can go tomorrow.
- Come on.
Let's go right now.
We can do this.
I don't know.
I'm the boss.
I'm ordering you.
Come on.
You know it's like an hour
and a half from my parents.
They're coming to visit soon.
I know.
You're right.
And we don't have
to work much tonight.
Someone named Dale is going to
give us the royal treatment.
You like orange sherbet?
- I don't know.
- You've never had it?
- You are in for a treat.
- Sounds great.
Everything okay?
I'm just tired.
So take a nap.
Relax.
When you wake up, you will
feel like you're on vacation.
You know what? Tell me more about
what we're going to be doing
in Howard Johnson's
so I can get some sleep.
( Exhales )
( Coughing )
Could you open your window?
I wonder how Heinz went.
Peggy seemed nervous.
Peggy knows what she's doing.
What are you worrying
about that for?
I feel like I abandoned
the team.
You feel bad because you got to
take off and they had to work?
I don't.
There has to be some advantage
to being my wife.
I'll check in with Peggy later.
Okay.
They got an indoor pool.
Did you bring that
suit from Acapulco?
I forgot.
I was rushing.
We'll get you a new one after we check in.
I brought mine.
- Mr. Draper?
- It's Don.
Pleased to meet you.
This is my wife Megan.
Dale Vanderwort.
A little more notice, I would have
rolled out the orange carpet.
I've got your room
all set for you.
Actually, I'd like something
to eat and something to drink.
Sure, I'm going to bring you
a sampling of everything.
- Do you like clams?
- I like everything.
I got you something.
I got one for Bobby and I got a
box of saltwater taffy for Sally.
What did you get for gene?
Sally will share
and she'll make Bobby share.
I was the youngest, Don.
You can't forget about him.
Trust me, he won't
know the difference.
Didn't make much of a dent.
Anything to your liking?
- We had a little of everything.
- Should I bring some desserts?
Yes, how about some pie?
No, you know what? Just three scoops
of orange sherbet and two spoons.
The colors are bright
and cheerful.
The kids have candy.
Full bar for mom and dad.
Would you say it's
a delightful destination?
It's not a destination.
It's on the way to someplace.
That's true.
It's a long car drive.
Mom probably needs
to use the restroom.
Kids get a look at the place,
force them to stay.
You like to work,
but I can't like to work?
You should have told me
if it was so important to you.
- We didn't have to go.
- I never got the chance.
It was in front of everyone.
And it's embarrassing.
I ruined the whole damn thing by
pulling you off that crack team.
I am on the team.
- Here we go.
- She's never tried it.
- You're kidding.
- Try it.
Oh, no, sorry.
- It's not for everybody.
- It tastes like perfume to me.
That's why we make 28 flavors.
Can I get a scoop of chocolate?
Really?
I don't like it.
There's no chance you're
trying to embarrass me?
You're right.
I'm-- I'm sorry.
Mmm, it's so delicious.
Mm-Mmm!
Mm, it's so good.
Stop it.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry. Maybe you could
make up a little schedule
so I'll know when I'm working
and when I'm your wife.
It gets so confusing.
I know, I'm terrible.
Making you eat ice cream.
Why don't you call
your mother and hurl
a string of complaints at her
in French like you always do?
- I'm always talking about you.
- The woman speaks English.
Why don't you call your mother?
Don.
Do not walk away from me.
- Get in the car.
- No, I am talking to you.
Okay, don't get in the car.
( Scoffs ) Go ahead.
You care more what some truck stop
waitress thinks than what I say.
Get in the car.
Eat ice cream.
Leave work.
Take off your dress.
- Yes, master.
- ( Engine starts )
Don't you dare pull away!
I'm talking to you.
( Tires squeal )
Excuse me.
Was my wife just in here?
- She was.
- Where'd she go?
- I don't know.
- To the hotel?
She was talking to
those fellas over there.
They all left.
They went towards
the parking lot together.
I thought she
was looking for you.
Wow, you're really
checking the place out.
I've got your room key.
Do you want help
with your bags?
No. Did you give
my wife a key?
No. Do you want
another key?
No.
I-- No.
Uh, I have some bad news.
- What?
- We closed the pool.
Some kid had an accident.
I swear it doesn't
happen a lot.
- Oh, you took care of me, sir.
- No, can I get some dimes?
Oh, le will let you
use the phone.
That's okay.
Pay phone's fine.
It's none of my business,
but couples fight in here
all the time.
There's no reason
to think the worst.
She probably got a ride
home with those kids.
( Sighs )
- Peggy: Hello? - Dawn didn't
get any calls. Did you get any calls?
- About what?
- Has anyone called you?
I don't think so.
( Sighs ) Oh.
- Okay.
- Listen, it didn't go well.
( Phone dings )
- Woman: Hello?
- Marie.
Hello, it's Don.
Hello.
Is everything all right?
Just wanted to call...
to say hello
and wanted to know
if Megan had called you.
Has Megan called
me tonight? No.
No. Huh.
Don, are you still there?
Well, I wanted to buy her
some jewelry
and I remembered that she had
an allergic reaction to metal,
but I don't remember
if it's silver or gold.
Ah, 24 karat gold is fine
and so is sterling silver.
Well, good.
What a fine husband you are.
It is only gold alloy--
Listen, Marie,
if she does call...
Don't ruin the surprise, okay?
- Of course. Of course not.
- Thank you.
Okay.
Au revoir.
Nice talking to you, Don.
( Sighs )
Are you okay?
I'm sorry to do
that to you, sir,
but they don't let patrons
sleep in the restaurant.
No, no, of course not.
What time is it?
It's a quarter to 2:00.
Oh.
Well, my wife, she--
She's missing.
She took off from here.
- When was this?
- I don't know.
Almost seven hours ago.
Well, I'll be back
and forth here all morning.
I'll keep an eye out.
( Radio playing )
The Whitestone bridge to
the Hutchinson river
parkway to 95.
You cold?
It's like I'm in shock.
Where are we?
Where are we going?
To your new house.
I don't want to go there.
I don't want vacation to end.
Me either.
When can we go back?
If you go to sleep, when you
wake up, I'll tell you.
( Whistling tune )
I thought you hated that song.
You keep telling her
to stop singing it.
And now it's stuck in my head.
( Laughs )
( Whistling )
( Radio continues )
Megan.
- Megan!
- Megan: Go away!
- Open the door.
- No.
Open the damn door.
I don't want to see you.
Open the door
or I'm gonna kick it in.
Leave me alone!
- Get out.
- I said I was sorry.
- I don't care.
- Where the hell were you?
I stopped every 20 miles
and called the apartment.
Why didn't you answer
the goddamn phone?
Because you're a pig!
You left me there!
Where the hell were you?
I thought you were dead.
Six and a half hours on a bus.
And then try getting a cab at Port
Authority at 5:00 in the morning.
Try getting anything
but an offer.
I thought you were dead.
( Whimpers )
( Sobbing )
( Coughing )
( Panting )
How could you do that to me?
I don't know.
It was a fight.
It's over.
No.
Every time we fight, it just
diminishes us a little bit.
I have to go to work.
I thought I lost you.
Mr. Draper.
I didn't expect you back.
- How was your trip?
- Great.
Would you like some coffee?
- What's this? - Oh, Mr. Cooper
dropped those off this morning.
- Bert Cooper?
- Yes.
He's in the conference room.
Would you like me to get him?
What the hell is this?
A client left here
unhappy yesterday
because you have a little
girl running everything.
My department is fine.
We just need more bodies,
but Lane won't let us.
You've been on love leave.
It's amazing things are
going as well as they are
with as little
as you are doing.
That's none of your business.
This is my business.
I have an announcement to make.
It's going to be
a beautiful day.
( Music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net