Just a minute.
Mr. Draper?
Thank you, Dawn.
She was the most qualified.
What am I gonna do
when you go home?
Are you really going
back to that office?
Mohawk Airlines has chosen to
return to Starling Cooper Draper Pryce.
Mr. Sterling will be handling
the day to day.
My husband's been gone so long...
I feel alone.
- So I'm not getting the job.
- No! You start tomorrow.
You sound terrible.
You even look terrible.
You don't.
( Coughing )
I'm going to stand over here.
Fine, if you think
you'll be safe
over there by yourself.
( Elevator dings )
- Going up.
- So am I. Thank you.
My God, Don.
My bad penny.
Andrea, this is my wife Megan.
Megan, this is Andrea.
She's a freelance writer
for, you know,
the firm.
Oh, nice to meet you.
Yes, you as well.
( Elevator dings )
Andrea:
Well, goodbye.
It was nice meeting you.
( Coughing )
Incroyable.
- Look--
- You look.
How many times is this
going to happen?
What? I worked
with her six years ago.
We're in midtown.
I'm going to run into people.
You know, there are
some parts of town
where we can run into
some people I worked with.
( Coughing )
( Sighs )
All they care about
is that they're see-through.
Why is transparency
desirable in pantyhose?
I can see fine.
You want to get
in here with me?
- Hello, Pegasus.
- Hey, you.
- You have to let me announce you.
- Go ahead.
Hello, Stanley, Ginso.
I have amazing photos--
Crime scene snaps from
Chicago's student nurse massacre.
- Not suitable for publication.
- What?
( Typewriter clacking )
Oh, my God.
( Sucks in breath )
I'm telling you,
you're upset over nothing.
- You're making it worse. I'll get over it.
- Megan.
I'm fine.
You should be.
- They look like rag dolls.
- Were they raped?
They don't know, but a
couple of these are naked.
- It went on for hours.
- Ugh.
- The rest just waited.
- They were tied up.
- ( Door closes )
- I'm sorry I'm late.
Megan. I've got
some pictures.
Ginsberg, you got to see these.
( Coughing )
I'll see you later.
And I'll see you later.
The sex murders in Chicago.
- The student nurses.
- Really?
Take it.
- Oh, my God.
- Look at the bottom row.
I think this is going to make
the cover, not the riots.
- Really?
- Yeah, we did the riots this week.
Watts a year later.
Plus, there have been
five riots this summer.
I say it's better
than even money
Mr. Luce finds a
tasteful way to do this.
You know what-- Put it away.
It's disgusting.
It's one of those things
I wish I didn't see.
- And why are you laughing?
- We're not laughing.
No, you're excited by it.
Some girl trussed up
like a cut of meat?
Eight girls, but nine
were kidnapped.
One survived.
I only am escaped alone
to tell thee.
How did she do that?
She hid under the bed.
He lost count.
You know what?
You're sickos.
Michael.
He's right.
( Gas hissing )
It's been 25 minutes.
It's not even set.
I told you the jets
are clogged.
Give me some money.
I'll go to the bakery.
And we need to get beer.
Greg likes Schaefer.
Do we have time?
Not if you want me to get
the baby out of here by noon.
Why? He's going to want
to see Kevin more than me.
That's what he's going to say,
but he's going to
want you right away.
Let me go get my purse.
You're making me
very anxious right now.
It's okay to be anxious.
It's normal.
Everything's going to be
unfamiliar for both of you.
And who knows what he's seen?
Who knows what he's done?
He's a surgeon.
He wasn't in combat.
He saw the same things
there he saw here.
Well, there are other things
that happen when men are away,
- especially at war.
- Stop it.
Stop talking
about men in general
when I know
it's all about daddy.
Even if there haven't
been other women,
he's not used to
listening to a woman.
It's just the idea
of coming home
and finding a little
hole in his life
and sticking his elbow through
until he can walk
all the way in.
I know.
And that's why I want
to start with him
seeing his son
for the first time.
He'll know how to do that.
You're right.
Do you really want a cake?
Because it's going to take
me a while to get dressed.
Could you?
- ( Intercom buzzes )
- Your daughter's on line one.
Hello, sweetheart.
What's the matter?
Grandma Pauline is still here
and I hate her.
Stay out of her way.
Your mother will be back
Friday morning.
It is Friday morning.
Someone called on Henry's phone
and said that they couldn't
get an airplane flight,
so someone's driving them back
from Buffalo tonight.
You'd think Henry
could get a flight.
I know.
He's so important.
They call Bobby all the time
in sleepaway camp.
I guess if I was peeing
in my pants, they might want to say hi.
That's not nice.
Grandma Pauline
wears so much perfume.
Every time she comes near
me, I want to barf.
And you know what else?
She doesn't believe me,
that I'm allowed
to watch as much TV as I want
because it's the summer.
Your mother lets you do that?
I'm on vacation.
I think the best thing
is for you to go out
in the fresh air
and get some sun.
I did.
It's really hot.
Stop complaining.
I don't want you to get rickets
in that haunted mansion.
I'll see you next weekend.
( Coughing )
How are you?
I have a cold, but you've
made me feel better.
Can't you come get me?
No. And don't ask again.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- Are you sick?
- I'm great. Let's go.
So it starts with Ken Cosgrove
climbing out of the muck
and walking on dry land.
He says a bunch of nice stuff
about Ginsberg and you.
I told him not to use the word
genius about either of us.
Ahem, a woman
and her secrets--
Oh, the things
she'll never tell,
like how long
it took her to get ready
or the reason she's smiling.
A good-looking woman
at a party.
And where she got
the incredible shoes.
Another woman, not too catty,
says, "I love your shoes.
Where did you get them?"
We hold on five seconds of her showing
off the shoe from the calf down,
and this girl's legs
will be spectacular.
And, yes, you can
come to casting.
( Coughing )
That's plenty.
Are you kidding?
I'm ready to take off here.
I just wanted to hear the tone
of your voice so I can make sure
it's not as annoying
as it is in everyday life.
- ( Snickers )
- It's called a regional accent.
And believe it or not,
you've got one, too.
We can't all sound
like Walter Cronkite.
Do you like this?
I never saw boards
for the Cinderella thing.
Well, you killed it,
and for good reason.
Cinderella and shoes
is a cliche.
- You could have TB.
- Sleeping beauty?
Snow white?
Nothing worked?
They're more about
necrophilia than shoes.
It's footwear.
Don't make that mistake.
( Doorbell rings )
( Gasps )
( Both laugh )
- Oh, my God, you're so skinny.
- So are you.
Gail: Somebody wants
to say hello.
Jesus, is that him?
Holy crap, look at him.
Joanie, I'll get that.
You have your hands full.
We thought your flight might
be late because of the strike.
Yeah, we picked up
some folks in Honolulu
who had been stranded,
but everything was fine.
Gail, go get the brownie.
I don't think we have any film.
You know what?
I'll take Kevin
and go get some,
so you two can visit a spell.
Okay, that's a good idea.
You have supplies in case you
have to be gone for a while?
I have everything.
And so do you, Greg.
Get over here.
Where have you been?
Out in the wilderness, baby.
( Phone ringing )
- What are you doing?
- Looking for aspirin.
- Why don't you have Dawn do it?
- I'm embarrassed.
I've eaten up a bottle
since she's been here.
My husband's an aspirin addict.
- I'm so ashamed.
- ( Coughing )
You're very warm.
I'm sending you home.
I'm sorry about this morning.
It couldn't be avoided.
It was a long time ago
and I was unhappy.
Because you were married.
It's fine.
It's just embarrassing.
Why should you be embarrassed?
Seriously?
Because you're
married to me now.
And after Allison
and faye Miller
and who knows how many more...
I was divorced.
And now you're not.
And that kind
of careless appetite--
You can't blame that on Betty.
I tell you, let it go.
- You brought it up.
- No, I didn't.
You did.
And all I can think
is you feel guilty,
which makes it worse
than I thought.
I married you.
And I'm going to be
with you until I die...
Which could be this afternoon.
Is this really how you want to
end my last hours on earth?
Sweetie, go home.
I have to go to this meeting
so I can skip the next two.
At least go lie down.
( Dog barking )
Eat your sandwich.
I'm not hungry.
Oh, my lord.
- Those poor souls.
- What?
Nothing.
Ow!
Some things are not
for children.
Mommy lets me watch the news.
You demanded tuna salad,
so you're going to sit
there until you eat it.
It has relish in it.
You haven't even tasted it.
You hurt my hand.
Well, I shouldn't
have done that.
I'm sorry.
But you have to be respectful.
I know your mother
has other rules.
- She doesn't have rules.
- I don't believe that,
but I believe that
she may be distracted.
And I am sure she would be sick
if she knew how
you were behaving.
Now you're going to finish
that sandwich, crusts and all.
I don't care
if it takes all day.
( Music playing )
How'd you sleep?
Very well, thank you.
What are you doing?
He's making lunch.
He won't listen.
Greg, honey, I have steak.
Mom bought a cake.
Believe it or not,
I had steak in Vietnam.
I did not have bologna.
And I'll have veal
tonight with my folks.
What are the three
of you up to?
I'm showing Kevin how good
I am with my hands.
We were talking
about the riots.
Plenty of negroes in Saigon
and they're plenty brave.
I think we should have a rule
that you have to wear
your uniform
all the time when you're home.
Gail, is there a chance
you could pick up more beer?
Of course.
I wanted to get
the afternoon paper anyway.
Thank you so much, mom.
We'll be back
in time for dinner.
You look incredible, you know?
Thank you.
I need to tell you something.
Greg, if something
happened over there
and you feel the need
to tell me, you shouldn't.
And if you do, you certainly
shouldn't ask me to hold your hand.
What? No.
No, it's not that.
Listen, Joanie, there's
been a change of plans.
I have to go back.
I know, for another 40 days.
No, for a year.
What?
It was one year here
and one year there.
That's what they told you.
Look, I know you're hearing
a lot of horrible things
about what's going on
over there.
It couldn't be further
from the truth.
- You don't need to worry.
- You did your part.
They're a bunch of liars.
Nobody lied to anybody.
It's more complicated.
It's war.
It doesn't stop for our plans.
And I've come
to terms with that.
Now we have 10 days together.
Let's not waste it.
I need to store up
as much of you as possible.
And yes, you can
come to casting.
Michael: And you think
it sounds good,
wait till you see it in print.
"You'll never tell.
They'll never be able to."
I don't know.
What do you think, Mr. Butler?
I think Ken was right--
You're a genius.
( Coughing )
Square-on strategy.
I think the boys
did a good job.
The girl should be
European-looking.
Maybe get a French girl.
Great.
So?
Sold.
I have to tell you, young
man, you really know women.
I've never heard that before.
This really gets
inside their heads.
Well, to tell you the truth,
they confuse me.
I mean, I keep thinking
about Cinderella.
We were going to come in here
and talk about Cinderella,
but it's too dark.
Really?
We were kind of hoping for it.
Nah, I don't think so.
I mean, she's running down
this dark side street.
And it's outside a castle,
so it's got those walls
and the cobblestones.
And she's running,
but she's only got
this one incredible shoe
for her incredible gown,
so she's hobbling,
wounded prey.
She can hear him behind her,
his measured footsteps
catching up.
She turns a corner.
Those big shadows.
And she's scared.
And then she feels
a hand on her shoulder
and she turns around.
And it doesn't matter
what he looks like.
He's handsome, at that moment
offering her her shoe.
She takes it.
She knows she's not safe,
but she doesn't care.
I guess we know in the end
she wants to be caught.
See? It's too dark.
Why don't we do that?
The man said sold.
You wanted Cinderella anyway.
- You forgot that.
- No, I said it was a cliche.
That's because you thought
they wouldn't like it,
but in your heart
you knew it was good.
In my heart I'm on the verge of
throwing you in front of a cab.
Okay.
So however proud of yourself
you're feeling right now,
just know that everything I'm
saying has "or else" after it.
Don't do that again.
Think of those ideas
in front of me.
Don't do that again.
( Coughs )
I gotta make a call.
He's such a decent guy.
You know you almost
got fired just now.
I don't think
you're right about that.
I'm positive.
- ( Intercom buzzes )
- Mr. Draper is on line one.
Hello. How'd it go?
Good.
What are you up to?
I'm keeping your chair warm.
So I'll swing by
and get you in an hour?
Well, why don't
you just go home,
climb into bed?
- Really?
- Yes.
I only need another
couple of hours.
And, Don,
no smoking.
( Coughing )
( Sighs )
Mohawk says that LBJ is scared
of forcing the mechanics
to arbitration
because he has
midterm elections
and he's worried about
losing the labor vote.
- That's good news.
- Yes, it is.
The strike's going to go on for
at least a couple more weeks
and Mohawk can sop up
all the extra routes.
So they want us to walk
them through the campaign
first thing Monday morning.
- A phone call will do.
- The campaign, of course.
We're ready to go.
Have a good weekend.
Damn it.
Good night everyone, Clara.
Good night,
Mr. Campbell.
( Laughter )
Where's Ginsberg?
He's probably everywhere after
Don scattered his ashes.
Apparently he went haywire
in the presentation downstairs.
I don't care.
Call him.
I just did.
He's not home.
- Is he coming back?
- You know what?
I'm going to go
out there and find him.
I'm going to start
the whole world
and then I'm going to
eventually check my apartment.
What are you doing tonight?
I don't know.
What did you have in mind?
Are you drunk?
Get your feet off that desk.
I need you to work up
something for Mohawk.
Oh, I'm sorry.
For Mohawk, your, quote,
"man" is Ginsberg.
Let's say you were
to do this for me
and on Monday you explain
to Ginsberg and Campbell
that I asked you to...
Only I asked you
sometime last week.
Do you have a brief?
- Did Ginsberg have a brief?
- I never told Ginsberg, okay?
You have to remember that.
- You know about the airline strike, right?
- Yes.
Why is Mohawk still flying?
Because even though all the
other mechanics are on strike--
Boo-hoo, they need more
wrenches or something--
Mohawk's mechanics
have a side deal,
so they have to keep working.
They must love that.
Yeah, well, they're going
to love the overtime.
American airlines
is taking everything big
and giving their northeast
corridor to Mohawk.
( Sighs ) So what do you want?
How about something like
"Mohawk, breaking the strike
one flight at a time"?
Or maybe "Fly over
the picket line with Mohawk"?
Hey, Trotsky,
you're in advertising.
Fine. So what's
the angle?
Campbell or I had this idea that
it would be something about,
you know, how times are tough
and you can't get anywhere.
So thank God Mohawk is
offering emergency service.
You don't want to use the word
emergency with an airplane.
I don't want to do any of this.
I'll see you Monday.
Hold on a second.
You want me to work up an entire
corporate image campaign for $10?
I can make you do it for nothing.
I'm the boss.
You're right
the work is $10,
the lie is extra.
Incredible.
What do you make
a week, sweetheart?
Mm, you don't know, uh?
That's helpful.
You know, I could fire you.
Great, there are some
portfolios in Joan's office.
Maybe you could find
somebody tonight.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because you're being
very demanding
for someone who has
no other choice.
- ( Sighs)
- Dazzle me.
Fine.
How much you want?
How much you got?
- $400.
- Give me all of it.
Jesus!
It better be good.
You want me to take your watch?
( Sighs )
I'm on my way out.
Are you staying?
Hello.
Good night.
Yeah. Something came up.
Would you tell Patricia
she can go home?
Okay.
( Doorbell rings )
Get in here.
- What are you doing here?
- We didn't get to talk.
We've done all the talking
we're ever going to do.
Are you okay?
How the hell
did you get in here?
- I have a way with doormen.
- I have some bad news for you.
You can either take the steps
or you can go off the balcony
because if you run into my
wife on the way out of here,
you're going to wish you had.
Ooh, forceful.
My, oh, my.
Everybody probably thinks
that she did this,
but I know it was you.
You really should go.
I gotta lie down.
I'll take the steps.
You know what--
Take the service elevator.
Goodbye.
I'm sorry.
- You've gotta understand.
- Are you okay?
Please, you have to go.
It was just sex.
It doesn't mean anything.
I'm sorry.
I've gotta lie down.
( TV playing )
The girl under
the bed-- Oh!
I'd be surprised if she
could ever talk again.
That poor thing--
Paralyzed with fear
while he opened
that door eight times
and dragged another one out?
And that...
No, as much as I'd love to
go, I can't make any plans
until they waltz
through that door.
Mm.
You need to take out the trash.
Right now?
( TV turns off )
Take out the trash or you
can go to bed right now,
watch the sun set
from your bedroom window.
It's the saddest thing
in the world.
If I take out the trash, will
you tell me about the murder?
No. I will not
bargain with you.
How old are you?
That's something we girls
keep to ourselves.
Was your mom strict?
No, but my father was and
I'm a better person for it.
I know you don't think so,
but I'm a good person.
Sally, I just think someone in
your world needs to discipline you
so you can start
acting like an adult.
My fath-- My father.
I remember one time he was
sleeping on the couch
in the living room
and I walked by.
And all of a sudden,
out of nowhere,
he kicked me so hard that I
actually flew across the room
and hit a piece of furniture.
And then he looked
at me and he said,
"That's for nothing,
so look out."
That's not very nice.
No, but it was valuable advice.
( Band playing )
When in doubt, go with the
most expensive, right, pops?
I don't want any wine.
Okay, can we all
cheer up, please?
We're together,
I have a new baby boy,
not to mention this place
costs a fortune.
So how are we starting?
The lovely senora?
- I'll have a gin fizz.
- Everybody else is having wine,
but you have to
give me a second.
- How are you doing?
- Can't complain.
Enjoy yourself.
Thank you.
You, too, sir.
First Armored Division.
Fort Hood.
Do you want me to come back?
No, but you can
recommend something.
- Are you in a rush?
- No, it's just that I got a bunch of tables.
Well, I'm sorry if that little display
of respect is slowing you down,
but a lot of kids your age
would be thrilled
to be waiting tables tonight.
I'm sorry, sir.
Of course.
- ( Song ends )
- ( Applause )
This is a nice one.
Thank you.
That would be perfect.
The scampi looks very good.
I'm sorry, this is
a painful charade.
- Mom, please.
- I just don't understand it.
Everyone else
is trying to come home.
Ruth, Greg is facing this
with great bravery
and I'm proud of him.
He did his time.
You've got to talk him
out of it.
Mom, I don't want your grandson
hearing this argument.
Joe, you were in the service.
Can't you write a letter
to your congressman
and tell him he's got a family
why?
Is some congressman
going to talk him
out of going back?
I don't understand.
I'm putting a moratorium
on this conversation.
Now we are either
going to have this dinner
that I've been
dreaming about for months
or we can all go home.
He didn't tell you about it.
Of course not.
What is she talking about?
Did you have a say in this?
You're a father now.
- What?
- Joanie, calm down.
You volunteered?
They need me.
( Accordion playing )
You know, Joanie plays
the accordion.
( Typewriter clacking )
( Soft tap )
Hello?
Is somebody here?
( Both scream )
( Sighs )
What are you doing?
I fell asleep.
Well, it's time to go home.
I will, in a bit.
Come on, I don't want
to walk out alone.
I don't know.
I think I'll just stay here.
You can hop in a cab.
I happen to have
a lot of cash for once.
Even if a cab
was going to take me,
they're not going to
take me past 96th Street.
Really?
Well, then, take the subway.
My brother won't let me--
You know, with everything
that's happening in Chicago.
( Laughs )
Well, you're not a nurse.
Oh, right.
Is there a riot in Harlem?
There was a thing
in Bed-Stuy.
There's a lot of police.
Well, I know that
doesn't make it safer.
My boyfriend's in Chicago.
He's covering the riots.
Is that right?
Why don't you stay
with me tonight?
I've stayed here before.
I'll be fine.
Get your things.
( Distant traffic blaring )
Are you asleep?
Oh, you're home.
You're mumbling.
How the hell
did you get in here?
I was worried about you.
You left the back door
unlocked.
- Why can't you leave me alone?
- I can't.
You have to.
We're alone.
I just want it fast.
No.
I know she's coming home.
I'll be gone.
I promise.
Andrea.
I can feel you against me.
Remember that night
at Lincoln Center
when you took me back
to the loading dock?
Your wife was waiting inside.
So it's just me,
my brother, who's 19,
and my mother,
who says she's 39.
- Like Jack Benny.
- ( Both laugh )
- Is your brother in school?
- No. He delivers furniture
and argues with my mother
about joining the army.
Mm.
You were saying something in the
taxi about Don and I cut you off.
No, I was finished.
You can talk to me.
I was his secretary, you know?
You were?
- So how did you--
- I didn't even ask for it.
Sometimes they drag
the secretaries in
for focus groups to try things
and I was discovered...
Like Esther Blodgett.
( Laughing )
Oh, God, I'm really drunk.
Y'all drink a lot.
( Laughing )
So what were you going to say?
I was going to say--
Go ahead.
You can talk.
- I'm trying to.
- Oh.
( Laughing ) I'm sorry.
I was going to say
I hope you won't
tell Mr. Draper
about me sleeping there.
You two talk sometimes.
Nah.
We have to stick together.
I know we're not really
in the same situation,
but I was the only one
like me there
for a long time.
I know it's hard.
I appreciate that.
Do you want to be a copywriter?
No. I like my job.
Yep.
You're right.
Copywriter's tough,
especially for a woman.
Do you think I act like a man?
I guess you have to a little.
I try, but...
I don't know
if I have it in me.
I don't know if I want to.
( Gasps )
I'm sorry.
I can't sleep.
Well, you cannot sneak up
on someone my age,
especially in this house.
I'm scared.
Can I sit with you?
Only for a bit.
What's that for?
Why are you scared?
I read the newspaper.
Oh, honey.
Did you pull it
out of the trash?
Why did that man do that?
Well, probably because
he hates his mother.
- I don't understand what happened.
- What happened?
Those girls got ready for bed
and there was
a knock on the door,
and a handsome man was there.
And maybe one of them knew him,
but probably not
because he was probably
just watching them from afar.
All those young,
innocent nurses
in their short uniforms
stirring his desire.
For what?
What do you think?
You're old enough to know.
Why didn't they run away?
Because they were scared.
They probably thought,
"He can't rape nine of us."
- Why not?
- You just can't.
They didn't know it was going
to be worse than that.
They didn't know what
was in store for them.
Now I'm really scared.
It's not going to happen,
not while I've got
my burglar alarm.
How am I going to sleep?
Get the water.
What's that?
It's Seconal.
Do you know how to take a pill?
- ( Kevin crying )
- You two stop it.
Damn it, Joanie!
- Stop it.
- Gail, out!
Take him out of here!
- ( Pounding )
- Open this door
or I will kick it down!
Who goes back?
I will throw a parade
for you every day
- to thank you for preserving freedom.
- It's done.
Well, you can't make a
decision like that without me
and you have never
understood that.
If this was World War II and the
Japs were still attacking us,
you'd say,
"Yes, of course!"
Soldiers wanted to come home
from world war ii also!
I've got my orders,
you've got yours.
- Where are you going?
- To meet the boys for a drink.
He just needs
to blow off steam.
Don't get involved, mother.
You're a military wife.
You make sacrifices.
Someone's Kevin is over there and he's
going to get hurt and Greg won't be there.
But our Kevin is right in
there and he doesn't care.
It's a year.
You can do it.
- I'll help.
- No.
Go lie down.
You don't even know
how tired you are.
I hope you don't
mind the couch.
Since my roommate moved
to the other room,
I just have a pile
of Abe's clothes.
This is perfect.
Well, good night, then.
I-- I'll just--
I'll throw these out.
Thanks.
Good night.
I'll see you later.
No, you won't.
Don't argue with me.
I have to get out of here.
Hotel next time?
No next time.
That was a mistake.
A mistake you love making.
I'd better not see you again.
You're not going to ruin this.
You loved it.
And you'll love it again
because you are
a sick, sick--
( Gasping )
( Choking )
( Coughing )
( TV playing )
- ( Door closes )
- Betty: Hello? We're home.
Ma.
- Ma.
- ( Groans )
What's going on?
Where's Sally?
Sally?
( Door opens )
How are you feeling?
Where were you?
I was right there.
You're burning up.
No, last night.
I was waiting for you.
I came right home.
You were a mess.
I was really worried.
You don't have
to worry about me.
Okay.
There are some scrambled
eggs in the bowl
and I made flapjacks.
Just coffee.
- Where's Kevin?
- You slept a long time.
He was awake and went
back to bed already.
I barely slept at all.
I've been thinking
about it and...
I want you to go.
I'll put this away.
I'm glad you came around.
It's only a year.
No. I want you to go
and never come back.
Damn it, Joanie.
They need me.
Well, then, it works out,
because we don't.
I'm very important there.
I have 20 docs and medics
who rely on me.
They look to me
for my skill and leadership.
I'm glad the army
makes you feel like a man,
because I'm sick
of trying to do it.
The army makes me feel
like a good man.
You're not a good man.
You never were,
even before we were married,
and you know
what I'm talking about.
If I walk out
that door, that's it.
That's it.
It's over.
( Distant siren wailing )
( Sighs )
( Music playing )
d he hit me d
d and it felt like a kiss d
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
d he hit me d
d but it didn't hurt me d
d he couldn't stand
to hear me say d
d that I'd been
with someone new d
d and when I told him d
d I had been untrue d
d he hit me d
d and it felt like a kissd
d it felt like a kiss d
d he hit me d
d and I was his. d
www.tvsubtitles.net