Someone once said
that two halves make a whole.
When two halves move in together,
it makes a whole lot of stuff.
Where you been
and what you been doing?
I got coffee and the papers,
but the more pressing question is:
what have you been doing?
- I made myself an area.
- I can see that.
I needed a space for work papers
and stuff. Is that OK?
Sure. It's just that you're blocking
the bathroom door.
Who needs two bathroom doors?
I do. Me, the one who loves
her two bathroom doors.
- Why do you need two doors?
- If I'm in a hurry,
it's quicker to use that one.
- It's my escape route, in case.
- In case what?
In case rapists come in my window.
Boing...I'm gone.
There's a lot of "boinging"
going on in that bathroom.
It's just going to be like this till we
take over the apartment next door.
Would that be happening in the next
five minutes?
Closing at the end of next week.
Hello, Petie. What's the problem?
It's just boxes, right?
A plant! The man brought
a living thing into my apartment.
I kill everything I bring in there.
- You said yes and he moved in.
- He's taking over whole areas.
That's why I've never lived
with a man.
- They're out an hour after I climax.
- You let them stay an hour?
You'd be surprised how many
can go again after a quick nap.
As soon as I walk in the door,
he's in my face with,
"Who did you see, where did you go,
what do you know?"
I need time to decompress,
just be alone.
There have to be some adjustments.
Relationships are hard.
I miss walking into my apartment
with no one there
and it's all quiet.
I can do that stuff you do
when you're totally alone,
things you would never want
your boyfriend to see you do.
- Like masturbate?
- My SSB:
my secret, single behaviour.
I like to make a stack of saltines
and put grape jelly on them.
I eat them standing up in the kitchen
while reading fashion magazines.
- Why standing up?
- It's weird, but it feels great.
I like to put Vaseline on my hands
and put on conditioning gloves
while watching infomercials.
Before I was married,
I used to study my pores
in a mirror for an hour each night.
I'm afraid Trey will think it's weird.
He would.
You can't do that stuff in front of men.
What about you? Anything
you wouldn't want a man to see?
No.
I believe her.
Don't we have a rule
about those things?
It's my boss. I have to take it.
Samantha Jones.
Richard, it's Sunday.
Fine, I'll see you in an hour.
He wants me to drop
something off this afternoon.
Nice! A little "skyrockets in flight,
afternoon delight"?
- No, it's just work.
- Hardly.
- You're sleeping with him.
- You told them?
I like to gossip on the phone
while pumicing my calluses.
How is he? Spare no detail,
I'm a horny, pregnant person.
I don't want to talk about it.
Samantha likes a guy!
- Samantha likes a guy!
- I do not.
You do or you would tell us
all the dirty details.
We're going to have to ice skate home.
Hell just froze over.
You want details? OK.
He's got the most perfect dick
I've ever seen.
Long, pink, amazing.
It's "dickalicious".
What should I do about Aidan's stuff?
- The girls are coming over for dinner.
- That sounds like fun. What night?
Just the girls.
I have so much more free time
now we're not on the baby track.
Some apartments are cluttered with
physical stuff. Others, emotional stuff.
It's a big readjustment.
I've wanted a baby since I was a girl.
We have a baby room and no baby.
I've got some good news.
Bram Pomander thinks he's snagged us
orchestra seats
to "The Producers" next week.
Charlotte, yes, we're disappointed,
but life goes on.
We still have to find a way
to have a giggle.
Come on, give me a smile.
Investors in Munich.
How do you say "fuck you" in German?
Impressive.
Why do you speak German?
A gal has her reasons. That wasn't
"fuck you", it was "fuck me".
That's a negotiation ploy
I haven't tried before.
- Where's the magazine layout?
- Signed, sealed, delivered.
One more thing.
It was perfect:
long, pink, amazing.
I thought about you all weekend.
Maybe I can give you something
to think about all evening.
Bring out that gorgeous dick.
You're getting down on your knees here?
What if my assistant sees you?
I dropped my portfolio.
It may take some time to pick up.
Better get those
while you're down there.
If I'd known you were going to be
so not a loser,
- I would have changed after work.
- Or put on some fresh deodorant.
Careful. I was a much younger man
when we first set up this blind date.
You're the one who kept cancelling
to go... Where?
First time, Spain and Rome.
Second time, Luxembourg and Athens.
Walker Lewis, fluent in five languages,
was a State Department interpreter.
Seriously, Miranda.
Best blind date I've ever had...
...in the continental USA.
What? Listen,
any reason I can't see you again
before I go to Brussels?
He is so cute and funny and sexy.
I want to have sex with him,
but I don't know.
Can you fuck a guy when you're
carrying another's baby?
If one more person
asks me that today...
I'm not in a relationship
with the father of the baby.
I've rarely heard that used as a plus,
but go on.
Is it tacky?
And beyond tacky, is it safe?
- Let's assume he's a great fuck.
- As so many men are.
Could all that poking
shake the baby loose?
That's silly! Married couples
have sex all the time.
- But what if he's huge?
- As so many men are.
- Could the dick dent the baby?
- What do you think dimples come from?
- That is so cute.
- I try.
I really need
to have sex with him now.
Next time he's back,
I'll be too big and he won't want to.
Nothing puts a man off sex
like pregnancy.
This is my last chance.
- Last chance for sex.
- You're not on death row.
Yes, I am.
Dead woman fucking.
It's your body, your life.
You do what's best for you.
Easier said than done.
You can't even ask Aidan not to talk
when you walk in the door.
Hi, Mrs Cohen.
Hold on a second.
Let me help you.
Here we go.
That's a crazy outfit.
- This is my friend, Miranda.
- Hello, Mrs Cohen.
You tell your boy
I'm not leaving for 30 days.
What? But we're closing in a week.
Read the contract!
I didn't think Mrs Cohen could
move any slower,
but apparently she could.
What's up? Where you been?
What do you know?
Brace yourself, partner.
I've been outside.
What's up is old lightning rod
next door informs me
she will not be leaving
for 30 days.
I was afraid she was going
to do that.
Fuck! What the fuck
are we going to do now?
Thank you! You hate it, too.
I'm so relieved.
I thought you'd already
changed into a pod.
Invasion of the Single Snatchers.
Of course I hate it.
We cannot live like this.
I've got all my boxes in the hall,
you can't get in the door.
Did you see me?
- Every single time.
- We have to move this stuff out.
We could make some room
if we cleaned out your closet.
Careful!
- OK. Damn! My ears?
- Listen to me.
I have laid out clean towels
on the floor of the bathroom.
Gently place the shoes
and boxes on them.
I forgot I had these.
Things are looking up.
How many pairs of shoes
do you need?
That is not the way
to get out of this alive.
I figure I'll need
about half this space.
- I figure you're mentally ill.
- You never wear most of this.
Yet. I never wear most of this stuff yet.
Some day I will.
Like this?
When and where
were you planning to wear this?
Don't do that.
Don't mock the clothes.
For the record, have worn it.
December '99.
Union Square, book signing.
- We've got to start somewhere.
- I love this outfit.
I realised I was holding onto
a Roberto Cavalli outfit
and throwing away my relationship.
- OK, it goes.
- Good.
Bye, bye.
Stop it! Pete, stop it!
Oh, my God!
Don't even show it to me!
I think I saw turquoise.
That better not be the pair I think.
Goddamit!
- That dog owes me $380.
- Fine.
You can't buy it!
It's circa 1996.
He's a dog. What's he supposed to do
with all your shit lying around?
My shit wouldn't be lying around
if we weren't making room
because your shit is lying around.
- You've got more shit than me.
- Look at this place!
It's loaded with your shit.
Look at this bathroom.
Look at all your shit in my bathroom.
Who needs five almost empty deodorants?
Are you a crazy bagman?
- They're different smells.
- When have you ever worn musk?
Look at this stuff.
You've got old razors, Rogaine...
- I didn't know you used Rogaine.
- It's preventative.
- Is your hair...?
- I don't want to talk about it!
It seems not only women
have secret, single behaviour.
Don't be going through my stuff!
- You were happy to go through mine!
- Your stuff. Your bathroom.
You always do that.
You never want to let me in.
I don't always do anything
and I have let you in.
You're fighting with me
about a stupid outfit.
Shut up. It's Roberto Cavalli.
I threw it away and I love it.
- What more do you want?
- Shut up? Shut up?
Yes, shut up.
- You're telling me to shut up?
- Please, just shut up.
I am so sick of your talking all the time.
Don't you ever just shut up?
I'm going to take a walk.
I'm taking a walk.
Stay here with your boxes of shit
and your shoe-eating dog
and knock yourself out putting on
the Rogaine and the speed stick.
This is why I need a second door.
I heard that!
I used to think people who sat alone
at Starbucks writing on laptops
were pretentious posers.
Now I know:
they are people who have recently
moved in with someone.
I wondered how many of them
were mid-fight like myself.
The hard thing about fighting in
relationships is that there's no referee.
There's no one to tell you
which comments are below the belt.
As a result,
someone usually gets hurt.
The closer a couple gets and the more
stuff they have between them,
the harder it is to figure out
why they're yelling.
When it comes to relationships,
I wondered: what are we fighting for?
Hello, my darling. I'm home.
- Is that a surprise for me?
- Yes, it is.
It's just a little silly something.
- What is it?
- Open it.
It's a cardboard baby.
I saw it in the window of a novelty
store next to the hospital.
Now we can relax
because we have one.
Oh, dear...
It was supposed to be funny.
I thought we'd have a chuckle.
Don't talk to me.
It was a novelty store.
The clerk said that...
But to Charlotte,
it was hitting below the belt.
If the meat is a quarter
of an inch thick...
Across town, Miranda decided
it was time to put on the gloves
and come out swinging.
Hi, Walker. Miranda. Before you leave
for Brussels on Monday,
how about getting together Friday night?
My apartment, call me.
Pregnant or not, Miranda had needs
and decided to stop fighting them.
Surprisingly,
Samantha developed some secret,
single behaviour of her own.
Seven hours
and a landslide of lattes later,
I vibrated home prepared to admit
how silly I'd been.
That was, until he wasn't prepared
to admit how silly he'd been.
He yelled, then I yelled.
It's been three days
and nothing, not a word.
I'll be damned
if I say I'm sorry first.
Trey and I hardly ever yell.
WASPS don't yell, it's genetic.
- More salad anyone?
- No! What's the main course?
Relax. Chew. You'll get laid.
You're not meeting him till 10:00.
Beef with Thai noodles.
Richard is thinking
of opening a hotel in Thailand.
Sweetie, it's perfectly OK
to like a guy.
For the last time,
the only thing I like about Richard
is his big, throbbing, rock hard,
perfect dick.
- I forgot it was ladies' night.
- Trey, you shouldn't be here.
Good evening, everyone.
Hello, Missus.
Still mad, I see.
- I suppose she told you about the baby.
- No, I didn't.
I never want to think about it again.
I was trying to make Charlotte laugh...
- It's not funny.
- Maybe they'll think it is.
We were so tense
about not being able to have one
that I gave Charlotte a cardboard baby.
Isn't that funny?
You're funny. A cardboard baby.
That's funny, right?
It's not funny ha-ha, but silly.
They sell them in novelty stores.
Other people buy them
and the clerk said it was funny.
- Maybe you have to see it.
- Don't bring that in here!
- It's silly.
- Not to me, it isn't.
How would you feel if I gave you
a cut-out of a flaccid penis?
It's not so funny now, is it?
Don't you bring that flat baby in here!
- How dare you talk to me like that?
- They know about your penis problems!
We were in the middle
of a WASP nest.
This is unforgivable.
You're unforgivable for denying me
a baby because of your spoiled needs.
I'm spoiled?
You are spoiled.
Ever since we moved back in...
Samantha Jones.
Richard, hello.
No, it's not too late to call.
- Everything but a baby!
- We're going to go.
Good!
Don't talk to my friends like that!
With no baby, they're all I have.
You are the man
who gave me a cardboard baby!
- It was funny!
- No, it wasn't!
Goodnight.
What's so important
that it couldn't wait until...?
This.
Let's get something straight.
I want no part of that.
That turns everything
into a big mess.
We are work and sex.
Nothing more.
Now kindly take off those pants
and show me your dick.
I'll show you mine
if you show me yours.
That's what I'm talking about.
Seeing a bantamweight fight
like Charlotte and Trey's
made me thankful that Aidan and I were
still in the banter-weight division.
I'm sorry, too.
That night, I slept in my clothes.
Trey and his baby
slept in the guest room
and Charlotte no longer cared
what Trey thought.
Fuck me! Fuck me
like there's no tomorrow.
For her last meal, the condemned
woman had seconds...
...and thirds.
Samantha met the dawn after a night
of SSB:
sexy, swimming behaviour.
- Dance with me.
- What did I say?
I'm your boss.
It's an order.
Dance.
Samantha finally threw in the towel.
All this time, she'd been trying
to make him just a perfect dick,
fighting her feelings that
he might be the perfect Richard.
Back at the Bradshaw/Shaw residence,
it was business as usual.
What's up, where you been,
who did you see?
- I need you to do something.
- What?
I've never lived with anybody
so I don't know how to say
this correctly, but...
I need you to not talk to me
for one whole hour.
I know that sounds selfish,
but it's just what I need.
Is that OK?
Good.
We don't have any other rooms yet,
so I'm going to close these.
Then it's like I'm not here.
For one whole hour, I'm not here.
Thanks.
I love you.
What are you doing out here?
That's the thing about needs:
sometimes when you get them met,
you don't need them any more.
As our 30 days wore on,
Aidan and I miraculously managed
to not kill each other.
But, as I predicted,
the plant was not so lucky.
www.tvsubtitles.net