ln the expanding galaxy of New York,
there are heavenly bodies
one orbits around everyday.
And stars whose gravitational pull
one drifts in and out of over the years.
Bobby Fine - satellite friend,
piano bar legend.
I usuaIIy do this number at home
In a pink kaftan and Peggy Lee wig
You've never done the same
after three daiquiris?
l must take a break to say hello
to a celebrity friend.
ls there any other kind?
Little Miss Carrie Bradshaw.
She writes books. Remember books?
Primitive versions of the DVD.
Please stop. OK, one more time,
for the cheap seats in the back.
Is that aII there is?
Yes, that's aII there is
How long have you known each other?
''Cats'' was just kittens.
''Cats''. The musical? Hello?
- l loved ''Cats''.
- Medic!
lt hasn't been that long.
When we met, you took aerobics
and Stanford had hair.
- Bobby?
- Bitsy. l thought you had a dinner.
l do. The driver is circling.
l had to say hello.
Bitsy Von Muffling.
Carrie, Miranda, Samantha
and the one who liked ''Cats''.
Samantha Jones.
l did PR for your museum benefit.
Samantha, of course. l loved you.
l was just so thrilled
that someone liked ''Cats''.
- l didn't like it that much.
- Waiter, sense of humour, table five.
- Samantha, how are you?
- Fabulous. You?
Delirious. l'm madly in love
and getting married.
- Big Hamptons wedding.
- Who's the lucky stud?
Me.
- You're getting married?
- Can you believe it?
Bitsy and l are enfianced.
l finally found the right girl.
Mr Broadway has to tinkle
before he can tinkle.
l have your address. You must come.
Nice meeting you all.
l thought he was gay.
''Mr Broadway has to tinkle.''
That has to be the gayest sentence.
- lt must be for the money.
- He doesn't need money.
He was an original investor
in ''A Chorus Line''.
When you thought you'd never hear
a phrase gayer than
''Mr Broadway has to tinkle.''
Why is he getting married?
ln 1988, Bobby Fine announced
he was selling his piano bar
and going to volunteer
with the Nicaraguan orphans.
The orphans are still waiting.
This wedding will never happen.
lt's happening.
Everything's booked.
The big question is where will we stay?
That's the big question? What about,
why are these two getting married?
- ls that all there is?
- Bitsy said they were in love.
l find the love facade
the most offensive part.
We're adults. We can handle it.
Bitsy should say, ''l'm getting older.
l want companionship.''
Bobby should say,
''Hot men don't go for me any more.''
Don't print invitations and call it love,
as if it transforms people.
That's bullshit.
- You don't want to be my date?
- Not unless they have summer houses.
- We'll stay with Stanford and Marcus.
- l was a fool to break up
with Richard before Labor Day.
He has a fabulous house.
l wouldn't go to this charade
if you paid me.
Like there's a pink suede elephant in
the room and no one can talk about it.
- Do you think they won't have sex?
- All married couples stop having sex.
- You've had sex with married people.
- That's how l know.
OK, let's say it's companionship.
How do you sustain a relationship
without the zsa zsa zsu?
The what?
The butterflies when you not only love
the person but you've gotta have them.
Doesn't that get you through the years?
Even if it fades, you have the memory
of the zsa zsa zsu.
l'm fine with whatever people
want to do. Just be straight.
l think that's how
Bitsy proposed to Bobby.
Right then, Charlotte decided
to be straight with us.
l'm seeing someone...sort of.
You're in a sort of relationship?
lt's ridiculous. He's so not my type.
- ls he heterosexual?
- Yes.
But he's bald and short.
He talks with his mouth full.
l don't want to be seen
in public with him.
l hate his name - Harry.
He is, everywhere but his head.
Wow. ls the sex bad too?
lt's the best sex of my life.
l think l might really like him.
You want to go to a wedding
in the Hamptons?
- Bitsy Von Muffling's.
- You're invited?
- l handled her divorce.
- You aren't a Hamptons' type.
l am the Hamptons.
l own a house in Bridge.
l can't go.
l'm not ready for swimsuit season.
- You're a fucking knockout.
- lt's your back.
- What's wrong with it?
- lt's very hairy.
You're not supposed to be able
to grab someone's back.
What am l supposed to do about it?
Get it waxed.
You come with me to the wedding
and l will get my back waxed.
Fine.
- Come here, you.
- Your hands are all greasy.
That night, l thought about what it takes
to make a relationship work
till death do us part.
Most singles have
long-term success with friends.
Maybe it is a better strategy
to marry a friend.
However, in the absence of sex -
whether that's the arrangement
or what happens after a few years -
what distinguishes this companion
from your many others?
When it comes to saying ''l do'',
is a relationship a relationship
without the zsa zsa zsu?
Or in Samantha's case...
...how much is a woman due
for surviving the zsa zsa zsu?
This is Richard.
Our pathetic relationship
is as close to marriage
as either of us hopes to get.
l feel l deserve a settlement.
Like a weekend at your house
in the Hamptons. You're not invited.
l'm having a party.
You're not invited to that, either.
lt's Samantha. Call me.
A couple of weeks later,
another couple of exes
were working out their summer share.
- Hi. How you doing?
- Hey. Me and Brady were napping.
l miss napping.
They look down on napping at work.
lt's so hot out.
l was gonna give him
one more bottle before l left.
- l can do it.
- l know, but l like it.
lt used to be breasts.
Now we've got a bottle thing.
- Did Magda bring those?
- No, l did.
Nice garden in Queens.
Oh, lilacs.
Yeah.
Good flowers.
Miranda wasn't sure if it was
the smell of the lilacs,
the smell of the baby
or the smell of Steve's skin.
But that afternoon,
Steve went from ex to sex.
l slept with Steve.
Miranda admitted they were
between friends and lovers
between Manhattan and the Hamptons.
That's why you're participating
in the charade. You're fleeing.
l'm a fucking fugitive...literally.
Was it the zsa zsa zsu?
No, it was an itch we shouldn't have
scratched. Now we're into a grey area.
Not having sex
was holding us together.
You're fleeing to the right wedding.
That's the theme.
You can't have a kid with someone
and get along and have great sex
without giving the wrong impression.
Being what, that you're happy?
Absolutely!
Bring them along.
l look forward to seeing you too.
This party is going to be amazing.
Strictly 'A' list.
Are we still invited?
Yes, but shitty pants there is not.
l won't be able to find a sitter.
He's ruining my lunch,
not my party. No babies.
There's already a party pooper.
Ketchup.
Carrie?
Yeah. Hey, hi.
- Jack.
- Berger. l know. l remember.
You OK? Should l make a tourniquet
out of a hot dog bun and a twig?
- lt's just...
- Ketchup.
Yeah. Thanks.
l didn't figure you for a motorcycle guy.
l'm not. l bought it as a reaction
to my break-up.
Exactly what l wanted -
a Berger with a side of single.
You look good on it.
No, l look good next to it.
On it l look like this...
l'm not really hungry.
l pulled over cos a bug hit my visor.
- My hands are still shaking.
- So, you're ''Uneasy Rider''.
lf you make it to the Hamptons,
my friend is having a party tomorrow
at Richard Wright's house.
l heard about that. Quite a place.
l pass it on the way to mine.
l'm gonna get a soda. My throat's dry
from screaming inside my helmet.
- lt's nice to see you.
- You too, Berger.
- Maybe l'll see you tomorrow.
- lf you don't, call highway patrol.
Definitely zsa zsa zsu.
The next morning, Samantha prepared
her borrowed house for the big bash.
l want half the tables set up near
the house and the others near the pool.
Ladies?
- Cassandra, did you bring my tote?
- Where are my Merits?
Excuse me. Hi.
The wait staff is to change
in the guest cottage
near the entrance.
Aren't you here to waitress?
We go to restaurants.
We don't work in them.
- Where's Richard?
- Richard isn't here.
l've got the house this weekend.
Excuse me!
Where are you going?
Richard said we could hang
by the pool whenever.
You can't today.
l'm having a party at 3:00.
We'll be fried by then.
l have no cell reception at all.
Miranda brought the kid.
Don't say anything.
l know you didn't want babies.
He's wearing Ralph Lauren
and l stuck a cork up his ass.
This is supposed to be an 'A' list party.
Who's the double 'D' list by the pool?
They won't leave. They say Richard
lets them hang out. Freeloaders.
- People in glass houses...
- l am not freeloading.
l went through a lot. People should be
rewarded for not getting married.
l don't know why you broke up.
What's lying and cheating
compared to a pool with a cabana?
Did you say no babies or no boobies?
Lady and Brady.
- That is so inappropriate.
- Greetings from Silicone Valley.
People can hear you.
Like everyone here
can't see those tits are fake?
Stop saying tits.
Why are you wearing that shirt?
Tropical shirts are out.
This is not tropical. lt's Tiki.
- Please Tiki it off.
- l thought you would never ask.
Your back! You must have had
a bad reaction to the waxing.
l thought it felt a little itchy.
Suddenly a little hair isn't so bad.
Carrie, woman to woman,
the sex is amazing.
l've never had a man
make me feel this way.
Hush, Ms Scarlet, how you do go...
Well, who ordered the Adonis?
Bobby, Bitsy. My boyfriend, Marcus.
For God's sake, get yourself to a gym.
Look at that body. lt's disgusting!
Wow, l could grate cheese on your abs.
One large pizza, and hold the salami.
Please put a shirt on
before l marry you.
l haven't touched a carbohydrate
in three months.
- l have to fit into that dress.
- Eat something.
Look at her. She's itsy Bitsy.
l see the Talcots. We've gotta
say hello. See you all tomorrow.
l'm totally serious.
l almost fainted when he mimed
grated cheese on Marcus.
lt's so obvious that he wanted him.
Try to keep up. Bobby is straight.
- What is she doing?
- Maybe he just makes her laugh.
Can't you wait to sit down to eat?
lt's so crass.
ls there anything about me today
that doesn't bug you?
People are eating.
You should have your shirt on.
You have sauce on your face.
Now so do you.
Why did she need to tell me
the sex was amazing?
lt is amazing. She's amazed
he can get hard without another penis.
Speaking of dicks, do you think
Richard slept with any of those bitches?
No, l'm sure they're just good friends.
Berger.
- How do l look?
- Great.
- Where's a mirror?
- Here.
Great.
All right. Put it down.
Thanks for having a party.
- How long have you had a house?
- Three years.
Moments later, among the butterflies,
l felt butterflies.
There's a nice garden.
- You garden?
- No, l have been known to hoe.
My ex planted the garden so
we could enjoy fresh summer salads.
We didn't make it to summer.
lt's more fresh pain than vegetables.
l can't go out there.
l know how you feel.
When l broke up with my ex,
l couldn't go within six blocks
of his furniture store.
- When did you break up?
- Last year for the second time.
We broke up first the year before.
You broke up twice. Way to go.
We hadn't sufficiently
hurt each other enough the first time.
We definitely took care of business
this time because he moved in.
We had the merging of things,
the dividing of things.
The things left that you don't want
to give back because that's mean.
You don't want to throw them away.
lt's all you have left.
lt's harder as we get older. We're not
dating wildly inappropriate people.
There's no, ''Glad that's over.''
After every break-up,
l tell myself l'm never doing this again.
lt's too hard. How many
of these things can one survive?
They should institute
a helmet law for relationships.
- Right. That's excellently put.
- Thank you.
l should get going.
lt's gonna take me six hours
to drive two miles home.
My jacket.
- l hope there aren't grass stains.
- lt's old.
- OK, bye.
- Bye.
The man could not get away
fast enough.
Apparently it's a short road
from ''commisery'' to misery.
Are you OK?
Perfect. Everything's going out on time.
There's no Tab in here.
- What are you doing in my refrigerator?
- lt's Richard's.
l stocked it.
Did you see any rice krispie treats?
Richard usually leaves those for us.
No, l didn't.
Those lemons are for the drinks,
drinks l paid for.
- Whatever.
- l also paid for the food.
The only thing at this party you two
actually paid for are your breasts.
Jealous?
Oh, yes. l'm jealous.
l'm just dying to look like this.
Maybe if you did,
you'd be out here with Richard.
Snap!
Evidently, people who borrow glass
houses shouldn't throw cantaloupes.
The next morning,
while Stanford and Marcus had Brady,
Miranda and l had brunch.
- How about these muffins.
- These eggs.
- These napkins.
- These plates.
- How about we marry gay guys?
- Now l have no choice.
- Was it really that bad?
- One minute we were laughing.
The next he had to get away so fast,
he left skid marks. l can show you.
Jam, please.
l know what l did.
l revealed too much too soon.
l was emotionally slutty.
- That's not like you.
- The zsa zsa zsu makes me crazy.
Bitsy Von Muffling-Fine
may have the right idea.
Stop looking for a great relationship
and settle for a fine one.
l'd marry Steve if he were gay.
Everything would be so easy.
A gay area is better than a grey area?
Oh, yeah. More coffee. Want some?
- Great coffee.
- Tell me something l don't know.
- What?
- You did it, Stanny.
Great man, great house...
great relationship.
We've all been looking and you found it.
Marcus and l haven't had sex since
we bought the Cynthia Rowley china.
Thank God, l am so relieved.
Bitsy Von Muffling,
the first time l saw you, l fell in love.
You walked in wearing
that red vintage Dior.
Pink elephant in the room.
Do you mind?
l'm listening to the bride and...bride.
My dear Bobby Fine...
Something tells me Bitsy
isn't doing Fine.
That's the little piece of information
she's been Von Muffling.
You are there in the morning.
There for me at night.
There in the good. There in the bad.
There in my thoughts.
There in my dreams.
But most of all, my darling,
you are there in my heart...forever.
Perhaps we were all much too cynical.
Perhaps despite the odds, Bobby
and Bitsy had found something real.
l now pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
One more time
for the cheap seats at the back.
Somebody over here is about to dance.
- l think you may have sold him short.
- Me too.
With a little time
and the right astringent...
There's nothing on my face,
in my teeth.
You'll hate my moves
on the dance floor,
but that is the risk
every man must take.
What a beautiful night.
Too bad l blew my chance
at a boyfriend this year.
You wanna hold my boyfriend?
l think l'm gonna drown my sorrows
in another piece of cake.
And if anybody asks,
l had two, not three.
Do you smell that, Brady? That's lilac.
Should we call Daddy
and tell him we miss him?
lt's Steve. l'm not here.
Leave a message.
Do you believe this wedding?
Funny where life has taken us.
l remember when we went to these
for the free food.
l have rolls in my purse.
There's my song.
And there's my girl...
...whom l love.
ln case you had any money on it.
Not a penny.
Look out. She's got a piece of fruit
and she's not afraid to throw it.
- Can we not talk about that?
- OK, but we'll be the only ones here.
l'm glad Brady wasn't
the biggest baby at the party.
l went a little crazy
being at Richard's house...
...around his party crashing
pussy posse.
What do you call
zsa zsa zsu gone bad?
Zsa zsa... eugh!
l fell in love with
the most wonderful boy in the world.
- Bitsy, honey, everything was perfect.
- lt was.
Except the dessert. The top layer
of the crème brûlée wasn't hard enough.
That's the problem with this wedding.
The crème brûlée isn't hard enough.
Then one day, he went away.
l thought l would die, but l didn't.
When l didn't, l said to myself,
''ls that all there is to love?''
l'm not technically crashing.
l was having lunch in town today
and the groom invited me.
Shall we?
- Harry?
- You want me to wax my eyebrows?
l think l may be falling in love with you.
l've been falling for you since we met.
- But l never thought...
- What?
You could have
any blue-blooded guy here. l'm...
You're wonderful.
And Jewish.
- So?
- So, where can this go?
l don't know. Let's find out.
l have to marry a Jew.
She can marry a gay guy,
and you can't marry an Episcopalian?
- What do we do now?
- l don't know.
Dance.
Apparently,
Charlotte had a zsa zsa Jew.
You're awful quiet.
- l intend to stay that way.
- No.
You were fine. l just wasn't sure
if l was up for all that again.
Then l thought...
Then you thought what?
Maybe we should go out on a date
before we break up.
When it comes to relationships,
maybe we're all in glass houses
and shouldn't throw stones.
You can never really know.
Some people are settling down.
Some people are settling.
And some people refuse
to settle for anything less...
...than butterflies.
www.tvsubtitles.net