So, how does this game work?
I just throw it,
like a real ball?
Yeah, just nice and easy,
right over the plate.
All right.
You suck, Wolowitz!
What's that about?
I'm heckling you.
It's a beloved part
of baseball.
He's right.
And given that you're
probably still waiting
to be picked for a game that
was played in fifth grade,
I'm sure you do suck.
Hi. What's going on?
Baseball.
Okay, this is not
what I meant when I said
go outside and play.
He's practicing.
For what?
The Angels wanted an astronaut
to throw out the first pitch,
so guess who they called?
What, you? Really?!
Well, a lot of people who
weren't available, but then me!
That's so cool!
Congratulations.
I guess that makes you
the athlete of the group.
Well, not just him!
May I remind you that you're
talking to the seeker, beater,
chaser and water boy
of the third place
Griffith Park Quidditch team.
I know.
Watching your boyfriend
run around with a broomstick
between his legs
isn't something you forget.
C'mon now,
throw one.
All right,
here we go.
You look like a jackass!
Cut it out!
You're hurting my feelings!
Now you know why
we're not outside.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x03 ♪
The First Pitch Insufficiency
Original Air Date on Septem
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Did you enjoy
my lecture?
No, and neither did
our waiter.
Well, if you're going to
serve Cornish game hen,
you should either be familiar
with the history of Cornwall
or be prepared
to learn it.
It's hard to argue with that.
And I know because I saw a
sad man with a pepper mill
desperately try and fail.
Hey, how was dinner?
Good, I had Cornish game hen.
Oh, that poor waiter.
Sheldon, how about tomorrow
night we see a movie?
You guys are going out
two nights in a row?
I missed a number of date nights
while I was on my train trip,
and I'm contractually
obligated to make them up
under the terms of the
Relationship Agreement.
That's so hot.
It's better than hot,
it's binding.
If you're free
tomorrow night,
I'd love to have you
join us on a double date.
Aw...
You are aware that a double date
doesn't count as two dates.
Oh.
Well, then come
or don't.
I don't care.
I can't believe you're sore.
Hey, even professional pitchers
need a rubdown after the game.
But they throw
an actual ball.
You were throwing
air at a TV.
For your information,
I also gave Leonard
one hell of a high five.
I'm kind of surprised
you agreed to do this
in front of a stadium
full of people.
They're doing Space Day
and NASA asked me.
I felt like I couldn't say no.
Okay.
Well, if you want,
I could help you practice.
I played a lot of softball
growing up.
Thank you, that
would be great.
Great.
And while we're at it,
maybe we could butch up your run
for when you head out
to the mound.
What's wrong with the way I run?
Oh, just kidding.
Nothing.
Sheldon, I'm surprised
you'd choose to go to a pub.
At our committee meeting,
Amy made a motion
for a picnic in a park,
but I tacked so many amendments
on that thing
it sank like a lead balloon.
I then suggested a pub.
Yeah, which I was
initially skeptical of until
I saw online that they serve
Yorkshire pudding.
You don't even like
No, it's yucky,
but informing people about
the history of Yorkshire
is yummy, yum-yum.
After a lively debate,
that proposal passed
by a two-zero margin.
Nice to see a busy couple
keep the spark
of bureaucracy alive.
Ignore them, Amy.
They're just jealous
because they'll never have
a relationship as good as ours.
Isn't this when he says
“bazooka” or something?
I wasn't
making a joke,
I was merely
stating fact.
Amy and I have a superior
relationship to yours.
You don't honestly
think that, do you?
Y... Leonard,
I assumed you knew.
The ranking of
relationships in our circle
by quality is:
me and Amy,
Howard and Bernadette,
Raj and his girlfriend,
Penny and Chardonnay,
Penny and you.
There isn't any ranking.
And if there were, we wouldn't
be at the bottom of it.
Yeah, and actually,
I drink Sauvignon Blanc.
That's the part
you have a problem with?
Relax.
There they go,
fighting again.
You'd never hear her talk
that way to Sauvignon Blanc.
So you never played
baseball as a kid,
not even
Little League?
Well, I was going to,
but the day of tryouts
I found my dad's
Playboy collection.
Threw my arm out.
All right, the pitcher's mound
in Major League Baseball
is 60 feet, six inches
away from home plate.
Great. You take this
and say when to stop
How much further?
Keep going.
How about now?
I'll let you know.
Are you saying “stop” and we're
just too far away to hear you?
Okay, stop.
Are you kidding me?!
That's 60 feet.
There's no way
this is 60 feet.
I'm looking at it.
You realize this isn't
one of those times
I want you to exaggerate
how long something is.
Okay, I got to...
I-I just...
I got to ask:
what makes you think
that your relationship
is so wonderful
and ours isn't?
For starters,
we enjoy spending time together.
So do we.
And I've seen you guys
ignore each other for hours
doing totally
different things.
It's called parallel play.
Yeah, toddlers
do that.
Not as well as we do.
You believe this guy? He has to
be the best at everything.
So what?
Why do you even care?
Oh, listen to them.
Not even married
and the honeymoon's over.
Whatever. You can't
even go on a date
without checking your
relationship agreement.
If you've got a problem basing
a relationship on a contract,
I'd like to tell you
about 13 plucky colonies
that entered
a “relationship agreement”
called the U.S. Constitution.
And it may not be cool
to say so,
but I think that love affair
is still pretty hot today.
It's a good thing I'm not
wearing flag underwear
right now, 'cause there's
about to be a fire.
Okay, it's not
that hard.
You just look to where
you want to throw it,
step towards where
you want to throw,
and throw it.
That's your help?
That's like saying,
“Here's how you fly a plane:
“get in the airplane,
know where you want
to go and fly it.”
Just throw the ball. Let's see what
we're working with.
Come on Howard, fire it in.
Throw the damn ball!
So when do you guys
plan on getting married?
Uh, we're not sure.
But I want to wait long enough
to prove to my mother
I'm not pregnant.
May I have
one of your fries?
Of course.
Can I have a bite
of your burger?
Absolutely not.
Some perfect couple.
He won't even share
his food with her.
It has avocado on it.
She's allergic
to avocado.
Are you so jealous
of our relationship
you want Amy to die?
I'm not jealous.
I just think it's silly for
you to compare relationships
like they're something
that can be quantified.
Everything is quantifiable.
That French fry? A seven.
Spider-Man? A nine.
The number nine--
oddly, only a four.
How ridiculous is he?
A hundred.
Sheldon, you're just
assigning random numbers
to things based on your opinion.
No, I'm not.
French fries have
three variables--
crispiness, saltiness
and shape.
Which is why a curly fry
only gets a two.
If I wanted curls for dinner,
I'd order a clown wig.
Well, a relationship is more
complicated than a French fry.
Not according to the work
of Berscheid, Snyder and Omoto.
Oh, what did those
rascals do now?
They developed the Relationship
Closeness Inventory,
which predicts the stability
of a couple based on behavior.
Yeah, not to be confused
with the French Fry
Goodness Inventory.
That's pure Cooper.
So, this is accurate?
It's been around for 25 years,
and has been extensively
corroborated
by other researchers.
Well, kind of takes the romance
out of relationships.
Kind of? It does it perfectly.
Sheldon and I got
an eight-point-two
out of ten.
Fine. We'll take it
right now.
No, don't.
What?
Just don't take it.
Why not?
'Cause it's stupid.
Who cares what
number it is?
Come on. It'll be fun.
I said I don't want you to.
I'm getting
another drink.
Sorry.
I'm gonna let you
count this as two dates.
They're a lot of work.
Think he's getting
any better?
Yup.
That was a close one!
Okay!
Is it too late
for him to cancel?
I think so.
Heads up! Watch out!
Are you mad at me?
No, stop being stupid.
Um... whew?
Is this about the test,
or is this about us?
Look, I don't need
a score on a test
to make me worry about something
I'm already worried about.
What are you worried about?
That we're engaged and
have nothing in common,
and it scares me.
Yeah, that scares me, too.
It does?
Sometimes.
Well, that's not good!
You being blindly infatuated
with me was the rock
we were building
this relationship on!
Okay, well, this might
make you feel better.
Uh, we're both scared that
our marriage will be a disaster,
and so, that's something
that we have in common.
Also, we both think
I'm not funny.
Huh? See, you're not laughing.
Hey, Froot Loops, what's up?
Hey, Mike.
Listen, NASA asked me to
throw out the first pitch
at an Angels game.
You got any advice?
Yeah. Don't do it.
What else you up to?
Why shouldn't I do it?
There's no upside.
If you do well, no one cares.
And if you screw up,
you're an idiot
on YouTube forever.
But it's for a good cause.
What about all the kids
that'll be there?
That's what I'm telling you.
Kids are the worst.
My own daughter tweeted
I have a giant nose.
Well, maybe I'll do a good job.
I don't know.
In space,
you couldn't even toss me a pen,
and that was in zero gravity.
Okay, thanks for the pep talk.
Anytime, Froot Loops.
Give your wife a hug for me.
She's so much cuter than you, I
don't know how you ever got her.
He's so nice.
Hey, sorry about that.
No, we're sorry.
We never should have been
comparing relationships
in the first place.
Why? We won.
You know, I say, next, we take
on Koothrappali and his dog.
Really give
ourselves a challenge.
I just want to say
one more thing about this.
Just because Penny
and I are very different people
does not mean
that we're a bad couple.
The answer is
one simple test away.
Hmm? You know,
it's like
when I thought there was
a possum in my closet.
Did I sit around
wondering?
No, I sent Leonard in with
a pointy stick and a bag.
I killed
his Chewbacca slippers.
Let's just
take the test.
No, no, no,
I don't want to.
Oh, well, 'cause you
know we're gonna do bad.
Because it doesn't matter.
I don't care
if we're a ten or a two.
Or a one.
A one is possible.
Marriage is scary.
You're scared, I'm scared.
But it doesn't make me
not want to do it.
It-it just...
makes me want to hold your hand
and do it with you.
Leonard...
It would make me so happy
if you said things like that.
We got an
eight-point-two.
Trust me, you're happy.
Mm! I love how they put
a waterfall at center field.
It really ties
the whole stadium together.
Look at you, talking sports.
This is fun, huh?
We get to see our friend
throw out the first pitch,
have a hot dog,
watch the game.
Whoa.
Nobody said anything
about watching the game.
Sheldon, what
did you expect?
I expected to see Howard throw
the baseball, finish my hot dog,
and hightail it across
the street to Disneyland
just in time for Mickey's
Soundsational Parade.
I'll tell you what.
If we stay, I'll buy you
cotton candy and a bobblehead.
Who's the bobblehead of?
Does it matter?
No, as long as it bobbles.
Howie, I am so proud of you.
Thanks.
I'm proud of me, too.
Mm-hmm.
You ready?
Let's do it.
All right.
Wish me luck.
Go get 'em.
Ladies and gentlemen,
in honor of Space Day at
Angel Stadium, the first pitch
will be thrown out by NASA
astronaut Howard Wolowitz.
Thank you.
Can he really
throw a ball?
On our Quidditch team, he...
Yeah, that's a “no.”
I have a message
for the young people here today.
When I was asked
to throw the first pitch,
a little voice in my head said
I couldn't do it.
So, I practiced and practiced,
and you know what?
That little voice...
...was right, but...
...then I remembered
that I'm not an athlete.
I'm a scientist.
So, today's
first pitch will be delivered
to home plate by science.
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls, I present to you
a working prototype
of the Mars Rover!
And here's the wind-up...
and the pitch!
Why is it going so slow?!
'Cause I'm an idiot
who didn't think this through!
Okay, new plan.
We go to Disneyland,
play hide and seek
on Tom Sawyer's Island,
and then come back
and see the end of the pitch.
Okay, while we're waiting
for the ball to arrive,
here's some fun facts
about Mars.
You suck, Wolowitz!
He makes a valid point!
Okay, booing isn't gonna make it
go any faster!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net