What color would you like to be?
Well, I'd like to be green,
but you know you always take it.
That's not true.
Any color's fine with me.
Yeah, I could be a-a combination
of blue and yellow.
Blue and yellow make green.
Well, then it's settled.
Hi. Ready to go?
Oh, good news, we ordered lunch,
so we can all stay here
and play Lord of the Rings Risk.
Sheldon, we said that we would
play games with you tonight.
Oh, no, we'll still
be playing it tonight--
this game can easily
take eight hours.
Sweetie, you really thought
I'd want to do this?
No.
Well, did you tell him that?
Yes.
Did you say it out loud with words?
No.
I don't want to spend the whole
day playing a board game.
Yeah, well, you may change
your mind when you hear
that this is the
new expanded edition
which contains a more
complete map of Middle Earth,
now including
the Haradwaith Territories.
I will literally
race you to the car.
No, no, no, come on,
don't leave. Just try it.
No. We're always doing
what you guys want.
Just once, it'd be nice
if you did something we wanted.
You want to be green?
You know, they
really have tried to like
a lot of the same stuff we're into.
Yeah, we do game
nights and video game
nights and we watch movies
with director's commentary.
Oh, my favorite--
George Lucas can talk
all the way through
Star Wars, I say one word
and I'm banished
to the kitchen.
Yeah, today Amy and I
are deciding
what we're all gonna do.
You got it, you girls
are in charge.
Thank you.
Sheldon?
Fine.
Now that we're not playing,
you can be green.
Thank you.
And since you're green
this time, I can
be it next time.
All right, let's see.
What's something fun
the guys would
never take us to do?
Oh, I know-- we could
go horseback riding.
I actually can't.
My hips don't open
wider than 22 degrees.
I rode a very
thin pony once.
On the first bump...
just popped right off.
All right, well,
what do you want to do?
There's a craft and folk
art museum on Wilshire.
Well, that's Wilshire's problem.
Come on, you know, there-there's
got to be something fun we could
do that the guys will hate.
Hang on, why do we
have to hate it?
Three words:
Doctor Who convention.
I-I did not force you
to go to that.
You walked out of the house
in a fez and bow tie. I went
so you didn't get beat up.
I wasn't gonna get beat up.
You were, but somehow
I held myself back.
You know what you could
make us do? Ice-skating.
The cold air will trigger
Leonard's asthma
and it plays right into
my well-known fear of
getting flattened by a Zamboni.
Now you're helping them
find ways to make us miserable?
Well, I'm sorry, Leonard, I'm a
problem-solver, it's what I do.
I actually can't
go ice-skating.
I have unnaturally
brittle ankles.
Is there any part
of your body that's normal?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
Oh, my God, oh, my
God, oh, my God.
Will you please relax?
I can't take it, dude.
You okay?
No, I'm not okay. I feel like
I'm gonna jump out of my skin.
I told you
not to wax down there.
It's itchy when it grows back.
I'm worried about
the New Horizons space probe.
What's he talking about?
Nine years ago
he was part of a team
that launched a spacecraft
to collect data about Pluto.
It's finally close enough, so
this morning
it turned itself on.
We hope.
The signal has to travel
over three billion miles.
So it's gonna be hours before
we know if it even survived.
Now we get to see him flip out
because he's worried
it was demolished by space ice.
Space ice is no joke.
I can't even watch
Frozen anymore.
Ooh, the philharmonic
is playing Beethoven downtown.
Yeah, well, before
you say yes,
it's not the movie
about the big dog.
How come we can't think
of something we both want to do?
Because you always
pick what we do
and I just
go along with it.
Ah, interesting--
we're being accused of
making you do things
you don't like,
and here you are,
doing the same
thing to poor Amy.
You should point out
the hypocrisy of that.
That's what I was doing.
Oh, that wasn't clear.
Try it again, but this time
drive it home
with, “How do you like
them apples, Missy?”
All right,
keep thinking.
You're making it
too complicated.
Why not stick
to the basics?
Go shopping for clothes
while Leonard and I sit in those
uncomfortable chairs
and hold your purses, hmm?
I know I'd hate that.
Leonard?
Well, yeah.
Well, then, it's settled?
What do you say?
Sounds kind of perfect.
It does-- somehow he managed
to take all the fun out of it.
Well, once again,
it's what I do.
Oh, another two hours to go.
The wait
is killing me.
I know. I get it. When I was
in the Soyuz capsule
returning from the space
station, plummeting toward Earth
at 17,000 miles per hour...
Before you finish,
is this a story about
patience and waiting
or just another reminder
that you went to space?
A story can
do two things.
Ugh, I feel like I'm gonna
have a heart attack.
You work in
pharmaceuticals--
don't you have
anything you can give him?
All I have is our new
urine flow drug.
Won't help with his anxiety,
but it's so strong, when he pees
he'll fly around the room
like he's got a jet pack.
I can't stop thinking about it.
You know, worrying won't
have any effect on what happens.
I know.
Maybe you need to do
something more productive.
Okay.
Ah.
If I make this shot
in the trash can,
the probe will have arrived
in perfect working order.
So, in addition to being crazy,
you're resting the fate
of the mission
on your athletic prowess.
Yes.
The man who crashed
his stationary bike.
I didn't crash it, okay?
My playlist was too up-tempo,
I got light-headed
and I fell off.
Okay.
It all...
comes down...
to this.
You happy? Now you can relax.
What kind of scientist are you?
Everyone knows
you got to make
two out of three.
This isn't so bad.
That's easy for you to say.
Your chair's not
facing the lingerie section.
Boy, that's a lot of panties.
You guys comfy?
This might take a while.
You know, I don't
understand why women
insist on making
a big production
out of buying clothes.
No, you're right,
we should do what you do.
Have our mom send us pants
from the Walmart in Houston.
They have a man there
who understands
my personal style.
Bye.
Uh, I've got some bad news.
There's no cell service in here.
Oh.
Well, that's all right.
There were plenty of ways
to pass the time
before smart phones
were invented.
That's true.
I'll look them up.
Son of a biscuit.
Sheldon, it's fine.
No, it's not fine.
What kind of store
in the 21st century
doesn't at least have Wi-Fi?
I'm going to call
their corporate office...
Son of a biscuit!
Let's see, my armies
are going
to attack the Shire
from Buckland.
And I roll...
a five and a three.
Okay.
And to defend, I roll...
two sixes. I win.
Boy, double-sixes again.
You know...
if I hadn't seen it
with my own eyes,
I wouldn't believe it.
I wonder how long
we're gonna be stuck here.
I don't know, but the girls
do a lot for us.
It's the least we can do.
Oh, that's true.
I suppose it's only fair
we make compromises.
Look at you,
being all mature.
I don't know why
you're so surprised.
If there's one thing I know
about after living with you
for so many years,
it's how to compromise.
I-I'm sorry?
You make compromises for me?
All the time.
On Earth?
In our lives?
That-That we're living?
Oh, yes. I...
Just yesterday, you had
a-a big piece of lettuce
stuck in your teeth at lunch.
Did I say anything? No.
I compromised
and kept my mouth shut.
Like you should've, because
everyone was laughing at you.
That is not
a compromise.
A compromise is me
driving you everywhere
because you refuse to learn how.
Oh, I learned how.
Amy taught me.
What? Then-Then why
don't you do it?
Uh, well, it's scary.
And sometimes
I get the pedals mixed up.
But, more importantly,
driving me to work
is one of the things
that gives your life purpose.
I can't take that away from you,
so... what do I do?
Oh, come on, I'm practically
feeding you the answer.
I compromise.
Hey, uh, thanks for
keeping me company.
I'm happy to.
I think getting out of
the apartment will do you good.
So... where we headed?
If it's okay with you,
I'd like to go to temple.
Buddy, trust me, you don't want
to convert to Judaism.
I mean, I know I make it
look cool,
but... it's not all briskets
and dreidels.
I meant a Hindu temple.
Oh. Okay.
It's not like Indiana Jones
and the Temple of Doom, right?
Some bald guy with horns
isn't gonna rip my heart out.
Dude, that movie's
an imperialist fantasy
that makes the followers of a
beautiful and peaceful religion
look like a bunch
of bloodthirsty barbarians.
You love that movie.
Yeah, it's pretty great.
I'm surprised to see you
suddenly get religious.
Why?
Well, because I've known you
for ten years
and you've never gone to temple,
you never talked
about believing in God,
and last Diwali I watched you
eat two pounds of sacred cow
at a Brazilian steak house.
Religion is
a very personal thing.
I do go to temple--
I just... I don't talk about it.
Yeah, but you're
a scientist.
So?
So, as a scientist,
you believe the way
to understand the universe
is through facts and evidence,
and now
you're counting
on some blue chick
with a hundred arms to help you?
That is so offensive.
Does everything you know
about Hinduism come
from Indiana Jones?
No. There's also Apu
from The Simpsons.
Well, lots of scientists
believe in God.
Okay? Newton,
uh, Faraday,
uh, Pascal-- all were believers.
Even Einstein was famous
for attacking quantum theory
on the grounds
that “God does not play dice
with the universe.”
Well, of course
he believed in God--
he slept with Marilyn Monroe.
Actually
there's no proof of that.
You believe in your religion,
I'll believe in mine.
How's it going
in there?
Eh.
Not really a great outfit
for work,
unless something opens up in
the hookers and whores division.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Sure.
Do I really force you
to do things you don't want to?
Yeah, but it's okay.
How is it okay?
I promised myself,
if I ever got friends,
I'd do whatever they said.
Really, I'm lucky you found me
before a cult did.
Well, you know,
that was a long time ago.
You're a different woman now.
You're smart,
you've got great friends,
you've got a boyfriend,
you're pretty, you have
zero fashion sense, but...
Anyway, tonight we're gonna do
whatever you want.
Really?
Absolutely.
You name it, we're doing it.
Basket weaving
at the craft museum.
Well, you named it.
Oh, here's another one.
I wish that the apple pancake
mix was on the top shelf
because it starts with an “A,”
but I don't put it there
because I don't want you
breaking one of your little legs
when you're supposed
to be making my breakfast.
Is it my turn to talk
about the compromises I make?
I wasn't done, but go ahead.
He said, compromising.
Because of you, I'm not allowed
to adjust the temperature
in my own home.
I'm not allowed to whistle.
I don't wear shoes
that might squeak.
Well, you're a physicist,
not a circus clown.
Sheldon, do you realize I don't
live with the woman I love
because of you?
No other reason. Just you.
Is that true?
Yes, it's true. The last time
I brought it up,
you had an emotional breakdown
and got on a train and ran away.
Well, given my history
on the subject,
it seems a little reckless
to bring it up now.
You have no idea
how much you inconvenience
the lives of everyone
around you.
It's exhausting!
You know what?
You think you're so tolerant,
but the truth is...
you're mean to me a lot.
Yeah,
you think
that I don't notice
all those sarcastic comments
and those eye rolls,
but I do. Hmm?
I have
excellent peripheral vision.
On a good day,
I can see my ears.
Sheldon, I-I'm sorry
if I hurt your feelings.
I've been holding a lot
of this in for a while.
Well, I'm sorry, too.
And if you want
to live with Penny,
then I think you should.
Do you mean that?
Yes. Yeah, just put
on your squeaky shoes and...
your way out of my life.
Come on, don't get upset.
I'm not upset.
I'm just imagining a world
without my best friend in it.
Sheldon.
It's okay.
I-I'm not leaving your world.
I'm just talking
about living across the hall.
I understand.
Either way,
I want you to know that...
I'm aware of how difficult
I can be.
So I just want
to say...
thank you
for putting up with me.
Buddy...
How are you guys
getting alo...?
What? Why are
there tears?
Everything's fine.
We just started talking
about living arrangements.
Are you crazy? You know
he's a flight risk.
That's exactly
what I told him.
Sheldon, we know this
is a sensitive subject,
and Leonard's not gonna
move out until you're ready.
Well, what if you did it
gradually?
All right. Well...
how about we start
with two nights a week
I live with Penny?
How about one night and...
I let you whistle?
Okay.
When I'm not home.
You got it.
There we go,
compromising again.
We really are the best.
Here we go,
my first
Hindu temple.
You see behind the
fountain, that tower
that looks like a pyramid?
It's called a Sikhara.
It symbolizes
the-the connection between
the human and the divine.
Huh.
I always thought
it was mini golf.
All right. Shall we?
Yeah. Just, uh, is there
anything I should know
before I go in?
Like what?
Like am I dressed okay?
Really? So every other place
you've been,
you thought this was fine?
I know you're under a lot
of pressure,
so I'm gonna let that pass.
Sorry. You're right.
I'm so stressed.
But you know what,
whenever I walk
into that temple
I realize that whatever happens,
it's okay.
We're all part of
an immense pattern,
and though we can't understand
it, we can be happy to know
that it's-it's working its will
through us.
That's nice.
Whether you call it God
or the universe or the self,
we're all interconnected,
and that's just a beautiful...
Son of a bitch!
That guy just dinged my car!
S-Seriously?
Y-You were
just gonna drive away?
Like my life
isn't hard enough right now.
A space probe
might be destroyed,
my parents are going
through an awful divorce,
the guy who cuts my dog's hair
just gave her bangs!
Raj.
You saw her. She looks like
Jim Carrey from Dumb and Dumber!
Raj, you just
got a text.
The probe turned
on. It's fine.
Oh, good.
Namaste, Grandpa.
I thought
this was gonna be boring,
but it's actually kind of fun.
Don't tell Amy that. We'll
be here every Sunday.
Sheldon, that really is
an excellent basket.
It's not a basket.
It's a soldier's helmet
from 16th century China.
Very nice.
Yeah, it
looks great.
I saw that.
Well, roomie,
it's only one night a week,
but it's a start.
I know. I'm really
proud of Sheldon.
Yeah, I'm proud of him, too.
Can you keep it
down? Some of us
are trying
to sleep out here.
== sync, corrected by Nitish ==
@Nitish
www.tvsubtitles.net