English Subtitles
[MP4] The Big Bang Theory S08E01 (720p) Locomotion Interruption WEB-DL-Rip [KoTuWa]
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
We were worried about you.
Don't be melodramatic.
I'm just getting on a train
and leaving forever.
So a few things don't go your
way and your best decision
is to ride the
rails like a hobo?
Leonard, I am overwhelmed.
Everything is changing,
and it's simply too much.
I need to get
away and think.
Sheldon...
Yes?
I'm gonna miss you.
Of course you are.
You just made that easier.
Excuse me.
Is it at all possible that
you're knitting a pair of pants?
Oh, well, no, you're
understandably terrified.
But, you know, allow
me to explain.
45 days ago, um, I embarked on
a railroad journey of healing
because my university was
making me do string theory,
and my favorite comic
book store burned down,
and when my roommate
got engaged,
my girlfriend wanted
to move in with me,
which was no doubt a
ploy just to see my...
well, excuse my language,
but my bathing suit parts.
Uh, sir, may I
use your phone?
- I don't think so.
- Yeah, well,
I understand that I'm half naked, but
there is a reasonable explanation.
While I slept in my sleeper car,
all my possessions were stolen.
Now, typically,
I wear pajamas,
but I recently adopted
a hobo lifestyle
and pajamas are the
sleep-pants of the Man.
I'll have you know, Mahatma
Gandhi wore no pants
and a nation rallied
behind him!
My good man... Now,
before you walk away...
I know that I may
appear deranged,
but I am, in fact, a
world-renowned physicist.
Ask me the difference between a
boson and a fermion. Go ahead, ask!
Bosons have integer spin,
fermions have
half-integer spin!
My legs are getting cold!
Why won't anybody help me?
♪ Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth
began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪
We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x01 ♪
The Locomotion Interruption
Original Air Date on Septembe
Sync, corrected by Elder_Man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
- Morning.
- Hi. Want to do yoga with me?
Um, let me just have
some coffee first,
and then I'll have the strength to tell
you how much I won't be doing that.
Hello?
Hello, Leonard.
Hey, buddy. Good to
hear your voice.
Uh, I'm in Kingman, Arizona, and,
uh, I need you to come pick me up.
I'd love to. I'm just about
to do yoga with Penny.
Leonard, I'm at the police station.
I was robbed.
Th-They took my phone, my
wallet, my iPad, everything.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
No, I'm not okay. I-I'm
wearing borrowed pants,
I-I don't have I.D.,
and one of the officers here won't
stop calling me Chicken Legs.
Okay. Uh, I'll-I'll come get you.
What's the address?
- Hey, what's going on?
- Oh. He got all of his stuff stolen.
Oh...
Okay...
Sheldon, hang tight.
Hey, do you want me
to bring anything?
Oh, yes, please.
A pair of pants.
And my toothbrush.
Yeah, and my mail.
And a really good comeback
for Chicken Legs,
because “I know you are, but what
am I?” was met with stony silence.
I'll be there as
soon as I can.
Is he okay? Yeah, he's fine,
he's just a little rattled.
- Oh... - Feel like driving
to Arizona with me?
- No, I can't, I have that
job interview. - Oh, right.
Besides, I don't need six hours
of “Your hair is different.
“Why did you
change your hair?
I'm holding my breath until
your hair grows back.”
All right, fine.
Hey, can you think of a reason I
shouldn't invite Amy to come with me?
- Nope.
- Come on, you didn't even try.
Thanks for the lift.
- What's wrong with your car?
- I'm having my windows untinted.
Why?
Got a hot girlfriend now. I
want the haters to know.
What are you talking about? No
one's paying attention to you.
Wow.
How's that Hater-Ade
taste, bro?
Hey, this isn't
the way to work.
I just want to pop in and
make sure Ma's okay.
I thought Stuart was
looking after her.
He was, but now that her
cast is off, he moved out.
And honestly, I'm kind of glad.
It was getting a little weird.
How so?
I don't know, they're...
chummy.
Like us?
No, not like us. Creepy chummy,
like you and your dog.
She feeds him out
of her own mouth?
I mean, he calls her Debbie,
she calls him Stewie
and they're all giggly
around each other.
And believe me, when food goes in
that mouth, it does not come out.
So are you worried because
he's replacing you as a son
or are you worried because
he's becoming her lover?
First of all, no one can replace me
as a son. I'm her little matzo ball.
And secondly, my mother is well
past having any kind of sex life.
Okay, okay.
Although many older women
lead vibrant, active...
I said well past it!
Excuse me, Officer
Hernandez?
Any leads on the person
who stole my belongings?
- Not yet.
- Well, perhaps I can help.
Sherlock Holmes always says when
you eliminate the impossible,
whatever remains, however
improbable, must be the truth.
Now, have-have you
tried doing that?
Nope.
Well, maybe you should.
Th-Th-There's lots of books
called “Sherlock Holmes”
and there's no books called
“Officer Hernandez.”
Thanks again for coming. Six hours
was gonna be a long drive by myself.
My pleasure.
And I'm not angry at
all that my boyfriend
was in trouble and called you
instead of me. I love that!
Yeah, time's gonna fly by.
I haven't been on a job
interview in years.
- I'm really nervous.
- Don't be.
You are built for
pharmaceutical sales.
You're cute, you're
flirty and...
Started that like there
were gonna be three things.
I don't have any
experience in sales.
Unless you count the bikini car
wash I did in high school.
But you already made me
take that off my résumé.
This job is a lot like
being a waitress,
except instead of pushing the fish
tacos 'cause they're about to go bad,
you're just pushing
our antidepressants
before the FDA finds out they
may cause rectal bleeding.
They do?
Maybe.
But like our lawyers say,
the world is full of things
that can cause a
rectum to bleed.
Anyway, I talked
you up to Dan.
He's the guy who'll
be interviewing you.
Oh, I really appreciate this. I
just hope I'm not in over my head.
You'll be fine.
Just be yourself.
I wish I felt
more confident.
Penny, I wouldn't have
put you up for this job
if I didn't think you
could handle it.
Oh, thank you, but
maybe I should cancel.
It's too late to cancel.
You're going.
But I don't know anything
about pharmaceuticals.
Oh, I understand. You want to do
something you're already good at.
I know. Why don't I
get you a job at
the Sitting Around All Day
Wearing Yoga Pants Factory?
They're comfortable.
Ma, I hope you're decent.
Raj is here!
You just started seeing
naked women again,
and I don't want you to be confused
about where the boobs should be.
Oh, hey, guys. What
are you doing here?
Uh... w-what are you doing here?
I thought you moved out.
Oh, yeah, I was going to,
and then Debbie and I got to talking
over dinner the other night.
I didn't have anyplace to go,
she likes having me around,
so we both said, “Why
leave?” at the same time.
It was precious.
It's not that precious.
I'd like to back you up, but it
sounds like it was pretty precious.
Stewie, I can't
find my glasses!
Be right there, Deb Deb!
They're probably
on her head.
Or in her neck. Listen.
You staying here seems like something
she would've talked to me about.
Well, maybe if you called your
mother more often, you'd know.
It wouldn't kill you
to pick up the phone.
Any word on my
stolen items?
We're doing
everything we can.
You know, Sherlock Holmes liked to
use cocaine to sharpen his focus.
But I'm sure those Cool Ranch
Doritos are doing the trick.
- Sheldon.
- Leonard!
Oh, I'm so happy
to see you.
- Are you okay?
- Oh, I'm fine.
Why did you come?
What do you mean,
why did I come?
You're my boyfriend. I haven't
seen you in over a month.
I just drove six hours
to help you out.
Don't you have anything to say
besides, “Why did you come?”
I do, but...
I feel uncomfortable saying it out loud
in front of these police officers.
Fine. Whisper it.
Shotgun.
So, Sheldon, tell us about your trip.
Where'd you go?
Where didn't I go?
I went to New York, Chicago,
Atlanta, Denver, Seattle.
How were they?
Oh, I have no idea.
I never left the
train station.
Hang on. You traveled across the entire
country and never left a train station?
Why would I?
That's where all the
cool trains are.
I'm sorry, so you
never went outside?
Or had a single
piece of fruit.
So...
why do you think you'd make a
good pharmaceutical sales rep?
- Well, I'm a people person.
- Mm-hmm.
People like me. Some of my
favorite people are people.
I feel like I'm saying
“people” a lot.
People, people, people, PE...
Okay, I'm done.
You sure?
People. Yes.
Good!
So, how do you feel your previous
job experience has prepared you
for a career like this?
Uh, well, as a waitress, sales
was a big part of my job.
I mean, believe me, I convinced
a lot of very large customers,
who should not be eating cheesecake,
to have more cheesecake.
I mean, one of those chubsters
even had an insulin pump!
Uh-huh!
I have an insulin pump.
People.
It's weird, right?
A grown man in his 30s
living with my mother.
That is weird. I thought
he was, like, 45.
Come on, you don't think
it's a little odd?
I don't know! I mean, she's lonely.
He needs a place to stay.
I doubt there's any funny
business going on.
And even if there was, who cares?
They're both adults.
“Who cares”?! You wouldn't
care if I slept with your mom?
You know what? You're my best friend,
and she's in a bad marriage.
I give you my blessing.
This is stupid. I'm just gonna call
my mother and be honest with her.
'Cause that's what
little matzo balls do.
This is Debbie!
And this is Stuart!
Just kidding!
Leave a message!
This is the part
where you talk.
All right, let's say a physician was
prescribing one of our competitor's drugs.
How would you convince
them to switch to ours?
Um...
any chance his car needs to be
washed by a girl in a bikini?
No...
Okay, I'm really sorry
for wasting your time.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks for stopping by.
Okay, thanks.
Um, I'm sor... Listen,
could you do me a favor
and not tell Bernadette how
badly I blew this interview?
She'll get upset. And
honestly I'm a...
a little terrified of her.
Wait, wait. You're
scared of Bernadette?
Yeah, kind of.
I thought it was just me!
E-Everyone thinks she's so nice
with that squeaky little voice.
I know, but she's
kind of a bully!
She is! I-I didn't
even want to meet you,
but, uh, I was too
scared to say no to her.
Me, too!
Yeah, yeah! One-one
time, I had...
Oh!
I had to tell her we were cutting
the-the research funding
for one of the drugs
she was developing.
What happened?
I couldn't do it! She's
still working on it!
Oh! We're not gonna tell
her about this, right?
Oh, my God, no! No, no...
At the hot dog stand in the
Denver train station...
Heinz ketchup.
At the hot dog stand in the
Salt Lake City train station...
Heinz ketchup.
At the hot dog stand in the
Indianapolis train station...
I don't care.
Wrong! Hunt's!
Hey, Amy! What do you say? You ready
to move on to the mustard round?
Have you not noticed that
I've been sitting back here
quietly stewing for
the past two hours?
I just thought you
were bad at the game.
I'm mad at you!
How could you just go away like
that without even saying good-bye,
and then call Leonard
for help instead of me?
Amy?
May I please have a moment of
privacy to speak with my roommate?
We're in a moving car!
What do you expect me to do?
Stick my fingers in my ears?
Well, I was thinking put your head out
the window like a dog, but that'll work.
Please? This'll be quick.
Leonard?
As soon as we get home, I
want to have coitus with Amy.
Okay, she can't hear.
The reason I called
you is because
I didn't want Amy to know I
couldn't make it on my own.
What's the big deal?
Oh, of course it's
no big deal to you.
You idolize me, and nothing could ever
knock me off that pedestal you put me on.
Well, yeah, it's true.
You-you are a god to me.
Can I stop now?
Just tell her.
I called Leonard
because...
I failed. And I didn't want
you to think less of me.
You were worried
about that?
Yes.
Sheldon...
it's okay with me that
you're not perfect.
Can I have one more
moment with Leonard?
Sure.
Amy just hurt my feelings. I
want to break up with her.
Now, I never thought I'd say this, but
I'm kind of excited to see Sheldon.
I never thought I'd say this,
but Penny got a job today.
She did?
Well, the only reason she got it is 'cause
the guy who interviewed her loves me.
What do you want?
I, uh, kind of got the feeling you might
not be okay with me staying at your mom's.
You're right, I'm not.
I think it's weird.
- Howie?
- It is. He's a grown man.
He's just gonna live
there rent-free?
How is that gonna motivate him to
get off his butt and get a job?
I mean, do you
even have a plan?
Hey, you're not
my father, okay?
And besides, your mother
and I were talking...
“Your mother and I”?
You're not my father!
- I didn't say I was your father!
- Well, I didn't say I was your father!
Okay, calm down. You're not his
father, he's not your father!
Nobody's anybody's father.
I-I'm sorry you don't like my
life choices, but it's my life!
Well, it's my house,
it's my rules!
Oh-oh! Okay, Dad!
If I mow the lawn, can
I have my allowance?
Hey, don't you take that
sarcastic tone with him!
- I don't have to listen to you!
- Don't talk to her like that!
That is my mother... Wife!
My wife! I said my wife!
You know what? This isn't
getting us anywhere.
When you're ready to apologize,
you know where to find me.
Well, yeah, in my house!
That's right, sucka!
I wish I'd never
gone on that trip.
I feel no better now
than when I left.
But you still
accomplished something.
Yeah. If you had told anyone that you
were going away on a train by yourself
across the country, do you know
what they would have said?
- That I couldn't do it?
- Exactly.
Right after they
said, “Yay!”
But you did do it.
So what if it didn't all go your way?
That's what makes it an adventure.
That's a good point.
Yeah, I'm a lot like
Gandalf the Grey.
He fought the Balrog and emerged
stronger than ever as Gandalf the White.
I was robbed of my phone and pants,
and I, too, came back stronger.
And whiter, too, 'cause I wasn't
in direct sunlight for six weeks.
See? This trip was
good for you.
Indeed.
I was the world's
smartest caterpillar.
And then after pupating in
our nation's railway system,
I've burst forth as the
world's smartest butterfly.
Butterfly could've gotten
himself home from Arizona.
Yeah, I feel renewed.
I'm ready to deal with any
changes that come my way.
- Hey!
Look who's back!
Your hair is different.
You changed your hair.
I can't take this.
I'm out.
Would you like to see
pictures from my trip?
I thought your
phone got stolen.
Yeah, it did, but luckily all my
photos got backed up to the Cloud.
And you thought they all
had a silver lining.
Here... day one.
Uh, this was the seat
I was going to sit in
but didn't because there
were cracker crumbs on it.
As it was first class,
I suspect Ritz.
This is the
train bathroom.
This is the Imodium I took so I would
never have to use the train bathroom.
I cannot believe you traveled the entire
country and never left the train station.
I know. You know, I almost died in a
fire in Des Moines, but I stayed put.
FYI... that's when the
Imodium gave out.
Sync, corrected by Elder_Man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net