English Subtitles
[MP4] The Big Bang Theory S08E02 (720p) Junior Professor Solution WEB-DL-Rip [KoTuWa]
I recently read that
during World War Two,
Joseph Stalin had a research
program to create supersoldiers
by having women
impregnated by gorillas.
What a sick use
of science.
Hey, as long as the
baby's healthy.
I wonder if Stalin considered
any other animals.
Hippos are the
deadliest creature.
A half-human, half-hippo soldier
would be pretty badass.
Yes, but when they're hungry-hungry,
you can stop them with marbles.
Yeah, the correct animal for
interspecies supersolider is koala.
You would wind up with an army
so cute it couldn't be attacked.
But half-man,
half-owl could fly...
The answer is cuddly soldiers
with big flat noses. Moving on.
So, Penny, when's
the new job start?
Next Monday.
Did you get a chance to look
over the materials I gave you?
- Uh, not yet, but I will.
- Great. When?
I said I'll get to it.
I'm sensing awkwardness,
am I right?
Yes.
Swish.
I don't want to be pushy, but you've
never done pharmaceutical sales before.
It seems like you could use
this time to get a head start.
Well, the first few weeks
will be all training.
They'll tell me everything
I need to know.
But imagine how impressed
they'd be if you showed up
already familiar
with the material.
Okay, so what, you want me
to be like a teacher's pet?
Couldn't hurt.
Mm, I don't know.
Who here has ever been hurt because
they were the teacher's pet?
It was like the rest of the class
wanted Ms. McDonald to forget the quiz.
♪ Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth
began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪
We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x02 ♪
The Junior Professor Solution
Original Air Date on Septem
Sync, corrected by Elder_Man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Mrs. Davis.
- Guess who?
- Dr. Cooper.
That's right, good job.
Hello.
Uh, you wanted to see me?
Yes. Uh, welcome back.
Thank you.
I assume you'd like to
reopen our dialogue
about the university forcing me
to continue with string theory?
You mean the
dialogue that went,
"Please?" "No." "Please?"
"No." "Please?" "No."
That's the one.
I believe you went
last, so, uh, please?
Dr. Cooper, while you were away,
we came up with a solution
that would allow you to
change your field of study.
Wow.
Pouting and running
away actually worked.
Yeah, I must say, that may not be a
lesson you want to reinforce with me.
So, um, what is
the solution?
Currently, you're being paid under a grant
to specifically research string theory.
If we promote you to
junior professor,
you'll be able to choose whatever
field of research you'd like.
But if I'm a professor, then
I'll have to teach a class.
That is correct.
So your solution is to promote
me and pay me more money
so that I can impart my knowledge to
the next generation of scientists?
Yes.
You people are sick.
Hey. Ready to go to lunch?
Just give me a minute. I'm stimulating
the pleasure cells of this starfish.
- I just need to turn it off.
- What happens if you don't?
Then I have to sit
through lunch
knowing this starfish is
having a better day than I am.
Is Bernadette meeting
us at the restaurant?
Uh, no. Actually, I
didn't invite her.
How come?
Well, ever since she helped me get
this job, she won't stop bugging me.
Well, I think she just
wants you to do well,
and she's worried that you won't 'cause
you were just a stunningly poor waitress.
That is not true.
I'm still waiting on my mini
corndogs from two years ago.
I told you, they'll
be right out.
Okay, so no Bernadette.
Well, you saw her the other night.
Am I wrong?
No, I just...
I feel kind of uncomfortable
talking about her like this.
Usually when someone's being
talked about behind their back,
it's me and it's right
in front of my face.
I-I'm sorry. I just need
a little break from her.
I understand.
You know,
there is some research
that indicates that
sharing negative attitudes
about a third party
can be a powerful bonding
force between two friends.
So, what are you saying?
I'm saying, in the
spirit of science,
what is that little
skank's problem?
So, I've been trying to come up with a
cute couple's nickname for me and Emily.
What do you like better...
Emippali...
or Koothrapemily?
Why is it your last name
and her first name?
Oh, well, her last
name is Sweeney,
and something just didn't seem
right about Koothrapeeney.
Hey, how'd it go with
human resources?
Awful.
Yeah, they're allowing me to
move on from string theory,
but they made me a junior professor and
are requiring me to teach a class.
I don't understand. Why is it
bad that you have to teach?
What a stupid question.
The kids are
gonna love him.
I can't believe I have to waste my time
babysitting a bunch of grad students
who probably think dark matter
is what's in their diapers.
This might not
be that bad.
Uh, you like telling
people they're wrong.
Wrong!
Just because I enjoyed that
one doesn't mean I always do.
You enjoy giving
people grades.
A valid point, but
unoriginal... B-minus.
And you love the sound
of your own voice.
Yeah, well, of course I do.
Listen to it.
It's like an earful
of melted caramel.
Look, most importantly, this will let
you move on and study dark matter.
It is true that many of my heroes have
taken students under their wings:
Feynman, Einstein,
Professor X.
Humorously, in the
case of Professor X,
some of his students
actually had wings.
That's rich.
I'll use that one to lighten the mood
after my entire class fails the midterm.
Measuring starfish serotonin
levels in response
to one point two molar
stimulation of pleasure cells.
You like that, don't you?
That's right, say my name.
Hey.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Not much.
You want to get a drink later?
Just the two of us?
- No Penny?
- Not tonight.
I'm a little
frustrated with her.
Because you got her
the job and you think
she should be working
harder to prepare for it?
So it's not just me.
You see it, too!
I do, I see it.
It's driving me crazy.
Just this afternoon,
I saw on Instagram
that instead of studying, she went
out to lunch and got a manicure.
That's outrageous!
I know!
If she doesn't do well, Th-this
could reflect poorly on you.
Exactly. Does she not realize
it or does she not care?
I don't know.
The important thing
is I am here for you
so we can mutually disparage
this unpleasing third party.
Hey. We just wanted to see how your
class was going. Where is everybody?
There is no class.
Did you send everyone to the
principal's office already?
No one signed up.
Well, that's not
your fault.
I called the department
secretary to see what happened.
Apparently, I have a reputation
for being obnoxious.
What?
Hey, Sheldon, I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
Now I can devote all my
time to dark matter.
Aw, you brought
cookies for everyone?
Oh, yes. Fig Newtons.
I was going to ask them:
Which scientist both helped
to develop calculus and had a
famous cookie named after him?
And then after someone said "Newton," I
was going to tell them they're wrong.
The cookies are named after
a town in Massachusetts.
And then I'd throw
the cookies away.
Hey, what if I
took your class?
Why would you do that?
- Yeah, why would you do that?
- What's wrong with you?
I'm thinking about getting my doctorate,
and he wants to teach... why not?
Oh, Howard.
I appreciate the gesture, but this
is a graduate-level physics class.
I don't think you'd understand a
single thing I was talking about.
Ask why not again;
I've got an answer.
Sheldon, I'm more than smart
enough to take your class.
No.
Yes.
How would you determine
the ground state
of a quantum system
with no exact solution?
I would guess a wave-function
and then vary its parameters
until I found the
lowest energy solution.
Hmm.
Do you know how to integrate
X squared times E
to the minus X, without
looking it up?
I'd use Feynman's trick... differentiate
under the integral sign.
Okay.
Um...
What is the correct interpretation
of quantum mechanics?
Since every interpretation
gives exactly the same answer
to every measurement, they
are all equally correct.
However, I know you believe in
the Many Worlds Interpretation,
so I'll say that. Now do you
think I'm smart enough?
No.
Oh, come on. You
might've gone to school
for a couple more years
than me, but guess what...
engineers are just as
smart as physicists.
You take that back!
No.
So, after drinks
with Bernadette,
I get home, and Penny calls
to complain about her.
And then while I'm talking to Penny,
I get a text from Bernadette.
Wh... I'm trying to prepare
my lesson plan for Howard.
Why are you
telling me this?
Because it's taken 15 years, but
high school is finally awesome!
I love them both, but I'm in the
center now, and I love that even more.
Amy, please. I am trying
to figure out a way
to intellectually emasculate
a dear friend of mine.
- But I'm just...
- Not now.
You better watch that attitude, buddy.
You're dating the popular girl now.
Hmm. You're up late.
Oh, I'm working on my
lesson plan for Wolowitz.
He is going to be so lost.
Look at this
section over here.
Even I don't really
understand it.
Sheldon, why are
you doing this?
I'm a teacher, Leonard.
It's my job.
No, I-I mean, why are you
going to so much trouble
to prove that you're
smarter than Wolowitz?
Oh, it's no trouble; It's
actually a pleasure.
You want to know
what I think?
I think the idea that someone
could be as smart as you,
or even smarter, scares the pants off
you, and you can't deal with it.
Interesting point.
Wh... You're suggesting that I have
emotional issues below my consciousness
which drive my behavior,
thus causing me to lash
out at anything or anyone
that threatens my
intellectual superiority.
Might be something
to think about.
- Leonard?
- Yeah.
Howard's allergic to peanuts.
How can I use that against him?
Hey.
Okay, now that everyone's
here, we can begin.
Before we do, I just
talked to Leonard.
And if you're gonna spend all
your time trying to belittle me
by making this class unnecessarily
hard, then I'm out.
But if you're interested in making a
sincere effort to be a good teacher,
then I'm willing to
give this a shot.
I suppose that's
a fair request.
There's no reason we both can't
benefit from this experience.
- Okay.
Well, then, uh,
first things first.
Um, are you familiar with the
Brachistochrone problem?
- I am.
- Good.
And how it relates to the
calculus of variations?
- It's an inverted cycloid.
- Wonderful.
Now, what about
Euler-Lagrange theorems?
- That's where I'm a little fuzzy.
- Ha! I knew it! All right.
We have a lot of information to
cover before your first test.
Which, by the way,
is in eight minutes.
The good news is I'm
grading on a curve,
so you're pretty
much guaranteed a C.
♪ All I do is
win, win, win ♪
- ♪ No matter what ♪
- What are you doing?
♪ Everybody hands go up, up... ♪
♪ And they stay there! ♪
What are you doing?
If you're gonna be a crappy teacher,
then I'm gonna be a crappy student.
♪ Ludacris going
in on the verse ♪
- ♪ 'Cause I never been defeated and I
won't stop now... ♪ - Will you stop it!
This is a classroom. This
is not  American Bandstand.
Okay. Now, where was I?
Let's see. Oh, yes.
Over here. You...
- What are you doing now?
- Making a straw.
Why?
So I can shoot you
with a spitball.
You're not going to do that,
and I'll tell you why.
This is an institution
of higher learning,
I am your professor, and you're
going to treat me with the prop...
You shot your
spit in my mouth!
Is that gonna be on the test? Because
I don't think I can do that again.
Hey, girlfriend.
Can I get a what what?
What?
Close enough.
Um, I was just calling to see
what you were up tonight.
Thought maybe we could
hit up Color Me Mine,
maybe sneak in some Pinot Greej.
Whatevs.
Uh, thanks, but I think
I'm gonna stay in
and go over the stuff
Bernadette gave me.
Oh. Oh, I hear you. Try and get
that nag off your back, right?
I mean, you're not a bicycle;
Why's she riding you like that?
No, I think she was
just trying to help.
Plus, I really want to do
well at this job. So...
Okay, good luck.
And call me later,
you know, if you decide
she's a bitch or something.
- Hey, girlfriend.
- Hey, Amy.
Tonight. You, me,
Color Me Mine.
Maybe we sneak in some Pinot...
make it Color Me Wine.
That sounds fun, but I promised Penny
I'd come by and help her study.
Oh. Well, good luck
getting her to do that.
She's probably off getting
another manicure.
You remember when she did that?
You remember?
I was probably being too hard on her.
We talked, we're good.
Oh. Great. I'm happy
for you guys.
You know, when the two of
you aren't getting along,
it puts me in a really
weird position.
Well, don't worry...
everything's back to normal.
You mean, like, where she's nice
to your face? Okay got it. Bye.
Hey, boyfriend.
Can't talk. Spitball.
Probably gonna die.
Well?
Sheldon, I-I promise. Your
uvula does not have an STD.
Are you sure?
It just doesn't feel as
innocent as it used to.
You reported me to
human resources?
You violated the
sanctity of my mouth.
Well, I dropped your class,
so I hope you're happy.
I told you you weren't
smart enough to take it.
I'm smart enough, Sheldon.
Asking me a bunch of questions about
a topic I'm not familiar with
doesn't prove anything. I
could do the same to you.
Yeah... Try me.
Okay.
You enjoy making fun of
engineering so much;
How do you quantify the
strength of materials?
Young's modulus.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Okay, how do you prevent eddy
currents in a transformer?
- Laminate the core material.
- Come on, give him a hard one.
That was a hard one.
All right.
How does the flow rate in a
pipe depend on its diameter?
You don't know, do you?
What's the matter,
smart guy?
Don't know
Poiseuille's law?
Thank goodness I got it!
Now I can quit
checking my stool.
Okay, what are the potential side effects
for our erectile dysfunction drug?
Headaches, dizziness
and nausea.
Yes.
Those are also the side effects of having
a 75-year-old man with an erection
climb on top of you.
- Want to stop here?
- Uh, no. I can keep going.
Nah, you got this.
Let's go for a drink.
I'll call Amy.
Okay, good. She seemed like she
really wanted to go out tonight.
Hey, girl.
Okay, next question,
for the Butterfinger:
- How long is a galactic year?
- 250 million years!
Yes!
Okay, this one is for
a Cadbury Creme Egg.
It's not even Easter time.
This is crazy!
Which Archimedean solid has
20 regular triangular faces,
30 square faces, 12 pentagonal
faces, 60 vertices and 120 edges?
The
Rhombicosidodecahedron!
Yes!
We are so smart!
Why didn't girls like
us in high school?
Because we were awkward and
weird and couldn't play sports!
Right again!
Sync, corrected by Elder_Man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net