I've invented a science joke,
would you like to hear it?
Sure.
How many Edisons does it take
to screw in a light bulb?
How many?
Who cares?
He stole the idea
and doesn't deserve
his own joke.
Is that really true?
Of course, that's how you know
it's a good joke.
It not only entertains,
it informs.
Hey, sorry
to interrupt.
Uh, Barry,
uh, how many Edisons does it
take to screw in a light bulb?
Did you know Edison didn't
actually invent the light bulb?
What do you want,
Barry?
Just wanted to drop this off
as a little thank you for Amy.
What's this for?
Your idea really
helped me out.
My light-cone quantization
paper's online already.
The response
has been amazing.
Well, that's
fascinating.
I can't wait to read it.
Oh, no, me as well.
Uh, please e-mail it
to Sheldon@Bazinga.biz.
Why "dot-biz"?
Because I just gave
you the business.
And also Bazinga.com
was taken.
Anyway, thanks again.
Cooper, suck eggs.
Since when do you help out
Barry Kripke?
Well, I'd been thinking about
a cellular automata approach
to neuronal connectivity,
and I thought it might have
some interesting applications
to string theory--
it's not a big deal.
Oh, really?
When I was doing string theory
and hit a dead end,
why didn't you try to help me?
I did-- you said the only
math biologists know is
if you have three frogs
and one hops away,
that leaves two frogs.
That's pretty funny,
that does sound like me.
But that doesn't mean
that you should be
standing on street corners
handing out your math
to whatever guy comes along.
Sheldon, we're all scientists.
I helped out
a fellow colleague.
You're being petty.
I'm being petty?
You know Barry and I
have a professional rivalry.
You heard him--
he told me to suck eggs.
If we were friends,
he would have suggested
I suck something
more pleasant.
Why are you laughing?
Did you learn
something?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x15 ♪
The Comic Book Store Regeneration
Original Air Date on Fe
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Okay, Ma.
Say hi to Aunt Gladys.
Yeah, I love you,
too.
Bye.
Your mom having fun in Florida?
Mmm, she loves it.
She finally found a place
where everyone talks about
how sweaty they are.
Anyway, she wants us
to go to the house
and check in on Stuart
because he might be "lonely."
She's just being nice.
Well, I'm her son, how come
she doesn't send someone
to check on me if I'm lonely?
Because you have a wife.
Yeah, well, sometimes
you work late.
I know you don't like
Stuart being in the house,
but the store's
about to reopen,
I'm sure he'll get
back on his feet.
That would be great.
I'd love for things between me
and Mom to get back to normal.
Well, normal's a
strong word, but sure.
Hey.
Hello.
You okay?
If I was okay,
I would've said "hello"
and not the much more
ominous "hello."
What's going on?
I'm mad at Amy.
Did she leave pit stains
in your favorite crop top, too?
No.
She helped Barry Kripke make
an advancement in string theory.
Oh, that sounds
like a good thing.
Well, it would be,
except that I left string theory
because I decided
it was a dead end.
Yeah, and then she went
behind my back
to help someone else
prove me wrong.
My rival, no less.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
I'm sorry I didn't have
a camera.
Why would she
do this to me?
Well, I'm sure she didn't
upset you on purpose.
Besides, aren't you
the one who says
there's nothing more important
than the advancement of science?
No, I said there's
nothing more important
than me advancing science.
All right, well, if I'm
understanding this right,
and all she did was help
out another scientist,
I'm thinking you might
have to let this one go.
Ugh, "let it go."
I have heard that
my whole life.
Every time something upsets me
somebody says, "let it go,"
you know,
like it's my fault,
and it's not okay
to feel the way I feel.
I don't know
what to tell you.
I mean, why don't
you talk to her?
Is that all you have?
Shopworn tidbits like
"talk to her" and "let it go"?
Gee, Penny,
life's giving me lemons.
What should I do?
Well, you could shove
them somewhere.
Okay, now you're
getting creative.
Thanks again
for your help.
No problem.
Our pleasure.
The place really
looks great.
Yeah, you should have
burned it down years ago.
I keep telling you
I didn't burn it down.
We know, we know--
because burning something down
for the insurance money
is a "crime."
Stuart, this place
looks amazing.
Thanks.
You really did
a nice job.
And thank you
for putting up with me
staying at your mom's
through all this.
I-I couldn't have done it
otherwise.
I appreciate that,
and I'm glad you were able to...
Is that my mother's furniture?
Yeah, she said
I could use it.
Doesn't it look
great?
Not as great as it looks in
the den where it belongs.
Howie.
Why don't you just clean out
the whole room?
Take the string art clown
I made her in third grade
and the ribbon I got
in swim class
for putting my face
in the water.
What is your problem?
She said it was okay.
Well, I'm her son,
and I say it's not okay.
Some son-- looks like you spent
ten minutes on that clown art.
Well, maybe I should've gone
to a fancy art school like you.
Then I could run
a failed comic shop
and mooch off
some guy's mother.
Why don't we leave
so you can cool off?
I think that's
a good idea.
Take him out
of my store.
Your store?!
My mother gave you
the money to reopen.
I'm not going anywhere.
Why don't we go get
the food for the party.
Thank you.
Smart-- looks like
we're being helpful.
Mmm, when really
we're just exiting
an uncomfortable
situation.
Kripke, you know, of all
the people-- Barry Kripke.
I'm so... Are you folding
it like a crazy person
to get me to
do it for you?!
No.
Oh, give me that.
Just out of curiosity,
if I were to let something go,
how would I do that?
I don't know-- just think
about something else.
Can I think
about the spiny anteater?
Sure.
The spiny anteater...
never went behind my back
and worked with Barry Kripke.
That didn't help at all.
You know, some people
try visualization.
How does that work?
Okay,
imagine your problems
are a pen.
Okay.
Now imagine
you're holding that pen.
Okay.
Now open your hand
and let it go.
But I just got this pen.
It's got my initials on it
and everything.
Look.
Sheldon, this isn't
that hard.
I may have a better way
that you can teach me.
How?
What if I told you
that over the past few months
Amy has secretly been giving you
little puzzles
to test your intelligence
against chimpanzees in her lab?
What? She didn't
give me any puzzles.
Are you sure?
Boy, I just can't seem to get
these scissors back together.
Can you do it?
Darn it.
There's something
in my eye,
and I need to sort
these coins by size.
Can you help?
Penny?
I really want to
eat this banana,
but it's stuck inside
this bamboo puzzle box.
Son of a bitch!
Okay, that's great.
Now, let it go.
I can't believe you were
testing me against a chimp!
Well, excuse me,
Amy was testing you.
I was rooting for you.
Good job on that banana box,
by the way.
Why would she
even do this?
She's been conducting
an experiment on apes
where they're given
various puzzles to solve.
I was surprised
at the complexity of the puzzles
and thought some humans wouldn't
be able to solve them.
That's when Amy said,
"Want to make this interesting?"
"Make this interesting"?
You bet money on me?
No, no.
We designed an experiment
involving you.
See? Now, isn't that
interesting?
It's not interesting.
It's incredibly insulting.
Okay,
maybe this will help--
imagine you're holding a pen.
Before you go too far,
not a special pen
with your initials
engraved on it--
that'll make the next part
really hard.
Oh...
That's it.
Get out!
I don't understand
why you're mad at me.
You should be mad
at Amy.
Like I was
this afternoon.
Hey, look at that--
I let it go.
Get out!
Penny?
What?
I think I left
my pen in there.
I understand
why you're upset,
but he worked really hard
to get the store ready.
And it's just furniture.
It's my mom's furniture.
It belongs in the house
I grew up in--
next to that pile of TV Guides
and in plain view of what,
for a ten-year-old, was
a quality piece
of string art!
Howie, if the store succeeds,
Stuart has a source of income,
and he can move out
of your mother's house.
Seems like some old furniture
is a reasonable price
to pay for that.
That is a good point.
But I didn't marry you
for good points.
I married you
to blindly support me
no matter how ridiculous
I'm being!
This is why I had
to rewrite our wedding vows.
Hi, we're here to pick up
an order for Comic Center.
Sure, let me go check on that.
Dude, I-I think
that's Nathan Fillion.
Oh yeah,
look at that.
And he's picking
the tomatoes out of his salad
just like I do.
I always did feel
a connection with him.
Oh, I have got
an idea.
We're not selling
his tomatoes on eBay.
No, if we got Captain Reynolds
from Firefly
to do a signing
at Stuart's store,
that would be
amazing.
That would be great.
So should we go
talk to him?
I don't know.
I mean, if he's not nice,
it's gonna make it hard for me
to watch him in anything again.
What?!
The-the guy who plays
Jon Snow was a jerk.
We still watch
Game of Thrones.
He was a jerk because
you rear-ended him.
I was distracted.
It's weird seeing a member
of the Night's Watch
with a kayak strapped
to his car.
Come on.
Hi,
excuse me, s-s...
I-I don't mean
to bother you,
but we're just really
big fans of Firefly.
A-And Dr. Horrible.
Oh, uh, I think
you made a mistake.
I'm not an actor.
Don't say that.
I mean, you're not
Dame Judi Dench,
but you're
pretty great.
Oh, yeah, I get it--
you think I'm Nathan Fillion,
but I'm not.
So if you don't mind, I would
just love to eat my lunch.
Come on.
Sorry to bother you.
Don't know why
he's so grumpy.
I got mistaken for that guy
in Life of Pi once,
and I'm still
floating.
Sheldon, it's me.
Oh, hey.
D-Did you see that?
I-I figured out how to open
the door all by myself.
Maybe I'll fling some feces
around my cage to celebrate.
What are you talking about?
I know you've been giving me
secret puzzle tests.
Sheldon, open
the door.
I can't.
I'm naked.
I just saw you.
Hang on.
Open the door now.
- Oh, hey.
- Pull up your pants!
It's not a big deal.
I run tests like this on
undergrads all the time.
If you fill out some
paperwork at the university,
I can get you $5.
I don't want $5.
I want my dignity.
So what are we talking,
like, ten bucks?
Thank you.
Thanks.
Sorry again.
No problem.
A-Are you sure
you're not him?
Uh, you can tell us.
We're scientists,
not crazy fanboys.
All right, fine.
I'm him.
And you're eating
alone at a deli.
I don't buy it--
you're not him.
I just wanted
to eat my lunch in peace.
But I really am him.
And thank you very much
for being a fan.
If you want, uh,
let's take a picture.
That would be great.
Great.
Yeah, thank you.
You bet.
Wait, hang on.
If you're really
Nathan Fillion,
what's the line from Firefly
about your bonnet?
"I swear by my pretty floral
bonnet, I will end you."
That's it,
that's the line.
Although...
I knew the line--
doesn't make me Nathan Fillion.
Do you want the picture or not?
I want a picture
with Nathan Fillion.
How about a picture with a guy
who looks like Nathan Fillion
but a little more annoyed
than Nathan Fillion usually is?
What do you think?
Eh, it's good enough
for Facebook.
I can't believe
they did that.
I know-- it's so insulting.
At one point,
they had me figure out
how to get a banana
out of a puzzle box.
Wait, Sheldon gave me
a banana in a box.
He was testing me, too.
Unbelievable.
And how could a chimp
even solve that?
That was impossible.
Really? You couldn't get it out?
Thank you.
Wow, the
store looks great.
So you guys were
testing us both?
What is the
matter with you?
Eh, what's
the matter with them is
they think they're so smart
they don't care
if they hurt
other people's feelings.
Sounds like us.
That's not true.
I still don't understand
why you're upset.
You solved every puzzle faster
than all of the chimps.
Well, except Barnabas,
but he was on Adderall.
I'm sorry, but it's
making me crazy.
Can you please
just let it go?
Oh, I can help
you with that.
Imagine you're holding
an ordinary pen.
While your favorite pen is
safe and secure in your pocket.
Hold that thought.
Hello?
How can I make this up
to you?
The answer's
in this puzzle box.
Let's see
if you can open it.
You could have at least warned
him about the furniture.
That's what I said
when we moved it.
You helped him?!
No, Stuart picked out those
throw pillows all on his own.
Hey, you okay?
Uh, no.
What's wrong?
Um...
my mom died.
What?
Uh...
that was my aunt.
Ma took a nap.
She never woke up.
Oh, my God, Howie.
I'm so sorry.
What can we do?
I don't know.
May I say something?
Not right
now, Sheldon.
But I think it would
be comforting.
Buddy...
No, it's okay.
What?
When I lost my own father,
I didn't have any friends
to help me through it.
You do.
I really thought
he was gonna say, "Let it go."
Okay, thanks, Bernadette.
Travel safe.
Okay, bye.
They booked a flight.
They're heading
to the airport now.
How's Howard holding up?
He's hanging in there.
How are you doing, Stuart?
Still can't believe she's gone.
I mean, that woman took me in.
If it wasn't for her,
I-I would have been homeless.
One of us would
have taken you in.
Yeah, I don't recall any offers.
But, you know, uh, I-I'm glad
it worked out the way it did
because I got to know
this wonderful person.
Yeah.
Mrs. Wolowitz was
pretty special.
When I first moved to America,
Howard was my only friend.
She made me feel
so welcome in her home.
Which says a lot,
because, those first few years,
she thought I was the gardener.
Whenever I saw her,
she'd say I was too skinny
and try and feed me.
She did that to me, too.
Don't take this away from me.
I didn't care
for her yelling.
But now that I'm not going
to hear it again,
I'm sad.
If you want,
I can yell at you later.
It won't be as good.
Let's have a toast.
To Mrs. Wolowitz.
A loving mother...
...to all of us.
We'll miss you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net