Leonard, I've been working
on an opening joke
for our lecture at Berkeley.
Oh, I like to laugh.
But say it anyway.
Okay, um...
What do you say
to a graduate
of the UC Berkeley
physics department?
I'll have fries with that.
Because his education
hasn't prepared him
for a career in the sciences.
You know, when they chase
you out of there,
you only have to run
faster than Sheldon.
Are you all set
for your trip?
Yeah, I think so.
I just restocked the old PRK.
"PRK"?
Public restroom kit.
Everything a boy needs
for making pee pee
in new and strange places.
I don't see what's crazy
about bringing a backpack
with your own toilet paper
and Purell.
Keep going.
And rubber gloves,
uh, air freshener.
Um, noise-cancelling
headphones.
Oh, danger whistle.
Um...
pepper spray.
Ooh, a multi-language
"occupied" sign.
Uh, let's see.
We have seat protectors,
uh, booties for my shoes,
a clothespin for my nose.
Oh, and a mirror on a stick,
so I can make sure the person
in the stall next to me
isn't some kind of weirdo.
You still worried some Berkeley
girl is gonna steal him away?
Yes, who do you think gave him
the danger whistle?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x19 ♪
The Skywalker Incursion
Original Air Date on April 2, 201
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Would you like to play
a physics car game I invented
called "I Can't Spy"?
It's all the nail-biting
tension of "I Spy"
but the added fun of subatomic
particles and waves
outside the visible
spectrum.
If it's half as much fun as
"One Times Ten to the Fourth
Bottles of Beer on the Wall,"
I'm in.
I'll begin.
Uh, I can't spy
with my little eye...
...something passing
right through us.
That soy Frappuccino I had.
Will you please
play the game?
I can't spy
with my little eye
something passing
right through us.
I don't know, um...
If 65 billion
solar neutrinos pass
through a square centimeter
every second,
given the surface
area of this car is
about 60,000
square centimeters,
that means 3.9 times ten
to the 15th solar neutrinos?
I don't want
to play anymore.
We haven't been on a road trip
in a while.
This is fun.
We get it-- you won the game.
Stop bragging.
No, listen, we wrote
a paper together.
Now we get to go to a university
and talk about it?
That's pretty cool.
I suppose it is.
In fact, if you'd like to
celebrate with a little music,
I'd be okay with that.
What...?
This road trip just got crazy.
Play that funky music,
white boy.
I'm surprised you know
that reference.
What reference?
So, I put stickers
on everything we're gonna sell.
We just need help taking it
all out to the driveway.
Can I be in charge
of pricing?
I've been going to garage
sales my whole life.
Can you believe I got these
pantyhose for a nickel?
All right, Amy's in charge
of pricing and being 75.
Hey, Penny, can you
give me a hand with this?
Sure.
Aw, we had one of
these growing up.
I used to play
all the time.
Oh, yeah?
I love Ping-Pong.
Oh, I meant beer pong.
I had a table, too,
but I didn't have any friends,
so all I did was serve.
You know, you can leave one
side up and play against it.
And if I had a friend,
they might have told me that.
Excuse me.
Why is there a sticker on this?
It's my TARDIS
from Doctor Who.
I was planning on
moving it in the house.
I think you just answered
your own question.
Come on, one day,
this may double in value
and be worth half
what I paid for it.
Sweetie, we have a lot to do.
We don't need
to decide this right now.
Well, I guess as long as
you're keeping an open mind.
Of course.
♪ ♪
So... they're requesting
that the white boy play
the funky music, yes?
Yes.
And this music we're listening
to right now is funky as well?
Sure.
Let me ask you this.
Do you think
this song is the music
the white boy ultimately plays?
It could be.
So it's like the musical
equivalent of Russell's Paradox,
the question of whether
the set of all sets
that don't contain themselves
as members contains itself?
Exactly.
Well...
then I hate it.
Music should just be fun.
Making great time.
Gonna be there pretty early.
Will our hotel room
be ready?
I doubt it.
Aren't you worried
that sitting in the lobby
for a long period of time
might attract the attention
of the hotel detective?
If we do,
we'll just tell him
to "hit the bricks, see?"
Seems a little confrontational,
but all right.
You know,
we won't be very far
from Skywalker Ranch.
Oh, that's true.
It's not like
we can get in there.
Why not?
I-I don't think George Lucas
put his headquarters
in the middle of nowhere because
he wanted people dropping in.
Yoda's swamp was
in the middle of nowhere.
Tatooine was in the middle
of nowhere.
Hoth was in the middle
That's code, Leonard.
He wants us
to drop in.
We do have time.
I mean, we could drive by
and just look at it.
Yes! Oh...
I'm so excited.
And I just can't hide it.
"I'm about to lose control,
and I think I like it."
What are you
talking about?
So when do you guys think
you're gonna move in?
We're still figuring how much
remodeling we want to do.
It's tricky finding
the right balance
between "tasteful modern"
and "Jewish mother
tchotchke crapfest."
Have you made a decision
about the TARDIS?
I think I can sell it if we call
it, "Big British Porta-Potty."
We're not selling
it-- it's mine.
You can't just decide.
How about I arm-wrestle you?
That's not fair.
It's like me challenging you
to a sexy pants contest.
You could play
Ping-Pong for it.
I would do that.
How is that fair?
You grew up
with a table.
Yes, but I mostly used it
as a battlefield
in an ongoing war between the
Transformers and the ThunderCats
for control of a bra
I had found in the woods.
Bernadette, for every episode
of Doctor Who
Leonard has made me sit through,
I will play on your behalf
and send that TARDIS
back to Gallifrey,
where I hate
that I know it belongs.
Yes, Penny
plays for me.
That's not fair--
she has upper body muscles.
Dude, three-time
Sanskriti School
for Well-Born Boys
badminton champion.
That's right-- okay,
Raj can play for me.
Ooh, you just chose champions.
It's like we're reenacting
the ancient German practice
- of trial by combat.
- Yeah, it's also like
when the Mountain fought the
Red Viper in Game of Thrones.
Leonard makes you
watch that, too?
No, no, I like that show.
It's got dragons
and people doing it.
So it's settled.
The fate of Doctor Who's TARDIS
will be decided
by a Game of Thrones inspired
death-match on the battlefield
of ThunderCats
versus Transformers.
If you still have that bra,
I'll give you a nickel for it.
There it is.
It's just a gate.
On a road.
Wasn't even that
hard to find.
This is so amazing!
I know!
You want to
get a picture?
I want more than a picture.
I want to go in.
Well, so do I, but
they'll never let us.
Is that the attitude
that helped you get Penny?
No, but I don't have three years
to make that gate
feel sorry for me.
Uh, there's
a speaker box.
Drive up, push the button,
and let's see what happens.
Okay, yeah.
What do we
have to lose?
I'm a little nervous.
Well, get over it.
Confidence is key
in these situations.
Right.
You pushed it--
are you out of your mind?!
May I help you?
Um...
Uh, uh... we don't
have an appointment,
and-and we don't
belong here,
but we-we're, like,
crazy-big fans.
I mean...
"crazy for Star
Wars" crazy,
not crazy like we have a
backpack full of duct tape,
although we do
have a backpack
that you really don't
want to look in.
You're blowing it.
We want to meet
George Lucas
and become his friends
and play with him!
Hello?
This speaker's not working,
just pull up.
And that's how it's done.
All right, we've defeated
the first challenge.
Now we must steel ourselves
to face the monster
who defends the gate.
We're trying to get past
a security guard,
not rescue Zelda.
I think what really needs to be
rescued is your sense of whimsy,
but one quest at a time.
So what's the plan?
Uh, I'm just gonna be honest
with the guy.
Honesty will never
get us in.
Well, what's
your plan?
All right, my plan is
predicated on the assumption
that they have
a nurse's office
and your willingness
to be lightly stabbed.
Who are you here to see?
Uh, I'm just gonna
tell you the truth.
Oh, you are killing me.
We don't have
an appointment.
We-we're just fans
of Mr. Lucas's work,
and we thought
we'd take a shot
and see if we could get in
and look around.
Sorry, guys, we get this a lot.
Can't let you in.
What if I told you
that I was the voice of Yoda?
A recording
session I must attend.
I'm sorry, don't
listen to him.
We're actually
physicists.
We're giving a lecture
at Berkeley later today.
We just... we had
some time to kill.
Hey, listen, you
seem like decent guys.
I can't let you in,
but I got some hats and T-shirts
I can give you.
Thank you so much.
See?
Maybe honesty is the best...
What are you doing?
Shedding the yoke
of my oppressors,
you blind,
sad little man.
Don't move!
Code A-A-23, A-A-23.
Copy.
I can see the ranch, Leonard!
Oh, it's rustic,
it's lovely.
I'd take a picture,
but people are chasing me.
I'm gonna make it...!
I'm gonna make it!
They have Tasers,
but they wouldn't dare use...
Come on, Raj.
You are the King Kong
of Ping-Pong.
You are the menace
of table tennis.
Put her away,
'cause I don't have a third one.
Yes!
Rajesh eight, Penny four.
Sorry,
he's really good.
Hey, Raj.
if Howard can't
keep the TARDIS,
how great would it
look at your place?
What?
Yeah, what?
I don't know much
about Doctor Who,
but if, um, you were to put this
right outside your front door
and open up the back,
it would be like
your entire apartment was
the inside of the TARDIS,
which is pretty cool
'cause on the show,
the inside of the TARDIS
is bigger than the outside.
But then again, I don't know
much about Doctor Who.
Don't listen to her.
You and I go way back--
we're like brothers.
We are. We are.
Oh, no!
What a terrible serve!
Sorry, brother.
Eight-five.
This is ridiculous.
I want a new champion.
Amy, were you serious
about being able to serve?
Uh, it-it's been
a long time.
I don't know.
I'm probably
pretty rusty.
Wow.
She's my champion!
Well, if you can switch
champions, so can I.
I want Raj.
Hey.
Oh, come on, like
you even care.
I care!
Oh, wait, no, I don't.
Good luck, Raj.
You know, I thought our
friendship meant more to you.
So did I.
Do you think
they're gonna call the police?
I don't know.
Maybe they'll call Imperial
Officers to take us
to a holding cell
on the Death Star.
Oh, I think that's below the pay
grade of an Imperial Officer.
Stormtroopers are really
the ones who...
Oh, shut up.
He's right.
Uh, Stormtroopers actually
combine both the function
of infantry and military police.
Uh-huh, I'm normally
very nice,
but you shut up, too.
So...
what are you in for?
Honestly, I just wanted to meet
Mr. Lucas and say thank you.
You know, growing up, the movies
had such an impact on my life.
I never really fit in anywhere.
Till I discovered
the worlds he created
and finally found a place
where I belong.
But why are you here?
Oh, I, uh, I hopped a fence,
and they caught me
in the sculpture gallery
making out
with a Chewbacca statue.
Excuse me.
Leonard,
they have a
sculpture gallery.
All right, I talked
to my supervisor,
and we're gonna let you go
with a warning.
But if you ever
come back,
we will call the police
and press charges.
We understand.
Thank you so much.
Uh, what about me?
No, you're not going
anywhere, kissy face.
Let's go.
I have to take your picture
to post at the guard gate.
Uh, one question
about that picture.
Can it be with
George Lucas?
Ooh, grumpy you are.
Okay, this is the match
that decides it all.
First to 11 wins.
Serve switches
every five points.
And just so you know,
when this started,
I was going to put the TARDIS in
a discreet corner of the house,
but I've since turned
mean, and now it's going
right in the middle
of the living room
on a rotating platform with
a sign that says "suck it."
Game on.
Except...
Raj is gonna win.
Isn't that right, Raj?
Uh, yeah, I mean,
her serve was pretty good.
Come on, get
in her head.
Be intimidating.
Okay, uh...
I'm gonna own you, bitch!
Whoa!
Hey!
That's not nice.
Let's just play.
One-zero.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five-nothing.
Wait,
did you play badminton
or sad-minton?
Don't listen to him--
all she's got is a serve.
Now, grab a fresh tampon
and put her away.
Wha...?
A-And that's not offensive?
Where's the line?
It's in your purse. Play.
One-five.
Two-five.
Three-five.
Four-five.
Five-five!
Six.
Seven.
Eight. Nine.
Ten-five!
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten-ten!
Well, that was
an exciting 40 seconds.
It was, and now
the serve is back to you,
and the game is over.
You know, Amy,
I, uh...
can't help but wonder
how Sheldon would react
if the TARDIS was
at your place.
Don't listen to her,
just hit the ball.
Keep talking.
If this doesn't get him
into your bedroom,
nothing will.
Are you still
mad at me?
Yes, we missed our lecture,
we were almost arrested,
and you got me locked
in a room with a man
who forced his tongue down the
throat of a stuffed Wookiee.
Boy, some people are just
glass-half-empty.
The glass is
empty, Sheldon.
It's completely empty.
If you gave that glass to a
man who was dying of thirst,
he would be dead,
do you know why?
Before I answer,
was he a smoker?
I think you're looking
at this all wrong.
Fine, then tell me
how I should be looking at it.
Well, not only did we go to
Skywalker Ranch, we got in.
No one we know
can say that.
And for all the times
you find me irritating,
today you got to watch
someone shoot me with a Taser.
That part was pretty good.
See?
You did flop around a lot.
I'll take your word for it.
I was too busy
trying not to defecate.
You know, when they were
escorting us
to the detaining room,
I looked through a door,
and I'm pretty sure
I saw a display case
with the Ark
of the Covenant.
That's amazing.
I know.
And I saw Jabba the Hutt
riding by on a motorcycle.
Although that was
right after the Tasing,
so who can
say for sure?
I-I guess this could count
as an adventure.
It was.
And even though we're
not allowed back there,
they can never take
today away from us.
Unlike my sense
of smell,
which hasn't returned
since the Tasing.
No, I got nothing.
Amy, the Daleks
are right on my tail!
Quick, we need to reset
the time circuits.
Oh, no, I left my sonic
screwdriver behind.
Really should have
thought this through.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net