I was unstoppable.
I mean, I was...
I was on fire.
It was like my mind and my body
were totally connected,
like-like athletes must feel
when they're in the zone.
Again, it was
miniature golf.
Admit it, you're a
little turned on.
You can't be this proud.
Why not?
Because I beat you.
Hey.
Hi.
Oh, good. You're back.
We have some
exciting news.
Okay.
As you know, Amy and I have
been together a long time,
and a lot of things
I never thought possible
now seem possible.
Okay...
After a careful evaluation
of our relationship,
we decided that the time was
right to take a step forward.
Okay.
Do you want to say it?
Let's say
it together.
We're getting a turtle!
This is why I've been saying
we should keep champagne on ice.
Sarcasm?
Yes.
Okay.
That was tricky,
'cause when it comes to alcohol,
she generally means business.
Well, we're-we're
very happy for you.
Yes.
Thank you.
Acquiring a joint pet
is a big step for us.
No. It's true.
It means that we care so much
about each other,
there's enough left over
for an eight-ounce reptile.
Why a turtle?
After much deliberation,
we've determined that a turtle
is the ideal pet.
They don't shed fur,
they don't make noise...
For Halloween, we can dress him
as a cobblestone.
Yeah.
And if he ever goes berserk,
I know I can outrun him.
Coincidentally, that's also
why I chose you as a roommate.
Well, congratulations.
Who would've thought
you two would be the first
in our group to start a family?
Mm-hmm.
That's what I said!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x17 ♪
The Colonization Application
Original Air Date on March 5
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
So, where's
your roommate tonight?
Well, I thought it
was a little unfair
that she's always here,
and you never
get a chance to stay over,
so... I killed her.
But remember our agreement?
You can joke
about murdering people,
but you have to say,
“Just kidding.”
And the more important
thing to remember is
that I'd never hurt you.
Oh, crap.
I have to run over to the
hospital and check on a patient.
That's okay. I can come back later.
No.
No, don't be silly.
I won't be gone long.
Just stay here.
Okay, cool.
Oh, and you're sure
your roommate's
not gonna come back
while I'm here alone, right?
'Cause that'll be awkward.
Oh, don't worry.
She's in Palm Springs.
Oh, good.
Well, her torso is.
Just kidding.
I put her in a wood chipper.
Oh, dear Lord.
It's okay.
You made it.
We're fine.
That was a lot of puppies.
Let's forget about them, and...
pick ourselves out
a nice turtle.
Yeah.
Oh, how about this one up on the log?
Oh, I don't know.
He kind of looks
like a jerk.
How about this one?
Well, he's barely moving.
He looks half dead.
I know. I like him, too.
Hi, little guy.
How'd you like
to come home with us?
You'll be living with me because
we don't live in the same house.
But that's not your fault.
Like you, we're taking it
ridiculously slow.
You'll stay with me when he's
at Comic-Con or away for work.
Or if they accept Daddy's
application to live on Mars.
What are you talking about?
Oh, there's this company
that's attempting
to establish a colony on Mars,
and I applied
to be among the first to go.
What should
we name him?
You know, I came in
thinking “Seth,” but...
he kind of looks Italian.
You applied for a mission
to be a colonist
on another planet,
and couldn't be bothered
to tell me?
Would you have approved?
Of course not.
Well, based on
your reaction,
it looks like I made
the right choice.
Isn't that right, Giuseppe?
Hey, hey.
Listen, I-I have a little
confession to make.
Aw, is this your first time?
No, I got you something
for Valentine's Day,
and I was too embarrassed
to give it to you.
Well, why?
Well, 'cause I got it
at the dirty store.
You went to the dirty store
without me?!
In sunglasses and a hat after
I parked two blocks away.
Well, get it! Get it for me!
Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay, uh, well, I hope it's fun.
I mean, it-it comes
with paints, and-and
it's kind of creative
and artistic.
Okay, did you go to
the dirty store or Michaels?
No, no.
We cover ourselves
in body paint,
and then-then we get on this
big canvas and do our thing.
Whoa, that's kind of
a big step for a guy
who only recently agreed
to take his socks off.
You're making fun of me.
Forget it.
No! No, come on, I want to do it.
Really?
Yeah, let's you, me,
and your very, very pale feet
make some art.
Hey, when you got back to this
store, I want to go with you.
Okay, but it's a drive-- the
one I went to is in San Diego.
How are the taxes going?
Okay.
But you got a lot of receipts
for the Lego store in here.
Those are business expenses.
You can write those off.
A $200 R2-D2 is
a business expense?
Oh, Bernie,
you're gonna have to sound
a lot more confident
when we get audited.
Hey, what's up?
Eh, Emily ran back
to the hospital,
so I'm just hanging out
at her place.
What are you, uh,
what are you doing?
Just playing video games
while Bernie does the taxes.
What are you, a little kid?
Is she gonna cut your dinner
into little pieces, too?
She doesn't have to--
I filled up on jelly beans.
So, uh, what game are you...
Oh.
Crap.
What's wrong?
I can't get Emily's
nightstand to close.
So?
She's gonna know
I was looking in it.
Why were you looking in it?
Well, there's a question
I better have a good answer to
before she gets back.
Okay, calm down.
There's probably something
jammed behind it.
Just, uh, pull it out
and see what's there.
Hang on.
Oh... no. Oh, no.
Oh, God, no!
You know what, you sound busy--
I'm gonna let you go.
Dude, the whole front came off.
Now she's gonna know
I was snooping.
What's happening?
Raj was snooping through
Emily's drawers and broke one.
Aw.
I'm gonna miss her.
So what do you think?
I thought it'd be
a little more... just more.
I'm not even sure
why we were out of breath.
Uh, I mean, d-did
we move at all?
Maybe along the z-axis,
but x and y are looking
pretty sad.
Okay, come on.
We are not old
boring people.
We can do better
than this.
Uh, Th-that's true.
How late did we stay up
last night?
Almost 1:00 a.m.
Damn straight, almost 1:00 a.m.
And we weren't even watching TV.
We were watching Netflix,
like the kids do.
Yeah, is it a comedy?
Is it a drama?
Nobody knows.
Now, come on.
We are gonna do this.
Yeah.
You get the paint,
I'll rest for 30-40 minutes,
and then we do this!
I can't believe you
almost had me bring
a wild animal
into my home.
No one told you to poke
the turtle's face.
I was playing
“Got Your Nose”"
That's how you get
children to like you.
I'm surprised you even care
if he likes you,
since you're planning
on leaving the planet
the first chance you get.
Ugh, this again.
Amy, I've already had one new
hole torn in my body today.
I don't need another one.
Sheldon, I know the odds
of you even going to Mars
are incredibly small,
but it still hurts
that you would volunteer
for something that would
take you away from me forever.
So you're saying you
wouldn't leave me
for the chance to be
one of the first humans
to colonize
another planet?
I would at least mention it
before filling out
the application.
Huh, that's exactly what
Leonard, Wolowitz, Koothrappali,
Bernadette and
Penny said.
And who says
you could even survive
an interplanetary
mission, anyway?
You could barely survive
a tiny turtle bite.
First of all, this...
has only made me stronger.
But beyond that, all I did
was fill out an application.
You know what?
Go to Mars, Sheldon.
Is there anything I can
do to cheer you up?
No. Forget it.
What if I play the Star Trek
theme on my nose?
Please don't.
Yep, you're mad.
Okay, let me see the damage.
Hang on.
Well, I think you
broke the dowels.
You're not gonna
have time to glue it
back on--
you'll have to nail it.
With what?
Does she have any
pillows or wine glasses?
She does.
Great.
Neither of those.
Try a hammer!
Did that feel good?
You feel like a big man now?
I was going to make you
red zinger,
but since Mars
is the red planet,
I went with peppermint.
Why do you even want to do this?
Actually...
as part of the application,
I was required
to make a short video
answering that very question.
You want to see it?
Can't you just tell me?
But I made a video.
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
and I'd like to tell you
why I should be chosen to...
go to Mars!
I'm exceedingly smart.
I graduated college at 14.
While my brother
was getting an STD
I was getting a PhD.
Penicillin can't take this away.
Being in close quarters,
cleanliness is important
and... my hygiene is impeccable.
In fact, animals don't trust me
because I smell like nothing.
Yeah...
Literally nothing.
During the seven-month
space flight,
I can keep up morale
with my wacky sense of humor.
Hey, Leonard...
is there any peanut brittle
left in that can?
You mean this weirdly
suspicious one?
Yes. Open it and check.
I don't get it.
There's actually
peanut brittle in...
Please go to Mars.
But on a more serious note:
The most important reason I want
to go to Mars is that
I believe, as a scientist,
it's my duty
to push the boundaries
of human knowledge forward.
Now, I know that life on Mars
will be difficult.
But life here on Earth
is no picnic.
Also, picnics are no picnic.
Where should we go for lunch?
Oh, I know, the ground.
In conclusion,
thank you for considering me
for this journey of a lifetime.
To Mars!
Afterwards,
Leonard blew his nose,
and pie came out.
Right there, right there,
Oh, God, that's it!
How did you get paint
in your eye?
Because you wouldn't let me
wear safety goggles!
This looks terrible.
She-she's gonna know.
It's fine.
You just need two more nails.
Okay, where should I put them?
In Emily's eyes.
You're not helping.
Well, maybe this is
what you get for snooping.
You know, it-it's bad enough
that I have to deal with this...
Raj? I'm back.
Oh, no.
Hey.
Hi.
How was the hospital?
Fine.
What were you doing in there?
Uh... w-well...
Okay, look, I-I don't
want to lie to you.
I-I got curious,
I was looking around...
and I broke the drawer
on your night stand.
You were looking
in my night stand?
Yeah.
So, the first time
I leave you alone,
you snoop on me?
You've never snooped
around my apartment?
No!
Come on, think back.
It would really help if you had!
I can't believe
you don't trust me!
She sounds really mad.
We should hang up.
Yeah, we should.
But we're not
going to, are we?
Not a chance.
What happened to
“snooping is wrong”?
Howard, you're going
to jail for tax fraud.
Who cares?
Well, we did it.
We sure did.
I mean, I was on fire!
I-I was in the zone,
like an athlete.
Sweetie, I beat
you at this, too.
So, where do we
want to hang it?
What? Are you kidding?
We're not hanging it!
But it's an expression
of our love.
And our butts!
Not hanging it!
Seems a shame to throw it away.
Yeah.
We could give it to Sheldon,
and tell him William
Shatner painted it.
God, I love you.
I love you so much.
I think I'm gonna go home.
Why?
I really don't understand
what's happening here.
You know, Sheldon,
at any other time,
learning that you had plans
to go live on Mars
would be a slow news day.
But a couple of hours ago,
we were getting a turtle.
And silly as it sounds,
I thought that meant something.
Amy!
Oh, why didn't I give her
Sleepy Time tea?
Amy, wait!
Getting a turtle meant
a great deal to me, too.
Sure.
Unless something
better comes along.
Do you want me
to withdraw my application?
What I want is for us
to be planning our
future together.
And in that future,
are we on the same planet?
Yeah, because I've seen people
make the long-distance
thing work.
We're on the same planet!
Okay!
Does that planet have
to be Earth?
Are you asking me to go
to Mars with you?
I am.
Yeah, if I'm going
to a barren,
lifeless environment,
where the chances of survival
are slim to none,
I want you there with me.
Why don't we go back
to the apartment,
and fill out your application?
Okay.
I suppose being
the first people
on a new planet would
be incredibly exciting.
Oh, I know.
We could be the first
to plant a flag on Mars.
We could be the first to
watch Mars Attacks! on Mars.
We could be the first
to say “Good Lord,
what on Mars are
you talking about”"
You know,
we could also be
the first people
to procreate on Mars.
You just can't keep it in
your space pants, can you?
Think about it.
If we had a family there,
our kids would be Martians.
They would, wouldn't they?
We could give them
cool Martian names.
And we could teach them
about Martian history.
Like, who planted those flags?
And, uh, where did that copy
of Mars Attacks! come from?
I guess we'll have to make
a new video together,
as a couple.
Good idea.
And since you've had
such a rough day,
I'm gonna let you throw
the pie in Leonard's face.
Thank you for forgiving me.
It's okay.
At some point, we were bound
to have our first fight.
Well, it almost happened
when you called
my apple pie crust “doughy”"
The truth is
you were right.
And I was just
angry at myself.
Can I ask you one thing?
Of course. What?
Did you look in my closet?
No. Just the drawer.
You promise you didn't
look in the closet?
I promise.
Why, what's in there?
Don't worry about it.
Good night.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net