Two one six four two zero
one nine eight nine.
And that, little lady,
is pi to a thousand places.
I'd say I'm sorry I asked,
except I didn't.
Oh, look, it's the
Scientific American
that covered the paper
Leonard and I wrote.
Oh, let me see.
I have mixed feelings
about doing interviews.
I like the part where I talk.
I do not like the part
where the other man talks.
Sheldon, this article doesn't
mention Leonard at all.
Well, that
can't be right.
It only refers to
“Dr. Cooper and his team.”
Did you even talk about him?
All I did was answer a few
questions about the theory.
And then expressed my gratitude
that Scientific American
doesn't include any of those
smelly perfume cards.
Poor Leonard.
Why? The theory
he came up with
just got mentioned in
Scientific American.
He ought to be thrilled.
He might not be.
Oh, maybe you're right.
He is kind of a lump.
Think about it.
How would you feel
if you were referred to
as part of Leonard's team?
Oh, I'd be incensed.
So you see what
I'm getting at?
Squeaky wheel
gets the grease?
No.
Grass is always greener?
Try again.
Well, I don't know--
we're all Groot?
Just tell me.
Leonard is as much
a part of this paper
as you are,
and he was overlooked.
He's going to feel bad.
But it wasn't my fault.
I didn't exclude him.
And I didn't write the article.
Remember that time you didn't
get picked to pull the sword out
of the stone at Disneyland and
they let that other kid do it?
Oh, that kid!
Poor Leonard.
Exactly.
For the record,
that kid was a terrible choice.
If you cry when you drop
your churro,
you do not have what it takes
to rule England.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x18 ♪
The Leftover Thermalization
Original Air Date on March 12
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Thanks for helping us sort
through all my mom's stuff.
Of course.
I know what it's like
having to go through
a loved one's possessions.
My uncle was
a worshipper of Krishna.
But after he died,
you know what we found?
A statue of Shiva.
It may not be
Crips and Bloods, okay?
But in India, it's a thing.
Well, it'll be good
that you're there.
Howard's been having
trouble deciding
what to keep
and what to let go.
Well, it's hard.
A lot of Ma's stuff
brings back fond memories.
Is that why you couldn't
get rid of
her drawer
full of ketchup packets?
Yes. It reminds me of us
eating out and her saying,
“Quick, nobody's looking,
fill your pockets with ketchup”"
Leonard?
Have you ever noticed that
only my name is
on the cable bill?
Yeah.
Good, good.
And your name is
on the electric bill
and mine isn't.
And I'm okay with that.
Actually, your name is
on the electric bill.
Oh, right.
This is a disaster.
I don't even know what you're
talking about and I agree.
Okay, I have
to tell you something,
but you're not going to like it.
What's going on?
An article was just published
in Scientific American
about our theory.
Did they hate it?
No. No, they loved it.
They, uh, couldn't say enough
nice things about it.
So what's the problem?
You know how the PennySaver
only has my name...
Sheldon!
They didn't mention you
in the article.
Only me.
Really?
I know.
It's not fair.
Let the anger
go, buddy.
You just...
you relax all
your muscles.
Except for your pubococcygeus
and anal sphincter.
Let's keep those tight.
Uh, that-that's not necessary.
It is-- they're what hold back
the urine and the feces.
Look, maybe-maybe
you shouldn't read it.
It'll only make you feel worse.
“Cooper and his team”?
You should know
I had nothing to do with that.
Uh...
at least they're talking
about the theory.
I mean, that's what's important.
You know, you're right.
Yeah. You know, it's like
when Stan Lee and Steve Ditko
created Spider-Man.
Stan Lee may get all the credit,
but Steve Ditko knows
he was just as important.
Even though Stan Lee gets
to be in all the Marvel movies.
And-and he's far richer.
And he's a household name,
you know?
Whereas, you know,
you say Ditko,
and that sounds like
a company that makes Dits.
That's not helping.
Well, I'd give more examples,
but, well, everyone in
your position's so forgettable.
Stuart, we're here.
It's nice of you to let him keep
staying at your mom's house.
Yeah, well, I tried putting him
out on the curb,
but nobody took him.
Hey.
Just so you know,
the power's out.
What happened?
I called,
they said a transformer blew.
It's the whole block.
Should be fixed by tomorrow.
Wait, when did it go out?
In the middle of the night.
Oh, my God.
Howie, what's wrong?
It's all defrosting.
It's okay. It's just food.
It's not just food.
This is the last food
my mother ever made.
This is her
last brisket.
last meatloaf.
This is her last...
I have no idea
what this is, but...
it's the last one.
Everything okay?
No.
All Ma's food is
gonna be ruined.
Well, why don't we take it home
and put it in our freezer?
You don't want
to do that.
Refreezing not only
removes moisture,
but it creates ice crystals
in the fibers of the meat
that can compromise
its taste and texture.
What? I saw a teachable moment.
I dropped some culinary science.
What should we do?
I'll tell you exactly
what we're gonna do.
We're gonna eat it.
There's, like, 20 pounds
of food in there.
All you said
was I had to get rid of things.
You didn't say they couldn't
pass through my colon first.
Howie...
Okay.
Then how about this?
Let's invite everyone
over to dinner.
It'll be like Ma's feeding us
one last time.
I love that.
Me, too.
Oh, look,
we've got enough ketchup
to cover every ounce of it.
I mean, who even reads
Scientific American?
It's kind of
a big deal.
If it's such a big deal,
how come the biggest celebrity
they could get for the cover
is a molecule?
Can we please just
stop talking about it?
I'm sorry.
What can I do?
Nothing, I'm fine.
No, no.
I'm gonna cheer you up.
Here we go.
What are we doing?
I am taking you shopping.
Oh.
My baby is sad, and I'm gonna
make him happy again.
Look, I know shopping
cheers you up,
but it's just not
really my thing.
Well, what about
this helicopter
you control with an iPad?
Does it have
a camera in it?
It does have
a camera in it.
Baby's listening.
Leonard?
- Leonard?
What?
I spoke to the reporter
at the magazine.
What happened?
Did you tell him it was my idea?
I did.
Thank you. What did he say?
He said they made
the editorial decision
to only cite the lead scientist.
Why did he think
you're the lead scientist?
It was my idea!
You know,
for an extra four bucks,
I can have this thing
here tomorrow.
Well, I know it
was your idea,
but the reporter said he's been
following my work for a while,
and the only reason they even
mentioned it in the magazine
is 'cause my name is on it.
You know what? I did it.
What's four bucks?
If you're trying
to make me feel better,
it's not working.
Well... then what if I told you
that I added your name
to the cable bill?
No.
Oh.
That's just as well.
They had me on hold
for 20 minutes and I hung up.
I...
- Leonard?
Leonard?
Also, Wolowitz invited us all
to dinner, so...
I'm ready whenever you are.
All he had was an idea.
Well, that is an important part.
Oh, please!
I have ideas all day long.
Reverse SeaWorld where dolphins
are allowed to pet people.
A new clothing size between
medium and large called Marge.
Snow White retold from
the point of view of Sneezy.
Why won't Doc
prescribe him something?
We finally find out.
But Leonard's idea was good.
Fine. Then Grumpy--
what's he so grumpy about?
Maybe his girlfriend
won't take his side.
I'm the one
who thought of it!
Well, didn't he do
a lot of the work?
But now he's happy
to let people think
he's responsible for everything.
And that's why you get
an iPad helicopter!
Is it my fault I have a much
bigger reputation than he does?
It's not your fault.
Is it my fault
that my name came first
on the paper alphabetically?
Not your fault.
Is it my fault
that when the reporter cited me
as the lead scientist
I didn't correct him?
Hey, look at that pretty bird.
He always needs
all the attention.
He's such a baby.
I know, I know.
I swear, he is never ever
playing with my helicopter.
Okay, I'll start heating
some of this stuff up.
Thanks.
Oh, man.
This is the boutonniere
from my high school prom...
...a piece of cake
from my Bar Mitzvah.
Did she throw
anything away?
No.
If I find my foreskin,
I'm gonna kill myself.
Okay, so we've got, um,
three briskets, four
meatloafs, one lasagna...
No, that's noodle kugel.
One Jewish lasagna...
...two pound cakes that are
about eight pounds each,
and one giant container
of matzah ball soup.
Ma always kept it on hand,
in case I got sick.
She thought she could cure
anything with her cooking.
Even the time
I got food poisoning.
From her cooking.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Let's get started.
You got it.
I'm never
gonna talk to her again.
Should we tell
everyone not to come?
No. I want to do this.
Okay. Well, I'll keep
it together if you can.
Okay.
I'm not making any promises!
Glad you guys
could make it.
Of course.
Wow, it looks really
pretty in here.
Yeah, turns out half a dozen
menorahs really sets a mood.
So, Stuart,
have you thought about
what you'd do
if Howard sells the house?
And there goes the mood.
Hi. Hello.
Oh, and a special
hello to Leonard,
who needs to be
mentioned by name.
Subtle.
But you got it, right?
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hi. Hello.
I just want
everyone to know,
uh, tonight's not
a sad occasion.
Yeah, we just want to have
the kind of dinner
that we've all had here
so many times before.
Good food, good friends, and
sometime around midnight,
heartburn that makes
you pray for death.
Do you need any help
in the kitchen?
No, we got it. You guys
make yourselves comfortable.
All right, hey, you two, we're
here for Howard right now, okay?
Yes, so please
behave yourselves.
Fine.
Of course.
So I heard you two, uh,
wrote a paper together.
How's that going?
This food is amazing.
Mm, and not
a vegetable in sight.
That's not true.
We've got tomatoes right here.
All these bright people sitting
around a table by candlelight.
Feels like we could be an
18th century French salon.
Indeed.
Penny, a salon is a gathering
where intellectuals
entertained each other
with sparkling conversations
about issues of the day.
Oh, so it's like The View.
Sheldon, The View is a daytime
talk show hosted by women.
Oh, I'm aware.
It features Whoopi Goldberg.
She played Guinan on
Star Trek: Next Gen.
Penny, Next Gen
refers to Star Trek...
Shut up.
I would like to
propose a salon topic.
Ooh, please do, Rajesh.
The lead in The Hunger
Games is a woman.
Marvel has made
“Tor” a female.
Wait, who's Tor?
You know, Tor,
the God of “Tunder.”
As I was saying,
is this a sign
that our society is
approaching gender equality?
Certainly a lot more women
are reading comic books now.
It's true.
At the store, I had to put
a seat on the toilet.
We won't know
if there's equality
until female Thor has a baby
and the Avengers are cool with
her pumping breast milk at work.
I wonder if only a baby
who is worthy
can suckle at the bosom of Thor.
Okay, new salon topic.
Salons-- dumb thing
from a long time ago
or interesting thing made dumb
by talking about superheroes?
Discuss.
I don't believe it matters
what the topic is.
What's crucial for a salon
is that we conduct
the discussion
in an elevated
and insightful way.
It's all about the execution.
Of course you'd focus on that
rather than the inspiration.
Uh, new salon topic.
What's more important,
an idea or its execution?
Oh, that's fun.
Yeah, good for you, Leonard.
That's a lovely little notion.
Kind of like,
“I wish I could talk
to my uncle in Chicago.”
Yeah, now stand back
while I invent the telephone.
“Hello? Oh, hold on.”
Leonard, it's your uncle.
He says you just got burned.
Sheldon.
You guys.
No, it's okay.
We're all adults trying to have
an intelligent discussion.
At least I am.
Howard, what
do you think?
Well, I guess, as an engineer,
I lean towards execution.
I spend my days
trying to take
ideas and make them real.
Well said, old chap.
I thought eloquence had died;
here it stands before us.
Starting today, it'll go:
Gettysburg Address,
“I have a dream”
and what you just said.
Oh, now he's a genius?
All you ever do is make fun
of him and engineering.
Leonard, please.
His mother just died.
You're being ridiculous.
Yeah, so are you.
Guys, if I wanted to hear
people be bitchy,
I'd go to my real salon.
Leonard, lots of people
could've had that idea,
but very few people could've
worked out the math
the way I did.
Lots of people
also didn't have that idea,
like everyone in the entire
world except for me.
Oh, well,
apparently Leonard thinks
he's better than everyone
in the whole world,
including those
fighting for our freedom.
Yeah, well,
I don't know about you,
but I support our boys overseas.
And girls.
Hey, you already ruined Thor;
give it a rest.
So I'm just supposed to be okay
with you hogging
all the credit?!
I didn't hog anything.
Unlike you and that weird
lasagna with raisins in it.
You want some of this?
- I'll give you some.
- Hey!
Sheldon, Leonard,
living room, right now!
She said my name first;
that must kill you.
I don't know
what you think you're doing,
but this is a very difficult
time for my husband!
We're eating the last food
his mother ever made,
and you were gonna throw it
at each other like children?!
Whatever it is you're
fighting about, put it aside,
go back in there
and be a good friend to Howard
or there's no dessert
for either of you!
Look at me
when I'm talking to you!
And don't think...
You guys ever notice sometimes
Bernadette sounds like my mom?
I don't hear it.
No, not at all.
I don't think I've eaten
that much in my entire life.
It's why my people wandered
the desert for 40 years.
Took that long to walk it off.
You see, Penny, the Israelites
were in the desert...
Shut up!
So glad you two
are done fighting.
Right now, I'm just trying
to burp without throwing up.
Hang on.
Physics Today
mentioned the paper.
What'd they say?
Who cares?
Did they mention Leonard?
They did.
Yay.
Good news, I found more Tums.
Yay!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net