Time!
All right, Klingons, pencils down.
Okay, I have:
- Have it.
- Got it.
Have it.
- Have it.
- Got it.
- I have...
And "kreplach."
Hold on a second. "Kreplach?"
It isn't Klingon;
it's Yiddish for meat-filled dumpling.
Well, as it turns out,
it's also a Klingon word.
Really? Define it.
"Kreplach":
A hearty Klingon... dumpling.
- Judge's ruling?
- Bilurrrbe.
Hey, guys, I need to use your TV.
- What's wrong with your TV?
- I don't know. It just died.
- I'm getting a bunch of static.
- Did you pay your cable bill?
You sound just
like the cable company.
All right, shh!
Tyra Banks is about to kick
someone off
America's Next Top Model.
- Excuse me, but we're...
- Don't tell her.
... playing Klingon Boggle.
What do you mean, "Aw"?
Like she didn't know we were nerds?
All right, if you must watch,
then mute it
with closed captions, please.
Fine.
All right, Boggle warriors...
Look at those women.
They're gorgeous.
Nice!
Too bad that's a proper noun.
Look, there's
the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
No, wait, that's
With her head in the lap of...
What a coincidence.
It's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
Yeah, and they can all move in
with you and your mother.
The current Mrs. Wolowitz.
Is "..." spelled
with a "..." or a "..."?
Why is that Mrs. Wolowitz crying?
That's Anais. None of the other girls
in the house like her.
House? What house?
- They all live in a house together.
- A house, where?
I don't know.
Somewhere in L.A.
Wait a minute.
You're telling me
that I'm within driving distance
of a house filled
with aspiring supermodels?
Yeah, I guess.
And they live together
and shower together and...
have naked pillow fights?
- Where are you going?
- To pay my cable bill.
All right, pencils down!
I have...
and...
Anybody got those?
Subtitles: sub-way.fr
Did I miss anything?
Did they kick Giselle off?
Not yet, but her underwater photo shoot
was an embarrassment.
Sadly, Mrs. Giselle Wolowitz
is sensitive to chlorine.
Lucky for her I like my fashion models
pruny and bug-eyed.
Sheldon, the food's here.
There's the house.
Freeze frame, freeze frame.
What are you doing?
Marking the star positions
and physical landmarks
so we can find the house
of the supermodels.
- Why?
- Isn't it obvious?
Every week,
they kick out a beautiful girl,
making her feel unwanted
and without self-esteem.
A.K.A. the future
Mrs. Howard Wolowitz.
Is my hamburger medium well?
Dill slices, not sweet?
Individual relish packets?
Onion rings?
- Extra breading?
- I asked.
What did they say?
Did you protest?
- Yes.
- Vociferously?
Then what took you so long?
Just eat.
Hey, guys, what'd I miss?
Giselle's hanging by a thread.
Oh, good, I hate her.
Then you're not invited
to our wedding.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Do we have to suffer
through this transparently
manipulative pseudo-reality again?
You and I have
a standing TV schedule,
which is the result of extensive
debate and compromise.
Any alterations
except for breaking news
have to be pre-approved
at the weekly roommate meeting.
Put it on the agenda.
You have to make a motion
to put it on the agenda.
I'll make a motion,
but you're not going to like it.
Fine.
Mock Parliamentary procedure.
At least put it on mute.
Giselle's not getting
kicked off.
It's totally going to be Summer.
- What?
- Sheldon's onion ring. Put it back!
It's one onion ring.
Just put it back before he comes!
- No, I don't think that's where it was.
- Here he comes. Deny, deny, people.
Wall of silence.
- Who touched my...
- Penny! Penny did it.
Why would you do that?
I don't know. I was hungry?
What's the big deal?
The big deal is that nobody
touches food on my plate.
All right. I didn't know, I'm sorry.
Well, I'm sorry,
but that is your second strike.
What?
You have two strikes.
Three strikes and you're out.
It's a sports metaphor.
- A sports metaphor?
- Yes, baseball.
All right, I'll play along.
What was my first strike?
March 18th.
You violated my rule
about forwarding email humor.
I did?
The photo of the cat who
wants to "has cheezeburger"?
Come on.
Everybody loves "LOL cats."
They're cute and they can't spell
'cause they're cats.
I trusted you with my email address,
and you betrayed that trust
by sending me Internet banality:
strike one.
Touching my food: strike two.
Don't worry. They only stay
on your record for a year.
You can get them removed early,
but you have to take his class.
Come on,
I touched one onion ring.
And then you put it back,
compromising the integrity
of all the other onion rings.
Honey, the buses don't go
where you live, do they?
I wish I could be
more lenient with you,
but since you've become a permanent
member of our social group,
I have to hold you to the same
standards as everybody else.
Congratulations.
You're officially one of us.
One of us, one of us.
Well, what a thrill.
You're sitting in my spot.
- You've got to be kidding me.
- Leonard, she's in my spot.
See, here's the thing.
After you leave,
I still have to live with him.
I don't care.
I'm taking a stand.
Metaphorically.
All right, that's it.
Strike three.
I'm banished?
What the hell kind of crap is that?
- Don't worry. I'll talk to him.
- Yeah, you do that.
Just so I know, would you be open
to taking his class?
You can do it online!
So based on our triangulation,
we've narrowed down
the location of the house
to three square miles
in the Hollywood Hills.
Or possibly Durham, North Carolina.
When we find it,
you want to go with us?
To do what?
Party with the pretty girls, dude!
Are you insane?
You're not going to party with them.
You're not even going to get
anywhere near that place.
That's what they said to Neil Armstrong
about the moon.
No one said anything of the kind
to Neil Armstrong.
The entire nation dedicated
a decade of effort and treasure
to put a man on the moon.
Well, my fellow Americans,
before this year is out,
we will put a Wolowitz
on one of America's top models.
And a large number of people
will believe it never happened.
Okay, let me guess.
A quesadilla with soy cheese
for the lactose-intolerant Leonard.
- Thank you.
- Shrimp Caesar salad with no almonds
for the highly allergic
kosher-only-on-the-high-holidays Howard.
And for our suddenly
"back on the Hindu wagon" Raj,
the meatlover's pizza, no meat.
- Coming right up.
- Wait. Excuse me.
You forgot my barbecue
bacon cheeseburger,
barbecue sauce,
bacon and cheese on the side.
I didn't tell you? You're banished
from the Cheesecake Factory.
Why?
Well, you have three strikes.
One: coming in.
Two: sitting down.
And three:
I don't like your attitude.
You can't do that.
Not only is it a violation
of California state law,
it flies directly in the face
of Cheesecake Factory policy.
Yeah, no, there's a new policy:
No shoes, no shirt, no Sheldon.
I bet we could sell that sign
all over Pasadena.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Here's the thing.
I talked to Sheldon
and he feels terrible
and he agrees that he was
unreasonable and out of line.
Really? That's great.
So just apologize to him, okay?
What? I'm not going to apologize
to that nutcase.
Come on. It's easy.
He'll even tell you what to say.
Don't you get it? If you guys
keep going along with his insanity,
- you're just encouraging him.
- We're not encouraging.
It's more like...
knuckling under.
I like hanging out with you,
but I'm not gonna apologize
for something I didn't do.
Well, actually, technically,
you did do it.
That's strike one, Leonard.
There you go: quesadilla.
Salad.
There's your pizza.
And thanks to Sheldon's
heated discussion with my manager
one barbecue bacon cheeseburger,
barbecue sauce,
bacon and cheese on the side.
Thank you.
Go ahead. Eat it.
I dare you.
That's it. There's the house.
I found America's top models!
- Are you sure?
- Look, on the roof.
Anais and Giselle are sunbathing.
European-style.
You can recognize people
on Google Earth?
Of course not. I got a buddy of mine
at NORAD to have a spy drone fly over.
NORAD?
You're using military aircraft?
It was already targeted
to poke around
a nuclear reactor in Siberia.
I took it an hour
out of its way, tops.
Where is he?
Sheldon? I just dropped him off
at the comic book store. Why?
Here. Try and go online.
- Problem with the WiFi?
- Just try.
Greetings, hamburger toucher.
You are probably wondering
why you cannot IM
with your little friends
about how much
you "heart" various things.
This recorded message is alerting you
that I am putting an end
to your parasitic piggybacking
upon our WiFi.
If you want to remedy
the situation,
you can contact
the phone company,
set up your own WiFi
and pay for it,
or you may apologize to me.
I reiterate: knuckle under.
No, no. It is on.
I am gonna introduce
your friend to a world of hurt.
You don't want to get into it
with Sheldon.
The guy is one lab accident away
from being a supervillain.
I don't care. I was in junior rodeo.
I can hogtie and castrate him in 60 s.
No need to neuter the nerd.
I can get you back online.
There, see? Problem solved.
Voilà.
Hello, puny insects.
As a consequence of your efforts
to circumvent my will,
everyone is awarded
one additional strike.
Thanks a lot.
What are you complaining about?
I have to take the class again.
Time to do your laundry, huh?
It's Saturday night.
Saturday is laundry night.
I know.
Every Saturday at 8:15.
Easy to anticipate.
What are you implying?
I'm implying
that you're a creature of habit.
And if something were to prevent you
from doing your laundry
on Saturday at 8:15,
you might find it...
unpleasant.
Knuckle under? My ass.
Are all the machines taken?
What are you gonna do?
No problem.
I'll just...
do my laundry another night.
Another night?
Well, I guess you can try, but...
deep inside your heart,
you'll know that laundry night
is always Saturday night.
Woman, you are playing
with forces beyond your ken.
Yeah, well, your ken
can kiss my Barbie.
- Where are my clothes?
- Your clothes?
I left them in the washers
and when I went down, they were gone.
Really?
Despite the sign that says
"Do not leave laundry unattended"?
Where are my clothes?
You know, I do recall seeing
some female undergarments.
Where was that?
Earlier this evening,
I happened to gaze out the window
and a brassiere caught my eye.
Do those look familiar?
How the hell did you get them up
on that telephone wire?
When you understand
the laws of physics,
anything is possible.
And may I add: mwuh-ha-ha.
- Get them down.
- Apologize.
- Never.
- Then may I suggest
you get a very long stick
and play panty piñata.
Wait, Sheldon,
this has gotten out of hand, okay?
I've done some stupid things.
You've done some stupid things.
How about we call it even
and move on with our lives?
I've done no stupid things.
- You gotta meet me halfway here.
- I am meeting you halfway,
I'm willing to concede
that you've done stupid things.
You guys are talking again.
Good.
What happened?
Remember when I said it was on?
Well, now it's junior rodeo on.
Not junior rodeo.
What did you do?
I had no choice, Leonard.
She ruined laundry night.
Mwuh-ha-ha.
Telephone wires can't electrocute you,
can they?
Look, this has to stop.
- No, no. It is just beginning.
- All right.
I really didn't
want to do this, but...
here.
What's this?
Sheldon's Kryptonite.
Oh, my God.
He can never know
that I gave that to you.
Look, I said
I wanted to hurt him, but...
but this?
It'll shorten the war by five years
and save millions of lives.
Pause it.
That's it. Confirmed.
We now have the address
of the Top Model house.
God bless you,
Google Street View registered trademark.
For the record,
what you're doing is really creepy.
You know what? If it's "creepy"
to use the Internet, military
satellites, and robot aircraft
to find a house full
of gorgeous young models
so that I can drop in
on them unexpectedly,
then fine, I'm "creepy."
Hold on a second, I'll get him.
Sheldon, it's for you.
- Who is it?
- Your mother.
Oh, good.
Hi, Mom. How are you?
But, Mom...
she keeps sitting in my spot.
And she touched my food.
Okay, yes, I took her clothes,
but she started it...
No, that's not fair.
Why should I have to apologize?
I don't think this is the kind of thing
Jesus concerns himself with.
No, you're right.
I don't really know
what Jesus thinks about.
All right, good-bye.
Did you tell on me?
Are you kidding me?
I already have two strikes.
I am very, very sorry
for what I have done.
Here's your laundry.
I rescind your strikes
and you are no longer banished.
Can I sit wherever I want?
Never mind, never mind.
That's not important.
Sheldon, this was big of you.
- Thank you. I really appreciate it.
- Thank you.
Well played.
- Just remember:
with great power
comes great responsibility.
Understood.
Can I help you?
We're here to fix the cable.
I think we have satellite.
That's what I meant.
Come on in.
She's taller than all the women
in my family combined.
What do we do now?
Follow Mrs. Wolowitz.
www.tvsubtitles.net