The problem appears
to be unsolvable.
Maybe we could run
some computer simulations.
There are too many variables.
It would take forever.
We've got to be missing something.
Let's start again.
The movie is playing here
at 7:20, here at 7:40,
here at 8:10 and here at 8:45.
These theaters
have to be eliminated.
Why? They're state-of-the-art digital
projection, 20-channel surround sound.
Yes, but they have no Icee machines.
Despite my aggressive
letter-writing campaign, I might add.
What about the multiplex here?
The seats are terrific.
They have Twizzlers
instead of Red Vines.
No amount of lumbar support
can compensate for that.
It's gonna take
at least an hour to eat,
and I don't see
a Sheldon-approved restaurant
proximate
to a Sheldon-approved theater.
- We could eat after the movie.
- Unacceptable.
The delay would result in tomorrow's
bowel movement occurring at work.
Hang on, hang on.
There's a 7-Eleven here.
We smuggle Slurpees,
which are essentially Icees,
in under our coats,
after having a pleasant meal
either here, here or here.
I don't see how we missed that.
Excuse me, in what universe
are Slurpees Icees?
That's how we missed it.
Sheldon, would you be prepared,
on a non-precedential basis,
to create an emergency ad hoc
Slurpee-Icee equivalency?
You know I can't do that.
I guess we only have one option.
I don't see any way around it.
- Bye, Sheldon.
- See ya.
They're right,
it was the only option.
Subtitles: sub-way.fr
Shut the door!
- Why?
- Just do it!
- Get inside and shut the door.
- Well, you didn't specify.
- Is Leonard around?
- He went to the movies without me.
It was the only option.
I'm sorry, I don't understand
which social situation this is.
Could you give me some guidance
as to how to proceed?
The building manager's showing
an apartment downstairs,
- and I haven't paid my rent.
- Oh, I see.
I'm not sure I'm comfortable
harboring a fugitive
from the 2311 North
Los Robles Corporation.
It's no big deal.
I'm just a little behind on my bills
because they cut back my hours
at the restaurant and my car broke down.
If you recall, I pointed out
the "check engine" light
to you several months ago.
The "check engine" light is fine.
It's still blinking away.
It's the stupid engine
that stopped working.
It cost me like $1,200 to fix it.
It occurs to me you could solve all
your problems by obtaining more money.
Yes, it occurs to me, too.
Hang on a moment.
Here. Take some.
Pay me back when you can.
- You got a lot of money in there.
- That's why it's guarded by snakes.
- Take some.
- Don't be silly.
I'm never silly.
- Here.
- No, I can't.
Don't you need money?
- Yeah, but...
- This is money I'm not using.
But what if you need it?
My expenses account for 46.9%
of my after-tax income.
The rest is divvied up between
a small savings account,
this deceptive container
of peanut brittle
and the hollowed-out buttocks
of a superhero action figure
who shall remain nameless
for his own protection.
Or her own protection.
- Take some.
- Really? I mean, are you sure?
I see no large upcoming expenditures
unless they develop
an affordable technology
to fuse my skeleton
with adamantium like Wolverine.
Are they working on that?
I sincerely hope so.
Well, thank you.
No, I can't.
Honey, I don't want things
to be weird between us.
Won't it also be weird
if I have to say hello to you
every morning on my way to work
and you're living in a refrigerator box
and washing your hair
with rain water?
- I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
- Of course you will.
It's impossible to pay me back
sooner than you can.
Assuming you subscribe to a linear
understanding of time and causality.
I'm regretting this already.
I've given the matter some thought,
and...
I think I'd be willing to be a house pet
to a race of super-intelligent aliens.
Interesting.
Ask me why.
Do I have to?
Of course. That's how
you move a conversation forward.
Why?
The learning opportunities
would be abundant.
Additionally, I like
having my belly scratched.
- Hey, Penny. How was work?
- Great.
I hope I'm a waitress at the
Cheesecake Factory for my whole life.
Was that sarcasm?
- Was that sar...
- Stop it!
- You appear to have a package here.
- Oh, thanks.
This must be the beret I ordered.
A couple of months ago.
It was back-ordered.
Did you know the beret is an example
of a piece of women's fashion
adapted from male military uniforms?
Another fascinating example
is the epaulet.
He's not lying.
He does find that fascinating.
Whatever. It's not like
I'm running up and down the streets
just buying myself berets.
I bought one a month ago,
and it was back-ordered.
- Look, it finally arrived, all right?
- All right.
Oh, my God, would you just
get off my case?!
- Weird.
- Good, that was an unusual interaction.
I wasn't sure.
- Did you guys have an argument?
- No.
You clearly did something
to aggravate her.
I'm at a loss.
If you like, you can review
my daily log of social interactions
and see if there's
a blunder I overlooked.
Here you go.
You owe me another two dollars.
The price of moo shu pork went up.
It's getting tougher and tougher
to be a bad Jew.
Here you go, Penny.
Shrimp with lobster sauce.
- Thank you. What's my share?
- Don't worry about it. It's my treat.
Really, how much?
Whatever. $10, $11.
Which is it, $10 or $11?
$14.50. But it's no biggie.
You'll get the next one.
What?
He was just wondering if he wore
skintight jeans and a tank top
if he'd get
his shrimp lo mein for free.
What are you saying?
That I'm using my body to get dinner?
That I'm some kind of Chinese
food prostitute?
Yeah, Raj, what are you saying?
Let me tell you something.
I pay my own way in this world, okay?
I don't rely on anybody!
What was that about?
He has a nervous bladder
when he's stressed out.
Kind of like a puppy.
Here, Leonard.
$10, $11, $12... $14.
It was $14.50, but it's okay.
Oh, good.
Dinner's here.
Yes, and I'm having some.
I'm having takeout food.
You're damn right it's okay. I've been
having leftovers at the restaurant
for like four days, and I wanted
something different. So sue me.
Forgive me, but that would be
the very definition
of a frivolous lawsuit.
I will pay you back as soon as I can.
You just have to give me more time.
- You lent her money?
- She need money.
You seem under pressure.
Did I not lend you a sufficient amount?
Because I can give you more.
You know, you would just
love that, wouldn't you?
You would just love to
open up your little snake can
and throw some money
at the girl who can't pay her bills.
- Where are you going?
- Going home,
where I won't be interrogated
like a criminal.
I forgot my fortune cookie.
In case either of you
have larceny in your heart,
you should know that I've moved
my money out of the snake can.
But if you're ever short, there's always
a couple of 50s in Green Lantern's ass.
- Hey.
A little mood lighting, huh?
When I didn't pay my bill,
the Department of Water and Power
thought I would enjoy the ambience.
Yeah, they're very considerate
that way.
I used Sheldon's money to pay my rent.
Then I had like $14 left over.
$14, huh?
Put it back in your pocket,
or I'll find some other place to put it.
Back in the pocket it goes.
You do understand
Sheldon really doesn't care
when he gets the money back.
It's actually
one of the few idiosyncrasies
that doesn't make you
want to... kill him.
Yeah, well, that's not really
my big problem.
So you're a little behind on your bills.
Everybody gets behind on their bills.
I know, it's just...
This wasn't the plan.
It wasn't supposed to go this way.
What was the plan?
Waitress for six months
and then become a movie star.
- Was there a plan B?
- TV star.
It's probably not as bad as you think.
Let's take a look.
Maybe we can find
some corners to cut.
Here's something.
If you don't have electricity,
then you probably don't need cable.
Just a suggestion.
$170 dollars for acting classes?
No, I can't give up my acting classes.
I'm a professional actress.
You've had an acting job
where you got paid?
That is not the definition
of professional.
Actually, it kind of...
Let's keep looking.
What's $1,800 to the Los Angeles County
Superior Court?
That's nothing.
Nothing?
It sounds like you got caught speeding
going 4,000 miles an hour.
Remember Kurt?
Your ex-boyfriend?
He got arrested for taking
a whiz on a cop car.
- What?
- He was drunk.
I would hope so.
He had a bunch of outstanding tickets
and a bench warrant,
so I, you know, I paid his fines.
- Did he pay you back?
- No, but he will.
And that's based on the inherent
credit-worthiness of people
who get drunk and urinate
on police vehicles?
Leonard, I'm not gonna call up Kurt
and ask him for money.
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know,
but I may have to find
a cheaper place to live.
You don't want to do that.
Why not?
Moving is a big deal.
You have to go to the supermarket
and get boxes,
and if they're not clean,
your books smell like melons,
and it's like...
Why don't you just get a roommate
and stay here?
Do you know anybody?
I'm sure the guy living with Sheldon
wouldn't mind moving in with you.
Leonard, honey,
if we started living together,
I wouldn't be able
to keep my hands off you.
Really?
And you thought my acting lessons
were a waste of money.
This Moo Shu pork's burning
a hole through my duodenum.
Leviticus 11:3:
"Only that which parteth the hoof
and cheweth the cud
among the beasts shall ye eat."
Do I mock you with the Bhagavad-Gita
every time you scarf down a Whopper?
- What's going on?
- We're on a quest
through the Valley of Fire
to acquire the sacred crown.
You want the Valley of Fire?
It's right here.
You guys want to go
on a real live quest?
Outside? I just made cocoa.
- Come on. It'll be fun.
- What is it?
Do you guys remember
Penny's ex-boyfriend Kurt?
Yeah, that's him.
Turns out he owes Penny a lot of money,
and I'm gonna go get it from him.
Who's with me?
Double sixes.
Really? You're just gonna
let me go by myself?
Cool, I got a sword.
I could use some help.
Here.
You guys are unbelievable.
You play a game
to simulate adventure,
but when there's real adventure
out there in the real world,
you just wimp out.
Do you not recall
the last time we visited this gentleman,
we returned home without pants?
- I do.
- Are you sure?
Because your proposal
suggests that you don't.
- I'm not afraid of him.
- All right.
Leonard fairly calls the question:
Who is in favor
of abandoning our game
and confronting Penny's
steroid-infused ex-boyfriend
in a suicidal mission
to extract money from him?
Say hi to Kurt for us.
Excuse me.
When Frodo left the Shire
to take the one ring to Mordor,
didn't Samwise, Pippin
and Merry go with him?
- They did.
- Well?
They had a terrible time of it.
Plus, no one stole their pants.
Fine.
Enjoy your little game.
I'll make this quest on my own.
Wait.
Take a jacket.
It's shpritzing a little.
You guys suck.
Come on, please? He's so big.
Is everyone clear on the plan?
Koothrappali's going to wet himself,
I'm gonna throw up,
Sheldon's gonna run away,
and you're going to die.
Shall we synchronize our watches?
Guys, there are four of us
and one of him.
Which means his triumph
will be even larger.
Minstrels will write songs
about him.
How about this? I'll do the talking.
You just stand behind me
and try to look formidable.
I should've peed before we left.
- Hi, Kurt.
- Lenny, right?
I don't really go by Lenny,
but that's okay.
You remember
Sheldon, Howard and Raj.
- What do you want?
- You don't remember me?
- How could he not rember me?
- Not now.
I remember him.
Here it is.
Penny's in kind of a financial jam,
and the money that you owe her
would go a long way
to solving her problems.
She sent you to get it from me?
No, no, she's too proud
to ask for the money.
I, on the other hand, feel
you should honor your debt.
You do?
"Feel" is a kind of a...
it's a strong word.
I just think it would be
a nice gesture on your part.
She'll get it when she gets it.
Well, there you go.
Problem solved.
A successful quest. Now let's go find
a gas station with a clean bathroom.
No, the problem isn't solved.
- He just blew us off.
- I've got it.
He didn't remember me
because the last time we met,
I was in a Halloween costume.
Come on, Leonard, let's go.
You can leave if you want to.
I'm gonna see this through.
I guess, technically,
that was my fault.
I'm not leaving here
without Penny's money.
What happened to your backup?
I don't need backup.
I have right on my side.
And I'm wearing cargo shorts
under my pants.
Congratulations.
You may not have succeed
in getting cash,
but you did secure
a formal acknowledgment of the debt.
Maybe we should have
your head notarized.
If anybody cares,
I still have to pee.
- Is Sheldon here?
- Hang on.
Nice hat.
It's kind of a fashionable look
these days.
Maybe if you're working
on a tuna boat.
- Hello, Penny.
- Sheldon, here is your money.
Thank you very much.
It helped a lot.
Sarcasm?
Darn. I can't seem
to get the hang of that.
I know it's none of my business,
but where did the money come from?
Well, I cut back my expenses
like you said
and picked up a few more hours
at the restaurant,
but the biggest thing was,
out of the blue, Kurt shows up
and gives me the money he owes me.
Really?
Did he say why?
He said he was feeling guilty
and wanted to do what was right.
That's it?
Did he give any reason
as to why he came
to this moral epiphany?
I just think he's really changed.
We're having dinner tomorrow night,
and I get to wear my new beret.
Bye, guys.
Well done, Leonard.
The true hero
doesn't seek adulation.
He fights for right and justice
simply because it's his nature.
Penny's hooking up
with her jerk of an ex-boyfriend,
and I have indelible ink
on my forehead!
That's your badge of honor...
your warrior's wound, if you will.
I was wrong.
Minstrels will write
songs about you.
Great.
There once was a brave lad
named Leonard
With a fi-fi fiddle dee-dee
He faced a fearsome giant
While Raj just wanted to pee
www.tvsubtitles.net