Your argument is lacking
on all scientific merit.
And it is well established,
Superman cleans his uniform
by flying into Earth yellow Sun,
which incinerate any contaminate matter
and leaves the unvulnerable Kryptonian
fabric unharmed and daisy fresh.
What if he gets something
Kryptonian on it?
- Like what?
- I don't know. Kryptonian mustard.
I think we can safely assume
that all Kryptonian condiments
were destroyed
when the planet Krypton exploded.
Or it turned
into mustard Kryptonite,
the only way to destroy a rogue
Kryptonian hotdog threatening Earth.
Raj, please,
let's stay serious here.
Superman's body is Kryptonian,
therefore his sweat is Kryptonian.
What about Kryptonian pit stains?
Superman doesn't sweat
on Earth.
He's invited for dinner
in the Bottle City of Kandor.
He miniaturizes himself, enters the city
where he loses his superpowers.
Before dinner, his host says,
"Who's up for a little
Kryptonian tetherball?"
Superman says "Sure," works up a sweat,
comes back to Earth,
his uniform now stained with
indestructible Kryptonian perspiration.
Boo ya.
Superman would have
taken his uniform
to a Kandorian dry cleaner
before he left the Bottle.
"Kandorian dry cl..." I give up.
You can't have a rational
argument with this man.
Isn't that the guy who won
the MacArthur genius grant last year?
No, not all at once.
Then how?
Leonard.
Now, Raj.
Now, Sheldon.
I didn't get a good look.
Can I go again?
- It's David Underhill. So what?
- So what?
His observation of high-energy positrons
has provided
the first conclusive evidence for
the existence of galactic dark matter.
I have two words for you.
The first is "big," the other's "whoop."
It is a big whoop.
It made almost all the work
you've done completely useless.
- Did not.
- Did, too.
Okay, maybe some of it, but...
The guy was just in the right place,
at the right time
with the right paradigm-shifting
reinterpretation of the universe.
He got lucky.
In more ways than one.
He's a very handsome man.
Doesn't do anything for me.
If I was gonna go that way,
I'm more of a Zac Efron kinda guy.
Yeah, like you have
a shot with Zac Efron.
Excuse me...
Are you Leonard Hofstadter?
I'm David Underhill.
Dr. Gablehauser said if I wanted
to set something up
in the photomultiplier lab,
that you'd be able to give me a hand?
- You want to work with me?
- If you have a little time.
Sure.
Yeah, no problem.
Here's my home number.
Here's my cell.
Here's my office.
Here's my parents' number
up in New Jersey.
They always know how to reach me.
Congratulations on the MacArthur Grant,
by the way. Big fan.
Thanks. I'll call you.
What are you looking at?
You've never seen a hypocrite before?
Subtitles: sub-way.fr
Trailing badly,
Wolowitz needs a strike
if he has any hopes of catching up
with Sheldon Cooper,
who is dominating in the ninth frame
with a career-best 68.
Hey, guys!
That doesn't count.
Do over! Do over!
There are no do-overs
in Wii bowling.
There are always do-overs
when my people play sports.
Where were you that's more important
than Wii bowling night?
- Actually...
- It's rhetorical.
There is nothing more important
than Wii bowling night.
Come on, it's just a video game.
And we suck at it.
Nice motivational speech
from the team captain.
- Where were you?
- I was working with Dave Underhill.
"Dave." Sounds like
Leonard's got a new BFF.
Actually, he's pretty cool.
Not only is he a brilliant scientist,
but it turns out
he's a Black Diamond skier.
He collects vintage motorcycles.
He plays in a rock band.
So? We're in a rock band.
No...
We play Rock Band
on our X-Box.
Nice motivational speech
from our lead guitarist.
He's funny, too.
He does this hysterical impersonation
of Stephen Hawking having phone sex.
What are you wearing?
That's not... He does it better.
He said he was gonna
take me to the gym tomorrow,
so I'm gonna go practice my situps.
Humongous man crush,
dude.
Yeah.
It's officially a bro-mance.
Are you and Leonard
putting up a Christmas tree?
No, because we don't celebrate
the ancient pagan festival
of Saturnalia.
- Saturnalia?
- Gather round, kids,
it's time for Sheldon's
beloved Christmas special.
In the pre-Christian era,
as the winter solstice
approached and the plants died,
pagans brought evergreen boughs
into their homes
as an act of sympathetic magic,
intended to guard the life essences
of the plants until spring.
This custom was later appropriated
by Northern Europeans
and eventually it becomes
the so-called Christmas tree.
And that, Charlie Brown,
is what boredom is all about.
Thank you for that,
but I got you and Leonard
a few silly neighbor gifts,
so I'll just put them under my tree.
Wait!
You bought me a present?
Why would you do such a thing?
'Cause it's Christmas?
I know you think
you're being generous,
but the foundation
of gift-giving is reciprocity.
You haven't given me a gift.
You've given me an obligation.
Don't feel bad, Penny,
it's a classic rookie mistake.
My first Hanukah with Sheldon,
he yelled at me for eight nights.
You don't have
to get me anything in return.
Of course I do.
The essence of the custom
is that I now have to go out and
purchase a gift of commensurate value
and representing the same
perceived level of friendship
as that represented
by the gift you've given me.
It's no wonder suicide rates
skyrocket this time of year.
Forget it.
I'm not giving you a present.
It's too late. I see it.
That elf sticker says, "To Sheldon."
The die has been cast.
The moving finger has writ,
Hannibal has crossed the Alps.
I know. It's funny
when it's not happening to us.
Sheldon, I am very, very sorry.
No, I brought this on myself
by being such an endearing
and important part of your life.
I'm going to need
a ride to the mall.
It's happening to us.
- Are you gonna make it?
- Yeah, I guess.
Thanks for letting me try out
your motorcycle.
No problem.
I had no idea it was so heavy.
The thing just fell right
over on me, didn't it?
Yeah.
Lucky for you it wasn't moving.
Hey, Leonard. Are you okay?
It's just a little
motorcycle accident.
My God, how fast were you going?
I don't know. It's all such a blur.
Good one.
He couldn't even get it started.
- Hi. Dave.
- Hi.
Penny.
So it's your motorcycle?
- Is it okay?
- It's fine.
Lucky for the bike
it landed on my leg.
You mind giving me a hand
with Speed Racer here?
- How do you know Leonard?
- I'm a physicist.
No, you're not.
Why is that so surprising?
Well, it's just that
the physicists I know
are indoorsy and pale.
I'm not indoorsy.
I just wear the appropriate sun block
because I don't take
melanoma lightly.
So, are you and Leonard
working on an experiment together?
- Actually we are.
- We're examining the radiation levels
of photomultiplier tubes
for a new dark matter detector.
Sweetie, sweetie, Dave was talking.
You know, I love science.
- Since when?
- Since always.
Call me a geek, but I am just nuts
for the whole subatomic
particle thing.
The last thing I would
ever call you is a geek.
Well, that's what I am...
queen of the nerds.
If you like, I could show you
the lab we're working in.
We've got some cool toys,
you know, lasers and stuff.
You know, I have always wanted
to see a big science lab.
- Since when?
- Since always.
Leonard, are you okay here?
- I guess.
- How about we go see it now?
Maybe afterwards we take the bike,
we grab a little bite to eat...
Yeah, that sounds great.
Let me just get my jacket.
Boy, she'll do, huh?
Yeah, if you like that type.
So, you and her...?
- No, just neighbors.
- Really?
I don't know how you live
next door to that
without doing something about it.
Actually...
science is my lady.
- Okay. Let's go.
- All right.
- See you tomorrow, Leonard.
- See ya.
Have fun.
Did you forget your key?
I don't see anything in here
a woman would want.
You're kidding.
You've got lotions
and bath oils and soaps.
That's the estrogen hat trick.
What it is is a cacophonous assault
of eucalyptus, bayberry,
cinnamon and vanilla.
It's as if my head were trapped
in the pajamas of a sultan.
If you don't like this stuff,
let's go next door and build her a bear.
I told you before,
bears are terrifying.
Come on,
bath stuff. It's perfect!
You got a scented candle,
a cleansing buff,
spearmint and green tea scented
bath oil, promotes relaxation.
That presupposes Penny is tense.
She knows you. She's tense.
We all are. Buy a basket!
- Excuse me, we're ready.
- No, we're not.
Let's say for a moment that I accept
the bath item gift hypothesis,
I now lay the following
conundrum at your feet:
Which size?
This one. Let's go.
- You put no thought into that.
- I'm sorry.
This one. Let's go!
I have insufficient data to proceed.
Excuse me, miss?
If I were to give you
this gift basket,
based on that action alone
and no other data,
infer and describe
the hypothetical relationship
that exists between us.
Excuse me?
Here.
Now, are we friends?
Colleagues? Lovers?
Are you my grandmother?
I don't understand
what you're talking about
and you're making me
a little uncomfortable.
See? Sounds just like you and Penny.
We'll take it.
- Leonard. Come, join us.
- Hey, Dave.
And Penny, what a surprise.
Dave was just showing me
around the university.
This place is unbelievable!
I know, I've been offering to show
you around for a year and a half.
You always said you had yoga.
- I never said that.
- Maybe I heard you wrong.
A lot of words sound like "yoga."
This is an amazing woman.
She has a curious and agile mind,
not to mention being curious and agile
in other respects.
Shut up!
Yes, please shut up.
So... Dave,
don't you think you and I
should get back to the lab?
You know, that dark matter
isn't going to detect itself.
Actually, I was thinking about
taking the afternoon off
so I could work on another
experiment with Penny.
Really? We're going
to do an experiment?
We're going to explore
the effects of tequila shots
on a gorgeous 22-year-old woman.
It's not an experiment!
You saw what happened last night.
- You ready to go?
- Yeah.
- Can I drive the motorcycle?
- Yeah, why not?
You can't do any worse than Leonard.
That's funny.
By the way, my leg is killing me.
Thanks for asking.
Great news, Leonard.
I've solved my Penny gift dilemma.
Yippee.
You see, the danger was
that I might under or over-reciprocate,
but I have devised a foolproof plan.
See, I will open
her gift to me first
and then excuse myself,
feigning digestive distress.
Then...
I'll look up the price
of her gift online,
choose the basket
closest to that value,
give it to her
and then I'll return the others
for a full refund.
Brilliant.
It is, isn't it?
Is it okay if I hide them
in your room?
The smell makes me nauseated.
- Do whatever you want.
- Thank you, that's very gracious.
Gentlemen.
Why couldn't you have just done
what Leonard did
and get Penny a new boyfriend?
My leg is killing me.
Thanks for asking.
I have just one question for you.
While I am perfectly happy with the way
things are between us,
you said you didn't want
to go out with me
because I was too smart for you!
News flash, lady:
David Underhill is
ten times smarter than me!
You'd have to drive
a railroad spike into his brain
for me to beat him at checkers!
Next to him, I'm like one
of those sign-language gorillas
who knows how to ask for grapes!
So, my question is...
What's up with that?!
Why are you yelling at me?
Sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Never mind, we're cool.
Dave is not smarter than you.
He's an idiot.
Really? Why would you say that?
Because a smart guy takes
the nude photos of his wife
off his cell phone
before he tries to take nude photos
of his girlfriend.
He tried to take nude photos of you?
That's what you took from that?!
The guy is married!
I'm so... Oh, that's terrible.
And you, if you are so okay
with the way things are between us,
why are you so jealous?
The important thing is
he's married and that's terrible!
Nice save, genius.
Eggnog?
Lactose.
It's just rum. It stopped being eggnog
like half an hour ago.
Smooth.
Smoother than you.
Come on, it's Christmas,
just give me this one.
Merry Christmas.
By the way, my leg is killing me.
Thanks for asking.
Merry Christmas.
How's your leg?
Very good, thanks for asking.
Come on in.
Good, Penny,
you're here to exchange gifts.
You'll be pleased to know I'm prepared
for whatever you have to offer.
Okay, here.
I should note I'm having
some digestive distress,
so, if I excuse myself abruptly,
don't be alarmed.
A napkin.
Turn it over.
"To Sheldon,
"live long and prosper.
"Leonard Nimoy."
He came into the restaurant.
Sorry the napkin's dirty.
He wiped his mouth with it.
I possess the DNA of Leonard Nimoy?!
Yeah, I guess.
But look, he signed it.
Do you realize what this means?!
All I need is a healthy ovum
and I can grow my own Leonard Nimoy!
All I'm giving you
is the napkin, Sheldon.
Be right back.
Here. Open it.
A gift cerficate
for motorcycle lessons.
- Very thoughtful.
- Yeah, and I checked.
Not letting the bike fall on you
while standing still
is lesson one.
Then, I think you'll appreciate
what I got you.
"101 Totally Cool Science
Experiments for Kids."
You know,
'cause you're so into science.
Sheldon! What did you do?!
I know!
It's not enough, is it?
Here.
Leonard, look!
Sheldon's hugging me.
It's a Saturnalia miracle.
www.tvsubtitles.net