Fellas, please.
Penny, come on.
We were just finding our sound.
You found it.
It's the sound of a cat
being run over by a lawn mower.
I'm really very busy.
Is there any way
that we can put this off
until I have more time to prepare?
Of course.
But, you understand my trepidation.
- What's that about?
- Not a clue.
Can't we just postpone it
till the spring?
Maybe next summer?
This should be fairly
easy to deduce.
He's holding the phone
to his left ear.
Ears do not cross hemispheres,
so he's using the analytical
rather than the emotional side
of the brain,
suggesting that he has no personal
relationship with the caller.
No, I didn't realize
it had been so long.
Sure, I guess there's no other choice
but to just go ahead and do it.
He's referring to an activity
he has done before.
It's unpleasant
and needs to be repeated.
This suggests some sort
of invasive medical test,
like perhaps a colonoscopy.
Aren't there any other options?
There's not a lot of room.
- It's gonna be uncomfortable.
- Yes, yes.
I'm definitely going
with colonoscopy.
Okay, bye.
My mother's coming to visit.
How about that, you were right.
Subtitles: sub-way.fr
Transcript: YYeTs
It's out of order.
Yes, I can read the sign.
I'm just pondering the implications.
I think it implies
that the elevator doesn't work.
Again, I can read the sign.
But the sign and the tape
are covered with a layer of dust,
which indicates that the elevator
has been nonfunctional
for a significant amount of time.
Which suggests
either a remarkable passivity
among the, I assume,
24 to 36 residents of this building,
based on the number of mailboxes
and given typical
urban population density
or a shared delusion
of functionality.
You must be Leonard's mother.
I don't know if I must be, but yes.
I'm Penny.
I'm his neighbor.
Dr. Beverly Hofstadter.
Nice to meet you.
You're a hand shaker.
Interesting.
Come with me.
I'll walk you to the apartment.
Would you like to exchange
pleasantries on the way?
- Yeah, sure, I guess.
- All right, you start.
I've always been curious. What was
Leonard like when he was little?
I think you mean young.
He's always been little.
Right.
What was he like when he was young?
You'll have to be more specific.
Okay, like, five or six.
Five.
At that age, he was well enmeshed
in what Freud would call the phallic
stage of psychosexual development.
An outmoded theory, of course,
but the boy did spend
most of his waking hours
with a tight grasp on his penis.
Leonard mentioned
you were a psychiatrist.
That is one of my degrees.
My primary field is neuroscience.
Well, I'm an actress.
Why?
What do you mean why?
There are studies that
suggest that many who go into
the performing arts suffer from
an external locus of identity.
Yeah, I don't know what that means.
It means you value yourself
only as others value you,
which is often the result
of unmet childhood emotional needs.
I had a wonderful childhood.
Tell me about it.
I know my dad wanted a boy.
I tried being good at sports,
but I hated getting dirty!
And then, I'm assuming,
you entered adolescence.
He called me Slugger
until I got my first training bra.
And then he just stopped
playing catch with me.
I wasn't Slugger anymore.
Your mother's here!
If you want
to have intercourse with that girl,
find out what kind of cologne
her father wore.
Good to see you, Mother.
Here's your tea, Mother.
Oolong?
Loose, not bagged?
Steeped three minutes?
Two-percent milk?
Warmed separately?
One teaspoon sugar?
Raw sugar?
It's cold.
I'll start again.
I have the same problem with him.
My theory is that his lack of focus
stems from an over-developed sex drive.
I don't know
where he would've gotten that.
Aside from a pro forma
consummation of our marriage,
his father and I only had intercourse
for the purposes of reproduction.
That seems a fairly efficient
arrangement.
Yes, we think so.
We've both done papers on it.
Mine from the neuroscientific
point of view
and his from an anthropological.
Mine, of course,
was the onlyne worth reading.
Of course.
I would very much like to read
about your sex life.
It's all online or you can order it
from the Princeton University Press.
Here's your tea, Mother.
So, what are you guys talking about?
The frequency with which
your parents had intercourse.
Swell.
If you're lucky, maybe she'll show you
the PowerPoint presentation.
I'm sorry, it's on my other laptop.
So, Mother...
- what's new?
- You'll have to be more specific.
All right.
What's new with you?
Well, I've been having some fascinating
menopausal symptoms recently.
Maybe something less personal.
Your Uncle Floyd died.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
His heart stopped beating.
I have to urinate.
What a remarkable woman.
Yeah, I-I thought you guys
might hit it off.
I envy you your childhood.
I hate to tell you,
but the only warm memories
I have of my childhood
are of my Uncle Floyd.
You're clearly misremembering.
Your mother is brilliant,
analytical, insightful.
And I'm betting
she never hit you with a Bible
because you wouldn't eat
your Brussels sprouts.
You don't give your mother
enough credit.
She's warm, she's loving,
she doesn't glue electrodes
to your head
to measure your brain waves
while potty training.
You were lucky.
When I was a kid, if I wanted an EEG,
I had to attach my own electrodes.
So, Dr. Hofstadter,
Leonard rarely talks
about his incredibly successful
brother and sister.
Please, don't go there.
I understand that,
unlike Leonard, they're at the top
of their respective fields.
Boy, you suck.
Leonard's younger brother, Michael,
is a tenured law professor at Harvard,
and his sister just
successfully grew
a human pancreas
in an adolescent gibbon.
So, she's close to curing diabetes?
Why else would you grow
a pancreas in a teenaged gibbon?
You must be very proud.
Why?
They're not my accomplishments.
I have to urinate.
- Why are you doing this?
- You know the rules.
You brought your mom to work...
you must suffer.
I had no idea your siblings
were so much more successful than you.
You're like the Jar Jar Binks
of the Hofstadter family.
Oh, mesa think
yousa lookin' so so sad.
Rather than mock me,
my friends might realize
that this is difficult
and try to help me through it.
Nope, I think mocking you
is more fun.
Next time, don't yousa
bring mama to work. Okee-day?
- That was fast.
- The middle stall was occupied.
I'll have to try again later.
That's totally understandable.
In bladder voiding, as in real estate,
it's location, location, location.
- So, where were we?
- Howard lives with his mother
and Raj can't speak to women
unless he's drunk. Go.
That's fascinating.
Selective mutism is quite rare.
On the other hand, an adult Jewish male
living with his mother is so common
it borders on sociological cliché.
It's just temporary; I pay rent.
He lives in the same room
where his bassinet was.
Both selective mutism
and an inability
to separate from one's mother
can stem from a pathological
fear of women.
It might explain why the two of you have
created an ersatz homosexual marriage
to satisfy your need for intimacy.
Say what?
That's basically what I just said.
You brought your husband to work.
You know the rules.
Mesa thinking yousa looking
pretty sad now too, betcha, betcha.
Leonard, it's 1:00. Weren't you going
to show me your laboratory at 1:00?
There's no hurry. Tell them more
about their secret love for each other.
But it's 1:00. You were going
to show me your laboratory at 1:00.
Her reasoning is unassailable.
It is 1:00.
Fine. Let's go.
I think you'll find my work
pretty interesting.
I'm attempting to replicate
the dark matter signal
found in sodium iodide
crystals by the Italians.
So, no original research?
What's the point of my seeing it?
I could just read the paper
the Italians wrote.
Just for the record, we're not
in an ersatz homosexual relationship.
- Then why didn't you say that to her?
- Why is it always my responsibility?
It's not always your responsibility.
I swear, this is the same thing you did
at the comic book store last week.
I can't believe
you're bringing that up.
- I didn't bring it up. You did.
- We'll talk about this later.
You always say that,
but you never do.
You went to the comic book store
without me?
- You got alcohol?
- Your mom still here?
Come on in.
Wait, she's not gonna come here
looking for you, is she?
Relax. She took Sheldon
to the hospital to get a brain scan.
Oh, my God. What happened?
Nothing.
Mother likes looking at brains
and Sheldon likes getting
his brain scanned.
Geez, what a fun couple.
She's only been here a day and a half
and I'm seriously considering alcoholism
as a new career path.
I talked to her for 5 minutes yesterday
and I've been half bombed ever since.
You can't let her
get into your head.
- My head, what about yours?
- It's too late for me.
My head is her summer house.
She was right.
The locus of my identity
is totally exterior to me.
Yeah, there she is. Hi, Mom.
Do you know where I was all morning?
Auditioning with 50 other blondes
for some stupid
antidepressant commercial.
And for what?
So I'll finally get
my daddy's approval?
- Did you get the part?
- No, they said I was too perky.
You want to talk
about not getting love from a parent.
You know what I used to do
when I was little
to have some sensation
of human contact?
Yeah, you grabbed your penis
and wouldn't let go.
Your mother told me.
Of course she did.
That's not what I was gonna say.
When I was ten years old,
I built a hugging machine.
A hugging machine?
I got a dressmaker's mannequin,
I stuffed it with an electric blanket
so it would be warm,
and built two radio-controlled arms
that would hug me and pat my back.
That is so sad.
You know what the saddest part was?
My father used to borrow it.
Your scan data will be very helpful
to my research.
You have a remarkable brain.
I know.
Although I've always hated
how my right frontal lobe
looks in pictures.
Common complaint among men.
Nothing's ever big enough.
Except when they get a tumor.
Then you never hear the end of it.
I'd love to see
a scan of your brain sometime.
I'll send you a link, but its physiology
is fairly unimpressive.
I can't believe that.
Your unwillingness to accept
empirical evidence
suggests an attempt at flattery.
My apologies.
I've been living with your son too long.
Gotten into some bad habits.
Understandable.
- Can I make you a cup of tea?
- I doubt it,
but if anyone has a chance,
it's probably you.
I feel very comfortable around you.
I feel very comfortable
around you, too.
It's surprising
because I generally
don't feel comfortable around...
well, anyone.
Nor I.
What are the odds
that two individuals
as unique as ourselves
would be connected
by someone as comparatively
workaday as your son?
Is that a rhetorical point
or would you like to do the math?
I'd like to do the math.
I'd like that, too.
Now this time,
you're gonna lick the salt...
off my neck...
do the shot...
and then...
bite the lime.
I'm sorry, I didn't hear
anything after "lick."
Neck, shot, lime.
- Shot, lime.
- Right.
Where's the lime?
We're sharing.
So, what do you think?
I'm very tempted.
I'm just not sure it's appropriate
with my son's roommate.
Normally, I'd feel the same way.
But based on everything
I've observed about us,
I can't help but speculate
we'd be very good together.
True. I've had
a similar observation.
It's certainly something
I could never do with my husband.
I was hesitant
the first time I tried it,
but I experienced an unanticipated
and remarkable release
of endorphins.
It's quite satisfying.
I see what you're doing.
You're appealing
to the neuroscientific researcher in me.
You see right through me, don't you?
Only when you're in a CAT scanner.
This is actually gonna happen.
Honey, shush, shush.
You shush, I'm happy.
I want to talk about it.
You know what my mother would say?
She would say
because you weren't loved by your father
and I was not loved by my mother,
that having sex is our way
of making up for the intimacy
we didn't get as children.
Why would you bring that up
right now?
I don't know.
Foreplay?
So you're saying
you're not having sex with me,
you're having sex with your mother?
I'm gonna go with "no."
That is the sickest thing
I've ever heard.
Come on,
you're trying to have sex
with your father and I'm okay with that.
Get out!
She said shush.
I should have shushed.
All right, Mother.
Have a nice flight.
That's not really
in my control, is it?
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- I was just coming over to talk to you.
- You don't have to.
Ever.
Gotcha.
- Good-bye, Mother.
- Good-bye.
So, Slugger, shall we pick up
where we left off last time?
I mean, my mom could've just said,
"Bob, get over it,
she's a girl, move on."
- But she didn't. Not one word.
- Interesting.
Would you be willing to fly
to New Jersey
and discuss your relationship
with your parents during a brain scan?
- Would it help?
- Well, it would help me.
www.tvsubtitles.net