Gentlemen, I put it to you:
the worst tapioca pudding
is better than the best pudding
of any other flavor.
First off,
that is axiomatically wrong
because the best pudding
is chocolate.
Secondly,
the organic structure of tapioca
makes it a jiggling bowl
of potential death.
- It is extracted from the plant...
- I'm thinking of growing a mustache.
No kidding? Fu Manchu,
a handlebar, pencil?
- It's extracted from...
- I'm not sure yet.
- George Clooney has one now.
- Really?
I once saw him shopping at Ralph's.
He was buying tequila.
You'd thinka guy like that
would have some kind of booze lackey.
This is cruel. We'd better let him
finish before his head explodes.
All right, why is tap...?
Tapioca is extracted from the root
of the plant manihot esculenta!
Due to a high concentration of cyanide,
it is poisonous in its raw form
and lethal if prepared improperly!
Feel better now?
It is also indigenous to Brazil
as is the cocoa bean,
from which we get chocolate,
the best pudding.
You promised
you wouldn't do that anymore!
Hey, Hofstadter.
Hey, Kripke.
Heard about your latest
anti-proton decay experiment.
20,000 data runs
and no statistically
significant results. Very impressive.
What a jerk.
Don't feel bad.
Negative results are still results.
Even 20,000 of them.
All right!
Please don't cheer me up anymore.
Don't let him get to you.
It's Kripke.
He's a ginormous knob.
That's why he eats by himself
instead of sitting here
at the cool table.
For shizzle.
It's true Kripke lacks the basic
social skills that we take for granted.
But he also controls
the new open science grid computer
that I need to use
to run some simulations
of structure formation
in the early universe.
Good luck getting time on it.
The only people he lets use it
are his friends.
Then the solution is simple.
I shall befriend him.
What would you say to the idea
of you and I becoming friends?
I would say I have no interest
in becoming your friend.
Really?
That seems rather shortsighted
coming from someone
who is generally considered
altogether unlikable.
Why don't you take some time
to reconsider?
Yeah, I'll do that.
I think we're off
to a terrific start.
Subtitles: sub-way.fr
There you go.
Now any e-mail from Wolowitz
will go right into your spam folder.
Thanks.
The e-mail doesn't bother me
as much as the vacation pictures of him
in a bathing suit.
Yeah, I got the same one,
and that's not a bathing suit.
It's a tan line.
Hello,
this is Sheldon Cooper.
I am leaving a message
for Barry Kripke.
It was pleasant
seeing you today in the cafeteria.
I saw that you purchased
the chef's salad.
Apparently, you did not know
that the chef's salad is kitchen
trickery to utilize scrap meat.
Nevertheless,
I hope you enjoyed it.
I'm following up
on our pending friendship
and I look forward to hearing
from you regarding its status.
Sheldon Cooper.
What's up with Ichabod?
He's trying to make
a new friend.
Really?
Well, good for him.
Unless he makes one out of wood
like Geppetto,
I don't think it's gonna happen.
How did you guys become friends?
There was a flyer on the bulletin board
at the university:
"Roommate wanted.
Whistlers need not apply."
- And you moved in anyway?
- I assumed he was joking.
You'd be surprised how many particle
physicists have a whimsical side.
What about Howard and Raj?
How did he become friends with them?
I don't know.
How do carbon atoms form a benzene ring?
Proximity and valence electrons.
Well, sure,
when you put it that way.
But it all worked out, right?
I suppose.
I do miss whistling, though.
Oh, come on. Really?
First warning.
This is for you.
Hello, Sheldon.
Hi.
- What is this?
- It's a questionnaire I devised.
I'm having some difficulty
bonding with a colleague at work
so I'm doing a little research
to better understand
why my current friends like me.
Yes, well, that is a good question.
But is this really the best way
to figure it out?
I agree.
The social sciences
are largely hokum.
But short of putting
electrodes in your brain
and monitoring your response
to my companionship,
this is the best I can do.
Okay, "Question one:
"Rank the following aspects
of Sheldon Cooper
"in order of appeal:
Intelligence;
"ruthless attention to hygiene;
playfulness;
JAVA applet writing"?
I know, I may have started out
with a fairly obvious one;
an aspect of my most appealing trait:
playfulness.
Go ahead and rank that number one.
I'm afraid you're on
your own for the rest.
It should take you
no more than three hours.
Wait. How many questions
are on this thing?
Only 211.
Don't worry.
In deference to you, I kept them all
at a high school graduate
reading level.
Thanks, pal.
You got it... buddy.
Honey, did you ever consider
making friends by being,
I don't know, pleasant?
That's certainly
a thought-provoking hypothesis.
May I suggest it
as the topic for your essay?
Your questionnaire,
very disappointing.
I answered every question.
You answered the multiple choice
questions in a pattern:
A-B-B-A-C.
Oh, you picked up on that?
How could I not?
Come on.
There's over 200 questions.
And look at some of these things.
"Sheldon is to camaraderie
as the space shuttle is to blank?"
There are a number
of acceptable answers.
For example,
"C: Near-Earth transport."
But certainly not
"B: Avocado rancher."
And your essay suggesting
that I'd have better luck
making friends if I wait
till the Cylons take over?
Please.
Hold on.
I put some real work into that.
Yes, well, it's better
than what Wolowitz did.
He drew a raccoon
with what appears to be
a distended scrotum.
It's kinda cute.
Until you get to the scrotum.
What hope do I have
for establishing new relationships
given that my current friends
apparently could not take
a few hours out of their lives
to help me?
I'm not going to defend
a big-balled raccoon.
I don't see how you could.
What I'm trying to say is that
maybe you can't approach this
as a purely intellectual exercise.
What do you mean?
Remember when you tried
to learn how to swim using the Internet?
I did learn how to swim.
On the floor.
The skills are transferable.
I just have no interest
in going in the water.
- Then why learn how to swim?
- The ice caps are melting.
In the future, swimming
isn't going to be optional.
But you do bring up
an interesting point.
I don't have
to break new ground here.
I'm sure much of the research
already exists.
No, no, my point is,
if you want to learn
how to make friends,
then just go out to a coffee shop
or a museum.
Meet people. Talk to them.
Take an interest in their lives.
That's insane on the face of it.
- Where are we going?
- You're driving me to the mall.
I'm going to acquire a book
that summarizes the current theories
in the field of friend-making.
Why don't you just lie down on the floor
and swim there?
Coping with the Death
of a Loved One.
- My condolences.
- Thank you.
Family or friend?
- Family.
- Too bad.
If it had been a friend,
I'm available to fill the void.
It's just as well.
She smelled like mothballs.
If you're gonna start sniffing people,
I'm gonna go get a hot pretzel.
Excuse me.
Do you have any books
about making friends?
Yeah, but they're all
for little kids.
I assume the skills can be
extrapolated and transferred.
I guess.
They're right over there
by the wooden train set.
I love trains.
I bet you do.
My, that's awfully sticky.
All right, let's see...
Bernie Bunny Has Two Daddies Now.
That's probably
about homosexual rabbits.
Gerry the Gerbil
and the Bullies on the Bus.
Read it. Not helpful.
Here we go.
Stu the Cockatoo Is New at the Zoo.
"Author Sarah Carpenter
lives in Fort Wayne, Indiana
"with her husband
and best friend, Mark,
and their cockatoo Stu."
Hardly makes her an expert
in making friends, wouldn't you agree?
I don't like birds. They scare me.
Me, too.
Most people don't see it.
- What are you reading?
- Curious George.
I do like monkeys.
Curious George is a monkey.
Somewhat anthropomorphized, but yes.
Say,
maybe sometime you and I
could go see monkeys together.
- Would you like that?
- Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm making friends
with this little girl.
- What's your name?
- Rebecca.
Hi, Rebecca.
I'm your new friend, Sheldon.
No, you're not. Let's go.
- We were really hitting it off.
- Don't look up. There's cameras.
I'm curious. In the "How well do
you know Sheldon" section,
what did you put
for his favorite amino acid?
Lysine.
Damn it, I had lysine
and changed it.
Good, you're just in time.
I believe I've isolated
the algorithm for making friends.
Sheldon, there is no algorithm
for making friends.
Hear him out.
If he's really onto something,
we could open a booth at Comic-Con.
Make a fortune.
See, my initial approach to Kripke
had the same deficiencies
as those that plagued Stu the Cockatoo
when he was new at the zoo.
Stu the Cockatoo?
He's new at the zoo.
It's a terrific book.
I've distilled its essence
into a simple flow chart
that will guide me
through the process.
Have you thought about
putting him in a crate
while you're out of the apartment?
Hello, Kripke? Sheldon Cooper here.
It occurred to me
you hadn't returned any of my calls
because I hadn't offered
any concrete suggestions
for pursuing our friendship.
Perhaps the two of us might
share a meal together.
I see.
Well, then perhaps you'd have
time for a hot beverage?
Popular choices include
tea, coffee, cocoa.
I see.
No, wait. Don't hang up yet.
What about a recreational activity?
I bet we share
some common interests.
Tell me an interest of yours.
Really?
On actual horses?
Tell me another interest of yours.
I'm sorry. I have no desire to get
in the water till I absolutely have to.
Tell me another interest of yours.
- He's stuck in an infinite loop.
- I can fix it.
Interesting, but isn't ventriloquism
by definition a solo activity?
Tell me another interest of yours.
Is there any chance
you like monkeys?
What is wrong with you?
Everybody likes monkeys.
Hang on, Kripke.
A loop counter
and an escape
to the least objectionable activity.
Howard, that's brilliant.
I'm surprised you saw that.
Gee, why can't Sheldon make friends?
All right, Kripke, that last interest
strikes me as the least objectionable,
and I would like to propose
that we do that together.
Tomorrow.
Yes, I'll pay.
All right, good-bye.
All right.
Time to learn rock climbing.
You know, I am a fan
of ventriloquism.
Maybe you, me and your dummy
could go get a hot beverage.
He could talk while you drink.
Nope. I wanna climb some rocks.
This appears significantly
more monolithic
than it did on my laptop.
One expects to see hominids
learning to use bones as weapons.
- You afraid of heights, Cooper?
- Hardly.
A fear of heights is illogical.
A fear of falling, on the other hand,
is prudent and evolutionary.
What would you say is
the minimum altitude I need to achieve
to cement our newfound friendship?
They have birthday parties here.
Little kids climb this.
Little kid hominids perhaps.
So is this your entire job?
Your parents must be so proud.
- Let's go, Cooper.
- I'm coming, Kripke.
The harness seems to be secure.
A small amount of incontinence
just now,
but the Web site said
that's to be expected.
This isn't so bad.
It's like vertical swimming.
Look at you.
- You're almost halfway to the top.
- I am?
I was wrong.
It is a fear of heights.
- You all right there, Cooper?
- Not really.
I feel somewhat like
an inverse tangent function
that's approached an asymptote.
- Are you saying you're stuck?
- What part of inverse tangent function
approaching an asymptote
did you not understand?
I understood all of it.
I'm not a moron.
Just keep going.
- Yeah, I don't think I can.
- Well, then climb back down.
No, that doesn't seem
any more likely.
What's your plan?
Well, it's not exactly a plan,
but I think I'm going to pass out.
Sorry, can we please
just do it one more time?
One, two, one, two, three, and...
It's a little thing,
but you really do miss it.
Hello, everyone.
I brought my new friend
Barry Kripke home for dinner.
Hello to you, too.
- How was rock climbing?
- He passed out.
Just hung there like a big salami.
That's where I sit.
You have a special spot?
What kind of wacko are you?
How much time you got?
You want some Chinese food?
Terrific. Got any dental floss?
In the bathroom.
Be right back.
I got to floss the Indian food
out of my teeth
if I'm gonna eat Chinese.
Sheldon, are you okay?
Yes, I pass out all the time,
but it was worth it.
I've made substantial progress
in bonding with Kripke,
which brings me
to an awkward moment.
What's that?
Maintaing five friendships
promises to be
a Herculean task, so...
I'm going to have
to let one of you go.
Me, me, let it be me.
Leonard, you are my roommate,
my source of transportation,
and you help me fold my sheets
when they come out of the dryer.
You are safe.
- Can I whistle?
- Don't be silly.
You do not have a PhD;
your cologne is
an assault on the senses;
and you're not available for video games
during the Jewish high holidays.
Guilty as charged. I'm out.
You too are safe.
Come on. What do I have to do?
Okay, you know what?
I see where this is going.
I'm not one of you guys.
I'm not a scientist, so just tell me...
Everything you're saying is true,
but please allow me to continue.
You're out.
That's a good question.
While you do provide
a certain cultural diversity
to an otherwise homogenous group,
your responses to the questionnaire
were truly disturbing.
How could you for a moment think
my favorite amino acid is glutamine?
He had lysine, but changed it.
Shoulda, woulda, coulda, Raj.
I like to floss before I eat
so my gum pockets are open
for new food.
How did I walk past you?
I'm Barry.
That's not a very hot name.
I'm going to call you Roxanne.
Pot stickers.
Suddenly, I'm looking
pretty good, huh?
So, Kripke, I was wondering
if there's any chance
you could get me some time
on the open science grid computer?
But we're friends.
I'm sorry.
No, my friend.
I'm confused.
I was given to understand
that you allow your friends
time on the machine.
No, that's wrong.
There's an official schedule.
I have no control over it.
This entire endeavor seems
to have been an exercise in futility.
Raj, you're back in.
He likes monkeys.
You've got to give him credit
for sticking with it.
I didn't think he had it in him.
And he almost made it
to the top this time.
www.tvsubtitles.net