Smell that?
That's the smell of new comic books.
They're on me today, boys.
You're paying?
Have you been selling
your sperm again?
No, I'm celebrating.
As we speak,
the space shuttle is docking
at the International Space Station
where it will deploy the Wolowitz
Zero-Gravity Waste Disposal System.
Get over yourself.
It's a high-tech toilet.
Just think. Thanks to your hard work,
an international crew of astronauts
will "boldly go
where no man has gone before."
- Is that supposed to be funny?
- I believe it is.
The combination of
the Star Trek reference
and the play on words involving
the double-meaning of the verb "to go"
suggests that Leonard is mocking
your efforts in space plumbing.
Okay, make your little jokes,
but of the four of us,
I'm the only one making
any real-world contribution
to science and technology.
He's right. This is an important
achievement, for two reasons.
Number one...
and, of course, number two!
Clever!
Playing on the use
of cardinal numbers
as euphemisms for bodily functions.
Here, Sheldon,
I pulled the new Hellboy for you.
It's mind-blowing.
Excuse me.
Spoiler alert.
I didn't spoil anything.
You told me it's mind-blowing.
So, my mind is going into it
pre-blown.
And once a mind is pre-blown,
it cannot be re-blown.
I'm sorry.
Said the Grinch to Christmas.
- Can I talk to you about something?
- What's up?
Remember I went out with Penny,
a couple weeks ago?
- Yeah, vaguely.
- Sure you remember.
You went to the bar
and made a fool of yourself
trying to pick up strange women.
What about it?
The thing is,
the date didn't go that well.
Too bad.
I guess the thing to do now
is just pick yourself up,
dust yourself off,
forget it and move on.
- I can't do that.
- Why the hell not?
'Cause we're going out
again tomorrow.
Excuse me, Stuart.
Have you read the new Flash?
Well, I have
and it will knock your socks off!
Good luck getting them back on.
This is probably my last shot with Penny
and I don't want to screw it up.
Nobody wants that.
So, here's my question:
It's the second date,
you think she'll be expecting things
to get physical?
Gee...
My initial reaction is "no,"
but let me think about it
and get back to you.
So, you'll give me a call?
- Yeah, or you call me.
- Great.
Or nobody calls anyone.
Interesting.
Penny's current suitor asking advice
from her former suitor.
You know, thanks
for closed-captioning my pain, Raj.
Hey, wanna make sure
he gets nowhere with Penny
without jeopardizing your friendship
with either of them?
I'm listening.
Just tell him to do everything
you've done with her
for the last two years.
Subtitles: The FW Team
- How's it going?
- Good, good. You?
Fine.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
You know your friend Stuart?
He asked me out again
and I said yes,
and then I started thinking
maybe I should talk to you first.
About what?
Does it bother you,
me going out with one of your friends?
'Cause you know, you and me...
No, that's the past.
I'm really more
of a "right now" kind of guy.
You know, living in the moment.
Although I do have to live a little
in the future, 'cause that's my job.
Of course, my fondness
for classic science fiction
does draw my attention backwards,
but those stories often
take place in the future.
In conclusion, no,
it doesn't bother me.
Okay, well,
that's really cool of you.
I wouldn't say cool.
I'd just say... "That's Leonard!"
In that case,
do you mind giving me some advice?
About Stuart?
Love to.
He's very shy.
How do I make him feel
more comfortable around me?
First of all, don't underestimate
the value of discomfort.
Really?
Stuart thrives under pressure.
That's why he works in
a comic book store.
It's Stuart.
You're not going to answer it?
He wants to talk about Penny.
I don't want to talk about Penny.
You're making an assumption.
Perhaps the comic book store
is on fire.
And he needs your assistance.
Why would he call me?
We don't know.
And if you don't answer the phone,
we can't know.
I'm not answering the phone.
Answer the phone, Leonard.
There, it went to voice mail.
Aren't you going to check
your messages?
You have to check your messages!
The living of a message
is one half of a social contract
which is completed by the
checking of the message.
If that contract breaks down,
then all social contracts break down
and we descend into anarchy.
It must be hell inside your head.
At times.
Guys, we have a code red.
"Code Red" the hospital emergency alert,
the computer worm,
or the cherry-flavored soft drink
from the makers of Mountain Dew?
Look, I was going over the schematics
on my zero-G toilet,
and I made a teeny tiny mistake
on the specifications
for the diverter valve.
How teeny tiny?
It's gonna fail
after about ten flushes.
- But the mission is for six months.
- See, that's the code red.
It's kind of like a jack-in-the-box.
No one knows exactly when,
but at some point
something way worse than a puppet
is gonna pop out of that box.
Have you notified NASA?
Are you crazy?
What am I gonna say?
"I screwed up your toilet
and there's gonna be crap floating
"all over your nice
shiny space station"?
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna figure out how to fix it,
then I'll tell them.
So, what do you need us for?
He can't figure out how to fix it.
You said you were
gonna be supportive.
I'm trying, but you have to admit
this is pretty damn funny.
I agree.
It's the juxtaposition of the high-tech
nature of space exploration
against the banality
of a malfunctioning toilet
that provides the comic fodder here.
Check your messages.
All right,
this is an exact duplicate
of the Wolowitz Zero-Gravity
Human Waste Disposal System
as deployed on the
International Space Station.
Don't you mean the Wolowitz Zero-Gravity
Human Waste Distribution System?
Good one.
It's hilarious. Now...
Here's an approximation
of the spare parts
available on the Space Station.
We gotta find a way,
using nothing but this,
to reinforce this so the waste material
avoids the spinning turbine.
You mean so it doesn't hit the fan?
I have to say,
I thought the toilet humor would
get less funny with repetition.
Apparently, there is no law
of diminishing comedic returns
with space poop.
You busy?
Classified, Leonard.
Yeah, it's a regular
Manhattan Project.
What's up?
Tonight's my date with Penny
and since we haven't been able
to connect by phone...
I'm sorry, it's been broken.
- Or e-mail.
- Yeah, that too. Everything's broken.
Anyway, I was just wondering
if you had any last-minute advice.
All right, well,
off the top of my head,
I think the most important thing
with Penny is to go really slow.
I mean, glacial.
Guys come onto her all the time,
so, you need to set yourself apart.
Be a little shy,
don't make too much eye contact.
And, you know, treat her
with, like, cool detachment
and-and, you know, fear.
- Fear?
- Yeah, like,
you're afraid
that if you touch her, she'll break.
Well, that plays
right into my wheelhouse.
Good, good.
You kids have fun tonight.
Thanks, Leonard.
What is that thing anyway?
You don't know what this is?
Good. Get out.
Be afraid of Penny.
Nice. Very crafty.
It wasn't bad advice.
It's just wasn't particularly helpful.
For what it's worth, my mother says
that when we deceive
for personal gain,
we make Jesus cry.
All right, what if we use
this two-inch PVC
- to reinforce the center cross-support?
- No good.
It might work for the Japanese
and the Americans,
but have you seen the size
of the Russians they got up there?
This thing has to hold up
against a hearty potato-based diet.
I feel terrible.
Maybe if you were helping,
you'd feel better about yourself.
I deliberately tried
to sabotage Stuart's date with Penny.
Of course you feel terrible.
You completely screwed up your karma.
You don't really believe
in that superstition, do you?
It's not superstition.
It's practically Newtonian.
For every action,
there's an equal and opposite reaction.
Leonard pretends to be a friend
and acts like a two-faced bitch.
Therefore, he is reborn
as a banana slug.
It's actually a very elegant system.
You know, what goes around comes around.
Speaking of what goes around
comes around...
Okay, look.
Instead of trying to reinforce
this structure here,
what if we just ran another line,
bypass it entirely?
It won't work. The diameter
of the tubing is insufficient.
What if we reposition
the collection tank?
It won't work. No way to mount it.
Okay, here's an idea.
What if I change my name and go live
with my cousin and her husband, Avi,
in Israel?
That could work.
- Morning.
- Morning. What's up?
Nothing. We just pulled an all-nighter
trying to fix a zero-gravity...
pasta maker.
I'm gonna make a coffee run.
Do you want any?
No, thanks. I have coffee.
Great. So how'd it go
with Stuart last night?
I really don't want
to talk about it.
Yeah. Right. Sure.
The thing is,
before you guys went out,
I spoke to him and...
I said I don't want
to talk about it.
I just... I kind of...
What goes on between me and Stuart
is none of your business.
So just leave it alone, okay?
If you want to clean up your karma,
go get my freakin' latte.
Hang on, I think I've got this.
Help me see if we can wedge
this little piece of PVC
behind the support rod.
You're overestimating
the tensile strength
of the substructure you're building.
Sheldon, I know what I'm doing.
If you knew what you were doing,
there wouldn't be a space toilet
where my coffee table should be.
Howard, wait.
Why don't you use this
instead of the PVC
to keep the transverse
filter assembly in place?
Because this is not a spare part
from the space station.
This is the thing from the pizza box
that keeps the lid
from touching the cheese.
That what that's for?
In India, the lid touches the cheese.
Of course, we also have rampant poverty
and periodic outbreaks of cholera,
so a little cardboard in our cheese
is no biggie.
- Where are you going?
- Comic book store.
An excellent idea!
I could certainly use a break.
- Me, too.
- You can go to the comic book store
when man can once again
safely poop in space.
Why does Leonard get to go?
'Cause he's upset
over his situation with Penny
and if I have to hear about it again,
I'm going to kick him in his ovaries.
- Thanks for understanding, Howard.
- I got your back, sister.
All right, I think we've got
a prototype ready to test.
Hand me that Tupperware.
That's heavy.
Damn right it's heavy.
It's my mother's meat loaf.
It's been testing toilets
for generations.
I must say,
I think a detailed letter to MIT
describing your current circumstances
might entitle you
to a refund on your master's degree.
Okay, simulated zero-gravity
human waste disposal test
with meat loaf analog in...
three, two, one.
Fascinating.
What do you think the problem is?
Not enough bread crumbs.
Hey, Stuart, I need to talk to you.
- Sure, what's up?
- I gave you bad advice about Penny,
- and I want to apologize.
- No, your advice was great.
- It was?
- Yeah, going slow really worked.
You're kidding.
Never worked for me.
Last night at dinner,
I did what you told me.
I went really slow,
I kept my distance,
and two bottles of wine later,
we were making out in my car.
Wine? I didn't say to give her wine.
It doesn't matter,
that's where it all went to hell.
During the kissing?
What did you do, sneeze in her mouth?
I did that to a girl once.
No, everything was good
and really hot.
And I said,
"Oh, Penny,"
and right where she was supposed to say,
"Oh, Stuart," she said...
your name.
That is your name, right?
I'm sorry. That must've been
the last thing you wanted to hear.
It beats,
"You know I'm a dude, right?"
Yeah, it was pretty bad.
No doubt, no doubt.
I'm sorry it didn't work out.
Not your fault.
Yeah, how about that?
- See you soon.
- Sure.
Yes, sir, I understand "classified."
We'll keep it all classified;
no one has to know but you and me.
What's classified?
Howard's space toilet.
I'll tell you later.
Well, they've deployed our solution.
Let's just all hope it works.
I don't see why I have to worry.
My career's not hanging
in the balance.
That was a joke.
It's funny,
because it's true.
Leonard, could you pass
the soy sauce, please?
I'm sorry, were you talking to me?
Yeah, I said "Leonard."
Yes, you did, didn't you?
What the hell is that?
Meatloaf.
What was it doing on the ceiling?
That's classified.
Houston,
International Space Station.
We have a little situation up here.
We'd like to make
an unscheduled space walk.
I.S.S., Houston.
Which crew members would be
involved in this E.V.A.?
Houston, we'd all like
to step outside for a few minutes.
I.S.S., I'm afraid
we can't authorize that.
Houston,
this is more of an FYI call.
We are basically out the door.
www.tvsubtitles.net