Oh, boy.
What?
I can't comment
without violating our agreement
that I not criticize your work.
Then what was "Oh, boy"?
Great restraint on my part.
There's nothing wrong
with the science here.
Perhaps you mean a different thing
than I do when you say, "Science."
How's that?
You actually had it right
in the first place.
Once again, you've fallen
for one of my classic pranks.
Bazinga!
Now here's a peculiar e-mail.
The president of the university
wants me to meet him
at his office
tomorrow morning at 8:00 a.m.
- Why?
- It doesn't say.
It must be an emergency.
Everyone at the university
knows I eat breakfast at 8:00
and move my bowels at 8:20.
Yes, how did we live before Twitter?
I guess you'll find out
what it is in the morning.
That's 14 hours away.
For the next 840 minutes,
I'm effectively one
of Heisenberg's particles;
I know where I am
or I know how fast I'm going,
but I can't know both.
Yet how am I supposed to carry on
with this huge annoying thing
hovering over my head?
I know the feeling.
Subtitles: The FW Team
Sheldon, it's 2:00 in the morning.
Why does everybody keep telling me
what time it is?
- Everybody?
- You, the president of the university,
his wife,
their sullen teenage daughter.
That entire family is fascinated
by what time it is
and whether people know it.
You went to President Seibert's house
in the middle of the night?
He didn't respond to my e-mail,
his phone number is unlisted.
Tell me what my other option was.
You could have waited until morning.
I know, look who I'm talking to.
Do you remember
the grant proposal I submitted
to the National Science Foundation
to detect slow-moving monopoles
at the magnetic North Pole?
Hardly a day goes by
when I don't think about it.
How nice.
Well, a space opened up
at the last minute on the NSF
expedition to the Arctic Circle.
Wait a minute.
He offered to send you
to the North Pole?
In fact, he was quite enthusiastic.
He said, "Frankly,
if I could send you tonight, I would."
Okay, well, do you want to go?
Of course not.
I'm a theoretical physicist.
A career I chose in no small part
because it's indoors,
but if I'm able to detect
slow-moving magnetic monopoles there,
I will be the scientis
to confirm string theory.
People will write books about me.
Third-graders will create
macaroni-art dioramas
depicting scenes from my life.
Sure, maybe a tableau of me
trying to pummel you to death.
Sarcasm?
Maybe.
I'm on the horns of a dilemma.
Can you imagine me, Sheldon
Cooper, at the North Pole?
Easy peasy, I'm doing it right now.
I'm not good with cold.
How often have we had
to leave a movie theater
because I got a headache
from drinking the Icee too fast?
- I can't go.
- Then don't go.
How can you say that?
The scientific opportunity
of a lifetime
presents itself
and my best friend says "Don't go."
- All right, then go.
- Listen to you.
How can I possibly go?
What are the words
I can say right now
to end this conversation
and let me go back to sleep?
Odd, President Seibert posed
the exact same question.
- How was it resolved?
- It wasn't.
His wife set their dogs on me
and rendered the question moot.
Just imagine.
If he says yes,
we'll have an entire summer
without Sheldon.
We could play outside.
We could sit
on the left side of the couch.
I could use the bathroom at 8:20.
Our dreams are very small,
aren't they?
Good news, gentlemen,
I have tentatively accepted...
... the invitation to join
the Arctic Expedition.
It's not gonna be the same
without you.
Thank you,
but your sentiments may be premature.
I don't like where this is going.
I would like to propose...
that the three of you accompany me.
To the North Pole?
Is this just so we won't touch
your stuff while you're away?
I'll admit that was a concern.
But the fact is,
I'll need a support team.
And the three of you
are my first choice.
Really?
There are others
who might be more qualified,
but the thought of interviewing
them gave me a stomachache.
I know I'm proposing
an enormous undertaking.
So, why don't you take
a few moments to discuss it?
We're not really gonna go
to the North Pole with him, are we?
I'm still within earshot!
You may want to wait
for my door to close.
We're not really gonna go
to the North Pole with him, are we?
Hang on. Let's talk about it.
This is a National Science
Foundation expedition.
I don't know how
we can turn it down.
Easy. Instead of saying, "No, we
don't want to go on an NSF expedition,"
say, "No, we don't want to spend
"three months stuck in a cabin in
the Arctic Circle with an anal nutbag."
But if we were part of the team
that confirmed string theory,
we could drink for free
in any bar in any college town
with a university
that has a strong science program.
Howard, this is big science.
You could be the engineer
who builds the equipment
that puts us on the cover
of magazines.
I could also be the engineer
who builds the crossbow
that kills Sheldon.
You still might get on a magazine.
So you guys are seriously
considering this?
- You think you can put up with Sheldon?
- Well, I'm a Hindu.
My religion teaches
that if we suffer in this life
we are rewarded in the next.
Three months
at the North Pole with Sheldon,
and I'm reborn as a well-hung
billionaire with wings!
Well, gentlemen,
have you reached a decision?
- I'm in.
- Me, too.
Damn it. Peer pressure. Fine.
Excellent.
Just an FYI,
as I am
the expedition's team leader,
protocol dictates
that be phrased, "Fine, sir."
But don't worry,
there will be a briefing.
What do you want?
I need access to the Cheesecake
Factory's walk-in freezer.
Honey, I already told you,
the hamburger meat is fresh
and stored at a safe temperature.
This is to train
for a three-month expedition
to the magnetic North Pole.
What?
I don't know how that sentence
could possibly confuse you...
but to elaborate,
I'm going to the Arctic Circle
with Leonard, Wolowitz
and Koothrappali.
- You're all going?
- Yes.
- For three months?
Excuse me.
Is that a yes or a no
on the freezer?
That woman has
the attention span of a gnat.
Sheldon says you're going
to the North Pole.
Pretty cool, huh?
Yeah. I'm just a little surprised
you didn't tell me.
It all happened kind of fast.
And we had to get physicals
and buy thermal underwear
and study up on, you know,
snow and stuff.
Sorry, I was gonna tell you.
You don't have to apologize.
There's no reason you have to tell me.
I was just...
you know, surprised.
You were busy, you were surprised,
all very fascinating.
Now where do we stand
on the freezer?
- Is he serious?
- Actually, it would help.
All right, I'll see what I can do.
So, three months at the North Pole.
That is... awesome.
I'm sorry, but at what point
do you put this
"see what you can do" plan
into action?
Just a warning, Sheldon...
The freezer locks from the outside.
Did she seem upset to you?
Good, I got it right.
Are you upset?
- A little bit.
- Two for two. I'm on fire.
I know she's not
my girlfriend or anything,
but wouldn't you think
she'd feel a little bad
that I'm going to be gone
for the whole summer?
That feels like a bonus question.
I'm going to stop here while I'm ahead,
but I've had a great time.
All right,
the purpose of this drill
is to acclimate us
to the use of tools
in extreme temperatures
such as we will face
in the Arctic Circle.
Where are your tools?
Right here.
All right, team,
open up your practice kits.
As the university did not permit me
to bring the actual equipment
we'll be using
to the Cheesecake Factory,
because apparently,
I'm "ridiculous,"
I've provided substitutes which
will exercise your fine motor skills.
Leonard, you will be doing a series
of complex mathematical problems
on a vintage Casio model
1175 calculator watch I received
when I won the Earth Science medal
in 3rd grade.
Treat it with respect.
Raj, you will be painting
sideburns and a Van Dyke
on a six-inch figurine
of Legolas the elf.
Now, remember, a Van Dyke
is a goatee without a mustache.
Wolowitz, you will be completing
a series of delicate
surgical procedures
on the classic children's game
"Operation."
To begin with, you will
"remove funny bone
for two hundred dollars."
For this I went to MIT.
And begin.
I think I swallowed some paint!
I can't press
any of the buttons with my gloves.
Son of a bitch!
Adversity is to be expected.
Continue.
Oh, boy, am I gonna get sued.
- Okay, I can't do this.
- Me either.
Gentlemen, use your imagination.
Innovate.
Did Han Solo let Luke Skywalker freeze
to death on the ice planet of Hoth?
He cut open a tauntaun
and used its internal body heat
to warm him up.
You heard the man.
Hold him down and I'll cut him open.
Hang on, I know I don't possess
the tools of leadership,
but why can't we assemble the equipment
inside the hut and then take it outside?
I hadn't thought of that.
I guess we're done here.
Here,
drink slash eat this.
- What is it?
- Hot chocolate with a stick of butter.
Okay, why?
In the frigid temperatures
in the Arctic,
we need to consume at least
5,000 calories a day
just to maintain our body weight.
You know I can't eat butter.
I'm lactose intolerant.
Way ahead of you, that's an
"I Can't Believe It's Not Butter" stick.
But Mummy, all the other guys
are going to the North Pole.
I don't care
what the other guys are doing.
If the other guys jumped
in the Bay of Bengal
and tried to swim to Sri Lanka,
would you follow them?
If you were standing
behind me nagging, I might.
Don't talk back to your mother.
This trip is much too dangerous.
No, it's not. Howard, tell them.
Doctor and Mrs. Koothrappali,
namaste.
I understand your concern,
but if it'll make you feel any better,
my mother is fine with me going,
and it's a woman who kept a safety rail
on my bed until I was 17.
So, she has no problem
with her son being eaten by a walrus?
That's very unlikely,
Mrs. Koothrappali.
If Raj dies,
it'll be from frostbite,
gangrene, acute sunburn
or being ripped to shreds
by a 1,500 pound polar bear.
Ma, I'm putting you on speakerphone
with Raj's parents.
Can you tell them that you're okay
with me going to the Arctic?
Arctic?!
I thought you said Arkansas!
I didn't say that.
You never listen to me!
He doesn't tell me anything!
He lives a secret life
because he's ashamed!
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Sure, but let's go out here
where there's a little
less yelling and guilt.
What's up?
Well, I got you
a little going away present.
- A blanket.
- No, not just a blanket.
See, it has sleeves.
So, you can be all snoodled up
while you do your science stuff.
Cool.
I'm gonna miss you.
- See you later.
- Bye.
I told you no!
Why don't you believe me?
'Cause it doesn't make sense to me!
How can it be
that in the entire country of India,
there isn't one Outback Steakhouse?!
I want a cookie, Meemaw.
It's me.
But Meemaw just made cookies.
I don't know if I can go
on the expedition.
What?
I don't think I can go
to the North Pole.
I know you're concerned
about disappointing me
but I want you to take comfort
from the knowledge
that my expectations
of you are very low.
Yeah, that's very comforting.
Comforting is a part of leadership.
It's not a part I care for,
but such is my burden.
Terrific, it's just that...
I don't think Penny wants me to go.
Assuming that's a valid reason
not to go, which it isn't...
How do you know this?
Did she say it?
Not exactly.
But she said she was gonna miss me
and she gave me this.
- What is it?
- It's a blanket with sleeves.
That's clever.
Let me see
if I understand correctly.
Her missing you
is an emotional state
you find desirable?
Yes, obviously.
Well, given that missing you
is predicated on you leaving,
logic dictates you must leave.
Yes, okay, but I'm gonna be gone
for three months.
What if she doesn't miss me that long
and she meets someone else?
She does have
a short attention span.
So, I can't go.
Leonard, you may be right.
It appears that Penny
secretly wants you in her life
in a very intimate
and carnal fashion.
- You really think so?
- Of course not.
Even in my sleep-deprived state,
I've managed to pull off
another one of my classic pranks.
Bazinga!
- What time is it?
- It's 7:00 a.m. I'm sorry it's early,
but we're leaving soon,
and I needed to talk to you.
What did you mean when you said
you were going to miss me?
I don't know.
You'll be gone and I'll notice.
What about this?
What does this mean?
Wine, credit card
and late night television
are a bad combination.
All right, fine.
What about that really long hug?
What did that mean?
That wasn't a long hug.
It was at least five Mississippis.
A standard hug is
two Mississippis tops.
Leonard, I don't know what to tell you.
It was just a hug.
- Glad we cleared that up.
- Yeah.
I guess I'll see you.
- Okay, have a safe trip.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Okay, bye.
It means I wish you weren't going.
- Damn it.
- What?
We're out of ice.
All right, we begin initial assembly
and deployment of the testing equipment
starting tomorrow at 0700 hours,
but until then,
you are all off duty.
I suggest you keep
the shenanigans to a minimum
as medical help is
18 hours away by dogsled.
- What are you working on?
- Crossbow.
Hey, guys, can I just say something?
How about we take a moment
to think about where we are right now?
This is literally
the top of the world.
Only a handful of people
in all of human history
will ever see
what we are going to see.
He's right.
It is remarkable.
So, who's up for a movie?
Good idea, what do you think?
Ice Station Zebra
or John Carpenter's The Thing?
- I say double feature.
- Dinner's ready!
- What are we having?
- Reconstituted Thai food.
Did you bring the dehydrated
low-sodium soy sauce?
- Freeze-dried spicy mustard?
- Check.
Flash-frozen brown rice, not white?
Sorry.
Not to worry.
I hid it.
Bazinga!
You're in my spot.
There's no time for a crossbow.
Find me an icicle.
Three months.
This is gonna be great.
www.tvsubtitles.net