Knight to queen's bishop-five.
Very nice.
What's Leonard going to do?
Give up the pawn
or give up the position?
Let's find out.
Ready?
Ready.
Go.
Damn it. I slipped.
Too bad. You know the rules
of Secret Agent Laser Obstacle Chess.
Leonard died again,
Sheldon. You're up.
Despite my deep love of chess,
lasers and aerosol disinfectant,
I must forfeit.
- Why?
- Because it's almost 11:00.
So?
Penny has a "don't knock
on my door before 11:00
or I punch you in the throat" rule.
You know what'd be a great idea?
We get some girls over here
and play Laser Optical Strip Chess.
Believe me, any girl
who would be willing to play that,
you don't want to see naked.
You underestimate me.
Hey, Sheldon.
- It's 11:00 a.m.
- I know. You're safe.
This package came
while you were at work.
Great, my rhinestones.
Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- What?
You have to sign this.
- What is it?
- When I signed for the package,
I was deputized
by the United Parcel Service
and entrusted with its final delivery.
I now need you to acknowledge
receipt of the package so that I'm
fully indemnified and no longer liable.
It's just a box of rhinestones.
The contents are irrelevant.
A legal bailment has been created.
Does that mean nothing to you?
It means nothing to anybody.
- Let me show you what I'm doing.
- "Bailment" describes a relationship
in common law where a physical
possession of personal property,
or "chattels," is transferred
from one person, the bailor,
to another person, the bailee...
Look, look!
I started a business.
Obviously, not a cleaning business.
No, I'm making flower barrettes.
See?
I call them Penny Blossoms.
I made one for myself,
then all the girls at work wanted one.
I showed some to this lady
who runs a shop in Old Town.
She sells cards and homemade jewelry.
She said she wanted to sell them.
I said, "Okay."
And in one week, I made a $156.
Good for you. Sign here.
Don't you get it? If this takes off,
I won't have to be a waitress anymore.
But then who will bring me
my cheeseburger on Tuesday nights?
- Another waitress.
- What's her name?
I don't know.
And you're going to let her
handle my food?
Nancy. Her name is Nancy.
I think you're just making that up.
I'm sorry about your hamburger.
I just don't want to be a waitress
for the rest of my life.
Cheeseburger.
I get a cheeseburger.
- Fine, cheeseburger.
- Maybe I'd be better off with Nancy.
So, what do you think?
I mean, this could be a business, right?
How many of these
can you make a day?
About 20.
And how much profit do you make per...
Penny Blossom?
Like, 50 cents. I'm not sure.
Of course you're not.
All right...
Ten dollars a day
times five days a week
times 52 weeks a year is $2,600.
- That's all?
- Before taxes.
I don't have to pay taxes
on this stuff.
I believe the Internal Revenue Service
would strongly disagree.
But, if you took advantage
of modern marketing techniques,
and you optimized
your manufacturing process,
you might be able to make
this a viable business.
And you know about that stuff?
I'm a physicist.
I have a working knowledge
of the entire universe
and everything it contains.
Who's Radiohead?
I have a working knowledge
of the important things in the universe.
- Good luck.
- Sheldon, hold on.
Could you maybe show me how
to make more money with this?
Of course I could.
Wait!
Will you?
Just to be clear here,
you're asking for my assistance.
And you understand that will involve
me telling you what to do?
I understand.
And you're not allowed to be sarcastic
or snide to me while I'm doing so.
Good.
Let's begin with the premise
that everything you've done
up to this point is wrong.
- Oh, imagine that.
- Sarcasm. Good-bye.
No, sorry. Wait!
Please come back!
Subtitles: The FW Team
- There. Done.
- All right.
12 minutes and 17 seconds.
- Pretty good, right?
- That's 4.9 Penny Blossoms per hour.
Based on your cost of materials
and your wholesale selling price,
you'll effectively be paying yourself...
$5.19 a day.
"A day"?
There are children in a sneaker factory
in Indonesia who outearn you.
That just can't be right.
- You're questioning my math?
- No, sorry.
- Want me to show my work?
- God, no.
Please tell me what to do about it.
All right. Are you familiar
with the development
that resulted from Honoré Blanc's
1778 use of interchangeable parts?
The assembly line, of course.
If I'm not allowed to be snide,
you're not allowed to be condescending.
That wasn't a part of our original
agreement, and I don't agree to it now.
Fine.
How are we supposed to set up machines
and conveyor belts in my apartment?
You're thinking of the moving
assembly line,
an understandable
but not excusable mistake.
The moving assembly line, that
was introduced by Henry Ford in 1908.
That innovation is what made possible
our modern consumer culture
by enabling a low-unit cost
for manufactured goods.
I guess that isn't one of the topics
discussed on your Radiohead.
Let's go. We're going to miss
the coming attractions.
What's the matter?
I think I bruised a testicle
capturing that last pawn.
Please pay attention
and listen to me
Give me some time
to blow the man down
I'm a deepwater sailor
just come from Hong Kong
To me way, hey,
blow the man down
If you give me some whiskey
I'll sing you a song
Give me some time
to blow the man down.
Hello?
Hello.
Come quickly lay aft
To the break of the poop
To me way, hey,
blow the man down
Or I'll help you along
with the toe of my boot
Give me some time
to blow the man down.
What's going on?
I assume you're referring
to the sea shanty.
It's a rhythmic work song
designed to increase productivity.
It's crazy, but it totally works.
We made this Penny Blossom
in under three minutes.
Terrific, but that kind of raises
more questions than it answers.
Penny's making hair accessories.
I'm helping her optimize
her manufacturing process.
Break's over.
Pay attention to orders
now you one and all...
Hold on. What are you
using as a bonding agent?
- Hot glue.
- You're kidding.
Any of the cyanoacrylates
would do a better job.
The flower's too porous.
What if we infused the bottom layer
with silicone-RTV to provide
a better mounting surface?
Intriguing.
What are your marketing
and distribution channels?
There are the waitresses at my work,
and this cute, little shop in Old Town.
Virtually non-existent.
I'm thinking that we set her up with
a hosted e-commerce system to start.
Why not eliminate the middle man?
We could install a small server farm
with a static IP in her bedroom.
With an industrial cooling system.
Of course, but before we set up
marketing and distribution,
we should finish optimizing
the manufacturing process.
To start with,
she has a terrible problem
with moisture-induced glitter clump.
Yeah, it's a bitch.
I've seen this before.
- Where?
- It's a common stripper problem.
They dance, they sweat, they clump.
Are you thinking about adding
a desiccant like calcium sulfate?
Actually, I'm thinking
about this one stripper named Vega.
But sure, calcium sulfate
could work.
Let's think
out of the box for a moment.
How about a molecular sieve?
I've got a spaghetti strainer
in the kitchen.
We could liberate some micro-porous
charcoal from the chem lab.
Great.
Raj, why don't you and Howard,
go get the charcoal?
Leonard, why don't you start working
on some preliminary Web site designs.
I'll make some space
in our apartment so we can move
the manufacturing process.
What's wrong with my apartment?
It's not my apartment.
Wait, what am I going to do?
It's your business.
Do whatever you want.
Okay, cool.
I'm going to take a nap.
I'm still tweaking things
a little bit,
but this will give you
the general idea of the Web site.
So, what do you guys think?
Pretty much any way I say that
is going to hurt his feelings.
- Okay, what's wrong with it?
- What's wrong with it?
Not you. I wasn't asking you.
Well, it's a little juvenile.
It kind of looks like the MySpace page
of a 13-year-old girl.
No, it doesn't.
Please. Dateline could use it
to attract predators.
This is your enterprise,
so it's ultimately your decision,
but based on the quality
of his work,
I'd strongly recommend
that we let Leonard go.
You want to fire me?
What I want is irrelevant.
This is Penny's decision.
Excuse me, but if I did such a bad job
then why do we already have orders?
We do?
Look.
Mrs. Fiona Fondell from Huntsville,
Alabama has ordered two.
No kidding. Two?
Look at the comments.
"Thank you, Penny Blossoms.
"These will be perfect
to cover my bald spot."
That is so sweet.
Camouflaging bald spots.
That's primarily a male concern.
Perhaps we could expand our market.
How are flower barrettes
going to appeal to men?
We add Bluetooth!
Brilliant. Men love Bluetooth.
Wait a minute, you want to make
a hair barrette with Bluetooth?
Everything is better with Bluetooth.
Holy crap. Someone just ordered
a thousand Penny Blossoms.
Get out!
Who needs a thousand
sparkly flower barrettes
with rhinestones?
"The Fifth Annual East
Rutherford, New Jersey,
Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
and Transgender Alliance Luau."
Another market to expand into...
balding gay men.
And I'll bet lesbians
love Bluetooth.
We should get to work.
Wait, why does it say
"one-day rush"?
Since when do we offer
a one-day rush?
Amazon offers one-day rush.
Yeah, but they don't have
to glue the books together.
How the hell are we going to make
a thousand Penny Blossoms in one day?
Don't yell at me. I'm not manufacturing.
I'm just Web design.
I'm gonna have to call them
and cancel the order.
Excuse me,
but was this not your goal?
Financial independence
through entrepreneurial
brilliance and innovation?
My brilliance and innovation,
of course, but still.
I just don't see
how we can pull this off.
That, right there,
that equivocation and self-doubt,
that is not the American spirit.
Did Davy Crockett quit at the Alamo?
Did Jim Bowie?
They didn't quit.
They were massacred...
by like a gazillion angry Mexicans.
Let me put it this way.
Your gross receipts
on this one order
will be over $3,000
for one night's work.
You guys get started.
- What are you doing?
- Going online to buy shoes!
She'll be coming round the mountain
when she comes
You know, if I wanted to spend
my Saturday nights doing this,
I could have stayed in India.
Stop with the fake third world crap.
Your father's a gynecologist.
And you had a house full of servants.
We only had four servants.
And two of them were children.
How we doing?
We have 128 assorted Penny Blossoms
ready to ship.
We're never gonna finish in time.
Who made Sheldon the boss anyway?
I believe I'm hearing some negativity
on the factory floor.
- So?
- Penny.
The labor force is a living organism
that must be carefully nurtured.
Any counterproductive grumbling
must be skillfully
headed off by management.
Observe.
Less talk, more work!
- Nicely done.
- Thank you.
You hear any union talk,
you let me know.
Someone's in the kitchen
with Dinah...
I know-ow-ow-ow
Someone's in the kitchen
with Dinah...
'Cause I sold my soul
to the company store
- Honey, do you want some coffee?
- I don't drink coffee.
But if you don't stay awake
we'll never finish in time.
Sorry, coffee's out of the question.
When I moved to California,
I promised my mother
that I wouldn't start doing drugs.
Leonard, help.
Sheldon, we still have 380
of these things to make.
I have complete faith
that you will make them.
Good night.
But, Sheldon,
without your insight and leadership,
this entire enterprise
will surely fail.
You're right, of course.
Here, this will help.
Very well,
but if this leads to opiates
or hallucinogenics,
you're going to have
to answer to my mother.
Look at Planck's Constant.
People say it's arbitrary.
It could not be less arbitrary.
If it varied slightly,
life as we know it would not exist.
Bam!
Now, now, let's reconsider
the entire argument,
but with entropy reversed
and effect preceding cause.
So you are thinking of a universe
that's not expanding from the center.
No, it is retreating from a...
from a possibility space.
This is a space
where we are all essentially
Alice through the looking glass,
standing in front of the Red Queen,
and we're being offered
a cracker to quench our thirst.
Of course, in another universe,
let's call it universe prime...
We should have let him go to bed.
I can't believe we actually did it.
1,000 friggin' Penny Blossoms.
I just want you guys to know
I am really grateful for your help.
And for ever dollar I make,
I'm going to give you 20 cents.
That's your entire profit margin.
Then never mind.
I'll print out the shipping label.
What?
We got an e-mail
from the East Rutherford, New Jersey,
Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
and Transgender Alliance.
They want
another thousand Penny Blossoms.
Really?
One-day rush.
I really need
to take that off the Web site.
Guess we'd better get started.
You can't be serious.
Come on.
What about the living organism
of the workforce
and the American spirit?!
And Jiminy Crockett at the Alamo?!
Davy Crockett.
Jiminy Crockett was a cricket.
Yes, I know that, okay? I'm tired.
I've had like 18 cups of coffee.
The point is,
if we just pull together...
We can do this.
Who's with me?
Although you may
find it hard to believe,
we do have lives.
Sorry.
My apologies to the gay community
of East Rutherford, New Jersey.
Where's the coffee?!
We're all out.
No problem.
I'll be back
before this banana hits the ground.
Sorry, guys, but Secret Agent
Laser Obstacle Lunch is just stupid.
www.tvsubtitles.net