What?
In life, there are
all sorts of wake-up calls.
But crowing on East 73rd Street
was one I was not prepared for.
It was my own fault.
I'd let my frenzy for a rent-controlled
apartment near Barneys,
override the fact that it was
animal-hospital adjacent.
That's the thing about New York - you
never know what's around the corner.
Or, in Samantha's case,
just outside your window.
There they were - Samantha's
neighborhood transsexual hookers.
Half man, half woman,
totally annoying.
Girl, she got herself
a handful with that one!
He was all up in my stuff once.
I told him to get that thing
out of my ass or I'll shit on it.
"Get that out my ass, or I'll shit on it. "
Is that the dirtiest thing ever?
Let's hope so!
I am paying to live in a neighborhood
that's trendy by day
and tranny by night.
- Tranny?
- Transsexuals. Chicks with dicks.
Boobs on top, balls down below.
- I don't get the appeal there.
- It's the other white meat.
I understand that pseudo-straight men
have to get laid, but not on my block.
I thought my chickens were bad.
Every morning at 4:00am they start.
It's like they're putting on a show.
The "Up-my-ass Players".
Too early for tranny talk?
It's so weird to be sitting here
eating omelet again
like nothing ever happened.
It was our first
Saturday morning breakfast
since Charlotte had left Trey,
her husband of three months.
I was married.
And now, what? I'm single again?
- You're not single, just separated.
- That's right.
I'll never be single again...
I'll be divorced.
The only thing worse than being 34
and single is being 34 and divorced.
Thanks.
I think it's worse to be 34 and trapped
in a marriage that doesn't work.
- Did I try hard enough?
- "Hard" is the word.
Sweetie, Trey has
an impotence problem...
I am so sick of talking about Trey.
I think and talk about Trey all the time.
Change the subject, please.
Talk about the "up my ass" stuff.
OK, here's the plan.
Sunday, we all come over, have
an unpacking party and no Trey-talk.
I'll bring the cocktails.
I'll bring the food.
How about roof-chicken?
Can I help you?
I live around the corner
and my window
looks over the roof
with the chickens and the crowing...
- Roosters.
- Excuse me?
They are roosters.
Roosters crow.
Yes, they do.
And very loudly.
Sorry. We just got them. Rescued
from a cockfight in the Bronx.
- My God.
- I'll move them to the basement.
You don't have to do that.
They had all that fight-trauma.
They need fresh air.
I don't want them to be miserable.
Don't worry.
They have a very lovely life.
That's all right. I'll get over it.
Thank you for being so nice.
Just gonna take one of these
for my friend. She has a cat.
Are you hungry?
Yeah?
I'm hungry too.
- Shanghai Garden. May I help you?
- I'd like to order some take-out.
- Address, please.
- 331 West 78th Street. Apartment 4F.
I'd like to order some chicken
with broccoli in a brown...
Brown sauce with brown rice.
Cold noodles.
I know. Every night the same.
Right.
The Chinese take-out lady
thinks I'm pathetic.
She said,
"Every night, the same thing. "
That's a tad bitchy for a take-out lady.
- Do you think I'm in a rut?
- A food-rut?
I'm sitting home with my cat, ordering
the same thing almost every night.
The only thing sadder would be
a Cathy Comic on my refrigerator.
Never say Cathy Comic to me again.
She giggled at me. The take-out lady.
Order from someplace else. There's
600 Chinese places on your block.
This place is my favorite. It's easier
than figuring out where else to go.
Then bear the take-out food shame.
There they were.
Our ex-boyfriends.
What are they doing together?
Are they friends now?
Apparently. This is bad.
What do you think
they are talking about? Their dogs?
Yeah, here's their conversation:
"How's your dog? Good, yours?
Was that the bitches
who ruined our lives?"
They didn't see us.
We have a choice. We can run
the other way or move in here.
We can't run.
These shoe-straps will break.
- How do I look?
- Good. Great!
You look great too.
Thank God I didn't wear
my drawstring pants.
Look who it is!
Another thing about New York -
who knows who is around the corner?
This is what I like about New York.
Street-traffic.
Well, look at you.
Look who it is, Pete.
My God!
Look how big he got.
He starts college next year.
You must be very proud.
Two beers at a time. Did we
give you guys a drinking problem?
They are not just for us.
I'll have nightmares
about that ladies room for weeks.
Carrie and Miranda,
this is Jessica and Susan.
Hello.
Honey, do you still wanna see
the movie or just crash?
I don't care.
- We have to go.
- Yeah, we gotta go.
It was good to see you, Aidan.
Come on, this way.
That night at Charlotte's - light
unpacking and heavy realisations.
Well, they're over us.
It's just so hilarious.
I'm hemorrhaging inside.
We thought they were pining
and they have new girlfriends already!
- Were they cute?
- The point is not if they were cute.
The point is, they were there.
- They were cute.
- Very cute.
How can they have
new relationships?
I'm still in the "I just broke up
with someone" phase.
It's infuriating. Women sit around
obsessing about what went wrong.
Men just say "all righty" and move on.
I take offence at that. Not all women
sit around and obsess about men.
As soon as my relationships
are over, I move on.
- Relationships?
- You know, dates.
I do try to figure out what went wrong.
But I don't think that I obsess.
You are Miss Obsess. Big?
Big was tricky.
I still don't knowwhat happened.
You should have
a relationship rear-view mirror.
Relationships may appear closer
than they actually are.
I didn't obsess about Aidan.
Aidan was clear. He moved on.
- It's much easier for men to move on.
- Is it?
Please! The ratio of women to men
in this city is huge.
They can sit outside, have a beer
and wait for the Jessicas
and Susans to come to them.
Maybe we only obsess over
relationships that feel unfinished.
I can guarantee that Trey
isn't sitting around with his friends,
obsessing about what went wrong.
Men never think anything is their fault.
I wish there were no men.
Call someone, she's gone insane.
If there were no men,
then we wouldn't feel hurt.
And we wouldn't be disappointed.
And we wouldn't be spending
our night obsessing about them.
I'm so over men.
What? I am.
Later that night I got to thinking about
men, women and relationships.
Or more to the point, howwomen feel
men disappoint them in relationships.
Then a radical, earth-shattering
thought popped into my head.
What if everything
isn't the man's fault?
After a certain age
and a certain number of relationships,
if it still isn't working and the ex's
seem to be moving on and we don't,
perhaps the problem
isn't the last boyfriend,
or the one before him
or even the one before him.
Could it be
that the problem isn't them,
but horror of horrors,
is it us?
Downtown, the "Up-my-ass Players"
were in the middle
of their late night repertory.
"Much Ado About Up My Ass"
and "Long Day's Journey Up My Ass".
Samantha decided if she was gonna
get a good night's sleep,
she'd have to test how effective
a PR professional she was.
Ladies, hello.
I live right up there,
the loft within earshot.
As much as I respect a woman's right
for a little something
with certain New Jersey gentlemen,
I have a request.
I have a very early business meeting.
And I think we all know,
there are certain dark circles
even the best make-up can't cover.
Am I right?
Sorry to wake you, baby.
We'll take it down here.
I appreciate it.
By the way, I'm Samantha.
- Destiny.
- Chyna.
- Jo.
- No "e". She got the "e" cut off.
Those heels are fierce, Miss Girl.
Don't I know it.
Samantha knew
howto get her way with men,
even if they were half women.
What?
'Rough night?'
- Who is this?
- It's me.
I didn't recognize your voice.
You sounded different.
Did I wake you?
It's only 11:30.
No, I was up late working.
And there are these chickens
that crow on the roof next door.
Roosters. Roosters crow.
The "Fun On The Farm" fact
everyone's aware of but me.
- So tell me, is red a mistake?
- In what way?
I'm repainting my bedroom.
- A red bedroom?
- Just one wall.
But I think it's too red.
It's like sleeping in communist china.
She left... We ended it.
- I heard.
- You did? How?
I think it was on the news.
Could we have lunch sometime?
I really need to talk to you.
- Please?
- Where?
Boathouse restaurant, Central Park.
How about Saturday at 2:00?
- Carrie?
- I'm nodding.
- So I'll see you at 2:00 then.
- Bye.
Later that day, I met Miranda
at my favorite thrift store,
to dig for buried treasure.
Do you think I can get away with
a "Hang in there, baby" halter top?
Nobody gets away with
a "Hang in there, baby" halter top.
Do you wanna go to the
Hopper exhibit Saturday afternoon?
I can't. I have to work.
I lied.
I don't have to work.
I'm meeting Big for lunch
and I didn't think you'd approve.
- You're meeting Big?
- He called.
- He sounded upset and needs to talk.
- Since when does Big talk?
What does that mean?
He's upset about Natasha leaving...
I'm not holding your hand
through this again.
I'm not asking you to hold anything.
We're just having lunch.
It's a huge mistake.
It's not a huge mistake, it's lunch.
How many more times are you gonna
go through this? He is bad for you.
Every time you get near him you turn
into this pathetic, needy victim.
What pisses me off is that you are
more than willing to go back for more.
I am not going back for more
and I can't even believe...
I can't believe
you would say that to me.
- If you start up with Big again...
- I am not starting up with Big again.
If you do, I don't wanna know
anything about it.
No calls. No crying.
Are you gonna cut me out of your life
like you did to Steve?
What?
The first sign of any little weakness
and you just write people off.
My God, Miranda.
You are so judgmental.
You can say I'm pathetic and needy
and I can't say anything to you?
Everybody is not
as tough as you, Miranda.
People... Some of us make mistakes.
That's just perfect.
Walk away.
It's all my fault.
Right there,
next to the two for $5 bin,
Miranda and I had our first big fight.
'You have no messages. '
I thought by the time I got home,
she'd have left an apology.
I was gonna call her,
but wasn't quite sure what to say.
Or whose fault it really was.
And at the exact
same moment across town,
Miranda was preparing to make
the call she'd been dreading all day.
'Shanghai Garden.
May I help you?'
I'd like to order some takeout.
'Address, please. '
331 West 78th Street, Apartment 4F.
I'd like some...
'Chicken with broccoli, brown sauce,
brown rice and cold noodles, right?'
You know what?
I don't need this. Never mind.
'OK. Bye-bye. '
After she hung up, Miranda couldn't
get the giggle out of her head.
She decided to walk the two blocks
to confront the woman
with the judgmental giggle
who thought she was better than her.
Shanghai Garden.
May I help you?
OK. Address, please.
224 West 78th... Sorry, 73.
Miranda realized the giggle wasn't
about her. It wasn't about anything.
It wasn't the noodles that kept her
coming back to this restaurant.
It was the fact that
this was their place
and it was filled with happy memories.
Twice in one week.
Am I lucky or what?
- I thought I got custody of this place.
- I like their hot and sour soup.
Are you here by yourself?
Me too. Sit down.
I've got this bowl of crunchies
that I'll never get through.
How are you?
Not good.
Carrie and I had a huge fight.
About what?
Me, her, you, Big... Me.
My judgmental stuff.
How bad was it?
- It wasn't good.
- I didn't throwyou away. Did I?
- No.
- She said I did.
Miranda, only you and I really know
what happened between you and I.
It's nobody else's business.
But she said that, huh?
Must've been pretty mad.
I didn't say nice things to her either.
I just don't want her to get hurt again.
So you yelled at her?
Yeah.
Sounds about par.
I guess your new girlfriend
doesn't yell.
No.
How's that going?
It's ok.
- Like to order?
- I'd like the chicken with broccoli...
Let me see the menu.
I should try something new.
You should.
Go ahead. Live a little.
There is so much.
You're so fucking hot.
I can't believe they go away for one
night and then back three in a row.
Forget them. Look at me.
I'm sorry. I'm here.
Where are those cops?
I called them half an hour ago.
Look at me.
Let's bring it on home.
I can't.
- I'm close.
- Well, I'm not.
The idea that she'd miss
a night's sleep pissed Samantha off.
The idea that she'd miss an orgasm,
was more than she could bear.
Shut up, you bitches!
I've called the cops.
Suck my cock!
Keep talking and I'll come down there
and cut it off for you.
I'd like to see you try, motherfucker.
You think we want that BS? No way!
Are you gonna pull a Lorena Bobbit?
$7,000 a month and I have to put up
with a trilogy of fucking trannies?
I don't fucking think so!
I am a taxpayer and member of
the Women's Business Association.
- I don't have to put up with this shit!
- Forget them and come back to bed.
There was nothing anyone could do
to stop her. Samantha was obsessed.
She had a date with Destiny,
Chyna and Jo, no "e".
Take this, ladies!
I'm gonna come up there
and kick your ass, bitch!
Get off my hair now!
'Move it along, girls. '
You heard the man, move it along.
Hey, where are you going?
Home. You freak me out.
And Uptown, Charlotte was
a bit freaked out as well.
Unable to sleep
and unable to unpack,
she was with the only man
she could tolerate - The Dalai Lama.
- Charlotte? It's me.
- Trey?
What are you doing here?
It's 4:00am.
I sawyour light on from the street.
I figured you'd still be up.
What do you want?
Ever since you left,
I can't stop thinking about you.
- Honey, we're separated.
- I know.
Once Charlotte swore off men,
this man couldn't get enough of her.
He wasn't a rooster and it wasn't
the Bronx but from deep inside,
Trey's cock began to crow.
Across town, I was still wide awake.
I couldn't get my fight with Miranda
out of my head.
I was not only capable of obsessing
about relationships with men,
I was capable of obsessing
about relationships with women.
East Side Animal Shelter.
Please leave a message.
This is your neighbor
who complained about the chickens.
I can't take it any more.
Move them in. Thanks.
I figured if they had a lovely life,
I was entitled to the same thing.
Well...
All righty.
I knewthat was in me somewhere.
You did?
I just hadn't felt it since before...
Why did you stop yourself?
Before what?
Since before we got engaged.
Oh.
Yeah. Oh.
Do you think our whole problem
had to do with the fact that...
What?
Say it.
- You didn't really wanna marry me.
- No.
I think it may be due to the fact that
I didn't want to get married at all.
- Then why did you?
- I guess I thought it was time.
I'm of a certain age,
people expect you to get married.
Yes, well... That sounds familiar.
- One other thing...
- What?
I married you because I knew
I'd never find anyone
as wonderful as you to marry.
He may have gone away,
the pre-op transsexual,
but he came back, loaded with eggs.
Nowwho's laughing, bitch?
Samantha knewthis was
one relationship with a man
she couldn't walk away from.
Because this man was half woman.
- Good, you're there.
- I was just gonna call you.
Do you really think I'm pathetic?
No, I'm so sorry.
I don't think you're pathetic at all.
I'm outside the restaurant,
hiding in some bushes.
Do you still not think I'm pathetic?
'I knowyou think it's a huge mistake. '
It's just something I feel
I need to do to move on.
Don't listen to me. I have no idea
what's right for you and Big.
But if I'm wrong and it is a mistake,
I need to know you'll be there for me.
I'm there.
I'm going in.
Any last minute advice?
Don't let him kiss you. That seems
to be where you get into trouble.
- 'Carrie?'
- I'm nodding.
Hello, you.
It's good to see you.
Are you OK?
My hair is in a duck pond.
My Dior purse.
I'll get it.
Oh, my God! What is that?
- Howwas your shower?
- I no longer smell of pond.
Exactly how many
terry-cloth robes do you have?
- Three or four.
- Oh, three or four.
I swore I would never be in this room
with you again.
You said to take you
to the nearest shower.
That is one red wall.
Yes, it's red.
I gotta ask you a question.
- Was it all my fault?
- No.
It wasn't all your fault.
We really screwed that up.
What were we thinking?
I have no idea.
Fuck. I was counting on you
for answers.
- How are you doing, kid?
- Pretty good. How are you doing?
Good.
Aside from the fact
I feel like I've been through a war.
Really, we're like war buddies.
War buddies in Calvin Klein robes.
I hate to admit this,
but I kind of like living alone again.
Why doesn't that surprise me?
- I should go.
- Don't you want to stay a while?
I can't.
Why?
Because, sweet friend,
you and I are like that red wall.
It's a good idea in theory.
But somehow, it doesn't quite work.
And just like that, I realized
Big and I weren't "us" any more.
We had become something else.
What it was, I had no idea.
'You have one new message. '
(Miranda) It's me. I'm wondering how
it went. Call me when you get home.
I had no idea where the chickens had
gone, but I hoped it wasn't the Bronx.
And I hoped they were happy.
Who wants a wiener?
Girl, I'm trying to get rid of one.
The next Saturday, Samantha decided
to throw a kiss and make up party
for the "Up-my-ass Players".
Trey called me three times last week.
He's dying to get back together.
But I don't know.
Is that wise?
- I'm obsessing again, aren't I?
- A bit.
So, what are we all drinking?
"Flirtinis. " Vodka, pineapple
and champagne.
Flirtinis.
- Destiny made them.
- I'm past a Flirtini. I need a "Fucktini".
Watch your language.
There are ladies present.
Where?
- You with the flower.
- Are you talking to me?
It's you, girl. Come on.
- What do you want?
- I want you to give me a swirl.
I need to see you spin first, sister.
- Is that good enough?
- Give me the shake.
Don't mind the weight.
Eat something.
Don't worry,
they have a very lovely life.
www.tvsubtitles.net