You can count on one hand
the things a New Yorker will wait for.
My list includes:
the perfect apartment,
the chocolate souffle at Le Bernardin,
and the annual Manolo Blahnik sale.
After four dates
with the furniture designer,
whose kiss made my knees weak,
this New Yorker
had waited long enough.
so, do you wanna sleep over?
I have to feed Pete.
I have to get up early in the morning.
Apparently, that New Yorker had not.
When one door closes,
another one opens.
At 2:00am, the door that opened
was samantha's.
What's going on?
Freda in 1D was held up at gunpoint.
Oh, my God!
It's under control.
We have the suspect on tape.
This is supposed to be
a safe building.
It was late. Doorman was off duty.
He entered behind somebody's guest.
That,s awful.
The guy came in behind the guy
who came in samantha.
That,s terrible.
- Who has a guest at 2:00am?
- I have no idea.
- What did everybody do last night?
- Nothing.
- I don't want to talk about it.
Did you sleep with someone
on the second date?
No. The third date.
Alexander Lemly, the investment
banker I met at an art show.
- The sex was bad?
- It was good, except...
I don't think I can say it.
Get over yourself.
What happened?
When he...
You know.
came, orgasmed, shot his wad.
He said:
You fucking bitch!
You fucking whore!
- Why would he say that?
- Because you were fucking him?
He didn't say it at the drycleaners,
but when he was in you.
Do you think I'm a whore?
If you're a whore,
what does that make me?
- Do you think I'm a whore?
- You have had a lot of bone in you.
This is bad.
Nobody wants to marry a whore.
Even charlotte
is having more sex than me.
What about Aidan?
I don't knowwhat's going on.
We're spending a lot of time together.
He keeps asking me out.
But he doesn,t wanna sleep with me.
- Gay.
- He's not gay.
- Mother issues?
- I don,t think so.
- Maybe his dick curves to the right.
- We'll work it out. I'll go left.
I may never know.
Wait too long to sleep with someone,
you become just friends.
As supposed to his fucking bitch,
his fucking whore.
come on.
If samantha was right,
I had little time left
before the relationship-window
closed.
so I wore my little dress
that left little to the imagination.
Do you want to take this inside?
I better get home. I gotta...
You gotta get up early.
Whatever.
- What's going on up there?
- Do you just wanna be friends?
I don't know.
Is that how you kiss your friends?
Why don't you wanna sleep with me?
Whatever it is
I'd rather know sooner than later.
I do wanna sleep with you.
I do.
Look at you.
I,ve been down that road before.
I've slept with women quickly
and I'm still single.
My new thing is, I want to try and
sleep with somebody I care about.
I really think
that I can care about you.
It's only been a week and a half.
Don't people date anymore?
Why did I expect to sleep with him
after only a week and a half?
Had I become so jaded
that I didn't recognize romance
when it kissed me on the lips?
Modern women need a cheat-sheet
to remind us romance isn't dead.
Romance.
I tell you, it didn't even occur to me,
which is so depressing.
Is that what 13 years of dating
in Manhattan does to a woman?
I'll tell you what it does.
It gives you chlamydia.
Excuse me?
My gynecologist called me today.
My tests, which she threw in
for good measure, were positive.
It's not terrible. There aren't any
symptoms, but it can cause infertility.
I guess it's good I caught it.
I mean...
Not that I caught it,
but that I found out.
- You got it from steve?
- I don't know.
It could be any number of guys,
which is what I told my gynecologist.
she seemed a little judgmental.
she told me to contact all the people
that I might have given it to,
so they can all be treated.
I knew what was bothering her.
The same thought had bothered me
since the guy I'd been seeing
for 10 days asked me to slow down.
If you're a 30 something woman in
Manhattan and you're sexually active,
it's inevitable that you'll rack up
a certain number of partners.
But how many is too many men?
Are we simply romantically
challenged or are we sluts?
It was the question
on charlotte's mind.
- How's your swordfish?
- Fine, thanks.
- You're awfully quiet tonight.
- sorry, my mind is somewhere else.
You fucking bitch!
You fucking whore!
I hate putting people out of work,
but it happens after a merger.
Maybe I should
teach EsL on the side.
Are you sure you're OK?
Actually... what you said
the other night kind of bothered me.
What did I say?
You knowwhen we were in bed
and you...
You yelled out something.
- During my sleep?
- No, during sex.
I don't remember saying anything.
I remember it being very nice.
What did I say?
It,s not important. I,m sure
it was in the heat of the moment.
Do you want to try my swordfish?
It really is good.
By dessert, charlotte had decided
to forget it and call it a do-over.
- You fucking bitch! Fucking whore!
- That! That's what you said.
- What?
- Just then. You said it again.
What did I say?
You fucking bitch, you fucking whore.
My God, are you sure?
That's terrible. That's a horrible thing
to say. I had no idea.
I just get lost in the moment.
I don't think that about you.
Believe me, you are sweet,
smart and lovely.
You are the kind of woman
I hope to marry some day.
I promise never to say that again.
That,s terrible.
As charlotte started to feel better,
Miranda started to feel worse.
steve, can we not?
I'm just getting started.
I'm only at the neck.
Maybe you'll change your mind
when I'm down around your elbows.
I can't tonight, I have chlamydia.
I don't even knowwhat that is,
but it sounds like a problem.
It's not a big deal. It's just
a sexually transmitted disease.
I might have given it to you
or you to me.
Either way, you should get tested.
I,m afraid of doctors.
I don,t even have one.
Go to the free clinic. Whatever.
What's gonna happen,
does it hurt when you pee?
Men are just carriers,
there aren't any symptoms at all.
Then why do I need to know?
If you don't get treated
you can pass it on to other people.
You are my only other person,
and you already have it.
Yeah, but if you've got it,
we'll keep passing it back and forth.
I'd rather not sleep with you
until it's out of my body.
I've got six more days of antibiotics.
Will you please just take care of it?
Get it over with.
steve's trip to the doctor
didn't cure his fear of doctors.
- Drop your trousers.
- There's nothing wrong down there.
I'm here because my girlfriend
said to get the test.
I need a sample
from the inside of your penis.
As steve faced something
every man dreads,
Miranda faced something
every woman dreads.
she was making a list
of all the men she'd slept with.
At least all the ones
she could remember.
she wondered
how she did all these men
and did her law degree
and became a successful lawyer.
samantha knew
her number was up there.
But she didn't know
everybody else knew.
We know it was you
who buzzed in the gunman.
- Excuse me?
- You always have guests.
Every time I'm in this elevator
you're with a different man.
That,s ridiculous.
This is your floor.
Excuse me.
The next day, Miranda's sex life
was flashing before her as well.
Thanks. OK.
sorry to bother you.
congratulations.
Nowyou're married, you don't
have to worry about stuff like this.
Bye-bye.
Miss Hobbes, line two is still holding.
- Miranda Hobbes.
- Hi, it's David, returning a call.
- How have you been?
- Lousy, I'm partner. All work, no play.
- What do you want?
- It's kind of awkward.
I'm busy, spit it out.
What is it?
OK. I've got this...
- It's chlamydia. Which is...
- I know what chlamydia is.
- Perhaps you should get tested.
- I,ve been tested.
- Recently?
- Yes. Is that it?
Yes. No... Did you have it?
Is that your business? You call me
after months to discuss my health?
- Yes, I had it. so, what?
- Perhaps you gave it to me.
- What are you gonna do, sue me?
- You could have called.
- You told me never to call you.
- Now I remember why. Bye!
Meanwhile, I was still waiting
for the diagnosis on my relationship.
Would Aidan become
friend or boyfriend?
Delivery for Miss Bradshaw.
It's about time.
I ordered this years ago.
He certainly kissed like a boyfriend.
Don't you have two matching plates?
No.
What do you use for wine,
promotional coffee mugs?
But he teased me like a friend.
come here. Let me get this.
Boyfriend.
I don't care what anybody says.
I think catherine zeta-Jones is hot.
Friend.
Not as hot as you, but she's hot.
Boyfriend. And liar.
- I think samantha was right.
- About what?
Me and Aidan. I think we're
just friends who kiss occasionally.
- Why are you whispering?
- cos he's still here.
That,s promising.
He's been in the bathroom
for half an hour.
All we did was eat chinese
and watch "zorro".
Now I'm working and he's
reading the paper on the john.
This isn't romance, this is bullshit.
- carrie!
- Yeah?
come here a second.
I have to go, my friend
wants to see me in the bathroom.
What did you want, because...
Wow.
It,s like a Danielle steele novel
in here.
From a writer,
I'm pretty sure that's an insult.
No, this is... Wow.
I thought a bath would help you relax.
You seemed kind of tense.
Are you sure this isn't
just a cheap ploy to see me naked?
Will you be naked?
That's the thing about baths.
This is about you, so enjoy.
I'm gonna get going.
But that doesn't make us friends
cos I'll be thinking about you naked.
Big tub, little person.
You talked me into it.
so nowwhat?
Nowwhat, what?
We're just taking a bath.
Fuck it, let's just do it.
This isn't how it should happen.
You said this was just a bath.
- come on, who cares?
- You do. And I do too now.
OK.
Out of the tub.
The next night,
samantha was feeling exposed.
Here she comes.
- Good evening.
- Hello.
If you wanna say something
about me, say it to my face.
You're bad for the building.
- What?
- You have too many visitors.
- There are always men in the hall.
- I got robbed because of you.
I can't close my left eye.
They practically chased me
like I was Fuckenstein.
They can't evict you for having sex.
They're jealous, dried up old farts who
haven't had sex since Eisenhower.
I remind them of what they can't have.
It might be time to move.
You can't. You have a rent-controlled
apartment on the Upper East side.
This isn't rent control, it's life control.
I have to go, I have a date with Aidan.
Don't tell me
you're not having sex yet.
- We're not having sex yet.
- What are you doing?
Tonight, we're going to a blues club.
- Who's singing, you?
- We'll have sex eventually.
By the way, I got a little preview.
I assure you,
there is no curving in any direction.
It is straight. very straight.
That night,
charlotte had a date as well.
And he was doing his best
to be the strong, silent type.
- What's the matter?
- I'm afraid to come.
What are you talking about?
I'm close.
Go ahead.
You fucking bitch, you fucking whore!
I hate myself, what's wrong with me?
That night, Alexander decided
to stop seeing charlotte
and start seeing a therapist.
And steve got his test back.
It was negative,
like the rest of the experience.
That doctor with the swab... Ouch!
I don't even want to swab my ears.
It's my fault.
I'm the one with the disease.
I'm a big, dirty, diseased whore.
That's my girlfriend
you're talking about.
You knowwhat? I had to make a list
of all the guys I've slept with
and it's not short.
How, not short?
It's... No, I can't tell you.
I've never told anybody my number.
I'm just curious.
You won't judge me?
I spent a day at the free clinic.
OK. It's like, about... 42.
- 42? That's not so bad.
- That's too many.
It,s fine.
- What's your number?
- I'm not telling you.
come on.
It's embarrassing. I've had enough
embarrassment for one week.
What is it?
Ten?
Higher.
60?
Higher than 60?
A lot higher?
I,m a bartender and I,m cute.
Note, men who have had a lot of
sexual partners are not called sluts.
They are called very good kissers.
A few are even called romantics.
I can't believe you've never been
to the Blue Note.
- call yourself a New Yorker.
- I've never done a lot of things.
I can think of one thing in particular.
- That I've done.
- I can think of one other thing.
What do you think
about me staying the night?
I don't know.
What about Pete?
I arranged for the super's kid
to walk Pete and feed him.
And you knewthis all night?
And then something weird happened.
For the first time in a long time,
I was nervous.
We were going to sleep together
and it was going to mean something.
I was no virgin,
but this was definitely virgin territory.
Good morning.
OK, that's what I wanted. Bye.
The nice thing about
a new relationship, it's a clean slate.
And speaking of clean slates,
samantha moved
to the trendy Meatpacking District.
Good morning, ladies.
Whores were whores,
men were women and rents higher.
Easy, that's my bed.
www.tvsubtitles.net