One ofthe best things
about being in a great relationship
is feeling comfortable enough
to leave it for an evening.
what do you girls do
when you get together?
The usual stuff - braid our hair,
crank calls, and that weekend stuff.
You don't talk about the boys?
I can't lie.
Sometimes there is talk of the boys.
Men's greatest fear.
- I thought it was hair loss.
- No problem here.
- I can tell.
- Feel free to pass that on to the gals.
I'll try to work that
into the conversation.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
EB white said no one should come
to New York unless they're lucky.
I was. I had an amazing boyfriend
who had all his hair, good friends...
...and a married ex-boyfriend
I had slept with a week ago.
May I just say, "wow!"
what can I say? I've arrived!
Samantha had invited us to celebrate
her new apartment, three new clients
and her general fabulousness.
who knew this existed
in the meatpacking district.
Just yards away from decaying cows.
- Homemade baby quiche.
- You made these?
No! I had them delivered,
along with dinner, the wine
and DvD of "An Affair To Remember"
that we're watching later, drunk.
- You can get DvDs delivered?
- I used this new delivery service.
Anything you want
they bring within an hour.
Anything?
- Last night I ordered condoms.
- You didn't fuck the delivery guy!
No, John, the hot guy from the gym.
The condoms
came faster than he did!
There's an ad-slogan.
Ladies, we have it all -
great apartments, jobs,
friends, and sex...
we can have quiche delivered
and eat it too.
At my age, my mother had three kids
and a drunk husband.
- You just have three drunk friends.
- By choice.
Having it all really means having
someone special to share it with.
Please. That's so barney.
I'm sorry. My life wasn't complete
until I met Trey.
And Trey's mom is so great.
You'll meet her at the engagement
party she's throwing for us.
You will love her.
Do you see us Manhattan?
we have it all.
- Fuck you!
- You wish.
carrie, go home.
I can take care of this.
Three hours later, Deborah Kerr had
revealed her secret to cary Grant,
and I'd still told no one mine.
- I slept with Big last week.
- You're having an affair?
No, no affair. Just one night,
and it is not happening again.
- Please don't tell the others.
- OK.
I am awful.
I have this great boyfriend.
I don't know what I was doing.
Nothing men
haven't been doing for centuries.
was it good?
It was great,
and it's not happening again.
Got it. Plates.
How can it feel so good
when it's so bad?
They design it that way.
Big and I... we have this thing.
It's all about the pheromones.
we're just animals reacting to smells.
I have a great boyfriend with all his
hair, waiting for me, who smells great.
Aidan hasn't said "I love you" yet.
- Until then, you're a free agent.
- The rules according to Samantha?
I'm more old-fashioned
than you think.
I don't wanna be a free agent.
Don't you wanna judge me,
just a little bit?
Not my style.
Hang on.
Hi. God, I missed you.
You gotta go see the girls more often.
come on.
Suddenly I felt safe again.
It had all just been a bad dream.
As long as I was near Aidan,
it would all be OK.
Until the morning.
why do you have to go
to Pennsylvania today?
See that chair? It's got owners
that miss it very much.
Go tomorrow. come on, stay.
- I'll make you cookies.
- You don't cook.
I'll buy you cookies.
come on, stay.
It's just for a couple of days.
You gotta have stuff you wanna do.
what I needed to do was not be alone.
Be good.
Downtown, Samantha woke up
to discover she did have it all.
Including the flu.
Shit.
She never wanted a man around
in the morning, until she needed one.
- John?
- It's Samantha.
Jones.
From the gym.
Yeah, right.
I wondered if you might be able to
drop by on your way to work.
Honey, I can hardly blow my nose,
let alone blow you.
Yeah, I wouldn't want
you to get sick, either.
Later, in the bridal registry
department at Bergdorf Goodman,
charlotte discovered,
she wanted it all, and more.
- $1,300.
- Yes. we do very well with it.
- It's really beautiful.
- Yes.
It'll look lovely under the noodles
we'll have to eat
due to my outstanding loans.
No, not that face.
All right. If it's what you want.
I'm too crazy about you to say no.
I gotta get back to the hospital.
- Did you do a guest list for the party?
- Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
Sweetie? what's this?
Prenuptial agreements. Standard.
Everyone in the family has one.
You sign on page four. Feel free
to have your lawyer look it over.
I'll call you later.
This looks normal.
charlotte wasted no time
having a lawyer look it over.
we're not married yet, and already
we're talking about divorce.
A lot of people do prenups.
Marriage is supposed to be
about love and happiness.
- And the protection of assets.
- That is so unromantic.
And necessary. 50 per cent
of marriages end in divorce.
There it is again - divorce.
I'm sure you'll live happily ever after,
but I wouldn't marry without this.
I'm safe. what's he gonna take
from me - shoes?
Maybe I do need one.
what?
This is unusual.
He has you on a vesting schedule.
For every five years you're married,
you get a percentage of $500,000.
I'm only worth $500,000.
- Over 30 years.
- Maybe that's your wholesale price.
If you have any boys,
you'll get another 100 grand.
How much for girls?
- Nada.
- That's bad business.
I can't sign that. I can't marry
someone knowing they feel this way.
This is just their opening offer.
It's standard to negotiate.
I can't even buy stuff on sale.
Talk to Trey. I'm sure his lawyers
will take care of this.
working over lunch? The New York
office is tougher than ours.
George, this is carrie and charlotte.
George works in our chicago office.
I'm taking depositions
and restaurant recommendations
from hip and trendy New Yorkers.
- You're hip and trendy?
- George is from chicago.
- So it's good?
- It's fantastic.
I hope the place tomorrow
lives up to your standards.
- I'm sure it will be great.
- I'll drop by your office later.
- OK.
- Nice meeting you, ladies.
Bye.
well, well, well, they sure
grow 'em cute in the Midwest.
I know. We have a date.
Find out how much he pays
for boys before you get attached.
24 hours, three degrees of fever
and two pages of her black book later,
Samantha was no closer
to closing her deal.
why don't you go fuck yourself.
I won't be doing it again... ever.
Samantha was discovering it was
easier to find a guy to screw her
than one who'd screw in
her curtain rod.
She wasn't the only one
who needed a fix.
I did everything I could
to keep busy until Aidan came back.
I re-arranged my sweaters,
defrosted my fridge...
broke into my emergency hidden
stash, and thought about choices.
Modern women have been told
that we can be anything we want -
an astronaut, the head of an Internet
company, a stay-at-home mom.
There aren't any rules.
choices are endless.
And apparently,
they can all be delivered to your door.
Is it possible that we've gotten
so spoiled by choices
that we've become
unable to make one?
That we know
that once you choose something,
one man, one great apartment,
one amazing job,
another option goes away?
Are we a generation who can't
choose just one from column 'A'?
Did we have too much to handle,
or was Samantha right?
can we have it all?
Two hours later, I had filed
every article I'd ever written,
but I couldn't file away
what had happened with Big.
I made a choice.
I called him.
- Yeah?
- It's me, carrie.
Jesus, carrie. How are you?
I'm good, fine. OK.
we need to talk about what happened.
- Right now?
- Yes. Rationally and right now.
- Apparently you're the boss.
- It was just a physical thing.
we gave in to our baser instincts,
shit happens, blah blah blah.
- Are you wearing glasses?
- No.
- You sound like you are.
- It can't happen. You're married.
I'm aware of that. But it was
pretty fucking amazing, wasn't it?
That is so not the point.
we're intelligent beings. we have to
learn to rise above the physical stuff.
You can learn to do that?
Apparently we couldn't.
Next time we're going to a hotel.
I can smell the guy on your sheets.
woodchips and Paco Rabanne.
He doesn't wear cologne.
Maybe he should.
By the way, there will be no next time.
This is gonna be like
"The Bridges Of Madison Avenue".
A brief affair
I'll write about to my grandchildren.
can I have a beard
in the book version?
I've always wanted a beard.
Maybe a goatee.
It all felt so easy and so good.
I was like the moth to the old flame.
Meanwhile that night,
Miranda was enjoying her new flame.
can't believe I have to
catch an 11 o' clock flight.
But it was fun.
If I weren't going back to chicago,
I would try to sleep with you now.
I'm drunk enough.
I might have let you.
Damn!
- I have to wait till next time.
- There will be a next time?
Of course.
I come back and forth a lot.
In the meantime,
there's always the phone.
- I have one of those.
- I'll call you tomorrow night.
Damn.
The next night, Miranda was surprised
to hear from George.
I knew you were a middle child.
I love it when I'm right.
Yeah, spoken like a true only child.
They talked for two hours
about everything.
Favorite foods, families... It was one
of the best dates Miranda had had.
- what are you wearing?
- Then the date got even better.
Nothing.
- wish I were there.
- Really? what would you do?
I would start
by kissing your neck. Slowly.
Then I'd work my way down,
start licking your nipples...
- where's your hand?
- On your dick.
Put the other one on you.
That night, Miranda started
sleeping with George regularly.
She had it all - her own life, and
a great boyfriend she could count on.
He always called,
and she always came to the phone.
while Miranda came, I was busy
preparing for Aidan to come back.
I had slept in Big's and my sex-sheets
for two days.
Like any good junky,
I knew how to hide the evidence.
Hey, you.
- come on.
- Hi.
Look at you.
I was sure he saw the scarlet 'A'
on my chest.
If Big could smell him,
could he smell Big on me?
I missed you so much.
I should send you
to Pennsylvania more often.
You should.
I realized something while I was gone.
- You did, did you?
- Yeah.
I love you, carrie.
Is that too much?
- I thought I shouldn't say...
- No.
I love you too.
Not only was my secret safe,
but I had become lovable.
I felt awful. And so good.
- wait. No sheets.
- Fuck the sheets.
You're bent over,
and I'm playing with you.
- Your dick is in my mouth.
- Jesus, I'm gonna come.
The next night, Miranda was
going to third with George
when her second line beeped.
Dammit, hold on.
- Hello.
- Trey says his mom won't negotiate.
- Hold on.
- Are you OK?
I'll be right back.
Your dick is in my mouth.
Keep it there.
The mom's the one holding the cards.
She's the one to go up against.
- How do I do that?
- charlotte, I'll call you tomorrow.
But...
Sorry.
So am I.
You got me so hot, I just came.
You did?
Now we have to take care of you.
The next night,
I went to take care of Samantha.
More cough syrup.
which for Samantha meant
making her mom's childhood remedy -
cough syrup
and Fanta orange soda over ice.
No offence, but this is about
to make me sicker than you.
Give me my drink.
A frosted martini glass
would make that more appetizing.
why don't you ask the super
to fix your window?
I don't have one.
I own this place, remember?
I should have got married. Then
at least I'd have a curtain that closes.
Oh, carrie, it doesn't matter
how much you have.
If you don't have a guy
who cares about you,
- it all means shit.
- Sweetie, calm down.
Three days of sleep deprivation had
turned Samantha into a new woman -
charlotte.
For someone who had it all,
she had never felt more alone.
I'm gonna tell you something.
There's two types of guys out there -
the ones that hold your hand,
and the ones that fuck you.
I'd slept with both of them
in the last 48 hours.
The guys that fuck you
aren't worth a damn.
we're all alone.
we are not alone.
we have each other.
- Bed?
- Yeah.
Three days of rest later, three healthy
girls attended a very uptown party.
Jesus. Looks like
Martha Stewart exploded in here.
- Look, headbands are back.
- where's the food?
Amazing what days of a cough syrup
and Fanta diet will do for the appetite.
They're wASPs.
There's never food, only booze.
Fine.
One martini, six olives.
I can't believe charlotte wants to be
in this world. Look at these people.
- They're like Ken and Barbie cut-outs.
- You made it.
- I see you found the bar.
- we're good that way.
Trey, you have to keep people
out of the maid's room.
There are photos of me rowing college
crew in there. It's mortifying.
These are charlotte's friends.
This is my mom, Bunny.
Pleasure to have you.
There's Reverend Williams.
Maybe we should say hello
before he gets into the Scotch.
It's about 20 years too late for that.
- I haven't signed the prenup.
- what are you gonna do?
I don't know. I'm confused.
I love him, but I feel like
no one cares about me.
I thought if we could negotiate,
it'd be OK, but now it all feels wrong.
- what does Trey say?
- Nothing. He leaves it to his mother.
You can take her.
- what should I do?
- we can't tell you what to do.
I wasn't one to talk about marriage,
considering I might break one up.
You have to do
what feels right to you.
It depends how much
you want to marry Trey.
- Bunny, do you have a minute?
- Of course.
charlotte realized, if she wanted
to close the deal with Trey,
she'd have to close the deal
with Bunny first.
- I haven't signed the prenup.
- You've been busy.
I have...
...a little problem
with how much I'm worth.
I see.
That is the standard amount.
It's how it's always
been done in the MacDougal family.
Right.
Not only would she have to negotiate,
she'd have to play hardball.
well, you know...
...we haven't finalized
the wedding arrangements.
Trey would be disappointed
if I backed out.
"The Times" announcement
would run, there would be questions...
- what do you want?
- I'm worth a million.
I did it. I negotiated with Bunny,
and I signed the prenup.
That's great.
- I'm getting married.
- congratulations.
- I love him.
- Ladies, may I sweep my bride away?
She's all yours.
It was then that we realized
that we didn't have it all.
we no longer had charlotte.
Then, there were three.
I can't believe
she's marrying that guy.
For a tenth of what she's worth.
I thought you were
Ms Pro Marriage now.
I was delirious.
I also saw spots all over my bathtub.
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but it feels weird without her here.
That's such a charlotte thing to say.
After a week full of Aidan
and no cigarettes,
I felt like I had
finally kicked my addiction.
- Emu.
- what?
- 32 across. Rare bird - emu.
- I was getting there.
Not with the wrong word in 15 down.
Then my addiction found me.
- Hello.
- I need to see you.
- Miranda, I'll call you back.
- come down or I'll come up.
Right, I'll call you later.
I told Aidan
I was taking Pete for a walk.
He believed me,
which only made it worse.
Don't ever call me
at home again. walk.
You can't just decide
you wanna see me, and I'm there.
- Is this his dog?
- Yes.
You want it all - the girl you screw,
and the girl you go home to.
That's bullshit. I just want you.
I can't do this any more, sleep with
two people at the same time.
- I'll tell her tonight.
- what?
- No, no.
Married men don't just leave their...
I have a man who loves me,
and you have a wife who loves you.
Don't talk about him and her
like it's you and me.
You have no right to do this.
You can't come and fuck up my life.
I think there were two people
doing the fucking here.
Shit. Pete. Oh, shit!
- where are you going? wait.
- Pete!
- Pete! Oh, shit.
- carrie.
Excuse me.
Pete! shit.
- watch out!
- Pete.
God. Shit!
No. Go home.
Don't tell anyone. Don't do anything.
- I wanna help.
- This isn't helping. Go home.
Back at Miranda's home,
things were heating up as well.
I unbutton the last button, slip
my hand in, and touch your breast.
Your nipple's so hard.
I'll be right back.
I'm thrusting, I'm thrusting.
I'm deep inside of you.
You were touching my breast.
Yeah, I'm touching your breast,
and I'm thrusting into you.
No, we hadn't gotten to that yet.
Oh.
Are you having phone sex
with other people?
I don't think we ever said
this was an exclusive thing.
Oh, my God.
Miranda stopped being hung up
on George. So she hung up on him.
Three hours later, I hadn't found Pete,
and I felt as lost as he was.
I had a man who loved me, and a man
who wanted to leave his wife for me.
I should have been
on top of the world,
but I didn't feel like I had it all.
I felt like nothing.
I had lost Pete,
and I would probably lose Aidan.
I decided to come clean.
Jesus, I was worried about you.
Oh, my God. Pete's here?
Oh, my God, I lost him.
I lost him and I looked for him and...
Oh, my... Pete, come here.
come here.
Oh, God.
- I'm an awful girlfriend.
- Take it easy.
- I'm awful.
- He's a dog. He runs away.
He found his way back.
So had I.
I need to ask you something.
- OK.
- I don't wanna be paranoid.
You took Pete for a walk.
we both know you're not big
on the dog-walking.
I can smell something.
Are you cheating?
I can smell the smoke on you.
You're smoking again, aren't you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
It was the truth.
- Are you going to quit?
- I really want to.
That was, too.
come here.
www.tvsubtitles.net