ÀÚ¸·Á¦ÀÛ - ³×ÀÌÆ® µå¶ó¸¶ 24
(http:/club. nate. com/24)
'Sex And The City'
Sarah Jessica Parker(Carrie Bradshaw æµ)
Kim Cattrall(Samantha Jones æµ)
Kristin Davis(Charlotte York McDougal æµ)
Cynthia Nixon(Miranda Hobbes æµ)
¿µ¾îëº»
ashley29(club. nate. com/24)
½ÌÅ©ÆíÁý
ÀÌ¹ÌÇâ(mintchoco@netsgo. com)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON HBO: 2003/08/10
Season 6
Epi 8. the catch
My career had reached new heights-literally
An editor at New York Magazine thought thatI would be the perfect person to write
about the ultimate challenge for swingers.
The flying trapeze.
Wouldn't you rather be at Jeffrey?
They're having a sale on stripes.
That's not supportive.
Step on up. Good. That's good.
Come around to my side.
I'm gonna take off your climbing limbs
and strap on your safety harness.
Yes. Please strap on anything that
would keep me from plummeting to my death.
Toes over the edge. Feet should-width apart.
Just a little bit more.
That's good. head up.
Now put your right hand out in front.
I've got you. Good.
Are you ready to grab the bar?
I'm ready to go to the bar.
Does everyone say that?
Pretty much. Okay.
Hold the bar in one hand.
You're queen of the world!
All right. That's good.
Keep your head up. Don't look down.
Are you ready?
And hup!
Swing it sister!
Two hours later, I was hooked.
Stanny, are you watching?
I'm about to try a catch.
Maybe you should quit while you're a¡¦live.
You can totally do this.
Just listen to me and trust me. Hup!
All right. Legs up.
Take your hands off and reach for me.
This time you got it. Let go.
- Let go.
- No. No. No. No.
That day. I didn't get caught.
But Samantha's zipper did.
This is one of the frustrating things about living alone.
There's not always somebody around to rip your clothes off.
Hey Smith. Wanna come over and do me?
What she meant was; undo me.
But two birds with one stone.
And in Central Park,
a photographer attempted to catch
two lovebirds sitting on a stone.
Honey, a little less teeth.
Just relax your lips.
No, now you're squinting!
A lesser man might have told Charlotte to take a flying leap.
But Harry loved her too much.
I thought the point was to look natural.
That's what I'm trying to get you to do.
Well, one might ask how natural is
it to be sitting in Central Park in a suit?
Honey. I read the wedding section religiously
and I know what they're looking for
and not all pictures are selected.
And I really, really want there to be
a York- Goldenblatt announcement
of our wedding in the Sunday Times
so please just a little less teeth.
Charlotte York. I cannot wait to marry you.
That's perfect! That's it!
I was having a moment.
Lipstick!
Wait no, no! Sorry.
No kissing pictures. It's tacky.
And speaking of tacky.
It's cute, huh?
Debby bought it for him over at the 6th avenue flea market.
Did you wash it first?
She also got something for you.
It's aromatherapy.
Oh. Huh.
You know I was thinking.
Maybe we should figure out a time
for the two of you to meet.
What? Why?
Well. She's around Brady and I know
how you're not so comfortable with that.
I'm completely comfortable.
I don't need to meet her. I trust you.
She bought me a fucking candle.
And it was an aromatherapy candle for serenity and calm.
I was much more serene and calm before the fucking candle.
Women with candles have replaced women with cats is the new sad thing.
And get this. He thinks I should meet her.
I sense that he wants us to become friends.
No. No. No. Forget it.
You do not need to become friends with the new girlfriend.
It's unnatural, uncomfortable, insincere and rife with ulterior motive.
Has this happen to you?
No. I'm just being supportive.
But there is a baby involved.
Exactly. She's using Brady to get to me and I am not falling for it.
Speaking of falling, I tried the trapeze yesterday for that piece that I'm writing.
I could never. I have the most terrible fear of heights.
Well I do not. You've seen my shoes.
So did you fly through the air with the greatest of ease?
At first, but then I couldn't do a catch.
All I had to do was let go and reach for the guy,
who was very cute, and I still couldn't do it.
You are insane for getting into a harness without even the hope of an orgasm.
- Hello ladies.
- Hi honey.
Hi Howie.
Everyone this is Harry's best friend Howie Halberstram from Portland.
I'm not crashing. I'm just here to drop off the photo proofs.
And the seating chart.
We're gonna have a quick bite to eat
then I'm going to take the place cards to the calligrapher.
And after that when there's time,
we're gonna go around the corner and try to find our balls.
Yes. Harry knows to show a guy a good time.
Howie, this is Samantha and Miranda. And Carrie.
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
- Good.
Good guy. You two, I see it happening.
So, Carrie. I was thinking you might
show Howie around a little later.
Unless Harry needs me to ice a cake or something.
Well. I'm kinda busy.
I have to do a flying trapeze thing.
That is so weird cause I have to have a lion
taming thing tomorrow so that's out for me.
But you know, if you change your mind,
I will give you my business card.
Okay.
There you go.
Thank you.
- All my line's on there.
- Okay.
- Call me any time you¡¦
- Okay. Okay.
What's wrong with you?
He was funny and cute.
And in town for a week. What's the point?
That is the point.
It's the best possible scenario.
Because you know he's leaving.
But it's like whatever happens,
there's an expiration date.
It's expiration dating.
It isn't dating. It's sex. It's fun, it's a fling.
Oh please. I'm too old for a fling.
I can barely do a swing.
And if you will excuse me,
I have to go home so I can write
about the fact that I couldn't do a catch.
He is a catch.
You should do him.
When you're young,
your whole life is about the pursuit of fun.
Then, you grow up and learn to be cautious.
You could break a bone or a heart.
You look before you leap and sometimes
you don't leap at all because
there's not always someone there to catch you.
And in life, there's no safety net.
When did it stop being fun
and start being scary?
I decided it was time to leave
fear behind and have some fun.
Okay, legs up.
That's good. let go and reach for me.
I can't.
All right, this time. Let go.
I can't. I can't.
Don't tell me you can't.
I want nothing but lilies on the Hoffa.
The theme is Yentl chic.
Don't forget the candles.
You think this is the first wedding I ever planned?
Jesus Christ, you're worse than me.
We want candles, candles, candles
and I don't want short stubby little broken-off DICK candles.
I want loooong tapers.
All right. Call me right back.
Ta-da. It's okay?
Okay? You're Audrey Hepburn. Owitz.
I'm so excited about this wedding.
We're gonna do everything according to tradition.
We're gonna smash the glass,
and the signing of the Ketubah. The Hora.
Be careful. God forbid you fall off the chair.
Oh the horror. The hora.
Well maybe we won't do the chair thing.
You have to. That's the big finish.
Just remember when you're up there.
Pretend you're having a good time,
hang on for dear life,
and for fuck's sake keep your legs together.
Nobody wants to see the bride's beaver.
Don't say that in front of my dress.
Hello. York residence.
Yes we have a minute.
It's the New York Times fact checker.
Yes. Goldenblatt has two T's.
Sure. Fax it over!
We're in. We're in.
This calls for a hora.
Hey.
Oh my god. What are you doing here?
Don't look at me. Don't look at me.
Jesus Christ, Char, my ear.
You're not supposed to see me in my dress.
It's bad luck. Very bad luck.
Close your eyes.
Keep them closed.
Oh no. This is so bad.
Are all brides like that?
That's nothing.
I once had a girl in Long Island
give herself a stroke.
She pulled it together for the big day though.
Hopefully I'll get cell reception down in Mexico.
Uh-huh.
Samantha, a fan of expiration dating,
was about to enjoy one of the benefits of dating an actor.
Location. Location. Location.
It's gonna be cool working with Gus Van Sant.
Uh-huh.
Here. Let me.
Can't believe we don't get to spend my last night together.
Are you dying?
No.
Then it's not your last night.
There.
I'm gonna miss you Samantha.
Oh, save that performance for Mr. Van Sant.
It's just two weeks.
It's a long time.
Would you get out of here already? I'm late as it is.
Yeah, yeah.
And listen. When you're on location,
don't do anything I wouldn't do.
What does that rule out?
Few things.
Karaoke. I don't do that.
He flies through the air with the greatest of ease.
That daring young boy on the flying trapeze.
This is it.
It's a very nice building.
Miranda. I can't find my keys.
Magda. I'm not home.
Do you understand?
I'm already at Charlotte's.
I am not home.
Is Miranda here?
She is not home.
That's too bad. I was really looking forward to meeting her.
Magda, this is Debbie.
Nice to meet you.
All right. We just need to grab
some things out of Brady's crib.
Last time I forgot Mr. Elephant and Brady
acted like a big baby. Didn't you B-boy?
He is a big baby.
I have not cleaned the room yet.
That's okay.
This is a nice room. She has nice taste.
Yeah. I help build the crib.
Really?
What's wrong Brady?
Did you drop your binky?
Where's your binky?
Oh it's right there.
Here you go Bradilicious.
Hey, wanna go to Blockbuster
and rent a tape or something?
Okay but this time, I get to pick.
- Bye.
- Bye Magda.
There's a lot of dust down there.
You really should vacuum. Under¡¦.
That night, we all gathered at
Charlotte's casual rehearsal dinner.
You're like a lint tray.
What's happening back here?
That Debbie is crazy.
She came to my apartment with Steve.
Totally ambushed me.
I had to hide under the bed to avoid them.
Seriously?
Maybe.
Well did you see her?
Just her shoes and her nails.
And?
Both acrylic.
You know maybe you should just
meet her and get it over with.
I don't wanna meet her.
If I meet her and she's real and that
means Steve has an actual girlfriend.
Apparently, I wasn't the only
one who had trouble letting go.
Hey. What's happening there?
Oh you know. Bride. Bride. Bride. Blah, blah, blah.
Hey I just saw your friend go into the bedroom.
It's like shooting fish in a barrel.
Still no.
It's just casual sex.
Nothing's casual anymore.
When even it says so in the invitation.
Just go in there and see what happens.
Worse comes to worst, you can always hide under the bed.
I decided they were right.
It was time to get back in the swing of things.
Oh. Hey. How are you?
Wow. This is kind of uncomfortable.
Look, would you please stop calling me,
I don't have time to chat.
I've got boot and ears on my mind.
I'm sorry I never called.
I understand. You're busy.
That time of year.
You know, final exams for clown college. Or something.
And what would that interia? think?
You know, seating arrangements,
the little car, walking in the floppy shoes.
Scorting? flower and nose application?
Continue appieing?, the clown kissing.
Maybe I would have a fling.
After all, how bad could it be?
That night, Howie and I had sex
like we were teenagers again.
Meaning, he had no idea what he
was doing, and I didn't say anything.
Meanwhile, Samantha was banging around as well.
You have one new message.
Hey I'm here. It's pretty cool.
You miss me yet?
That's the thing about getting used to a man.
There's always a catch.
It's here. It's here!
Not just her wedding day, but the New York Times.
Oh my god. I have a mustache.
It's an ink stain.
Hey now look at me.
That is a terrific smile.
This is a nightmare.
It's probably just our paper.
Anyway, who cares?
We're getting married today!
I look like Hitler.
I'm having a Jewish and I look like Hitler.
Hello.
In your paper do I have a mustache?
What?
In your wedding section,
does it look like I have a mustache?
Oh. Hang on a minute.
As I feared, my fling had become a pain in the neck.
You do not look like Hitler.
Fredo Bandito maybe.
Bad luck is starting already.
Yeah. There's a little something.
But maybe it's just my paper. And your paper.
I have to go.
Clearly Charlotte was bent out of shape. And so was I.
Come on granny. I'll take you to the early bird special.
Oh god. Don't make me laugh. It hurts.
Is this still from your days as a flying relenda?
Well that's my official story and it's partially true.
But this is a sex sprain.
Good for you.
No. It was not good for me.
It was jack rabbit sex.
You know, pound, pound, pound, pound, pound.
Are straight men still allowed to do that?
No. They aren't. It's bad.
It's basically masturbating with
a woman instead of your hand.
I don't enjoy.
Carrie. You made it.
Oh. Hi. Hi.
The jack rabbit?
Uh-huh. I better¡¦
Hop to it.
Hi. Hi. Hi.
You look hot.
Thanks.
- Guess what?
- What?
I got a suite at the Mercer for later.
King size bed, huge tub.
We can have breakfast before I leave.
Unless of course we're busy doing something else. Hmm?
Yeah. I don't know.
I'm pretty tired from last night.
I'm only gonna be in town for another
day and I wanna get to know you better.
Well. Okay. We'll see.
We'll see?
I know what we'll see means. We'll see.
No. The thing is you're just visiting so..
I figured..
I figured it was a one-night kind of thing.
Just fun.
Wow.
If I'd known you were just using me,
I wouldn't have made love to you like that.
We are here today to celebrate the
union of two very special people.
Harry Goldenblatt and Charlotte York.
It's important for everyone here
to be a witness to this moment.
For the Jewish wedding ceremony has two parts.
The first designates to the community
that the Kallah, bride, and the Chatan,
groom, are for one another alone.
And the second part gives them to one another.
It's a gift.
(fuck you)
And a huge responsibility.
As one man slipped a ring on,
one woman was still trying to slip a bracelet off.
Sorry. It's a back spasm I'm sorry.
It seemed to Charlotte that the wedding had gone
from to Jewish Law to Murphy's Law.
Mozel Tov.
Hey Charlotte, are you okay?
This is a disaster.
It's the worst wedding in the history.
That's not true.
Although I know saw most of it from here down.
Harry never should have walked in
on me wearing my wedding dress.
Now we're cursed.
You're not cursed.
You're married.
You just got married.
I know but I wanted everything to be perfect.
Okay you have to stop with the tears.
You already had the perfect wedding and the marriage,
not so perfect.
You know I think this is a good sign.
I think the worse the wedding,
the better the marriage.
I have a stain on my dress.
That's good. That's a good sign.
You're just trying to make me feel better.
No I'm trying to get you to open
your eyes because you're missing it.
- What?
- Everything.
You're missing your wedding.
You have a wonderful man who loves you.
Who will be there to catch you when you fall.
Do you know how special that is?
I would love to find a man
who's strong enough to catch me.
So, let's get to that reception so
you can fall in a cake or something.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Perfect.
Oh Christ. Oh Christ.
Are you okay?
Oh yeah. I'm just feeling a little sad.
It was just so beautiful.
The ceremony.
My bracelet.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Can I have you attention please.
Oh god, it's time for the toast.
Top me off. I'm next.
I would like to raise a glass
to Harry and Charlotte
cause they found each other despite all the bullshit.
Hey. Hey. It's tough out there.
I mean, people don't care like they used to.
People leave you hanging.
People, are a bitch.
Is this a toast or a roast?
Here's to love.
And love means never,
ever having to say
'you used me for sex'.
Thanks Howie. That's nice.
Mozel Tov.
It was a Mozel Tov cocktail.
Carrie said the worse the wedding,
the better the marriage.
Well then I think Howie just got us to our silver.
Hi. Hello. Great.
I would like to congratulate
my very brave friend Charlotte.
Who knows what she wants and who goes for it.
Not everyone can do that.
Especially when it comes to love.
Some of us can't even say the words. But.
Sorry hon. Good speech though.
Maybe Miranda just got us to our Gold.
He's certainly acrobatic.
Oh yeah. He's a regular jerk de soleil.
Do you think everyone knows I slept with him?
Yes. And they all think you're a big horror.
I don't like this. I'm afraid of..
What? What's the worst that can happen?
We'll live happily ever after?
And of course this being a wedding,
there was one more catch to go.
Okay. Who's ready to catch the bouquet?
Not me. I've lit myself on fire,
I showed emotion in public.
I think I'm done.
Oh you were fabulous.
I believe you mean flammable.
Okay. Now you're done.
It wasn't the perfect catch.
And neither was mine.
But I survived because I have a good safety net.
ÀÚ¸·Á¦ÀÛ - ³×ÀÌÆ® µå¶ó¸¶ 24
(http:/club. nate. com/24)
µ¿È£È¸ ¿Ü ¹«ÜÀ¯ÃâÀ» ±ÝÁöÇÕ´ÏÏ´ÙÙ
www.tvsubtitles.net