ÀÚ¸·Á¦ÀÛ - ³×ÀÌÆ® µå¶ó¸¶ 24
(http:/club. nate. com/24)
'Sex And The City'
Sarah Jessica Parker(Carrie Bradshaw æµ)
Kim Cattrall(Samantha Jones æµ)
Kristin Davis(Charlotte York McDougal æµ)
Cynthia Nixon(Miranda Hobbes æµ)
¿µ¾îëº»
ÁøÇö°æ(jhk8012@nate. com)
½ÌÅ©ÆíÁý
¿ÀÈï¹Î(echem@nate. com)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON HBO: 2004/01/04
Season 6
Epi 13. the unbearable lightness of seeing
A single gal spends most of her
life searching for the perfect male.
And out of the blue, it arrives.
Aleksandr Petrovsky was a
rather famous artist with whom I had
one rather infamous date.
It's been three whole weeks.
I thought you died or something.
I did die from dejection.
How could you have left me
on the street all alone.
It still hurts.
You'll get over it.
You're a big boy.
And where did you get this information?
- I was in Holland for work.
- Hmm, Holland??
Been there?
To the land of the wooden shoes, no.
No, no, no.
I brought you a little present.
Let's go.
Milk chocolate?
Or pehaps you like dark?
I've got right here.
You don't have a mouse trap in there, do you?
No, why would I?
I was being silly.
You know, in the cartoons, when they
put their hands and the thing..
Ok.
Et voila.
Light or dark?
Second only to the
search of the perfect male,
is the search for the perfect fragrance.
Am I peppermint musk?
Oh, no.
Ladies, I'm taking a lover.
Yes, a lover. Aleksandr Petrovsky.
Wait, the only guy?
I beg your pardon.
My lover is not old.
He is worldly and wise and very sexy.
He is sexy.
Very.
Yesterday I almost did it with him on
a park bench in front of children.
What stopped you?
Common decency.
Oh that.
Well, that and the fact that I'm not
lover ready.
I need a little bikini waxage.
Well, then snap to it.
Don't play hard to get with a man
who's hard to get.
Maybe cucumber basil.
Why would you wanna smell
like a salad?
I can't decide what I am.
What do mean not old?
Charlotte e-mailed me his photo.
Hello, sixty.
He is in his lover perfect, early fifties.
That's a good age.
They've been around the block, they know
how to use their cock.
Oh, you rhyme now.
And where did you get his picture?
I googled him.
I wanted Miranda to see your potential new boyfriend.
Not boyfriend, lover.
How long are you going to keep saying
in like that?
Uncomfortable with my taking a lover?
Maybe he cold be more than a lover.
Ah, no, the only place this is going is Loverville.
Well, I could see it going somewhere.
Oh, please, half the time, I can't even
understand him.
We have nothing in common.
He's in and out of Europe.
- That could be good.
- Honey, you're not listeing.
She only wants him to be in and out of her.
Yes, but in a much less obvious sounding way.
How about? petuli?
No, you need something classic, clean.
But just a hint of neurosis.
How about you?
Are you finding anything?
I don't know.
I'm trying to figure out what Steve might like.
Just get some old spice and call it a day.
Steve does not wear old spice.
He wears nothing and he smells great.
Oh, Miranda and Steve sitting in a tree
K.I.S.S.I.N.G, first comes..
Well, actually first comes baby.
Oh great.
Now I have to spend the rest of the day smelling like..
- Apples and hay.
- You bastard.
Ok, let's go.
Aren't you going to get something for your new lover?
I suspect he already likes the way I smell.
Hey.
How lucky are we?
Very.
If Miranda and Steve had a fragrance,
it would be called Perfection.
If Miranda, Steve, and Robert, her ex and neighbor
had a fragrance, it wold be called Less Than Perfection.
In fact, Awful, Uncomfortable, and Terrible.
Hi.
Well, if it isn't the happy couple.
How are you today.
Y'all have a nice day.
So the doctor said that Harry and I
have to wait at least two months before
we even get try to get pregnant again.
And I like to back to work, but then if I do
get pregnant, that's not really fair to the new
employer, so I..
I'm sleeping and walking,
sleeping and walking, how am I doing that?
That's rude.
This is important to me.
I know it's important to you,
you know it's important to you,
the homeless guy on the corner of 57th
and 7th knows it's important to you.
Could we please talk about something else?
I'll give a hundred dollars if you say something
bitchy about someone we know.
No.
I'm trying to figure out my next direction
and I need to talk about it.
Fine, Talk to my ears bleed.
But do yourself a favor and stop for a minute
and look at the light.
You mean the fact that no matter what happens
with the baby, Harry and I will always have each other?
No, Char, the frigging light over there in the park.
When did it become fall?
Somewhere between your ovaries and my boredom.
Imagine.
Being blind, not being able to see
a beautiful day like today.
Can you think of anything worse?
Stone washed jeans with a matching jacket.
Maybe I should stop thnking so much about
myself and volunteer for the blind or something.
That would be a nice thing to do.
Very Jacky-O
Ok, let me begin.
Can I ask you a question?
Yes, it will hurt a little.
No, that's not the question.
Are you Russian?
Yes.
See.
Hurt a little.
Yes, I was wondering
how do you say hello in Russian?
- Zdravstvuite.
And uh, how do you say thank you?
- Spasibo.
You're welcome.
The only thing more uncomfortable than a bikini wax,
is an elevator ride with an ex.
Luckily, Miranda had figured out a way to avoid that.
Unfortunately, Robert had also.
Robert, hi.
Ok, I guess I deserve that.
Robert.
I'm sorry.
I've never meant to hurt you.
Steve and I just fell back in love.
Oh.
And so what was I to you?
A little half time show?
What?
Not at all.
I never thought that Steve and I would
get back together, or I never would have
started up with you.
I hope you understand that.
Well, I'll try.
And I hope you understand when you get my bill.
- Your bill?
- Yeah, my bill.
For services rendered.
You know, my stud fee.
Robert, come on.
No, no, no, no.
Hey, It's cool.
I got your singing.
You're a busy working mother,
too tired to go out and eat,
Hoonen Kitchen, too tired to go out and fuck,
call Robert.
- That's not true.
- Sure it is.
- Fastfood, Fast fuck.
- You were not a fast fuck.
No, you're right, I wasn't.
I was slow.
Nice and slow.
Just the way you liked it.
Ooh, Robert, ooh, yes.
Robert, oh god.
Robert, ooh.
No man has ever been in this deep.
Hey, what are doing back?
I gave Robert custody of the elevator.
What?
We're moving my stuff in here next week
and you gave him the elevator?
You're lucky I didn't give him Brady.
I bumped into him on the stairs.
How bad was it?
Hug me.
Oh, it's that bad, huh?
So we can't ever use the elevator?
Not between 8 a. m. and 10 p. m.
- We have a baby in a stroller.
- I know.
Why, why, why did I have to shit where I eat?
Look, he's just upset, it'll blow over.
I don't think so, Steve.
The man is crazy in love with me and
now he's acting out, talking about how
I said no man's ever been in me that deep.
What?
Nothing.
Steve.
Nothing. Fine.
Wednesday night, after dinner,
I took the express elevator to Loverville.
Spasibo.
Oh, you speak Russian very well.
Is that the only word you know?
Zdravstvuite.
Yes, but is that the only word you know?
There is my studio, and here's my house.
You have the entire floor?
Not at first, but over the years.
- Spasibo.
- Zdravstvuite.
This used to be some kind of sewing
factory, sweat shop in 1920s.
That's a lovely story.
Very nice, if you like that whole window sky thing.
Yes, it's lovely light in the morning.
Study and kitchen
Would you like some fruit or martini
or something?
Why don't you show me upstairs?
My Russian may have been shaky,
but I discovered I spoke lover very well.
Turns out, I'd found a sweet bed
and breafast in Loverville.
Good morning.
Um, where?
Morning.
Come, come, sit.
In the light of day,
everything looked completely different.
Would you like some coffee?
What kind?
Um, Regular.
Regular coffee is for regular people.
You are not regular.
I hope I'm not in the way.
What, what?
No, no. It's Violet, Admar, Lee.
Hey, everybody, this is Carrie.
It's my staff.
I saw(?) them out sitting in the street with the sign
I'll do art for food.
Speaking of food,
pancakes for the lady.
You're hungry.
But you, Aren't you gonna eat?
No, I'm done.
I'm off to Amsterdam remember?
Oh, yeah. Right.
Maybe before I leave, I'll have one more little bite.
La voiture ne va pas attendre pour toujours.
Oui, oui, je pars toute de suite.
Passeport, portefeuille, bien.
Maintenant, sois poli avec M. Groge.
There I was having pancakes at eyehop(?),
the international house of Petrovsky's.
And they just went on about their business
totally unfazed.
Oh, honey, they've seen it all.
And you gotta give it to him,
making pancakes for pussy.
That's a classic touch.
What?
You don't think you're the first babe
he buttered up for.
No, no, no, you're right.
You're right.
thewhole thing was so choreographed.
No, he knew exactly what he was doing.
Sounds good to me.
I miss a man with the moves.
So Smith no moves.
No, he has them, most of them I've given him,
but he has them.
Truth time.
I'm a little jealous.
Of what?
My grand slam breakfast?
You've got yourself a man,
a real powerplayer.
Someone who takes charge, drags you to the bed,
has his way with you, doesn't have to ask what you want,
and fucks you and fucks you.
We're not talking about me anymore, are we?
No, I mean, Smith, he's hot but he's a baby.
He's almost thirty.
Still, I swear sometimes I don't know whether to
blow him or burp him.
I need a grown-up.
So, uh, how were they?
The pancakes?
Delicious, exactly what I wanted,
I couldn't get enough.
No, I was referring to the moves.
Oh, delicious, exactly what I wanted,
I couldn't get enough.
Good for you.
So, how many pancakes do you think
that kitchen has seen?
Does it matter?
In the cold, harsh reality of daylight,
I knew it didn't matter.
But in the colder, harsher reality of a woman
who just slept with someone he likes, it did.
Google dot com showed many many listings
on the art of Aleksandr Petrovsky, and one
on his many many women.
According to certain scientists, whenever a woman
has sex, her body produces a chemical which
causes her to emotionally attach.
This chemical may also account for the series of
terrifying questions that involuntarily pop into
our minds after just one casual tryst.
Questions like does he like me, will he call again,
and the classic, where is this all going?
When it comes to the men, even when we try to
keep it light, how do we wind up in the dark?
Hey, I've got this invite to a party
Teen Posse's throwing.
Top thirty under thirty.
- I'm one of them.
- Hah.
You wanna go?
Teen Posse and me, no.
And no.
Well, my agent and my manager
really want me to go.
At least look at the invite and tell me
how lame it is.
The party may have been all wrong
but it was being hosted by Richard Wright.
What?
Lame ass?
No, not so lame ass.
Richard Wright is a big name in
the hotel business.
He brings a certain something.
And it was exactly the certain something
that Samantha was missing.
You should go.
In fact, I'll go with you.
What the hell.
Cool.
And I'm not relly allowed to try and pregnant
again for another two months.
So you said.
And I thought I have all this time
on my hands to volunteer.
Ok, working as a guide for visually impaired person
is a serious undertaking.
We suggest allour potential volunteers go to
a public place like a park or a department store
with a friend and let him or her lead
your around blindfolded.
Blindfolded?
Yeah, try not to take the blindfold off
no matter how uncomfortable you feel
and you'll begin to get a sense of what it's
like not to be able to rely on your sight.
Ok, bye.
I mean where can this possibly go?
I thought you didn't want it to go anywhere.
Well, that was before I slept with him,
now, not so sure.
Interesting.
No, ridiculous, and according to my new best
friend google dot com,..
You googles him.
The man has dated every woman in New York
from 1977 until, well, until last Wednesday.
And who knows how many pancakes he's making
for other ridiculous women around the world.
Oh god, listen to me, and I've only slept with
him once.
Ok, let's get blind.
So once I put this over my eyes, I can't take it off.
I need you to guide me.
I'm there.
This is embarrassing.
No, thinking you can take a lover is embarrassing.
This is halping people.
How's my hair?
Oh, that's European code, it's him.
Should I answer it?
Ok.
Hello
Carrie, it's Aleks.
Hi. How's Amsterdam.
What?
I can, I can't hear you.
Oh you know what, I need better reception.
I'm gonna go right over there.
Don't go away.
Ok.
Hi.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Tomorrow night?
Yes.
What?
- The reception is very bad.
- Bad reception, yes.
- Tomorrow, are you free?
- Yes, I'm free.
- Sorry I can't hear you.
- I'm free.
- Ok, tomorrow at 9.
- Yes, I will be there.
- Carrie, Carrie?
- Hello?
Sweetie?
Would like the sample in the air?
- Do you need some assisstance?
- No, thank you.
I'm trying to help the blind.
I just got separated from my friend,
but I'm sure she'll find me.
- Lumiere?
- Oh, no, bad, bad.
- Oh, excuse me.
- Sorry.
And there in the dark, Charlotte realized
she had no idea where she was going in
Barney's or in real life.
but sometimes, even if you're not sure of your
direction, you can find your way
to something wonderful.
Don't they have these over there in the..
I swear I looked and looked and then I thought
best if she finds me.
I'm eating them tomorrow, cute, huh?
Oh yeah.
Ok, ok.
Let's just go in front of the line, like I suggested.
I don't like pushing in front of people.
Oh, grow up.
Smith Jerrod, we're on the list.
Oh my god, owesome.
Love your hair.
Let me just check you off.
And you are?
Samantha Jones.
Aren't you a sight for sore eyes.
Um, dude.
He's with me.
- Oh, I'm sorry, Richard Wright.
- Smith Jerrod.
Let's get some drinks, shall we?
So, how long have you been babysitting?
Said the man who's hosting a Teen Posse party.
Don't rub it in.
The hotels have to stay hip.
So I have to bend over backwards.
? of these trendy little pissass.
Well, you look good.
That's 'cause I'm looking at you, gorgeous.
Two more scotch rocks.
What's up?
Can I get you a scotch?
No thank, man, I'm an AA.
You kids today.
So how do you two know each other?
We used to go out.
And then I fucked it up royally
and lost the best thing I ever had.
Oh my god, Smith, you have to come.
Paulie is snorting pretzel out of his nose.
- You have to come.
- It's fucking hilarious.
- Come on.
- Paulie. do it again.
Paulie is snorting pretzels out his nose.
Fuck you.
Okay, this is the last load.
For a guy with no stuff, you've got stuff.
Let's get the TV first.
What the fuck?
That wasn't like that when we moved it in here.
Oh my god.
- Robert.
- What?
Nah, you think?
Um hello, he's mad, your name is on the boxes,
he lives in the building.
Nah, it doesn't seem like him, I musta
bumped it or something.
Steve, he's crazy in love with me.
You didn't see how angry he was on the stairs.
Ok, this is bullshit.
I'm not gonna live like this.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna take care of things.
Be kind.
He's still in love with me.
Steve?
Look, I need to talk to you
about this whole Miranda thing.
What about her?
I'll be right back, baby.
Turns out Petrovsky wasn't the only one
with the international house.
We're sorry.
She's sorry.
I'm sorry.
We're sorry.
I appreciate that.
What happened?
Let's just put it this way.
He won't be bothering us again.
Was he very upset?
When it came to Robert,
Steve thought it was kinder
to leave Miranda in the dark.
Samantha.
Hey, where are you going, babe?
Richard wanted to show me one of his
remodelled suites.
Cool, can I come?
No.
No, Smith, you can't come.
Look, this was fun, but where is it going?
Gorgeous?
You go play with your friends
and I'll go play woth mine.
Samantha.
Two years ago, I was on top of the fucking world.
I almost took bullshit beer basher
bunch of kids with six pack abs.(?)
This is a world class hotel.
Fuck it. I've down this road before.
Richard may have,
but Samantha haven't.
I just wanted to make sure you got
home safe.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I hate myself for doing this to you.
Oh god.
It's ok, it's okay.
Come on.
Let's get you out of here.
Even in the dark, Smith could still see Samantha.
And for the very first time, she saw him.
I have some work to do in my studio,
but you're welcome to stay, ok?
It was at that moment I realized
I wasn't really comfortable in Loverville.
I'm not that kind of google.
Why?
I just wanted to say thank you.
I'm gonna go.
Ok, then I'll call you tomorrow, all right?
Um.
This has been really lovely
but I don't think I'm cut out for it.
I don't understand.
The pancakes and the other ladies,
it's just not for me.
There are pancakes but no other ladies.
Well, I have a book with a few emergency
telephone numbers, yes.
But now I just see you.
This is not about great bang, this..
I just like you.
Why me?
You make a good breakfast.
So what's all this?
It's too soon to tell.
ÀÚ¸·Á¦ÀÛ - ³×ÀÌÆ® µå¶ó¸¶ 24
(http:/club. nate. com/24)
µ¿È£È¸ ¿Ü ¹«ÜÀ¯ÃâÀ» ±ÝÁöÇÕ´ÏÏ´ÙÙ
www.tvsubtitles.net