All I'm saying is, if they
took all the money they spent
trying to make
a decent Hulk movie,
they could probably
just make an actual Hulk.
That is apt and amusing.
I think I shall share that
with Amy Farrah Fowler.
She'll appreciate
the witticism.
Thank you.
It'll also help improve her
initial impression of you.
So what's going on with you two?
Well, the status is
as it always was.
She's a girl. She's a friend.
She is not my--
please forgive me
for doing this--
"girlfriend."
Right, right.
So you're still just
texting and emailing?
You don't feel any need
to hang out with her, you know--
be in the same room?
Leonard, you are
my best friend.
I've known you
for seven years,
and I can barely tolerate
sitting on the couch with you.
Imagine my attitude regarding
prolonged physical proximity
to Amy Farrah Fowler.
Got it.
I sense judgment on your part.
No, no.
Maybe a little.
May I suggest that your
criticism is based on jealousy.
Jealousy? What do I
have to be jealous of?
I have a functioning
and satisfying relationship
with a female.
You have none.
Oh, right. That.
Jealousy is an ugly
green-eyed monster--
not unlike the Hulk--
who, by the way,
also has a girlfriend.
In this iteration,
Jennifer Connelly,
whom you may recall as
the girlfriend of Russell Crowe
in A Beautiful Mind,
a feel-good romp if
there ever was one.
I'm not jealous.
Leonard not jealous.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 4x05 ♪
The Desperation Emanation
Original Air Date on October 21, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
You know, it just
occurred to me,
if there are an infinite
number of parallel universes,
in one of them,
there's probably a Sheldon
who doesn't believe
parallel universes exist.
Probably. What's your point?
No point.
It's just one
of the things
that makes one of
the mes chuckle.
What makes you
chuckle, Leonard?
Hmm, recently?
Not much.
Is it because of the
conflict that arises
from your desperate need
to pair-bond with a woman,
and the apparent collective
decision of all womankind
to deny you
that opportunity?
Um...
Shut up.
You know,
when my grandfather died,
and Meemaw was alone,
my mom arranged for her
to visit a center
three times a week
where she could socialize
with other lonely people.
It's very nice.
They discuss current events,
play bridge, get a hot meal.
That sounds lovely.
It is if you
like bridge.
Do you like bridge,
Leonard?
Sheldon, I'm just not
dating someone right now.
I don't need to go
to a senior center.
Meemaw resisted at first,
but now she loves it.
Fine. If I don't meet someone
soon, you can put me in a home.
It's not a home.
It's a senior center.
We'd never put
Meemaw in a home!
Hey, guys.
Hey.
All right, I'll bow
to social pressure: Hey!
Excuse me. That's my girlfriend,
Bernadette.
I assigned her
her own ringtone--
"Bernadette,"
by The Four Tops.
Hello, Bernadette.
When I call him, his phone
plays "Brown Eyed Girl."
Which, now that
I think about it,
is not so good.
You realize he's just
rubbing our noses in the fact
that he has a girlfriend,
and we don't.
You mean, you don't.
You have a girlfriend?
How could you have a girlfriend?
You can't even speak to women.
Two words-- deaf chick.
It doesn't matter
if I can't talk,
because she can't hear me.
What?
That's what she said.
Great. You have a girlfriend,
Howard's got a girlfriend,
Sheldon's got
a girl...
No, no, no, no!
...who's a friend.
Thank you.
What about you, Stuart?
You have a
girlfriend yet?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I met her at Comic-Con,
the one place in the world
where saying
"I own a comic bookstore"
is an actual pickup line.
Oh. Well, good for you.
Not really. She's horrible.
When she wants to have sex,
she puts on her plus-size
Wonder Woman costume and shouts,
"Who wants to take a ride
in my invisible plane?"
Why don't you just
break up with her?
No, no, I can't.
Why not?
'Cause then I'd be alone,
like you.
Dude, why don't you just invoke
your girlfriend pact
with Wolowitz?
Because I don't
need his girlfriend
to set me up with one
of her girlfriends.
I'm perfectly capable of
finding a girl on my own.
Oh, Leonard, you remind me
of the funny old story
about a man
who walks into a women's
correctional institution
with a stack of paperwork
that will allow
the female convicts to go free.
You're saying I
couldn't get laid
in a women's prison with
a handful of pardons.
Are you going to let me
tell the story or not?
Leonard?
Are you sleeping?
No.
Are you ill?
Are you still depressed
because you're alone,
and no one loves you?
I don't know. Maybe.
I want you to know
that I'm genuinely concerned
about your well-being.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
But it's still no reason
to have your feet in my spot.
May I offer an observation?
What the hell?
How long has she been here?
Since we got home
from the comic bookstore.
That was two hours ago.
As per your suggestion,
we're hanging out.
Quite frankly, I don't see
what all the hoopla's about.
Go on, Amy.
From a neurobiological
standpoint, Leonard,
you may be alone
because your psychological state
is causing
an actual pheromone-based stink
of desperation.
Did you know that, Leonard?
No.
I did.
I understand
that some people find mates
in social gathering places
such as bars or taverns.
Have you tried a bar or tavern?
No, I'm not gonna try
to pick up a woman in a bar.
Wise decision. You see, Amy,
success at a bar is based
on classic male attributes
such as height, strength,
attractiveness,
the ability to hold one's liquor
and throw darts--
separately or together.
Leonard has none of these
attributes, right, Leonard?
Right.
That's not true of all bars.
Juice bars, for example.
Oh! Good point, Amy.
Yeah, building
on your premise,
Leonard could
frequent sushi bars,
salad bars, oyster bars,
the Apple Genius Bar...
What are you doing?
Keep going. I'm listening.
That was rude.
He does it all the time.
He's a cornucopia
of social awkwardness.
Cornucopia.
What a mellifluous word.
Let's make that our word
of the day.
Agreed. And we'll use
mellifluous tomorrow.
Well, I have to void my bladder.
It was nice spending this time
with you.
Wait.
I have a request.
Yes?
I'd like you to meet my mother.
I see.
Can I get back to you on that?
Certainly. Good night.
Good night.
Leonard, Leonard, Leonard,
Leonard, Leonard,
Leonard, Leonard...
Yeah, what?
Amy Farrah Fowler has asked me
to meet her mother.
Yeah. So?
What does that mean?
Well, you know
how you're always saying
that Amy is a girl
who's your friend,
and not your girlfriend?
Uh-huh.
You can't say
that anymore.
Wait. What?
Look, she obviously wants
to take your relationship
to the next level.
I don't want
the next level.
I like this level.
Fix it for me!
Me?
Well, how am I supposed
to fix it?
Simple! You want a girlfriend,
Amy wants
to be someone's girlfriend.
Take her off my hands.
I give you my blessing.
That is insane.
You're right.
It would never work.
Amy finds you tedious.
Okay, good luck.
Wait! What am I
supposed to do?
Well, have you considered
telling her how you feel?
Leonard, I'm a physicist,
not a hippie.
All right, well, let me see
if I can explain your situation
using physics.
What would you be
if you were attached
to another object
by an inclined plane wrapped
helically around an axis?
Screwed.
There you go.
Amy's right.
He is tedious.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, get the door!
Why can't you get it?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
You know I'm doing a bowel cleanse
for my colonoscopy!
I'm like an upside-down
volcano here.
Oh, hey.
I hope you didn't hear that.
The volcano thing? No.
What's with the T-shirt?
You working at the
Apple store now?
No, it's just something
I threw on.
I know all your shirts.
That's not one of them...
You were pretending to
work at the Genius Bar
to pick up women,
weren't you?
Yeah.
Turns out,
they guard the iPods,
but they don't
guard the shirts.
So, how'd it go?
It was going well.
I was showing
this super hot girl
how to boot up in Safe Mode.
The manager got suspicious,
and, well, long story short,
they really do have
a little jail in the mall.
Just FYI, don't try to go
back with a fake mustache.
I mean, they may not
really be geniuses,
but they see
right through that.
I want to invoke
the girlfriend pact, Howard.
You that desperate?
No, I just...
I want what you have.
You know, I want
a woman in my life.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Holy Moses,
how much liquid can
be in one tokus?
To be clear, I meant like
Bernadette, not your mother.
Yeah, I know
what you mean.
Well, I'm off to meet
Bernadette's friend.
How do I look?
As if one of the plants
from
Invasion of the Body Snatchers
duplicated you in every way,
only with an absurd
amount of hair gel.
What are you
working on?
I'm removing
my digital footprint
from the Internet
so Amy Farrah Fowler
can't find me
and compel me to meet her mother.
Ah.
You're going off the grid.
Exactly.
The old Unabomber approach.
Kudos.
Thank you.
I've also sent Amy a
relationship termination notice
and changed my cell phone number
and e-mail address.
What if she just comes over?
She'll get lost.
We no longer live
at 2311 Los Robles.
We now live at 311 Los Robles.
You changed the address
on the building?
What about mail?
Oh, no worries--
I explained my predicament
to our letter carrier.
He was sympathetic.
His exact words were:
"Got your back, Jack.
Bitches be crazy."
Who is it?
Amy Farrah Fowler.
Darn! She found me!
She's been here before.
The only flaw in an
otherwise perfect plan.
Now, get my back, Jack.
What do you want to do?
Tell her I'm not here.
Okay, where are you?
I don't know.
You'll have to devise a scenario
that plausibly
explains my absence,
keeping in mind that the key to
a good lie lies in the details.
Hi, Amy.
Sheldon's not here.
All right.
Way to go on the details.
Thanks again for
doing this, Bernadette.
Oh, I take pacts
very seriously.
One time at my lab,
a petri dish
of genetically modified
super-virus went missing.
That day we made a pinky swear
never to admit
we crossed Ebola
with the common cold.
Why the hell
would you cross Ebola
with the common cold?
We never did.
That would be
a terrible, terrible thing.
Hi. Sorry I'm late--
I was at the gym.
Spin class--
worked up quite a sweat.
Joy, this is Leonard.
Leonard, this is Joy.
Hi.
You don't look
like a genius.
Go ahead, say
something smart.
Uh...
Aah! Time's up.
Just kidding.
First thing you need
to know about me:
I'm hilarious.
Yeah.
So, Bernadette tells me
she knows you from
self-defense classes?
Yeah. Israeli Krav Maga.
Lots of fun.
Basically,
a hundred different ways
to rip a guy's nuts off.
Wow. Wouldn't think there'd
be that many.
Number 42!
Whoa!
Isn't she a pip?
Proxima Centauri's
the nearest star.
The celestial bodies
that follow are
Alpha Centauri A, Toli,
Barnard's Star,
Wolf 359...
Lalande 21185,
Sirius A, Sirius B,
BL-Ceti, UV-Ceti,
Ross 154...
Ross 248...
Epsilon Eridani,
Lac-9352,
Ross 128,
Procyon A...
Oh, darn, that's wrong!
EZ Aquarii A,
EZ Aquarii B,
EZ Aquarii C,
Procyon A.
Those are the stars
that are nearest to me.
Tra-la-la and fiddle-dee-dee.
Oh, dear.
They really do be crazy.
This lobster's good
on the way down
and the way up.
Should be-- it's
$30 a pound.
Hey, this is a date, right?
Yep, it is.
73!
Whoa!
Excuse me, I have to go
to the little girls' room...
and take a wicked whiz.
I'll go with you.
Fair warning--
I had the asparagus.
My pea is gonna
stink up the place.
I think she likes you.
EZ Aquarii B...
EZ Aquarii C...
Excuse me, madam.
Sheldon?
Rats!
I believe a misunderstanding
may have occurred
when I asked you
to meet my mother.
No misunderstanding.
I've learned what that
request actually means,
and I don't want to be
joined to another object
by an inclined plane wrapped
helically around an axis.
In what way are
you screwed?
All I want to do is present you
as my boyfriend to my mother
so she'll be satisfied
that I'm in a relationship.
So we'd be
perpetrating a ruse?
Precisely.
And you haven't fallen
hopelessly in love with me?
Don't be absurd.
I find the notion
of romantic love
to be an unnecessary
cultural construct
that adds no value to
human relationships.
Amy Farrah Fowler, that's
the most pragmatic thing
anyone has ever said to me.
I trust this clarification
allows us to return
to boy-slash-friend-slash-
girl-slash-friend status.
Of course.
Would you like to join me
for Chinese food?
Sheldon, please,
you're suffocating me.
My apologies.
Good night, Amy.
Good night, Sheldon.
Come on, just
give her a chance.
Maybe she'll grow on you.
Or maybe she'll finally succeed in
ripping my nuts off.
There are still 93 ways
she hasn't tried yet.
Look, H-Howard,
I appreciate
the effort, but this is, like,
the worst date of my life.
Seriously?
I was once robbed by a pre-op
transsexual I met on J-Date,
and that didn't
even crack my top ten.
I guess the difference is,
I have some self-respect.
Not that I've ever seen.
It's relatively new.
I just know that
I'm not gonna spend time
with someone I don't like
simply to have a girlfriend.
I'm okay on my own.
Good news-- I made
lots of room for dessert.
Look, uh, Joy, it was nice
to meet you, but...
Yeah, you, too.
Hey, you got anything for next weekend?
I need a date for
my cousin's wedding.
You're asking me out?
Yeah.
And it's an open bar,
so I'll probably
be giving it away.
I look forward to it.
MRS. FOWLER
It's nice to meet you, too, Sheldon.
I honestly didn't believe Amy
when she told me
she had a boyfriend.
I assure you I am quite real
and I'm having regular intercourse
with your daughter.
What?
Oh, yes.
We're like wild
animals in heat.
It's a wonder neither
of us has been hurt.
Amy... what is he saying?
You wanted me to have
a boyfriend, Mother.
Well, here he is.
Have to sign off now.
My hunger for Sheldon
is stirring in my loins.
Oh, yes, it's time
for me to make love
to your daughter's vagina.
Thank you, Sheldon,
that went very well.
Agreed.
Amy, I find
myself wondering
if we should actually
engage in coitus
at least one time
in our relationship.
Bazinga.
Bedtime. Please
show yourself out.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net