(groans in disgust)
Problem?
This is the worst cobbler
I've ever eaten.
It tastes like it's made of
actual ground-up shoemaker.
Amusing. A play on the
two meanings of "cobbler."
(laughs)
Hey, guys. Guess who
I found at LAX?
My baby sister Priya.
Excuse me, I object.
You propose a guessing game,
yet you don't give me
enough time to guess.
For the record,
I was going to say:
"Your sister Priya."
Oh, Sheldon. You haven't
changed a bit, have you?
Why would I change?
The hope has been that
you'd eventually bend
to public opinion.
So, Priya, what brings
you back to L.A.?
I have a one-day layover
on my way to Toronto.
Corporate merger.
Can you believe it?
Little Priya's one
of the lead attorneys
for the biggest
car company in India.
Given that when we met her,
she was finishing law school
and planning an internship
at a large Indian car company,
it's actually
extremely plausible.
And your poll numbers
just keep dropping.
I want to catch up
with all of you,
but first I really
must visit the loo.
I'm going, too; I'll
show you where it is.
All right, this goes
without saying,
but I'm just going
to say it anyway.
Hands off my sister.
Why would I touch her? She's
covered with airplane germs.
I'm so not talking to you.
I'm talking to him.
Hey. I've got a girlfriend now.
Oh, please.
My sister's much hotter
than your girlfriend,
and you know it.
Let's just agree
they're both hot.
But dude, that's my sister
you're talking about!
Okay, forget who's hotter.
The first time Priya came to
L.A., Leonard and I made a pact
out of respect to our
friendship and to you
that neither of us
would hit on her.
Did you pinky-swear?
Yes.
Okay, then.
Cobbler. I'm still laughing.
It's really nice
to see you again, Leonard.
Yeah. It's good
to see you, too.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 4x06 ♪
The Irish Pub Formulation
Original Air Date on October 28, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
So you got any special plans
with your sister?
Oh, not really. Just hang out.
I always tell people,
"If you have only one day
in Los Angeles,
make it a train day."
Train day?
The fun starts with brunch
at Carney's in Studio City,
a hotdog stand in a
converted railroad dining car.
Next stop, Travel Town,
an outdoor museum featuring
43 railroad engines,
cars, and other rolling stock
from the 1880s to the 1930s.
And, finally, we're off to the
glitz and glamour of Hollywood,
for dinner at--that's right--
the Hollywood Carney's,
a hotdog stand in a different
converted railroad dining car.
I don't think
we're going to do that.
Well, then apparently
you hate fun.
Priya's not back yet?
Well, I guess
that's not unusual.
Women, men, the whole
sitting-standing deal.
So what are we talking about?
Uh, my plans
with Priya.
He rejected Train Day.
Did you make it clear that
it's two different train cars
turned into hotdog stands?
Abundantly.
I guess he just hates fun.
That's what I said!
Okay, so... what's
new with you guys?
I have a girlfriend now.
Hey, good for you!
Yeah, I just want
to put it out there
in case I inadvertently
squirt any pheromones
in your direction.
Happy?
So, Priya, what are your
plans while you're here?
I don't know. I just
have the one day.
Do you like trains?
Not particularly.
You might as well just wait
at the airport for your flight.
"You are in a forest.
"There is quicksand to the west,
a path leads to the east."
(typing)
Go east.
"An iron gate blocks your way."
(typing)
Open gate.
"It's locked."
Hmm.
Well, so much for that.
It's getting pretty late.
How come you're still up?
I found an emulator online that
lets you play classic text-based
computer games from the 1980s.
That's pretty cool.
Oh, yes. It runs on the world's
most powerful graphics chip:
imagination.
You've really got
to get out more.
(typing)
Go north.
"You can't go that way."
(typing)
Go west.
"A troll blocks your passage."
Okay. Fasten your seatbelts.
(typing)
Kill troll.
"With what?"
(typing)
With sword.
(knock at door)
"You don't have the sword."
Good golly, it's as if
it's actually happening to me.
Raj finally went to bed.
Sheldon's still up.
You said he goes
to bed at 9:00.
Yeah, he does, but he got caught
up in a computer game and...
(typing)
SHELDON: Hit troll with axe!
Hit troll with axe!
My, this is one tough troll.
Can't you get rid of him?
If the past is any
indication, no.
SHELDON:
Leonard, I'm trapped
in quicksand!
The axe is dragging me down!
Drop axe!
SHELDON:
Drop axe, brilliant!
Give me a minute.
Sheldon.
Hold on.
Trying to figure out
how to get the bucket,
so I can carry the mud
past the dragon.
Sheldon, you need to
work in the morning.
I know!
Well, then bed, mister!
Five more minutes!
Really?
You're going to risk getting
sleepy in the middle of your
thermodynamic
fluctuations seminar?
You know what happens
when you yawn in public.
Everyone will see
my oddly shaped uvula.
You don't want that, do you?
No.
But it's a shame our society
mocks the differently uvulated.
Who was at the door?
Uh, building manager.
They have to fix a pipe,
so the water'll be off
tomorrow from noon to 2:00.
That's unacceptable.
We're supposed to be
given written notice.
Well, no, it doesn't matter--
we'll be at work.
What if I spill tomato
soup on my shirt,
and have to come home to change,
only to find there's no water
for an enzyme soak?
Bifurcated uvula, Sheldon!
I'll have the chicken noodle.
Good night!
(whispering): We're going
to have to be very quiet.
SHELDON:
I know how to
get the bucket!
I can turn the axe around
and use the handle to reach it.
Let's see.
(typing)
Go north.
"You are in a forest."
(typing)
Go north.
"You are in a forest."
(typing)
Go north.
"You are in a forest."
Oh dear, I believe I'm lost.
Well, I'll just have to get
a fresh start tomorrow.
No, no, no! You just
took a wrong turn.
You just need to map it out.
Come on, I'll help you.
So you stopped at the stream,
and you turned
north three times?
Yes.
You're right.
You're lost. Good luck.
Oh!
Leonard. Wake up.
Huh? Wh-- Sorry.
For what?
I don't know. When I'm in bed
with a girl, it's just--
it's my go-to response.
It's 6:00. I have
to get back to Raj's
before he wakes up
and realizes I'm gone.
Oh. Right. Sure.
I wish you could stay
in L.A. a while longer.
Mmm, me, too.
You know, I was thinking:
There are some great
research facilities in India.
Where are you going
with this, Leonard?
Well, I'm just saying, you know,
I don't have any real ties here,
so if I were to move to New
Delhi, we could, you know--
go out.
Leonard, didn't we have this
conversation five years ago?
Well, yes, but...
things have changed.
You know, you're older,
I'm older--
Look, no more
superhero bed sheets.
Sweetheart,
just because we have fun when
I come to town doesn't mean
I want to have a
serious relationship.
It doesn't?
Mm-mm.
And besides, I could never bring
a white boy home to my parents.
They'd have a cow.
Which is a much
bigger deal in India.
I'm not that white.
My great-great-grandmother
was half Cherokee.
I know that's not the right kind
of Indian, but it is something.
(chuckling):
You're funny.
(knocking)
SHELDON: Leonard?
Leonard?
(knocking)
What?
I heard a woman laughing.
Oh, uh, yeah. I was trying to
see if I could laugh as a woman.
Oh! Well, good job.
Quite convincing.
I smell perfume.
Air freshener.
And is that lipstick
on your cheek and neck?
Rash. That's a bad rash.
My sympathies.
I'm no stranger to the crimson
scourge that is dermatitis.
Can I interest you
in a topical steroid
from my lotion and
unguent collection?
Uh, yeah, yeah,
that sounds great.
Very well. I'm sure
I can find something
that will help
you ditch that itch.
Okay, he's in the
bathroom. Let's go.
Do you prefer
ointment or cream?
Cream.
With or without a numbing agent?
Without.
Really, Leonard?
There are no heroes when
it comes to dermatitis.
Fine. With.
Prescription or
non-prescription strength?
Use your best judgment.
Well, I think I have a
nice 2009 AnaMantle HC.
It's usually indicated for
acutely inflamed hemorrhoids,
but it also goes nicely
with non-mucosal body parts.
Sounds great.
Excellent choice.
(whispering):
Okay, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Come on, come on, come on.
SHELDON:
Priya?
Good morning, Sheldon.
For shame, Leonard, for shame.
And to think,
I was ready to waste
the last of my good
hemorrhoid cream on you.
Making pretty
good time, huh?
Is that really what you want
to talk about, Leonard?
No.
What do you want to talk about?
Please don't tell anyone
I spent the night
with Raj's sister.
There it is.
What if someone asks?
No one's going to ask if I spent
the night with Raj's sister.
Perhaps, but they might ask me
something else.
Like what?
Like
"Has Leonard betrayed any
of his friends recently?"
Priya and I are both adults.
I didn't betray Raj.
In fact, you did,
but I was referring to Howard.
What are you talking about?
April 12, 2005.
Bob's Big Boy,
Toluca Lake.
Raj had just introduced us
to Priya for the first time.
She was enjoying the sweet taste
of Hindu rebellion
in the form of a Bob's
Super Big Boy hamburger.
In order
to preserve
your friendship, you and Howard
made a pinky swear
that neither of you
would attempt to woo her.
(sighs)
I had a patty melt.
Okay, fine, I betrayed Howard.
And Raj.
All right, and Raj.
And me.
You?
Violation of the
Roommate Agreement's
overnight guest
notification clause.
Okay, fine,
I-I'm a horrible human being.
I'm the Darth Vader of Pasadena.
You're far too short
to be Darth Vader.
At best you might be
a turncoat Ewok.
My point is: Priya's gone
and it would be much better
if no one else found out
about us.
You mean you want me
to keep a secret?
Yes.
You know I can't
keep a secret.
You can if you try.
Think about
it this way:
um, if I were Batman
and you were Alfred,
you'd keep that
secret, right?
Why do you get
to be Batman?
Because Batman has the secret.
Alfred has secrets, too.
Like what?
Alfred knows
that Barbara Gordon
is Batgirl.
Which I've now just
told to Batman.
See, I cannot
keep a secret.
Ta-dah!
What?
Ta-dah.
It's short for...
♪ Da-da-da-da! ♪
Kind of busy here, Sheldon.
I know,
that's why I shortened it.
What do you want?
I came to go over your alibi
for last night.
What alibi?
You've asked me
to lie on your behalf,
and as you know,
I am deeply uncomfortable
with impromptu dishonesty,
so I've provided you
with an ironclad alibi.
You couldn't have spent
last night with Priya
because you were
with another woman.
Oh, I'm so sure
I'm gonna regret this,
but who was I with?
The fun-loving and morally loose
Miss Maggie McGarry.
Oh, God.
You met her at Pasadena's most
popular Irish watering hole,
Lucky Baldwin's, where Maggie
spends her nights tending bar
with a head full of curls
and a heart full of dreams.
"Leonard, call me if you
are interested in coitus.
Sincerely,
Maggie McGarry."
And if anyone were
to actually call that number,
they will hear this.
FEMALE TEXT-TO-SPEECH VOICE:
Top of the morning to you.
You've reached Maggie McGarry.
Leave a message
after the wee little beep.
It's pretty convincing, huh?
That wasn't even
a real person.
And here is
the clincher:
a lock of Maggie's
flaming auburn hair.
Where'd you get that?
From an orangutan
in the primate lab.
An orangutan?
Well, no one's going
to run a DNA test
on it, Leonard.
Honestly, you overthink
everything.
Sheldon, I don't need an alibi.
Nobody's going to ask
about last night
as long as you just
zip your lip.
Thank you.
Now, don't worry,
everything is going to be fine.
Hey.
Hey, Leonard, will you
please tell Howard
my sister has never
been attracted to him?
Come on, Raj,
how am I supposed to know
who she is attracted to
or was attracted to
or who she might be
attracted to in the future?
And I have nothing
to contribute
to this conversation.
Because I, too,
know absolutely nothing
about Priya's preferences
in male companionship.
And with that,
I will re-zip my lip.
Hey, so what did
you guys think
of the new episode
of Caprica last night?
I didn't see it.
Didn't see it?
(chuckles)
What were you doing?
Uh, I was out.
What, on Caprica night?
Yeah, I, uh, went
for a drink.
Really, you?
Where, w-where'd
you go?
To, uh...
Lucky Baldwin's.
Oh, I've heard
of that place.
Isn't that Pasadena's
favorite Irish watering hole?
Yes.
Did you meet
anyone interesting there,
perhaps a promiscuous,
redheaded barmaid?
As a matter of fact...
I-I-I-I-I can't, I can't,
I can't do it.
Sure you can, you're doing
fine, it's very believable.
I'm sorry, Raj,
but the truth is,
I was with Priya
last night.
Don't listen to him.
He's still light-headed
from all the Irish whiskey
and pickled eggs
in his system.
What were you doing
with Priya?
I believe they engaged
in coitus,
but more
importantly,
if Leonard had not abandoned
his story,
would you have found it
plausible?
You slept with my sister?!
Yeah.
How could you?
We had a pact.
Excuse me, I think
"How could you? She's my sister"
takes precedence over
a five-year-old pinky swear.
May I point out,
in a parallel universe,
your friends are saying
"Maggie McGarry--
she sounds lovely."
Look, I-I admit it, I may
have crossed a line here,
but come on, Raj, your
sister is a grown woman,
and to her, I'm a forbidden
piece of white chocolate.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
I don't believe it.
This is a terrible
betrayal of my trust.
No, w-w-would it
help if I told you
that I offered her my heart,
and she kind of stomped on it?
How hard did she stomp?
Very hard.
Okay, I'm good.
Well, Raj,
I just want to say that I'd
never betray your trust.
Unlike Leonard,
I respect you.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Was it out of respect
that you didn't tell Raj
about the time you dropped
his iPhone in a urinal?
Dude, I put that thing
on my face!
I think a more amusing
violation of Raj's trust
is when Howard convinced him
that foreigners give presents
to Americans
on Thanksgiving.
Hey, I didn't see
you giving back
your Snoopy
snow cone maker.
That was all a lie?
This year's gifts
are already wrapped.
And as long as we're talking
about betraying our friends,
how about the month Sheldon
spent grinding up insects
and mixing them
into Leonard's food?
SHELDON:
Well, excuse me.
That was not a betrayal.
That was an experiment
to determine
at what concentration
food starts tasting "mothy."
You put moths in my food?!
For science.
I can't believe you kissed
my sister with moth mouth.
Well, I can't believe you
used Sheldon's toothbrush.
You used my toothbrush?
Not the brush part,
just the little rubber thing
to pick food from my teeth
and massage my gums.
Okay, I-I think
it's safe to say
that we've all done
some things
we're not
particularly proud of.
But come on,
we're friends.
Friends overlook
each other's minor lapses.
For the record, Howard, I'm
sorry that I broke our pact.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry
about your phone
and Thanksgiving.
And while we're at it,
you don't have to wash our
clothes on the Fourth of July.
As long as we're apologizing,
Sheldon, I'm, I'm sorry
I used your toothbrush.
And I'm sorry...
but that behavior
is beyond the pale
and cannot be tolerated.
We are no longer friends.
I got you a talking Thomas the
Tank Engine for Thanksgiving.
With real puffing smoke?
Yes.
All right.
But I'm watching you.
Hey, you've got Snoopy out.
Can I have a snow cone?
Well, sure.
This is pretty good.
What flavor is this?
Guess.
Papaya?
No.
Guava?
You're so close.
I give up.
Mango caterpillar.
What are
you doing?!
You said you
liked it.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net