Water Demon.
Ice Dragon.
Lesser Warlord
of Ka'a.
Not so fast.
Infinite Sheldon.
Infinite Sheldon?
Yes, Infinite Sheldon
defeats all other cards
and does not violate the
rule against homemade cards
because I made
it at work.
Do you understand why people
don't want to play with you?
No...
although it's a question I've
been pondering since preschool.
Hey.
Hey, your copy of Science
magazine was in my mailbox.
- Oh, thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
Check it out--
all about planets this month.
That's an atom.
Agree to disagree.
That's what I love
about science--
there's no
one right answer.
So...
you and Zack again, huh?
Yeah, yeah, me
and Zack again.
Were we here earlier?
Okay, we should,
we should go.
Ah, not yet.
I want to talk science
with the science dudes.
Oh, and the science dudes want
to talk science with you.
What do you want
to talk about--
rocks, dinosaurs, our
friend the beaver?
You know, I saw this great thing
on the Discovery Channel.
Turns out
that if you kill a starfish,
it'll just come back to life.
Was the starfish
wearing boxer shorts?
Because you might have
been watching Nickelodeon.
No, I'm almost sure that
it was the Discovery Channel.
It was a great show.
They also said dolphins
might be smarter than people.
They might be smarter
than some people.
Maybe we can do an
experiment to find out.
That's easy enough.
We'd need a large tank of
water, a hoop to jump through,
and a bucket of whatever
bite-sized treats
you find tasty.
I don't get it.
A dolphin might.
Oh, I see.
You guys are inferring
that I'm stupid.
That's not correct.
We were implying it.
You then inferred it.
Let's go.
You know, for a group of guys
who claim they spent most
of their lives being bullied,
you can be real jerks.
Shame on all of you.
What the hell did I do?
You laughed.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 4x11 ♪
The Justice League Recombination
Original Air Date on December 16, 2010
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Do you think
Penny's right?
Were we bullying Zack?
No,
I know bullying.
He left here unswirlied and his
ass crack was underpants-free.
And nobody drew
a penis on his forehead.
That happened to you?
First day of cricket camp.
They drew it
so the testicles were my eyes.
I don't know, I think
we might owe the guy an apology.
So go apologize.
Why me?
You started it,
we just piled on.
What would I even say?
Zack, I'm sorry you're stupid.
Have a Milk Dud.
A Milk Dud?
Yeah,
Milk Duds,
with their self-deprecating name
and remarkably mild flavor,
are the most apologetic
of the boxed candies.
I got a better idea.
We're all responsible.
I say we all go.
Come on, who's with me?
Free comic books
to anyone who comes with me.
I might get punched.
You really want to miss that?
Junior Mints are
pretty apologetic.
You're embarrassing
yourself.
Penny.
What?
Yeah,
we came to talk to Zack.
Hey, Zack.
What do you want?
Listen,
the stuff
we were saying before--
we were just kidding around.
No, you weren't.
You were making fun
of me.
Come on, that's what we do.
We give each other a hard time.
Hey, Sheldon,
you look
like a praying mantis.
That's very hurtful.
See?
I don't know,
it still wasn't very nice.
Milk Dud?
Oh, I love Milk Duds.
Okay, we're cool.
Junior Mints.
You guys want to come in
and have a beer?
Uh, we're on our way
to the comic book store.
Leonard's buying.
Really?
I haven't been
to a comic book store
in literally
a million years.
Literally?
Literally a
million years?
Don't.
You want to go with 'em?
No.
Okay, see you later.
Wait,
w-w-w-wait, you're ditching me
to go look at comic books?
Are you mad at me?
I'm not happy.
Milk Dud?
Wow, this place
is awesome.
Where do they keep
the Archies?
In the bedrooms of ten-year-
old girls, where they belong.
Oh, no, you're thinking
old-school Archie.
It's much more
sophisticated now.
Like, there's
two universes,
and Archie's married
to Betty in one
and Veronica
in the other.
Midge is even breaking
up with Moose.
No.
About time, right?
Hey.
You guys finally chip in
for a bodyguard?
Uh, no. Oh,
this is Zack.
He's a friend
of ours.
Zack, this is Stuart.
He owns
the store.
Wow, lucky you.
Yeah, I work
70 hours a week
and average
$1.65 an hour.
Sweet.
Is that sarcasm?
No, it's an indictment of the
American education system.
The Archies are over here.
Yippee.
So are you guys coming to
my New Year's Eve costume party?
Of course.
We're coming as the
Justice League of America.
Switching it up from last year
when we came as
the Justice League of America.
To that point,
it occurs to me that we
might have an opportunity
to finally snare
Best Group Costume
if we shore up
our weak link,
which is clearly
Leonard as Superman.
Hey, I got
new boots this year.
Guaranteed to add
three inches.
That's sad.
Is there anyone we know
who would make a more manly
and convincing son of Krypton?
Than Leonard
in high-heeled boots?
Howard's mother
I was thinking specifically
of the gentleman over there
moving his lips
as he enjoys
the latest exploits
of Betty and Veronica.
Zack?
He is the only person we know
with actual muscles.
You can't replace
me with Zack.
Why not?
Penny did it.
Yeah, she seems happier.
Why wouldn't we be?
Score.
I got an Archie,
Betty and Veronica,
and a Jughead.
All set
for my weekend number twos.
Congratulations.
Zack, how would you
like to be Superman?
I don't know, sounds like
a lot of responsibility.
Fine, if Zack's going
to be Superman,
I want to be
Green Lantern.
But I'm Green Lantern.
You can be Aquaman.
I don't want to be Aquaman.
He sucks.
He sucks
underwater.
fish pee.
Excuse me,
I believe Aquaman uses
his telepathic powers
to request the fish do
their business elsewhere.
Hey, babe.
I'm still mad at you.
Well, you won't be
when you hear the great news.
What great news?
We're going to
a costume party
at the comic book store
on New Year's Eve,
and you get to
be Wonder Woman.
Complete with bulletproof
bracelets and lasso of truth.
Invisible plane sold separately.
Wait, why me?
Wh-Why can't your girlfriend
be Wonder Woman?
She and her lab team
are under quarantine.
Seems at the Christmas party
they were doing Jell-O shots
out of petri dishes that used
to contain yellow fever.
Okay, what about
your friend Amy?
Amy Farrah Fowler doesn't
believe in wearing costumes.
She isn't the free spirit I am.
Okay, well, forget it.
I'm not spending
my New Year's Eve
at a comic book store
wearing a Wonder Woman costume.
He says he'll wear it
if you'll be Aquaman.
What are you doing?
We're going
to be late.
I'm pacing nervously.
You're jogging.
This is how the
Flash paces.
Just chill out, Sheldon.
I'm not Sheldon.
I'm the Flash.
And now I'm going
to the Grand Canyon
to scream in frustration.
I'm back.
I'm Batman.
Oh, I hardly think so.
The real caped crusader calls
his crime-fighting cohorts
when he's running late.
I had to walk.
I couldn't get Raj
on the back of my scooter.
I've said this before,
and I'll say it again.
Aquaman sucks.
Look up in the sky.
It's a bird. It's a plane.
I forget the rest.
All right. Let's get
this thing over with.
I'm sorry.
But in what universe
is Wonder Woman blonde?
Relax. No one's going to
be looking at her hair.
Ow!
I mean,
ow.
Hold on. The costume came
with a black wig.
Where is it, babe?
No. I'm not wearing
it. It looks stupid.
Come on. We're trying
to win a contest here.
Forget it. I'm not
wearing the wig.
Honey, there's no "I"
in "Justice League."
Well, actually...
Don't.
He's making our case.
Okay, babe. Uh...
Kind of embarrassing me
in front of my friends.
Okay.
You know what?
I changed my mind.
I'm not going.
Looks like someone
else is going
to have to be Wonder Woman.
Babe, open up.
I'm not talking to you.
Then who are you talking to?
Babe?
Penny, Penny, Penny, Penny,
Penny, Penny, Penny,
Penny, Penny, Penny, Penny
Penny, Penny...
What the hell
is wrong with you?
I'm the Flash.
I just knocked 30,000 times.
Okay. What do you
want, Sheldon?
I understand
why you're upset.
Really?
Yes.
You're afraid that costume
makes you look fat.
No.
Wh-What...
Does it?
Don't worry.
Wonder Woman
was an Amazon.
And Amazons tend to
be very beefy gals.
Good-bye, Sheldon.
But they're not blonde,
so put on your wig.
Hello?
Stupid Aquaman.
If it makes you
feel any better,
when I was dating Penny,
she used to flip out
on me all the time.
Whoa. You dated Penny?
She didn't tell you?
She told me she dated
a guy named Leonard.
Who would have
thought it was you?
Who else would it be?
I don't know. Somebody
bigger and...
Yeah, sure.
Why not you?
I may have failed.
Okay, I guess we just go
without a Wonder Woman.
I don't want to go
without Penny.
Oh, great. No Superman,
no Wonder Woman?
All we've got is a skinny Flash,
an Indian Aquaman,
a nearsighted
Green Lantern,
and a teeny, tiny
Dark Knight.
Obviously, we're no longer
a Justice League.
We have no choice but to switch
to our Muppet Baby costumes.
Ooh, I call Kermit.
I'm Kermit.
You're Scooter.
Oh, man.
Scooter sucks.
He's the Aquaman
of the Muppet Babies.
No, we can still
make this work.
Leonard,
you talk to Penny.
What makes you think
I can convince her?
You got her
to have sex with you.
Obviously, your superpower
is brainwashing.
Okay, let me see
if I understand this.
You want me
to convince my ex-girlfriend
to go to a costume party
with her new boyfriend
just so we can win
a stupid prize?
Yes. And make her wear
the black wig. Good luck.
Go away, Sheldon.
It's Leonard.
Oh.
Go away, Leonard.
Come on, let me
just talk to you.
It's open.
Hey.
I'm not going
to that party, Leonard.
Okay, listen.
You don't have to wear the wig.
At this party,
we're gonna win first prize
just by showing up with a girl.
It's not the wig.
Did I do something?
I mean, I tried to be
friends with Zack,
like you said, which believe me,
was difficult,
given how you and me
used to be...
you know, "you and
me," and now you
and him are
"you and him."
Okay, look.
We're not really "me and him."
Then what are you?
I don't know.
I only started seeing Zack again
so I wouldn't be alone
on New Year's Eve.
How pathetic is that?
Not as pathetic
as dressing up like this
and going to a comic book store
on New Year's Eve.
You make a cute Green Arrow.
Green Lantern.
Like there's a difference.
There's a big difference.
Arrow.
Lantern.
Whatever. Look,
if Zack and I had just gone
to a regular club or a party,
it would have been fine,
but this, with the costumes,
and you...
What about me?
Nothing.
Let's go to the party.
How do I look?
Um...
I guarantee you'll be
the prettiest girl there.
Okay, the good news is,
we have a Wonder Woman.
Oh.
Yes.
What's the bad news?
Superman probably isn't
getting laid tonight.
Aw, damn.
And the award
for best group costume
goes to...
Justice League of America...
Number three!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Okay. Okay, ten
seconds to midnight.
Ten, nine, eight...
No, wait!
I have a speech.
Seven, six...
Stop counting!
Five, four, three...
This is my moment, dag nab it!
Two, one!
Happy New Year!
I'm not going
to say another word
until you people settle down.
I'm waiting.
That was a
great party.
We should dress like
this all the time.
Are you high?
You're being
a bully.
Check it out.
Those guys are breaking
into that car.
What should we do?
We're the Justice League
of America.
There's only one thing
we can do.
Turn around
and slowly walk away.
Nah.
Hold up.
Look, I know our winter
thermostat setting
is 72 degrees,
but I'm a little warm,
so I'm going
to turn it down.
Good Lord,
how you frustrate me,
Leonard Hofstadter!
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Fine.
www.tvsubtitles.net