Whatcha doin' there?
Working on a new plan
to catch the roadrunner?
The humorous implication being
that I am Wile E. Coyote?
And this is a schematic
for a bird-trapping device
that will ultimately backfire
and cause me physical injury?
What I'm doing here
is trying to determine
when I'm going to die.
A lot of people are working
on that research.
So what is all this?
My family history
factoring in longevity,
propensity for disease, et cetera.
Interesting.
Cause of death for Uncle Carl was KBB.
What's "KBB"?
"Killed by badger."
How's that?
It was Thanksgiving.
Uncle Carl said:
"I think there's a badger
living in our chimney.
"Hand me that flashlight."
Those were the last words
he ever spoke to us.
I don't think you need to worry
about death by badgers
being hereditary.
Not true.
The fight or flight instinct
is coded genetically.
Instead of fleeing,
he chose to fight barehanded
against a brawny member
of the weasel family.
Who's to say that I don't share
that flawed DNA?
You can always get a badger
and find out.
But seriously,
even if I disregard
the Uncle Carl factor,
at best I have 60 years left.
That long!
60 only takes me to here.
I need to get to here.
What's there?
The earliest estimate
of the singularity,
when man will be able
to transfer his consciousness
into machines
and achieve immortality.
So, you're upset about missing out
on becoming some sort
of freakish self-aware robot?
By this much.
- Tough break. You want eggs?
- You don't get it.
I'm going to miss so much
the unified field theory,
cold fusion, the "dogapus".
- What's a "dogapus"?
- The hybrid dog and octopus.
Man's underwater best friend.
- Is somebody working on that?
- I was going to.
I planned on giving it to myself
on my 300th birthday.
Wait a minute.
You hate dogs.
A dogapus can play fetch
with eight balls.
No one can hate that.
The TBBTeam presents
Episode 4x03:
The Cruciferous Vegetable Amplification
Synchro:
Homer
Trad:
Strex, benji1000, MisterCaribou
Relec:
kiima, Titou
- What do we owe you?
- It came to $28.17.
Let's say six bucks apiece.
Here you go.
What?
- Never mind. I got it.
-
It's no big deal.
You're right. We're not going out
What?
He said: "If he had woman parts,
he'd eat for free the rest of his life."
but you wouldn't be able
to talk to yourself.
I'm a little low on cash.
- How much you got?
- Nothing.
- How can you walk 'm cute, I get by.
It's okay, you can owe me.
Sheldon, six bucks.
No, thank you.
I'm not eating pizza tonight.
But it's Thursday.
Thursday's pizza night.
Not for me.
Thursday is now
Cruciferous Vegetable Night.
Tonight's selection:
Brussels sprouts.
Really? You're changing
the Sheldonian calendar?
- It's a small price to pay.
- For what?
- Don't ask.
- Sorry
In order to live long enough
to fuse my consciousness
with cybernetics,
I need to change my diet.
Wait.
Cybernetics is robot stuff, right?
Correct.
You want to turn yourself
into some sort of robot?
Essentially, yes.
Here's my question.
Didn't you already do that?
Flattering, but sadly, no.
I'm also planning
to begin an exercise regimen
designed to strengthen
my cardiovascular system.
- AKA jogging.
- Wait.
- Honey, have you ever run before?
- Certainly.
I've run from bullies, dogs,
angry chickens,
and one particularly persistent
P.E. teacher
determined to bend me over
and give me a scoliosis test.
You're right, Penny jogs.
Maybe you guys can run together.
That's an excellent idea.
If we chat, it will create
the illusion of time going faster.
No, it won't.
How does he know I jog?
He watches you from his car
with high-powered binoculars.
That is so creepy!
I know!
And he says he's not gonna stop.
Then see a shrink
and figure out how to talk to women.
What the hell?
What's the matter?
I have pain radiating from my navel
to my lower right abdomen.
I'm nauseated and feverish.
I believe I may have cholera.
There's no cholera in Pasadena.
Just like last summer,
when there was no malaria in Pasadena.
If it's not cholera,
then based on a quick Internet search,
the other explanations
in decreasing order of likelihood
are Hirschsprung's Disease,
botulism, a 30-foot tapeworm
or accidental ingestion
of chrysanthemum blossoms.
When would you have accidentally
eaten chrysanthemum blossoms?
It's part of an unlikely scenario
that involves sleepwalking
and a 24-hour flower mart
with a less-than-vigilant proprietor.
Lord, my belly!
Ever had your appendix out?
I haven't.
I've been meaning to,
but who has the time?
Let's go spital.
So this is how it ends...
with cruel irony.
Just as I just make
the commitment to preserving my body,
I am betrayed by my appendix,
a vestigial organ.
Do you know the original purpose
of the appendix?
I do.
And yet I'm doomed
while you live on.
Funny how things work out, isn't it?
Lord, I think it's about to burst!
On the other hand,
it might have been
the Brussels sprouts.
Good night.
Appendicitis.
What a nervous Nelly.
Coming, coming.
Hey, nice knees.
Thank you.
They're er}'s.
Why the Flash shirt?You're gonna run really fast?
No,  because it's Friday,
but it's nice when things work out.
- Where's your on't have one.
- ur pedometer?
- Don't have one.
And telematics in your shoes
connected to an iPod?
What do you do,
you just go out there
and gambol about like a bunny?
I just run till I'm hungry,
then I stop for a bear claw.
Why are you doing that?
It's good to stretch your muscles
before you run.
- All right.
- Let's start with a toe touch.
You do it.
I am doing it.
Good job.
Can you do this?
We'll never know.
Let's just warm up on the run.
Let's go.
I've been reading up
on biomechanics.
I think you'll be surprised at my...
- e you okay?
- I think so.
- t me help you up.
- Thank you.
If it makes you feel any better,
Thursday is no longer
Cruciferous Vegetable Night.
Here's my chicken curry.
- Howard, your shrimp biryani.
- Thank you, sir.
- Palak paneer, that's Penny.
- Thanks.
And for Rajesh Koothrappali,
from whose homeland
these tasty dishes originate,
one large order
of chicken McNuggets.
What's my share?
12 bucks.
- Can I get you
- Sure.
What am I up to now?
With the Indian food, the pizza,
the Thai food, the tank of gas,
the frozen yogurt
and your rent
a little over $1,400.
What now?
He's just expressing his admiration
that you don't even have to put out
to get free stuff.
It's not free,
I'm gonna pay him back.
Shut up!
Sheldon, are you gonna join us?
Coming!
Greetings, friends.
Greetings,
whatever the hell you are.
I'm a mobile virtual
presence device.
Recent events
have demonstrated to me
that my body is too fragile
to endure the vicissitudes
of the world.
Until such time as I am able
to transfer my consciousness,
I shall remain in a secure location
and interact with the world
in this manner.
Really? That's your question,
when did he put a ramp in?
You're in my spot.
This may seem a little odd at first,
but over time,
you'll grow accustomed
to dealing with me
in this configuration.
To be honest,
I don't see much difference.
nk you.
That's what I was going for.
Now, Leonard, tomorrow,
when we go to work,
you'll need to allow some extra time
to get me down the stairs.
For your convenience,
I disassemble into four pieces.
This is ridiculous.
I'm coming to talk to you.
You don't know where I am.
My physical body is safely ensconced
in a secure, undisclosed location.
You're in your bedroom.
No, I'm not.
I can hear your voice
coming from your bedroom.
No, you can't.
Wait.
Come back.
Halt.
Authorized personnel only!
One of you weirdos
want to buy my underwear?
Only 1,400 bucks.
Sheldon, this is ridiculous.
I'm behind you.
Please, look at me
when you're talking to me.
- I am looking at you.
- No, you're not.
Pay no attention
to that man in the bed.
You cannot exist
as a virtual presence.
Not here and certainly not at work.
At my age,
do you know how I'm statistically
most likely to die?
At the hands of your roommate?
An accident.
That's how I'm going
to make it look.
Until I can transfer my intellect
to a more durable container,
my body will remain
safely ensconced in my bed.
Fine, but don't expect my help.
You have to help.
It's in the roommate agreement.
No, it's not.
Section 74 C.
The various obligations and duties
of the parties
in the event
one of them becomes a robot.
I'll be damned.
This is delightful.
It's much easier to enjoy
the picturesque route we travel to work
when you remove
the specter of fiery vehicular death.
Refresh my memory.
Why didn't I put you in the trunk?
Because I called shotgun.
Remember?
Right.
You seem tense.
Perhaps this will relax you.
I don't wanna listen to music.
Very well.
I don't understand
why you're not enjoying this.
Together, in this car,
with my enhanced capabilities,
we're like Knight Rider.
Except in Knight Rider,
the car isn't a yammering sphincter.
You mock the sphincter,
but it's a class of muscle without which
human beings couldn't survive.
There are over 50 different sphincters
in the human body.
How many can you name?
I was wrong,
this is exactly like Knight Rider.
Perhaps you'd be interested
in a different game.
This is a photograph
of the 1911 Solvay Conference
on the theory
of radiation and quanta.
Using Photoshop,
I've introduced a few anachronisms.
See if you can spot all 24.
I'll give you the first one.
Madame Curie should not be wearing
a digital watch.
And go.
That's it.
I have an override switch.
I almost died!
And I'm safe and sound in bed.
Who's crazy now?
I'm still gonna go with you.
Hello, Professor Hoskins.
Nice to see you, Mindy.
Konnichiwa, Dr. Nakamora.
Sorry the Swedes
disproved your theory.
My door.
What about it?
Be a lamb and open it for me.
Why? What's the problem?
You think you have me stymied,
don't you?
I think a doorknob has you stymied.
Look, it's Leonard and R2-D-Bag.
That's my joke, I told it last night.
You can't use it.
Be a lamb and open the door for me.
Sure.
He's a lamb.
You're not.
I'm a lamb.
Isn't this nice?
The pleasures of fellowship
and camaraderie
without having to tolerate
your germy breath on my skin.
Let's take him to Tatooine
and sell him to some Jawas.
That's two, dude.
Write your own jokes.
Great.
I'm Penny, I'll be your waitress.
You're introducing yourself?
I'd rather people not know
I've prior connection to you whatsoever.
Can you tell me
the specials this evening?
I'm not waiting on you.
Obviously.
I don't even have water yet.
Because you're not here.
That's discrimination
against the otherwise located.
I'll have to go over your head.
Manager!
Lord, look who it is.
- Is that Steve Wozniak?
- I think it is.
The Great and Powerful Woz.
He was one of the co-founders
of Apple Computer. He and Steve Jobs...
I know.
I watch Dancing with the Stars.
I must speak to him.
Of course.
There's an Olive Garden
down the street,
you should try it
Excuse me, Mr. Wozniak?
Nice virtual presence device.
I just want to say I'm a big fan.
You're my 15th favorite
technological visionary.
Only 15th?
It's still 6 spots above Steve Jobs.
I care neither
for turtlenecks nor showmanship.
I never got that turtleneck thing.
One of my proudest possessions
is a vintage 1977 Apple Two.
Despite the file system limitations
of Apple DOS 3.3,
it was a pretty nifty
little achievement.
Thanks,
we were shooting for "nifty".
If you had it here,
I'd autograph it for you.
Don't move for 15 to 30 minutes,
depending on how the buses are running.
Nerds.
I'm coming, Woz, I'm coming.
What up, Shel-Bot?
I can't get out of bed.
I hurt my ankle.
What do you want me to do?
Sing me Soft Kitty.
You want me to sing Soft Kitty
to a computer monitor?
Would you rather come over
and sing it to me in person?
Soft kitty, warm kitty
Little ball of fur
Closer to the microphone.
Happy kitty, sleepy...
You have to start over.
Soft kitty, warm kitty
Little ball of fur
Happy kitty, sleepy kitty
Purr, purr, purr
www.tvsubtitles.net