No, seriously,
I think
I've finally figured out
my problem with women.
The capybara is the largest
member of the rodent family.
What does that have to do
with me and women?
Nothing.
It was a desperate attempt
to introduce an alternate topic
of conversation.
My problem is,
I don't project confidence.
So I decided that
the next time I meet a woman
I think is attractive,
rather than holding back
and being cautious,
I'm going to assume
the mantle of self-assurance.
Oh, yeah?
What's that look like?
Hi.
I'm Leonard.
And you are beautiful.
You pop, sparkle
and buzz electric.
I'm going to pick you up
at 8:00,
show you a night
you will never forget.
Where are we going?
Good news.
I made it
onto the team
for the new Defense Department
laser-equipped
surveillance satellite.
Excuse me.
If we're changing topics,
I believe I have first dibs
with capybara, a rodent
the size of a baby hippo.
Congratulations,
Howard.
WOLOWITZ:
Thanks.
Listen, I have to get
a security clearance,
so you guys might be
hearing from the FBI.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I don't want to speak
to the FBI.
Why not?
I'm brown and I talk funny.
They're just doing
a background check on me.
It doesn't matter;
they'll find a reason
to give me a one-way ticket
back to Gandhi-ville.
By the way,
when I say that,
it's not offensive.
Don't be ridiculous, Raj.
You're here legally.
Nobody cares.
Do you know how long it's been
since I got through
airport security
without being given
a colonoscopy?
You know, I
try very hard
to make our lunch hours
educational and informative,
but your insistence on
talking about your own lives
stymies me at
every turn.
Fine, Sheldon, tell us
about your giant rodents.
1No, you squandered
your time with me,
and the moment
has now passed.
Feast on your disappointment,
much as the capybara
feasts on its own waste.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 4x07 ♪
The Apology Insufficiency
Original Air Date on November 4, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Oh, Bella, don't you see?
Edward's only pushing you away
because he loves you.
(knocking)
Coming.
(clears throat)
Dr. Koothrappali?
I'm Special Agent Page, FBI.
May I come in?
I'd like to talk to you
about Howard Wolowitz.
Oh, thank you.
All right.
Well, how long
have you known Mr. Wolowitz?
Rum cake?
No, thanks.
Now, about Mr.
Wolowitz...
Seven years.
I see.
I'm in this country
legally, you know.
I'm sure you are.
Now, to your knowledge, has Mr.
Wolowitz ever committed a crime?
Of course not.
I'm here on an H-1B visa,
which means I can't be
associated in any way
with crime
or criminal activity.
And I'm not.
Good.
To your knowledge,
does Mr. Wolowitz
have any foreign
contacts?
No, just me.
Oh, there it is.
Here comes a cavity search.
Excuse me?
Please don't send me back
to India; it's so crowded!
It's like the whole country
is one endless Comic-Con,
except everybody's wearing
the same costume: Indian Guy.
Dr. Koothrappali, I'm not...
I love this country!
The-the baseball,
the freedom,
the rampant morbid obesity!
From California
to the New York Island!
I'm a real Yankee Doodle boy!
Dr. Koothrappali,
please.
♪ My country 'tis of thee... ♪
(humming)
♪ ...liberty ♪
♪ It's really great. ♪
So, when Howard said the FBI
would be contacting me,
I was expecting Mulder.
Glad to see I got Scully.
(chuckles)
Who?
Mulder and Scully.
X-Files.
"The truth is out there."
Never mind.
Uh, so, what would you
like to know?
You work with Mr. Wolowitz here
at the university, correct?
Yes. Of course, we're in
different departments.
He's an engineer and I'm
an experimental physicist.
You know, one
of those guys
who examines the building blocks
of creation
and says,
"Hello, maker of the universe.
"I see what you did there.
Good one."
Right.
Now, how would you characterize
your relationship
with Mr. Wolowitz?
Good.
It's a good
relationship.
Of course, most of my
relationships are good.
Probably because
I exude confidence.
People are drawn to that,
you know?
Confidence, not exuding.
Do you know of any groups
Mr. Wolowitz is a member of?
You are beautiful,
you know that?
You pop, sparkle
and buzz electric.
I'm going to pick you up
at 8:00,
show you a night
you will never forget.
Sounds great.
Really?
Yeah.
Can my six-foot-two Navy SEAL
husband come with us?
Is that...?
Oh, my, I didn't see the ring
with my glasses off, so...
Look at that,
I'm starting to exude.
(chuckles)
(knocking)
Want to get that?
Not particularly.
Could you get that?
I suppose I could
if I were asked.
(knocking)
Would you please get that?
Of course.
Why do you have to make things
so complicated?
Dr. Cooper?
Yes.
I'm Special Agent Page, FBI.
You say you're Special
Agent Page, FBI.
Here's my I.D.
And here is
my Justice League
membership card.
But that doesn't
prove I know Batman.
I just want to ask you a few
questions about Howard Wolowitz.
Oh. All right.
I doubt anyone
would risk
the stiff penalties for
impersonating a federal officer
just to ask questions about
a minor league engineer
with an unresolved
Oedipal complex.
Thank you.
For the record,
I truly support the FBI
in the mission
which is expressed
through their motto...?
Fidelity, bravery, integrity.
Correct. Now to business.
18 years ago, I sent
the FBI Crime Lab samples
from a bag of excrement
that had been lit on fire
on my front porch...
...for fingerprinting
and DNA analysis.
Why haven't I heard back yet?
Well, the FBI Crime Lab
does have a lot on its plate.
That's of little comfort
to a nation
attempting to scrape
burning feces off its shoes.
Would you mind if we talked
about Mr. Wolowitz now?
A little, but go on.
Thank you.
Would you characterize him
as responsible?
I'm going to answer that
with a visual aid.
This is my nine-disc complete
Lord of the Rings trilogy
Blu-ray set.
Mr. Wolowitz borrowed it,
damaged plastic retention
hub number three...
...and then returned it to me,
hoping I wouldn't notice.
Would you characterize that
as responsible?
That's really not the sort of
thing we're interested in.
You heard me say
Blu-ray, right?
I did.
Very well.
Would you be interested
in knowing that Mr. Wolowitz
once snuck onto
my World of Warcraft account
and changed the name
of a certain level-80 warlock
from Sheldor to Smeldor?
I'm afraid not.
Is there anything else?
"Is there anything else?"
Where would you like to start?
He refuses to pay fines
when he's overdue
with books I lend him.
He crashed the Mars Rover while
attempting to impress a woman.
He recommended that I go see
the third Matrix movie
because it was, and I quote,
"just as good
as the first one."
If that's not irresponsible,
I don't know what is.
The Mars Rover?
Did I say Mars Rover?
You did.
That was actually
a poorly chosen example,
as it had nothing
to do with me.
Yes, well, let's talk
about it anyway.
I don't want to.
Not that my disinclination
to discuss the topic
should be interpreted as
evidence of Howard Wolowitz's
culpability in the destruction
of government property
worth millions of dollars.
Thank you, Dr. Cooper.
I think I have all I need.
(sighs):
Oh, good.
I was afraid you were
going to fixate
on that Mars Rover incident.
Hey, buddies.
Guess who didn't get
security clearance
to work on
the giant space laser?
What happened?
Apparently, the background
interviews didn't go well.
You guys wouldn't
know anything
about that, would you?
Well, actually,
I may have gotten
a little tipsy
when I talked to her.
And I may have
hit on her a little bit.
I may have thrown up
rum cake on her shoes.
I see.
Well, it's good to know, when
I need you guys, I can always
count on you to step up
and ruin everything.
I feel awful.
Ah, me, too.
To tell you the truth,
I thought if anyone was going to
screw things up for Howard,
it'd be Sheldon.
Well, your expectations
have been subverted.
Aha.
What are you doing up?
Sleep eludes me, Leonard.
Really?
Maybe sleep has met you before.
Mockery?
That's all you have to offer?
I'm sorry. Why can't you sleep?
Who knows?
I haven't watched
any scary movies recently.
I'm no longer obsessing
over why the predicted mass
of the quantum vacuum
has little effect
on the expansion
of the universe.
And it's been weeks since I took
that accidental sip of Red Bull.
Did something happen today
that's bothering you?
Well, I did mention
the Mars Rover incident
to that FBI agent
and probably cost Howard
his security clearance.
What?
But why should that keep me up?
Because you feel guilty?
Interesting.
So you're saying my insomnia is
caused by a guilty conscience.
Actually,
you don't have insomnia.
You're sleeping now.
Excuse me?
You're having
a guilt-ridden dream.
Do you have any evidence
to support that hypothesis?
How about that Gorn
sitting on the couch?
That seems fairly conclusive.
No, Gorn, no.
That's where I sit.
Thank you for agreeing
to see me, Agent Page.
Thank you for filing a complaint
with my superior, Dr. Cooper.
I understand
you want to recant
your statement
about Howard Wolowitz.
Yes.
Was your statement untrue?
No.
Then I'm afraid
you can't withdraw it.
I'm sorry. I don't recall
you saying "no backsies."
Is there anything else?
Yes. I'd like to offer
a laudatory statement
about Howard's many excellent
qualities that I believe
will tip the scales
back in his favor.
(clears throat)
"Howard Joel Wolowitz.
"H is for honesty,
of which he has much.
"O's for outstanding,
"which he is such.
"W's for witty,
he's quick with a joke.
A's for artistic, his ability...
" I'm sorry.
Dr. Cooper, this matter
is already closed.
But I still have
"rd Joel Wolowitz" left to go.
It's closed.
I don't understand
why you people
are picking on my
friend, Howard,
when there are much more serious
security threats to pursue.
For instance,
when I first met Leonard,
he was on the verge
of giving away
rocket secrets
to a North Korean spy,
and not one agent
ever investigated that.
This is Leonard Hofstadter?
No, it's a different Leonard.
He's...
Chinese, red hair, six fingers.
Good-bye.
Raj.
Have you seen Howard?
I think he's eating lunch.
Uh, Sheldon, I want you
to meet Neil deGrasse Tyson
from the Hayden Planetarium
in New York.
I'm quite familiar
with Dr. Tyson.
He's responsible
for the demotion of Pluto
from planetary status.
I liked Pluto.
Ergo I do not like you.
But I actually
didn't demote Pluto.
That was a vote
of the International
Astronomical Union.
If "ifs" and "buts"
were candy and nuts,
we'd all have a merry Christmas.
Think about that, Dr. Tyson.
Is that the guy you
were telling me about?
Oh, yeah.
Howard.
The person at fault for you
not getting
a security clearance is me.
You?
Yes, but before you get upset,
I want you to know
I went to the FBI
and retracted my statement.
And they were okay with that?
No. If anything,
I made it worse.
In any case, I have
been riddled with guilt,
which is causing
Gorn-infested REM sleep.
So, I'm here now
to say I'm sorry.
Are you kidding me?
You've set my career back
at least two years,
and you think you can make it
right with "I'm sorry"?
Yes.
I followed the social protocol.
I attempted to right the wrong,
and when I failed to do so,
I delivered a heartfelt apology.
Now you say,
"Apology accepted,"
and I will offer you
a one-time-only high five.
Your apology is not accepted.
You're tricking me.
It really is, isn't it?
Leave me alone, Sheldon.
Dr. Cooper, I just
wanted you to know
I'm sorry for the role I
played in the Pluto matter.
Oh, shut up.
Sheldon?
Hello.
What are you doing here?
I have troubles, Penny.
I've come to pour them out
to the sympathetic ear
of the local barkeep.
You know, they have
a really nice bar
over at the Olive Garden.
I don't like the Olive Garden.
They treat me like family.
Okay, Sheldon.
What can I get you?
Alcohol.
Could you be
a little more specific?
Ethyl alcohol.
40 milliliters.
I'm sorry, honey.
I don't know milliliters.
Ah. Blame President James
"Jimmy" Carter.
He started America on a path
to the metric system
but then just gave up.
He wonders why he
was a one-term president.
Would you say that's
about 40 milliliters?
More or less.
Great.
Now, where were we?
I believe you were about
to ask me to choose a cocktail.
Fortunately, thanks
to computer-savvy alcoholics,
there's an app for that.
Let's see.
Harvey Wallbanger. Eh.
Sex on the Beach.
I hardly think so.
Rob Roy,
Silk Slipper, Mad Hatter.
Ooh!
I'll have a Rosewater Ricky.
A what?
You'll need pitted,
brandied cherries, gin,
rosewater,
Angostura bitters
and overproofed rum.
Now, first, dust
the cherries with sugar,
then spray them with a mixture
of rum and bitters.
Then ignite the rum,
caramel...
Here you go-- one
Rosewater Ricky.
That's not how it looks
in the picture.
Oh, yeah, you know, every
bartender makes it differently.
Why don't you
give it a try.
All right.
To the metric system.
I can't taste the cherries.
All right.
Sheldon, what's on your mind?
I wronged Howard,
and he won't accept my apology.
Oh, right, that.
Yes, Leonard told me.
Sorry, honey.
Penny, you face failure
on a daily basis.
How do you cope?
I drink.
To drinking.
Nope.
Oh, if only there were some way
to force Howard
to accept my apology
so I could escape
this miasma of guilt.
You know, sometimes
stuff just happens,
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
For example, Lisa Peterson
hasn't talked to me
since the 11th grade,
because no matter how
much you apologize,
you can't go back and
un-dry-hump someone's boyfriend.
I see.
You're saying I'm facing
Starfleet Academy's
unwinnable command scenario:
the Kobayashi Maru.
Exactly.
Sometimes you can't win.
Captain Kirk won.
Kirk cheated.
Impressive that you know that.
It's hard to believe
I'm actually having
this conversation with you.
Right there with you.
Kirk beat the Kobayashi Maru
by reprogramming the simulator.
That's it.
What?
I'll reprogram Howard.
What...?
Sheldon, you can't
reprogram people.
No, you can't reprogram people.
To James Tiberius Kirk.
Hello, all.
LEONARD: Hello.
KOOTHRAPPALI: Hey.
Howard, you're feeling better
about me today, aren't you?
Not really.
Yes, you are.
I'm using
neurolinguistic programming
to modify your thought patterns.
Oh.
Go away, Sheldon.
There's a $9.95 e-book
down the drain.
What's in the bag?
It's for Howard.
Oh. Sheldon, you can't
fix this with gifts.
Nevertheless, I've hurt you,
and whether you
forgive me or not,
I want you to
have this.
You're giving me
a couch cushion?
No.
The cushion is merely symbolic.
I'm giving you my spot
on the couch.
But you love that spot.
No. I love my mother.
My feelings for my spot
are much greater.
It is the singular location
in space
around which revolves
my entire universe.
And now it's yours.
Oh, my God, dude.
Now you have to forgive him.
All right.
Apology accepted.
High five.
Not too hard.
Thank you.
I haven't cried like this
since Toy Story 3.
I got to tell you,
Sheldon, I understand why
you chose this spot.
I mean, the temperature is
good, but there's no draft.
I can see the television,
but I can still talk to...
I changed my mind.
Get out of my spot.
How long?
94 seconds.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net