Okay, help me out here.
How does an archeology professor
get that good with a whip?
Maybe he took a class
at the adult bookstore.
That's how I learned.
I can't believe you've never
seen Raiders of the Lost Ark.
And I can't believe you've
never read Eat, Pray, Love.
When she comes out with
Eat, Pray, Run Away From A
Giant Boulder, I'll read it.
I don't care if Eat, Pray, Love
changed your life,
I'm not reading it.
You know, I could totally
rock a hat like that.
That's the work of noted
Hollywood costume designer
Deborah Nadoolman.
She also designed
the iconic red and black jacket
in Michael Jackson's
Thriller video,
which I've never viewed
in its entirety,
as I find zombies dancing
in choreographed synchronicity
implausible.
And also, it's really scary.
Would someone please turn off
the Sheldon commentary track?
There's no switch.
Just listen and learn.
Penny, if you think
this is good,
you should come with us Friday
to see it on the big screen
at the Colonial.
Well, I'm watching it now.
Why would I want to see it again
on Friday?
Because the print
they're showing on Friday
has an additional 21 seconds
of previously unseen footage.
21 seconds? That'll be like
seeing a whole new movie!
Exactly.
They say it finally solves
the submarine controversy.
Did-- Leonard?
I'm no expert, but I believe
what we just heard from Penny
was sarcasm.
Oh! Good.
I'm eight for 26 this month.
Yeah, I think I'll pass.
But you guys enjoy
your extra 21 seconds.
Bet if I could
make you understand
why this is such a cool thing,
we'd still be together.
Mm, yeah, no,
we wouldn't.
Uh-huh.
I'm guessing 21 seconds had
something to do with that, too.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 4x08 ♪
The Apology Insufficiency
Original Air Date on November 11, 2010
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
May I point out to you all
that the screening is
"first come, first served"?
Relax, it's 5:00. The movie
doesn't start till midnight.
Another way of saying that is
"the movie starts at midnight,
and it's already 5:00."
Let's go.
You know, if we miss it,
we'll have the fun of
listening to Sheldon whine about
it for the rest of our lives.
See? Howard's on my side.
Actually, I'm not.
I'm using sarcasm to mock you.
Drat. Now I'm 8 for 27.
Don't worry, Sheldon.
We'll be fine.
What happened to
the Leonard Hofstadter
who waited in line
with me for 14 hours
to see the midnight premiere
of Star Trek: Nemesis?
Oh. Well, he waited
in line for 14 hours,
while you napped
in a lawn chair,
he got in a fight
with a Klingon
when he stepped
out of line to pee
and you wouldn't wake up
to vouch for him,
and worst of all,
he saw Star Trek: Nemesis.
But how were our seats?
Excellent.
I rest my case.
Amy, don't you agree we should
leave now and get in line?
Actually, as the newest member
of your social group,
I believe I'll gain more
acceptance by arbitrarily
siding with your friends
from time to time.
Shrewd.
Leonard, you're right.
We should enjoy our meal,
arrive late,
and risk winding up
with terrible seats,
assuming we get in at all.
Thank you, Amy.
See? It's working.
Knock-knock.
Who's there?
Olive.
Olive you, too.
Guys, that's really
starting to get old.
Knock-knock.
Who's there?
I have a girlfriend
and you don't.
Hysterical!
Wait, now, we don't know
that yet. He isn't finished.
I have a girlfriend
and you don't who?
So. Are you sure you don't want
to come with us to Raiders?
Oh, no. That movie
has melting faces.
It reminds me
too much of the time
I dropped that vial of
flesh-eating bacteria
into the Rhesus monkey lab.
Besides, Penny and I are having
a girls' night tonight.
Girls' night?
What does that entail?
Oh, you know, girls get
together,
hang out, share girl talk.
I'm a girl.
Oh. Well, maybe you can join us.
I'll ask Penny.
No need. Penny and I
are very close.
You are?
Yes. In fact,
our menses are synchronized.
Penny.
Bernadette tells me you're
planning a girls' night.
Yeah?
I'm a girl.
Oh. Um, it was-- it was just
going to be me and Bernadette.
Besides, I thought you
were going to the movies
with Sheldon and the guys.
Yes, but they're not girls.
I'm a girl.
Yeah, no, no,
I-I-I got that.
What's the dress code?
Uh, just wear something
comfortable.
All right.
I'll have to go shopping.
Knock-knock.
Who is there?
Hugh.
Hugh who?
Hugh people need to
listen to me.
It's time to get
in line for the movie.
And that's how you tell
a knock-knock joke.
Under normal circumstances
I'd say, "I told you so."
But as I have told you so
with such vehemence
and frequency already,
the phrase has lost all meaning.
Therefore, I will be
replacing it with the phrase:
"I informed you thusly."
Ooh. Can't wait
for that to start.
I informed you thusly.
Eight for 28.
This is where we could have been
if we hadn't stopped for dinner.
if Koothrappali
hadn't ordered dessert.
Well I earned it, dude,
I ate all my broccoli.
And here's where we are.
The runts in a large litter.
unlikely to ever reach
the nourishing teats
of Indiana Jones.
So I guess it's a good thing
we stopped for dinner.
You know, guys, when
facing disappointment,
Eat, Pray, Love  teaches us--
Oh, shut up.
...so anyway, to make
a long story short,
turns out I have
an unusually firm cervix.
You--
Amy, when we say "girl talk,"
it doesn't just have to
be about our lady parts.
Shame. 'Cause I have a real
zinger about my titled uterus.
Penny, your nails
look great.
Oh, thanks. I found
this place in Alhambra.
It's in a woman's basement.
I think it's a front
for human trafficking,
but they do a really good job.
A colleague of mine did her
graduate thesis on the fungus
that grows on improperly
sterilized manicure implements.
Well don't tell me
that's not "girl talk."
So where should
we go tonight?
A bar? A club? A movie?
Or we could just stay here.
Yes, and continue to bond.
I have a feeling
that after tonight,
one of you will become
my best friend forever.
Or "BFF," if you prefer.
Which I don't.
All right, time to open
Bachelor Number Two.
Gee, I don't know
if I should drink more.
I have to drive home,
and I've got enough trouble
seeing over the dashboard
as it is.
That's okay.
You can just sleep here.
Oh, good, a slumber party!
We'll do makeovers,
initiate phony phone calls,
and have spirited pillow fights
in our frilly nighties!
Oh, gosh, Amy.
I don't know if I would call
this an actual slumber party.
Well, that's disappointing.
I've always wanted to be
invited to a slumber party.
Oh, you never were?
Not even when
you were a kid?
Well, there was the time
I had my tonsils out,
and I shared a room with
a little Vietnamese girl.
She didn't make it
through the night,
but up till then,
it was kind of fun.
Okay. Well, I guess we're
having a slumber party.
Oh!
Pillow fight!
Oh, I hope they
let us in soon.
I'm tired of running to the gas
station to use the bathroom.
The guy makes me buy
a Gatorade every time.
It's a vicious circle.
Too bad you don't have
a stadium pal like me.
What's a stadium pal?
Let me put it this way:
takes care of
the bathroom problem,
and it keeps your calf warm.
Hey, guys, bad news.
I just did a quick calculation.
Given the size of the theater
and the length of this line,
we might not get seats.
What did he say?
Nice going, Raj.
Just got him down for his nap.
We might not get seats?!
It's fine, it's fine.
Go back to sleep.
Oh, I informed you thusly!
I so informed you thusly.
Howard, you talk to him.
Howard?
You're peeing,
aren't you?
Hey, look who's here!
Hey, buddies!
Well, if it isn't Wil Wheaton,
the Jar Jar Binks
of the Star Trek universe.
Mee-sa think that very funny!
Well, you-sa can go think that
at the back of the line.
No cuts, no buts, no coconuts.
Wil Wheaton.
Yeah.
I'm a big fan.
Of what? Poorly
executed beards?
Do you think you could get me
and my friends into the movie?
We got here
a little late.
No problem. Come on,
I'll hook you up.
Awesome.
We-sa gonna go into
the movie now! Bye-bye!
This is Indiana Jones,
not Star Trek.
There should be no value
to his pseudo-celebrity here!
And even at
Star Trek conventions,
they only let him in
if he helps set up!
Calm down, Sheldon.
I will not calm down.
This affront to justice and
decency cannot go unanswered.
As Captain Jean-Luc Picard
once said,
"The line must be drawn here!
"This far, no farther!"
Had to wake him up
from his nap, didn't you?
You know what I really love
about Howard?
His chest hair.
Howard has a
hairy chest?
No, just the one.
But it's really long.
Okay, there you go--
Sultry Sunrise Red.
What do you think?
My nails have never
looked so pretty before.
Get it off.
Oh, oh, uh, looks like
they're getting ready
to let people in.
Listen to what Mr. Wil
Wheaton is tweeting.
"Best seats in house
for Raiders screening.
Suck on that, Sheldon Cooper."
Why do you read
his Twitter feed?
You know it's only
going to upset you.
I believe in knowing
my enemy, Leonard.
Had Twitter existed at the time,
would not General Custer
have followed the tweets
of Sitting Bull?
Would not Lee have
followed Grant?
Would not Spy have followed Spy?
I have more examples,
but excuse me.
Hello.
Well, this seems
like an odd time
to test my cell phone quality,
but go on.
Test phrases? All right.
Imatote.
Ulba.
Twad.
All together?
I'm a total buttwad.
Why are you laughing?
Hello?
And that, girls, is how you make
a phony phone call.
I'm not sure I grasp
the full entertainment value,
but all right.
Next on Wikipedia's list
of slumber party activities:
"Truth or Dare."
Okay, it's your game.
You go first.
Hang on. I'm familiarizing
myself with the rules.
Seems fairly straightforward.
Bernadette, truth or dare?
Truth.
All right.
To what temperature
must you heat beef
in order to
kill the prion
that causes bovine
spongiform encephalopathy?
Um...
Remember, you have
to answer honestly.
Wait. No, Amy, you're
supposed to ask her
something personal
or embarrassing.
Oh.
All right.
What is the circumference
of your areolas?
"Munching on
complimentary popcorn.
Woot, woot."
Oh, the gall.
I hope his next tweet is
"Popcorn lodged in trachea.
"Choking to death.
Woot, woot."
Guys, I am sorry.
We are full up.
No!
We're full up.
We really want
to see this.
Isn't there anything
you can do?
Sorry. Fire regulations.
Should've gotten here earlier.
This is nothing but a
blatant abuse of power
by a petty functionary.
Explain to me why
Wil Wheaton and his lackeys
get in and we don't.
'Cause I'm the petty functionary
with a clipboard, bitch.
I guess that's that.
Let's go home.
You know what?
I'm going back to
"I told you so."
I told you so.
We can still see something.
Oh, the new Sandra Bullock movie
is playing two blocks away.
You know Sandy B.
always brings it.
Look-- a side door.
Come on, Short Round.
I guess we'd better
go after him.
Short Round?
Indy's young sidekick
from Temple of Doom.
Yeah, I know who it
is, but why is it me?
You're right. It should
be a cuddly Asian boy.
Like me.
"And Absolon hath
kist hir nether ye,
"and Nicholas is scalded
in the towte.
This tale is doon,
and God save al the rowte."
What the hell was that?
Bernadette dared me to
tell a dirty story.
"The Miller's Tale" by Chaucer
is the dirtiest story I know.
It would have been hidden
in sock drawers
if people in the 14th century
had worn socks.
I thought it was pretty spicy.
Especially the part
where he kisses her nether ye.
You might not
like it as much
if you knew what
"nether ye" meant.
if one cares
about hygiene,
one ought not be kissing it.
Okay, my turn.
Penny, truth or dare?
Truth.
Why are you still hanging out
with Leonard so much
even though you broke up
with him?
Oh, that's an
excellent question.
For two people who claim to be
no longer pair-bonded,
you spend an inordinate amount
of time in each other's company.
Yeah.
Dare.
I don't believe the rules allow
for an ex post facto
option change.
Yeah.
Okay, look, just because we're
not seeing each other anymore
doesn't mean
we can't be friends.
I mean, Leonard's a great guy.
Then, why did you terminate
your relationship with him?
I don't know.
He got really serious,
and I wasn't ready for it.
Interesting.
How will you react
if, in the future,
you become ready for it,
and Leonard is unavailable,
because another woman
has realized that he is--
to use your words--
"a great guy"?
You can only ask one question.
That one.
You know what,
I don't want to play anymore.
Well, I'm not sure
how this is scored,
but I believe
we may have won.
Sheldon?
Where did he go?
We're looking for Sheldon,
not Marmaduke.
You whistled?
What is that?
Raiders of the Lost Ark
with 21 additional seconds.
If I can't see it,
no one else can see it.
Sheldon, this is crazy.
No. Crazy was leaving
the projection booth unattended.
Listen to me.
You are over-tired.
You're not thinking right.
Put the movie back
before we get into trouble.
Trouble is my middle name,
Leonard.
Actually, it's Lee,
but I prefer Trouble.
Oh, look who
they let in.
Don't worry, Wil Wheaton.
I was just leaving.
Come on, Short Round.
Yeah.
Come on, guys!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Let's see you run
with a bag of urine
strapped to your leg.
He's got the movie! Get him!
Why is there never a pontoon
plane when you need one?
She's been in there
a long time.
Clearly, losing Truth or Dare
upset her.
Perhaps we should try
to take her mind off it
with another popular
slumber party activity.
Ooh, like what?
Well, the Internet suggests
that slumber party guests
often engage
in harmless experimentation
with lesbianism.
Where exactly on the Internet
have you been looking?
Penny?
Oh, hey, Amy.
Look, I'm sorry I got
so upset. I just...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
Don't worry. I'll
avoid the nether ye.
I might have gone
with eating raw cookie dough.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net