Clarify something for me.
Isn't the point
of a communal meal
the exchange of ideas
and opinions?
An opportunity to consider
important issues of the day?
It is.
You just kind of put
a damper on things
when you said,
"The next person I see talking
with food in their mouth
will be put to death."
Well, we could argue about
who said what all night long,
but to set things back
on course,
I will propose
a new topic of conversation.
(groans)
Great.
What is the best number?
By the way, there's only
one correct answer.
5,318,008?
Wrong.
The best number is 73.
You're probably wondering why.
No. Uh-uh.
We're good.
73 is the 21st prime number.
Its mirror, 37, is the 12th,
and its mirror, 21,
is the product of multiplying--
hang on to your hats--
seven and three.
Eh? Eh? Did I lie?
We get it.
73 is the Chuck Norris
of numbers.
Chuck Norris wishes.
In binary, 73 is a palindrome:
"one-zero-zero-
one-zero-zero-one"
which backwards is "one-zero-
zero-one-zero-zero-one"--
exactly the same.
All Chuck Norris backwards
gets you is: "Sirron Kcuhc."
Just for the record,
when you enter 5,318,008
on a calculator,
upside-down it spells "boobies""
Remember when you were wondering
why the girls didn't
want to eat with us tonight?
Yeah, I get it now.
I love your little
heart locket, Bernadette.
Oh, thanks.
Howard gave it to me.
It's the cutest thing.
Every time I have
dinner with his mom,
the next day I get jewelry.
Did you know that the iconic
Valentine's heart shape
is not actually based
on the shape of a human heart,
but rather on the shape
of the buttocks
of a female bending over?
Oh, so I spent seventh grade
dotting my I's
with little asses?
Cool.
Hey, Penny, how's it going?
Hey, Zack,
what are you doing here?
My dad's company prints
the menus for this place.
I'm just dropping off
some new ones laminated.
Makes 'em easier to clean
if people throw up on 'em.
Guess how I got the idea?
Yeah, I got it, I got it.
Uh, Zack, these are
my friends Bernadette and Amy.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hoo.
Okay, well, it was
good to see you.
Yeah, you, too.
He's really cute.
How do you know him?
Oh, we went out
a couple of times.
I'm often flummoxed
by current slang.
Does "went out" mean
"had intercourse"?
Yes.
No, no.
But in this case, yes.
Interesting.
And was it not satisfactory?
No, it was great.
He just didn't really challenge
me on an intellectual level.
Couldn't you just fool around
with him and then listen to NPR?
Wouldn't help. Zack
can't even spell NPR.
It's what I do with Howard.
I'm much smarter than he is.
But it's important
to protect his manhood.
Hoo.
What's the matter?
I'm suddenly feeling flushed.
My heart rate is elevated,
my palms are clammy,
my mouth is dry.
In addition, I keep
involuntarily saying "hoo."
Oh, we know what's
causing that, don't we?
It's no mystery.
I obviously have the flu
coupled with sudden-onset
Tourette's syndrome.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 4x10 ♪
The Alien Parasite Hypothesis
Original Air Date on December 9, 2010
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Did you hear about the
accident at the bio lab?
No.
What happened?
They were injecting rats
with radioactive isotopes
and one of the techs got bit.
Did he get superpowers?
No, he got five stitches
and a tetanus shot.
Oh. Well, that's disappointing.
Why?
Well, you get bit by a
radioactive animal in a lab,
you kind of want to turn
into a superhero.
Yeah, but who'd want
to become Rat-Man?
Who wouldn't?
You could zip through
a maze in nothing flat,
squeeze through
really small holes,
and shut down restaurants
in a single bound.
And the best part is,
if I were Rat-Man,
you could be my
sidekick, Mouse Boy.
Mouse Boy?
You don't like "Mouse Boy"?
How about "Kid Vermin"?
First of all,
if we had superpowers,
I wouldn't be the sidekick.
You'd be the sidekick.
Rat-Man is nobody's sidekick.
Leonard, settle this.
Of the two of us, who's
the obvious sidekick?
Yeah, Leonard, who?
12 years after high school,
and I'm still at the nerd table.
Aren't you slicing that
man's brain a little too thin?
It's too thin if I were making
a foot-long brain sandwich
at Quiznos.
For examination under a two-
photon microscope, it's fine.
Well, you're the expert.
If the correct way to do it
is the wrong way, then I yield.
Very well.
If you die and donate
your body to science,
I promise to slice your brain
like Canadian bacon.
Thank you.
Now, if you'll
excuse me,
I have to take my temperature.
Are you monitoring
your circadian rhythms
in order to identify your periods
of maximum mental acuity?
I did that one summer.
Ah, youth.
No, I experienced some
distressing symptoms last night,
so I'm checking
my vital signs every hour.
I'd be happy to create a chart
and participate in a
differential diagnosis.
Oh, that sounds like fun.
All right.
What were the symptoms?
Elevated heart rate,
moist palms, dry mouth
and localized
vascular throbbing.
Localized to what region?
Ears and genitalia.
Interesting.
Not body parts
that usually team up.
What about
environmental factors?
Describe the scene for me.
I was sitting in a restaurant
with Penny and Bernadette,
drinking water-- carbonated
as it was a special occasion.
Penny's friend Zack stopped by
and said hello and I said "hoo."
Who?
Zack.
Then why did you ask?
Ask what?
Who.
Zack.
All right, let's start over.
What did you say
when Zack walked in?
"Hoo."
Zack.
Why do you keep saying "Zack"?
Because you keep saying "who."
I'm not saying "hoo" now.
I said "hoo" last night.
And the answer was Zack,
correct?
There was no question.
I simply said "hoo."
All right, I think
I have enough to go on.
Possible explanations
for your symptoms are,
in descending order
of likelihood:
hyperthyroidism,
premature menopause,
hosting an alien parasite or--
and I only include it
for the sake of covering
absolutely all bases--
sexual arousal.
Where would I have picked up
an alien parasite?
There you are.
Oh, hey.
Let me ask you a question.
What are you most afraid of?
I don't know. Um...
Nuclear war.
Accidentally being
buried alive.
Any of those movies where
you get that phone call
that says you're
going to die.
And then you do.
No. Something very specific
that we both know you,
Rajesh Koothrappali,
are terrified of.
Well, type two diabetes
runs in my family.
The thought of
losing a toe...
Spiders!
You're afraid of spiders!
What the heck is this?
A jar with a big spider
in it, of course.
Bravery test.
First one to take his hand out
is the sidekick.
Are you crazy?
Perhaps.
Are you scared?
No. But it's a stupid test.
Oh, really?
What if the earth was in danger
and the only way to save it was
to stick your hand
in a jar with a spider?
Oh, yeah?
What if the earth was in danger
and the only way
to save it was to take a shower
in the locker room and let
other guys see you naked?
Oh, come on.
That's never gonna happen.
Put your hand
in the jar
or forever be revealed
as my sidekick.
All right, I will.
How did you get so brave
all of a sudden?
It's easy.
The spider's crawling
up your arm.
(screaming)
Get it off! Get it off!
Please, Raj!
(screaming)
Please.
Oh!
(blowing forcefully)
My blood work shows
thyroid function normal.
Cortisol levels normal.
How about your
follicle-stimulating hormone
levels?
Sheldon, I am not going
through menopause.
Are you sure?
You said that with
the testy bark of an old biddy.
I think we need
to face the cold, hard truth:
I was sexually aroused
by Penny's friend Zack.
Hang on. I don't know
that we've given
the alien parasite hypothesis
a fair shake.
Let's look at this logically.
I have a stomach; I get hungry.
I have genitals; I have the
potential for sexual arousal.
A cross we all must bear.
You know, in difficult
moments like this,
I often turn to a force
greater than myself.
Religion?
Star Trek.
Did you see
Star Trek: The Motion Picture?
No.
Don't. It's terrible. However...
in it, we learn that
when Spock finds himself
drawn off the path of logic
by feelings bubbling up from his
human half, he suppresses them
using the Vulcan mental
discipline of Kolinar.
Are you suggesting
we live our lives
guided by the philosophies
found in cheap science fiction?
"Cheap science fiction"?
What are you doing?
Using Kolinar to suppress
my anger at that last comment.
Is it possible that your
concern for me at this moment
is motivated by nothing more
than simple jealousy?
I hadn't considered that.
Give me a moment.
All right, I've considered it.
And?
I reject it.
You reject it because
you don't feel jealousy,
or because you are
suppressing jealousy?
I think
I'll eat my lunch at home.
That's not your
lunch, Sheldon;
those are the cadaver
brain specimens.
Oh.
As they were incorrectly sliced,
you can see how I could
mistake them for my sashimi.
Hello.
Hey. Isn't tomorrow
your usual laundry night?
The supermarket was out of
my regular fabric softener.
If this one under-
or over-softens,
I'll need time
to make things right.
That's thinking ahead.
The alternative would be
to think backwards.
That's just remembering.
So how's Amy?
Amy's changed.
I might have to let her go.
Oh, no. Why?
I thought she was
a highly evolved creature
of pure intellect, like me.
But recent events indicate that
she may be a slave
to her baser urges.
Like you.
Just going to
skip over that insult.
What insult?
Yeah. That's why
I'm going to skip over it.
Are you saying that Amy is...
oh, what's the
scientific word...
Forget science. She's horny.
Oh! Okay. Wow.
It's simple biology. There's
nothing I can do about it.
Are you sure?
What are you suggesting?
I'm suggesting there
might be something
you could do about...
Amy's urges?
It's illegal to spay
a human being.
Yeah. That's not
what I had in mind.
Oh.
Oh!
You mean...
something I could do.
Exactly.
Well, I was hoping
to avoid this.
But I might as well
get it over with.
Thank you, Penny.
I'll let you
know what happens.
Oh, Amy, you lucky girl.
Yes. This is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Is this the Zack Johnson
who used to have coitus
with my neighbor Penny?
Sorry to bother you.
Hello. I'm looking
for a Zack Johnson
who used to have coitus
with my neighbor Penny.
Coitus. It means intercourse.
And I have a feeling I'm
speaking to the right Zack.
This is Sheldon Cooper.
Fine. Shelly.
Yes, that does
sound like a girl's name.
No, it doesn't bother me.
Yes, "Smelly Shelly"
does bother me.
Let me tell you why I'm calling.
I'd like to know
if you'd be interested
in having sex
with Amy Farrah Fowler.
Amy Farrah Fowler.
Yes, that is  a girl's name.
Good grief. It's like trying
to talk to a dolphin.
Really?
This is going to decide who's
the hero and who's the sidekick?
You got a better idea?
Every idea is better
than this idea.
Ding!
Wait. What the hell is "ding"?
It's a bell.
I don't think this
kind of wrestling has a bell.
Fine. How do you
want to start?
I say, uh, how about
one, two, three, go?
One-two-three-go?
That's for babies.
Okay, how about, uh...
On your mark, get set, go?
That's for a footrace.
If you want to race,
we have to go outside.
No, it's chilly outside.
Didn't bring my jacket.
Oh, for crying out loud.
What kind of superhero
needs a jacket?
What kind of superhero says,
"Dibs on the red tights!
Dibs on the red tights!"
All right, how about this?
Ready, wrestle.
Wait. Are we starting now? Or
is that what you're going to say
when we do start, or...
We're starting now!
Don't yell at me!
Suppose there are worse ways
to spend a Friday night.
None come to mind.
Look at this stamp.
On what authority
are they permitted to
mutilate patrons as they enter?
I'm sure it'll wash off.
Little comfort tonight.
I look like a Hell's Angel.
There's Zack.
Are you sure this is
what you want to do?
It's not what I want to do;
it's what I have to do.
Go, Amy Farrah Fowler.
Follow your endocrine system.
Thank you, Sheldon.
You're a good friend.
Please don't drag this out.
This is never going to come off.
Excuse me?
Zack, I am Amy Farrah Fowler.
We met the other night.
I have spent my life in
pursuit of pure knowledge.
Until I met you,
my decisions
were founded in
logic and reason.
And yet here I stand before you,
130 pounds of raging estrogen,
longing to grab hold
of your gluteus maximus
and make Shakespeare's
metaphorical
beast with two backs.
My gluteus what?
On the other hand,
as I look at the blank, ape-like
expression on your face,
I have decided to adopt the
Vulcan practice of Kolinar.
Good-bye, Zack.
Bye.
(ecstatically):
Hoo.
That should hold me for a while.
I'm legally obligated
to inform you
that I took a karate lesson
when I was 11.
I'd be a regular ninja by now
if my mom could've
arranged a carpool.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I've been taking
Pilates class at the rec center,
and my abs look like
sections of a Hershey bar.
Oh, yeah? Won't matter,
you're going down!
No, uh-uh, you're going down!
If anybody's going to go down,
it's going to be you.
Fellas. It's been 30 minutes.
Nobody's touched each other.
I'm glad you decided to reject
your animal hindbrain
and return to the
realm of pure intellect.
As am I.
What are you doing?
An experiment.
Nope. Nothing.
Never mind.
You realize you can't win.
I prefer to think
that I can't lose.
You're wrong.
It's only a matter of time
before you fall into
Rat-Man's rat trap.
You pathetic fool!
If there were a rat-catcher,
wouldn't it catch Rat-Man?
Just because I didn't
express myself well
doesn't mean my
underlying point was invalid!
You bloviating buffoon!
You narcissistic nincompoop!
You crimson coward!
Oh, Leonard, wake up,
you're missing some very
excellent superhero quips.
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
www.tvsubtitles.net