Previously on Mad Men...
I assumed that we were
forgetting about that.
Well, I haven't.
His name is Manolo Colón.
He's an army trained
registered nurse.
Is he Spanish from Spain?
Because otherwise, Mother will refuse.
You know, we're losing the war.
Wouldn't know it
from looking around here.
Yeah, it's something, right?
I am going to continue on Chevy
evaluating other people's work.
That's all I can do right now.
Call me around 1970 when
they're ready to make an ad.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Good morning, Mr. Draper.
Mr. Sterling's inside.
- Do you want ice?
- Coffee.
It's one thing to be near the bar,
it's another thing to be under it.
Sunkist sent us a crate.
I've seen blind people juggle, but
somehow it seems to be beyond me.
Why don't you
just close your eyes?
That's what you did
in the meeting.
Whatever I did, it worked.
- We're in it.
- That's good news.
Step one,
I send it to research.
Step two, you'll need to get that
little idea factory working.
There's only one angle.
An orange--
that's orange on TV.
I thought they were pretty clear
they're too cheap to get out of print.
So talk 'em out of it,
or into it.
I'd love to, but I think it
demands a media strategy.
Forget research.
Put Harry Crane on it.
- Look at you.
- See?
Not all surprises are bad.
The ants,
they look like peoples.
He should be right out. Is
there anything I can get you?
I think she would
like a cup of tea.
- In a teacup.
- I'd be more excited
if we didn't have to go
in Ted's plane to present.
- Hello, Mother.
- Hello, Peter.
Manolo, may I speak
with you a moment?
Of course, Mr. Campbell.
Your tea is coming.
I'll be fine.
I'm not a child.
Peggy, would you mind?
Mrs. Campbell,
nice to meet you.
There's no reason for you
to be so formal, dear.
Sit with me.
How are you today?
I can't tell you
how much it relieves me
to see you and Peter reunited.
Well, it was really
a by-product of the merger.
I'm glad you both
swallowed your pride.
If nothing else
but for the good
of the child you have together.
Excuse me?
Oh, I've embarrassed you.
Your son and I are not
together that way.
Trudy, dear, don't deny him.
Don't reject his caresses.
Mrs. Campbell--
I hope you two can someday find
what Manolo and I have found.
I waited long enough
to experience the physical
satisfactions of love.
Did she go
to China for that tea?
Thank you for driving
her out to Bud's.
I've paid you
for the extra day.
- I know you don't drive.
- Well, I do,
but not to her satisfaction.
Bob Benson was right about you.
You're worth every penny.
Bob is a wonderful salesman.
Still, I want you to have a
little something off the books.
Mr. Campbell,
I refuse.
It's important to me
that you treat my mother well,
but also
that you treat yourself.
- The pleasure is all mine.
- I know that isn't true.
Sally, get in here.
Hello.
- What?
- Julie's mother called and told me
- you were the only two girls on the trip.
- So?
You're not staying in a Midtown
hotel with all those boys.
Miss O'Shea is gonna be there.
She's 25.
What's the point
of having a mansion
if you're gonna spend
all your time in here?
Fine, I won't do the Model UN.
- It was his idea.
- Fine, you're not going.
- Can't we stay with Daddy?
- You mean with no one.
You hate that Daddy
supports my dreams.
He doesn't think I'm
just a pain in the ass.
Your father is a hero.
Like everything
else in this country,
Diplomacy Club's just
another excuse to make out.
I thought she should join
the Student Congress.
The UN's a joke.
- Oh, you're home.
- Who's this?
This is Mitchell,
Sylvia and Arnold's son.
Nice to finally meet you, Mitchell.
I'm Don.
Thanks again, Megan.
What did he want?
Um...
I'm sworn to secrecy, but
he's in a lot of trouble.
- What happened?
- He's 1-A.
But he's in school.
He sent back his draft card
in protest.
They reclassified him.
What did he think
was gonna happen?
Stupid kid.
Don, he knows he screwed up.
He wants to run.
You know, to Canada.
I suppose I could
call my brother-in-law,
but I can't do that
to Sylvia and Arnold.
- Can I?
- Just leave it alone.
- He's so scared.
- He should be.
He can't spend the rest
of his life on the run.
I know how you feel,
but you don't want him
to go to Vietnam.
Megan, it's not our problem.
Could you get me
another whiskey sour?
- Sure.
- Maybe I'll switch to whiskey sours.
How about
a Shirley Temple, then?
I don't think Dramamine
and booze go together.
I don't think Dramamine and cranberry
juice go together, either.
But I thought we'd be back
on your little plane,
not having a romantic dinner.
Don't you want to celebrate?
I want to live, Ted.
What?
He doesn't like flying.
Well, you've seen
how simple it is now.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
My father died
in a plane... crash.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Was he a pilot?
Ha! No.
Passenger.
Look, you're driving.
Can we please, please
have another round?
You still have to get home
from White Plains.
I'll hail a cab.
He's such a New Yorker.
This is the agency
I always wanted.
Ambition, brains, and beauty.
Yeah, but what about him?
I'm gonna cut you
off too, my dear.
I should call home.
If the check comes, I'm
sending it to Ocean Spray.
Can you imagine what
it does to his wife
every time he takes that plane?
I guess so.
You don't want me
to talk about his wife.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
But I do.
I've seen that look.
I know, but...
nothing can happen.
And he's in love with you, too.
You're the one
who's in love with him.
Well, I could use an account
and he's been generous.
At least one of us
ended up important.
Please tell me
you don't pity me.
I don't.
Because you really know me.
I do.
Ahem--
I should tell you...
I had a very strange
conversation with your mother.
There's no other kind.
Well, it doesn't matter.
What did she say?
I think she thought
I was your wife
and Manuel was her husband.
My father never
treated her that well.
Maybe that's it. She thinks
she's in love with him.
I can see it.
Manolo is very charming.
I don't think you understand.
She thinks she's...
making love with him.
Tell me exactly what she said.
Did your father ever
give her spa treatments
that released
a "fire in her loins"?
Oh!
Oh, I think I'm gonna be sick.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have told you.
But I can't get the image
out of my head.
Stop it, please.
I don't even want to think
about her brushing her teeth.
I thought I cut you two off.
Ted.
I have never been less
afraid of flying in my life.
What?
What does he mean?
Nothing.
Well, I should get the check.
Honey, who's that gonna be?
- Arnold.
- Is it too late?
For what?
Come in.
Look, I would have
called, but Sylvia is...
Listen, about
this afternoon--
Oh, hello, Arnold.
I'm sorry about my kid
dropping in on you.
I didn't know
if I should tell you.
Well, he figured you would
and I don't want you
in the middle of this.
His mother's treating it
like he's dying.
She doesn't want
anyone to know.
Do you want a drink?
Sit up here drinking while they're
down there slamming the doors?
Been meaning to knock
on your door anyway.
You know, catch a game
or something.
I get baseball tickets.
Mostly the Mets.
Well, then I'm glad you didn't.
You know, I didn't
even know he left school.
Sylvia says
she didn't know either.
She's doing that
a lot lately--
lying about little things.
Could tell something's
been wrong all year.
- Another Manhattan?
- Nah. No.
Should have never
let him go to Paris.
He got there right in
the middle of the riots.
His French is excellent.
I think he got a lot of girls
as an expatriate revolutionary.
Could kill him right now.
There has to be a way.
Oh, believe me,
everybody's an expert on it.
Sylvia's father was
suddenly Clarence Darrow.
It's thrilling to see a plumber
interpret international law.
You're one of the top
surgeons in the country.
You must know somebody.
I know a lot of people,
but it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter
if he goes back to school.
He's 1-A. His induction
could be tomorrow.
He's on a damn list
for the rest of his life.
On some level you have
to admire his idealism.
You sound like Sylvia.
But she doesn't really
buy his bullshit.
You think she's gonna
let her baby
rot in jail for a cause?
I don't know what to do.
What would you do?
If it was my kid,
or if it was me?
You were in the service, right?
I was.
You see action?
It was very different.
I wanted to go.
And then when
I got there, well...
That's the trick.
Kids 18, 19 years old, they have
no sense of their own mortality.
Or anyone else's.
That's why they make
good soldiers.
Well, the Army
paid for med school.
I served in a hospital
in Pusan.
We were very lucky.
Lucky enough to live
in this country.
And service is part
of that bargain.
Sacrifice.
We knew that.
The war is wrong.
I'll tell you right now, if
anyone was ever gonna get it,
it's gonna be him.
He's soft.
I'm sure he's a good kid.
The best.
What you watching?
I don't know.
What's the matter?
I called.
I didn't want to get into it
when you're about to fly,
but you were supposed
to have dinner with us.
I made a mistake.
We'll do it tomorrow.
You don't have to make
a federal case out of it.
Why don't you get a legal pad
and write down a bunch of
excuses for the next week?
Because none of them
mean anything to the boys.
What about food, clothing, and shelter?
Does that mean anything?
Remember what the minister
said at Frank's funeral?
"God can turn off
the lights at any moment."
You know where you're gonna be?
The office.
This is temporary.
I just have
to do this until--
Until what?
Until you are back
where you were at the old firm?
Because things weren't
so great then either.
So we've moved on
from I'm working too much
to something else.
The problem is even
when you do come home,
you're not here.
You're obsessed.
And I can feel how
disappointing this all is
compared to
your battles at work.
I'm not enjoying that.
How did we get to
the point where you think
I don't want you
to enjoy things?
I know you like having a young
copywriter in your airplane.
Come on, Pete was there, too.
I know you like
facing Don Draper
every morning
more than the clients.
How was your day?
I just wish you liked
being here more.
Could you get
Mr. Campbell?
Do you want to see him
before the status meeting?
- Ugh, when's that?
- Now.
And I also need to know if you're
attending the Chevrolet dinner.
- When's that?
- Tonight.
- Morning.
- May I speak with you?
Does your friend still work
at the Department of Defense?
No, he left for Union Carbide.
But he probably still
has pull over there.
What happened now?
You must know plenty of people
with kids getting deferments.
How are they doing that?
They go to college.
Divinity school.
Medical baloney.
No, it's too late for that. I need
someone who can really pull strings.
Well, aren't you having
dinner with General Motors,
one of the largest defense
contractors in the world?
What are the politics of that?
I don't know, Don.
I'm not on Chevy.
Shall we?
That's not my fault.
Don't worry.
If I had Chevy
I wouldn't be able to devote my
full attention to Ocean Spray.
- Cranberries?
- Cranberry cocktail.
And they like us so much they
might even give us the blends.
- What about Sunkist?
- What about it?
It's orange juice.
Morning, everyone.
- Did you know about Sunkist?
- What about it?
Don told Harry to put together
a media plan right away.
Why didn't you
tell us about that?
Isn't this the meeting
where I tell you?
Are we having this meeting?
Why didn't you tell us you were
presenting to Ocean Spray?
There's been a series of memos.
Didn't you wonder
where everybody was?
- We can't present to both.
- Which one is bigger?
They're about the same.
Three million.
We've already spent
$5,000 on Ocean Spray.
What about our trip
to California?
Was it $5,000?
I have a lot of receipts.
I haven't figured it out yet.
Why don't you join this company
and read a memo once in a while?
Maybe they're not a conflict.
We don't have either yet.
I really didn't know.
I warned you
about the memos, Ted.
The more you send,
the less they get read.
Imagine if every time Ginger
Rogers jumped in the air,
Fred Astaire punched her
in the face.
Why are you taking
this to heart?
Because it's directed at me.
Can you not see that?
So what? You know we'll end
up with just one juice.
I don't want his juice.
I want my juice.
It's all your juice.
Tell him that.
Michigan's in the Big 10.
Ron Kutchinski just ran the
fastest half mile in the world.
He's going to the Olympics.
You're selling yourself short.
I'm telling you, they would
be lucky to have you.
I got it.
Look at this. Got a couple
of high fashion models.
Aren't you a gentleman?
- Hey.
- Hello.
Youse two don't know
each other.
These are my two
favorite people.
Mitchell Rosen, 16A,
I'd like you to meet
Sally Draper, 17B
and all points north.
I'm Julie.
I'm crashing at Sally's.
Cool.
They were supposed to leave a key for me.
I lost mine.
Nobody said nothing to me,
but that don't mean nothing.
We were going to go out
for dinner tonight.
- What's good around here?
- His mother's cooking.
Around here
it's just old people.
Are you a musician?
'Cause you look like one.
Who?
I don't see it.
I'll let you in.
Oh, good day to you,
Mrs. Rosen.
Hello. Mitchell,
did you get a cab?
- I was waiting for you.
- You're unbelievable.
I got it, Mrs. Rosen.
Do you know Sally and...?
- I'm Julie. - I'm sorry, girls,
we're in a bit of a rush.
I'll get you a cab
lickety-split.
Bring them right back.
You're living
with Mark Lindsay.
I don't live here.
What are you doing here?
I said I'd meet you
at La Grenouille.
Dorothy, you must let me
manage your calendar.
I'm not standing
in the hallway.
Come in.
You get ready, Mr. Campbell.
I'll entertain her.
Actually, Manolo, I'd like my
mother to myself this evening.
Very well.
Good night, my sweet.
Must he?
He has other plans, Mother.
Yes, Dorothy. I'll be
there when you wake.
- Can I fix you something?
- No.
Manolo doesn't
like me to drink.
He likes me sharp.
It's so nice the way
he looks after you.
Oh, Peter, he's a gift to me.
I just wanted to make
sure you're aware
he's your nurse.
You are prone to moments
of confusion.
I suppose there's a way
I could mistake
your tone for concern.
I am concerned
that you have--
how do I put this?
--misconstrued Manolo's
attention for affection.
If we're going to have
an adult conversation,
let's have
an adult conversation.
Has he taken advantage of you?
Manny has awakened a part of me
that was long dormant.
Don't you think I'm entitled
to the pleasures of love?
Do not be more specific.
Since when is it
any of your business
what goes on in my bedroom?
I am afraid that we are going
to have to let him go.
Oh, no.
What did he do?
He's a pervert.
You were a sour little boy.
And you're a sour little man.
How could I expect you
to be understanding?
You've always been unlovable.
Now I've lost my appetite.
I'm leaving.
You'll never find
your way home.
I have carfare
and a piece of paper
with my address
written in his
elegant handwriting.
Mother.
Cheesecake?
Chocolate cake?
- Two of everything.
- And another round.
- Why not?
- Oh, I can never get enough of it.
Growing up in Cleveland, my dad
would take me right on Lake Erie.
But, eh, water's gone bad now.
You should go to Florida.
Saltwater.
Down off the Keys
- where the marlin run.
- Write your own Hemmingway story.
And if you don't catch anything,
you have to blow your brains out.
So, Ross, where do you
take your kid fishing?
I just got the two girls, and they
could never keep their mouths shut.
But my grandson's just like me.
Last summer we went
up to Muskoka.
Ontario.
Jesus, now we got to hear
about this kid again.
Brendan's at Antioch.
Yup, studying the classics.
But I hope he'll come
to his senses.
He's got a couple of years
before he has decisions to make.
Well, as long as we're working
together, he's got a job with us.
Friend of mine's kid
just got to that point.
He doesn't have a lot of choices left.
1-A. Can you imagine?
Well, my heart goes out to him.
That's just one of those
problems that can't be solved.
I've got two sons.
Thank God they're too young.
I don't even like
to think about that.
I know.
My friend is just
beside himself.
I mean, people are
doing things, though.
Believe me, we know about that.
Makes me sick.
Well, next year this time,
we'll have won the war.
We'll take Brendan to
dinner, get him plastered,
and have him read
the menu in Latin.
Ted, are you an angler?
My hobby is coming up
with names for the XP.
_
Last one.
Okay.
"Things I like
about Mitchell."
"His ass"?
- Shh.
- When did you see that?
I couldn't think
of anything else.
What did you put?
"How he smiled at me."
"His shoulders."
"His red shirt."
You girls have
a big day tomorrow
and I can tell you right now, the next
time this door opens, it won't be me.
- Lights out.
- Good night, Mrs. Draper.
Why do you keep
calling her that?
'Cause she hates it.
Think about it.
He's right down there.
You should sneak down
and kiss him.
He talked to you.
God, I wish I lived here.
- Yeah?
- Did I wake you?
- Yeah.
- There's a rat in my apartment.
Told you to get traps.
It's in the trap
and it's mortally wounded.
I'm pretty sure
'cause there's a lot of blood.
Did you call an ambulance?
You have to come over.
It went under the couch.
I can't even look.
What if it's still alive?
What if I lift the couch
and it starts flipping around?
I'm not your boyfriend.
Maybe I'll make it worth
your while if you come over.
No, you won't.
Now good night.
You're not interested?
No.
Then why are you using
your sexy voice?
Tuesday morning's great.
For what?
Oh.
Why didn't you say so?
You can bring her.
It'll be dead by morning.
Eleanor Roosevelt.
I can't remember anything
'cause I didn't sleep.
Your floor smells like pee.
- No, it doesn't.
- Do I smell like pee?
You smell like Prell.
Sally, you're not ready?
I let the guest shower first.
Well, I have to go to work.
But first I have to put you
two in a cab, so shake a leg.
Oh, take out the trash.
I have to get ready.
I'll do it, Mrs. Draper.
It's Megan.
I would love to visit
the studio sometime.
Well, hopefully
I'll still have a job.
I have to make a phone call.
- Your agent?
- Yes, actually.
Could you get me some coffee?
What the hell were you
up to last night?
Mr. Draper.
I'm fine, Dawn.
You want some coffee?
What the hell
were you thinking?
You said you weren't going to be
involved in Chevy until 1970.
So stay the hell out of it.
Stop trying to poison
my relationship.
Last time I checked,
it's our relationship.
And not everything
is about you, Ted.
Then be better at it.
- What are you talking about?
- You know this.
A client shouldn't have a single
negative feeling in your presence.
Not the food, not the wine,
and certainly not the war.
I was just taking
their temperature.
Why would you do that?
It's Chevy, Don.
- You'd do it for your kid.
- But it's not your kid.
Oh, is it your kid?
No, it's my friend's kid.
Well, I bet you don't have
a lot of friends, Don,
so I'm going to assume
this is important.
It is.
I just--
I don't know what to do.
Do you know how young 19 is?
Did you ever think
about talking to me
instead of our most
important client?
I don't know.
It's GM.
Who else has that kind
of clout in Washington?
Does he wear glasses?
I don't think so, but he could.
The guy who taught me to fly
is a brigadier general
in the Air National Guard.
They're always looking
for exceptional young men
to become pilots.
And you'd be willing
to call him?
I'd consider it.
But first, you're going
to have to stop the war.
I can't stop the war, Ted.
Don't be an asshole, Don.
The war you're waging on me.
You have to lower your weapons.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about how we
are going to get Ocean Spray.
So you need to stop
chasing Sunkist.
You're not going to compete
with me like that anymore.
We're on the same damn side.
- That's it?
- Don't act like it's nothing.
It seems to be
impossible so far.
You'd really do that?
Thank you.
This is not
a handshake of gratitude.
- This is a binding contract.
- Of course.
- Whatever you want.
- That's what I want.
Hold on.
What's the next step?
Tell the kid to write a letter
about his childhood
dream of being a pilot.
And it better be convincing.
You should write it.
And tell him to get a haircut.
Be straight, Ted.
What are the chances?
I'm going to call right now.
Thank you.
Can you get Dr. Rosen
on the phone?
- Rosen residence.
- It's me. It's Don.
What do you want?
I'm trying to reach Arnold.
The office said
he was home sick.
It's about Mitchell.
What? Tell me.
I know someone who knows someone
in the Air National Guard.
He's getting him a spot.
You told someone?
It's my partner.
He's doing me a favor.
Did you fix it?
He just wants Mitchell
to cut his hair
and sign a letter.
And the two of you need to
make sure he follows through.
Oh, he'll follow through.
I bet.
My God, is it possible?
I think so,
but we have to act fast.
They went upstate to the VA
to call on an army buddy.
I'll send them up tonight.
Sylvia, sweetheart,
it's gonna be okay.
Are you there?
Yes.
Please, stop crying.
I feel better,
but I'll feel better
when I know it's done.
Don...
Yes?
I can't believe you
would do this for me.
You know I have children, too.
I know that's not
why you're doing it.
And I hope--
well, I hope you know that I
was just frustrated with you.
I do now.
I didn't want you
to fall in love.
You didn't feel anything?
No, I just...
I don't want
to go through this again.
You were good to me.
Better than I was to you.
- Are we going to lunch, because--
- Get in here and close the door.
You have given me
a terrible problem
and now you're going to fix it.
Is this about Sunkist?
Because I did some digging--
I told you we needed a nurse
and you sent us a rapist.
Manolo?
In fact, I never
told you anything.
You were just
"doing some digging."
Calm down.
Sit down.
Bob...
she has the mind of a child.
That man took advantage of her.
I assume she told
you this story.
Don't you have
your answer right there?
She says they're in love
and it's the first time in months
she's seemed sure of anything.
I don't think that Manolo's
interests turn that way.
Great, so he's a degenerate.
That means he's capable
of anything.
What exactly did she say?
Please, I'm just
trying to forget it.
Drink that.
- Feel better now?
- I do.
Can I ask you something?
Did she seem happy?
Yes.
She did.
Is it really
so impossible to imagine?
What?
Couldn't it be that
if someone took care of you,
very good care of you...
if this person would do
anything for you,
if your well-being
was his only thought...
is it impossible that you might
begin to feel something
for him?
When there's true love,
it doesn't matter who it is.
Tell him I'll give him
a month's pay.
And tell him it's disgusting.
Of course.
The capital of the
Philippines is Manila.
Its president
is Ferdinand Marcos.
Its national language
is Tagalog,
but many of its
inhabitants speak Spanish
due to its colonial past.
And their national
product is...?
I don't know.
Manila envelopes?
- You don't know anything.
- So?
How about this? All the boys are
going to think you're dumb.
Don't tell me how to get boys.
You went to second base twice.
That's a lot more than you.
So if I were you,
I'd be scared.
- Of what?
- Of what you're going to do
when Mitchell asks you
to go all the way.
He doesn't even know I'm alive.
Oh, I took care of that.
What did you do?
I introduced you.
I introduced myself.
No, I took the letter
and I signed your name.
- What?!
- And I slid it under the back door.
Ow! That really hurts.
How could you do that?
Now I can never go back.
You know you're going
to thank me.
Just because your shift is over
doesn't mean you can get
undressed in the lobby.
- Incredible.
- What?
He should greet you.
How you doing today?
I'm-- I got--
I left something.
And I don't have my key.
You mean you lost it already?
Can I have the keys, please?
Yeah. Okay.
Go fast.
Oh, what have we got here?
Couple of high fashion models?
Oh, God.
- Sally.
- Oh, God.
Oh, dear God.
Dear God, what have we done?
Sally!
Did Sally just come
through here?
Mr. Draper, I didn't
know you was home.
She hopped in a cab just now.
I'll go get her.
You okay?
Yes.
Did something happen?
I know she lost her keys. I gave
her the keys. It's my fault.
Mr. Draper?
Hello?
Oh, I'm glad you're home.
Let me get you a plate.
Oh, wow.
I had a client...
meeting-- lunch.
- Sit down.
- I'm--
I'm gonna lay down.
You need to get some food in you.
Sit down.
Do you want me
to cut you a piece?
No.
I got it.
Hello.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Don, Arnold and
Mitchell are here.
- I don't feel well.
- Stop.
Hello, Mitchell.
I'm sorry
to interrupt your dinner,
but we just got back and Mitchell
has something he wants to say.
Mr. Draper...
thank you very much.
We'll see if it works.
- What?
- He didn't tell you?
Don talked to somebody for us.
Really?
Sylvia sends her gratitude.
She is overwhelmed.
Do you want something to eat?
We should celebrate.
One step at a time.
Anyway, Don,
I owe you.
Let's go.
No, you eat. I got it.
You are the sweetest man.
You make me sick!
Sally, come back here!
What happened?
I don't know.
I'm gonna go talk to her.
No.
I'll talk to her.
She has a crush on Mitchell.
Oh.
Sally.
- Open the door.
- No.
You don't get
to talk to me anymore.
Sally?
Sally, open the door.
I need to talk to you.
I know you think
you saw something.
I was... comforting
Mrs. Rosen.
She was very upset.
It's very...
complicated.
Sally, can you hear me?
Yes.
Did you hear what I said?
Okay.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net