Raising the age of retirement is
an unacceptable erosion
of the American dream.
If the Republicans fail to pass
a reasonable omnibus package
by demanding entitlement reform,
they will force the federal government
into a spending freeze.
The frostbite will be
on their hands, not ours.
Do you think that's a bit much?
The frostbite bit?
It's the State of the Union.
We want to appeal to fly-over states.
- They'll like that line.
- I want something more forceful.
- "Blood on their hands"?
- No.
- "Throw us back into the ice age."
- Oh, I like that, Christina.
Let's try that. Linda.
Christina, you come up here too.
There are two types of vice presidents:
doormats and matadors.
Which do you think
I intend to be?
Raymond.
He's hung up on the domestic agenda.
Not a single word about China.
His instincts are right. If the government
shuts down one day after the speech,
not a single word in the speech matters.
We have to address the freeze now.
- China comes later.
- Both parties have been wrangling
over entitlements for months.
What makes you think
a miracle's gonna happen
in the next three days?
We give the Republicans
exactly what they want.
- Retirement age?
- Yes.
That's a line in
the sand we cannot cross.
We will cross it, eventually.
So why keep fighting it?
I can push this through the Senate,
and once I do, the president will announce
a major bipartisan agreement
in the State of the Union.
We avoid a government shutdown
and the White House gets credit.
It's a huge risk, and if it fails,
a huge embarrassment.
The embarrassment will be
entirely my own. This is on my shoulders.
Even so, the president is
gonna require some serious persuasion.
- I'm happy to talk to him.
- No.
No... I'll do it.
He'll be more amenable
if it comes from a friend.
You're right.
A trusted confidant.
Let me test the waters.
The Cult of Tusk.
one.
But that one disciple
just so happens to be
the most powerful man
in the free world. For now.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Entitlements. Raising
the age of eligibility to 67.
Your people will
never go for it.
They will if the
leadership does,
and the leadership will.
They've fought us on this
since I was in diapers.
Assuming that I can get this past
my people and convince them,
- can you convince yours?
- It's a tough sell.
You're the Senate majority leader, Hector.
You don't have to sell, you can dictate.
- What do you want in return?
- A working government.
- We stave off the freeze.
- You won on education,
we confirmed you
as vice president.
- The Republicans need a win, Frank.
- And that's what I'm offering.
You get a win on entitlements,
we avoid a shutdown.
Everyone gets points
for bipartisanship.
- You know who I'm worried about?
- Curtis Haas.
- He's a troublemaker, Frank.
- Who controls a third of your caucus.
And he'll never go for this.
He wants to see the Democrats suffer.
Just bring him to the table.
That's all I'm asking.
Miss Gallagher?
My name is Lucas Goodwin,
I'm a deputy editor
of the Washington Herald.
- Mr. Goodwin, please.
- Just a few moments,
- that's all I'm asking.
- If I wanted to talk to you,
- I would've returned your calls.
- Did you read my e-mails?
Yes. Which is
why I didn't call.
Give me a chance
to walk you through it.
I have to get back
to the White House.
- Peter Russo was killed.
- Let go.
So was Zoe Barnes.
I was working with her.
- Stop and listen.
- Frank Underwood is the one who did this.
Listen! This is nuts.
- The DUI, the brachiums. All of it...
- This has to stop. OK?
Underwood talk to you?
Tell you not to speak with anybody?
- No.
- Doug Stamper?
Whatever you think happened,
whatever compelled you
to stalk me like this...
You're the only person
who might know something,
who could understand.
I've got no one else
I can talk...
I don't understand.
And I don't want to. OK?
- There's no story here.
- Please, five minutes.
Think about what you're doing.
Waiting outside...
Peter would be alive if it
wasn't for Frank Underwood.
I've worked really hard
to put Peter behind me.
So if I see you again,
if I hear from you again,
I'll not only contact the police,
I'll let the vice president
know what you're saying,
and then you can deal
with the Secret Service, too.
It's the usual overseas chatter.
A bit of a bump in China,
but we chalk that up
to the trade tensions.
- Secret Service?
- Average number of death threats
to both POTUS and the VP.
We passed them along
to our dear friends at the FBI.
FBI?
The FBI confirms the level
of activity of our dear friends
at the Secret Service.
We've followed up on everything.
No high-level threats.
So nothing we need to report directly
to the president or vice president?
- No.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
The e-mail you sent,
has anyone else seen it?
Except for the agent
that alerted me, no.
Other agencies might
have stumbled upon this.
Even so, they
probably ignored it.
Any idea who's making the posts?
Deep Web forums. Almost impossible
to trace. Lone wolf, most likely.
- I want you to find him.
- We need a direct threat to life.
The vice president
just assumed office.
I can't have this conspiracy
stuff going mainstream.
- This sort of thing usually fizzles out.
- I can't take the chance.
I want you to find him
and put him away.
- He hasn't committed a crime.
- But he wants to.
- So help him.
- That requires manpower.
- You've got men.
- It exposes me, Doug.
I've always kept you informed
because you're an old pal and I trust you.
But...
We're talking
about an operation.
I'm an old pal who now works
at the White House.
Between old pals,
I've been stuck at the
executive liaison for way too long.
How worried are you that a mass
shooting could happen in a school
in your community? Great deal,
somewhat, not so much, not at all, unsure.
You sound hot. Are you hot?
- Sir...
-  Somewhat hot, a great deal hot?
Lynchburg Children's,
Pediatric Division.
Can I talk to Cheryl Posner?
Sorry, she's on duty right now.
- It's her daughter.
-  Hold on one moment.
Rachel? Rachel?
Sweetheart, are you there?
Please don't...
- Hello?
- Hi, Mr. Jay, my name is Rachel
and I'm calling on behalf
of the National Firearm Education Center.
Would you be able to speak with
me briefly regarding firearm legislation
and Second Amendment protection?
So you're Willa's top choice.
Why should you be my
husband's and my top choice?
Over the past ten years, the two
of you combined have gotten less coverage
than the average junior
congressman from Nebraska.
- Well, we don't seek the spotlight.
- I'm not suggesting you should.
But am I correct in assuming that your
husband will be an active vice president?
Well, it's harder to keep
an active VP out of the press than in it,
but it's possible if we give the media
just enough to keep them from starving.
- Where'd you grow up, Connor?
- Texas. Just like you.
- Dallas?
- Lubbock.
I had a much thicker accent
to get rid of than y'all.
- How do you know I had one?
- Your first joint interview,
when your husband was running
for state Assembly in '86.
- That's on the Internet?
- No. No, I contacted the
local affiliate in Greenville.
They wouldn't send me
the tapes via mail,
so I went down there
and watched in their vault.
To South Carolina?
When I want a job,
I do my homework.
I look forward to seeing
what you come up with.
Thank you, Mrs. Underwood.
Thursday.
I don't see how this
is a victory for us.
Our choices are the freeze,
which the Democrats get blamed for, or...
- Not necessarily, the Republi...
- Which we definitely get blamed for.
- Or we offer them...
- Entitlements, Frank?
We took a stand.
We can't turn back now.
I'd rather see the
government grind to a halt.
Think of the headline:
"Democratic Leadership
Enacts Entitlement Reform,
Staves Off Freeze."
We show unity.
We offer progress.
Let's convert some
lifelong conservatives.
You have Mendoza's assurance
he'll work with us?
- I do.
- I don't want to put our necks out there
just to have the
guillotine fall.
You won't. My neck will be right
out there with you.
Francis faints at the sight of blood.
He'd never let them break the skin.
To unity.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Come on.
Larry, can you come by? Something weird's
going on with my computer. Thanks.
Come on!
- Hey, what's the problem?
- Nothing. It's fine. I fixed it.
- OK. Cool.
- Yeah.
- It's not as progressive as I'd like.
- You mean radical.
Raising retirement age to
67 makes entitlements solvent until 2055.
And it saves us over a trillion dollars
without a single penny of taxpayer income.
Sixty-eight would give us
another 300 billion,
and I'd like to
eliminate early retirement.
- Entirely?
- Forget it.
What about... 68 and 64?
I have a responsibility
to my constituents.
- I promised I wouldn't waver...
- Are we really going to allow
the tea party to determine
fiscal legislation?
- Never been beholden to the tea party.
- Come on. You wouldn't have won
reelection if their PACs hadn't dumped
ten million into your campaign.
If their definition of budgetary
conservatism happens to overlap with mine,
- that's a function of...
- Curtis, let's show some goodwill.
- Can you stomach 68 and 64?
- Effective immediately?
- Five years from now.
- Not interested.
We can't throw this on people
without any warning.
- They need some time to digest.
- I'm sorry, I just can't do it.
OK, meet with your staff,
consult with your colleagues,
I'll consult with mine
and let's talk tomorrow.
- All right. I can agree to that.
- But this is a good first step.
How do we make sure Curtis
can't filibuster
- when we get the amendment passed?
- Assuming we do.
Between you and me,
I'm sure we can turn him around.
I just want to be
on the safe side.
Make sure the
passage of the amendment
- constitutes the passage of the bill.
- By previous agreement.
We pass the amendment,
then we're done. Wham-bam.
- Can we put that in writing?
- Have Erikson reach out to me.
"Muchas gracias."
Lucas Goodwin?
Good evening, Lucas.
Speak into the microphone.
- Who are you?
-  Go to the home screen.
- Open the other app.
- Tell me who you are.
You've done your research.
You know who I am.
Well, I know
who you claim to be.
If you're not
convinced by now, goodbye.
Wait a minute. Uh...
- All right, I'm on the home screen.
-  Open the notary app.
What is this?
To ensure you
aren't law enforcement.
- I'm not.
-  Then sign.
- How? - Hold your thumb to
the camera and press "capture."
How do I know you're
not law enforcement?
Sign the document or walk away.
All right. I did it.
- Press "send."
- Where is this going?
I'm VPNing through Iran and 12 other
countries, don't worry. It's secure.
Now, one last thing.
I need the two-step verification code
for the Herald's internal servers.
- I don't even know
how to do that.
-  Yes, you do. Check your
e-mail.
Destroy the iPad,
especially the serial number,
and delete the e-mail
after you've memorized it.
Good luck.
Hello?
Raymond, are you there?
Yeah, uh, sorry, Frank, I...
I thought I saw an Inca dove.
It must have flown
the wrong direction for winter.
- It sounds windy. Where are you?
-  Top of my building.
Got a bird feeder up here.
Nice work with the president.
I hear we have a green light.
He pushed back in the beginning but, yeah,
his writers are reworking the speech now.
I'm very close to a deal.
Sixty-eight, 64 in five years.
- Spending cuts as discussed.
- That rock solid?
- Soon as we shake hands.
- What's the holdup?
Curtis Haas, which isn't a surprise.
I'm meeting with him soon.
- He's the final hurdle.
-  Cutting it pretty close, Frank.
Well, this is...
this is historic.
The Republicans have wanted
entitlement reform since Johnson.
Curtis will come around. In the meantime,
we should get the new retirement ages
- into his speech.
- I would stay away from specifics.
- I mean, even if it passes, the House...
- I know the House
better than you know birds. Believe me
when I say they'll pass the Senate version.
I'll talk to the president.
- Just make sure this is airtight.
- Thank you. What is it?
- Lucas Goodwin.
- From the Herald?
He must have been
working with Zoe.
- How much does he know?
- No more than she did.
- She knew enough.
- I'm on it, sir.
- Proof?
- Not yet.
- Jesus, Doug. - It's under control.
I thought you should be aware.
I'm juggling the president,
the Republicans, Tusk. I can't...
And you should stay focused
on that. Goodwin's on my plate, not yours.
It wasn't until the 20th century
that the notion of noble objectivism
came into the forefront.
- But facts are facts.
- Nineteen ninety-two.
George Bush Sr. is shown asking how
a grocery scanner works,
and he gets nailed for it.
they were showing him a new model.
He was asking how the new one
was different than the old one.
Curiosity, not ignorance.
But the lack of context
told a more powerful narrative.
There is no arrangement of facts
that is purely objective.
We can finally do something.
We have the means to act.
Some teenage,
pimple-faced hacker...
This was a
sophisticated infiltration.
It's not the work of a child.
Look, here's the e-mail.
"Heronymous Bot." The FBI's
been hunting him for years.
- Listen to me...
- If we get these records,
I'll need your help tracking
timelines, piecing together...
No! You want somebody to hold
your hand and say it's OK to go on this
fucking goose chase.
You shouldn't be teaching in Ithaca.
You're better than that.
- You should be back...
- I belong here.
Droning on to a bunch
of hung over English majors?
- Exactly.
- You're wrong about the truth.
There is objective truth.
He killed her.
You know it's a fact.
Here's a fact: my mom has ten,
15 years left at best.
I've seen her more in the past
month than since I left for school.
It's simpler here. It's quiet.
I need that. She needs me.
I'm sorry, Lucas. I'm sorry
that night how I reacted.
I'm sorry you lost
your girlfriend.
I'm sorry the world
is this fucked up.
I really am.
But I can't help you.
Thank you.
- Where's everyone else?
- I did you a disservice yesterday.
We shouldn't have put you
on the spot in front of all the leadership.
Have a seat, Curtis.
We know that you have an obligation
to take a firm stance,
but entitlement reform
is something you ran on,
and now it's within your grasp.
So tell us your fears.
That the Democrats
get another win.
We suffer in the midterms and
the next Congress dismantles the agreement.
You think we're
being disingenuous.
My constituents
don't trust the administration.
I can't have them thinking the wool has
been pulled over our eyes.
As I suspected. Hector?
Frank and I propose this:
we include a super majority point of order
against revisiting
the issue for ten years.
You'll have it in black-and-white.
A serious, long-term commitment
with no opportunity
to dismantle.
That's on top of everything
else we asked for.
VA services and FEMA
stay at current levels.
Everything else at 80 to a hundred
percent of the cuts you propose.
You get your win, Curtis.
We just avoid disaster.
Maybe the country needs
to see what disaster looks like.
The tea party is a strong voice,
and you're its bullhorn.
Show your people that voice can translate
into law, and not just add to the noise.
Fifteen years before
revisitation, not ten.
- OK. - And if the House fails to pass
the bill after we do,
you go on record blaming your
own party for the gridlock.
I believe we have a deal.
What are you listening to?
- Sorry. I'll turn it down.
- No, it's nice.
Can I listen?
My ears are clean, I promise.
OK.
Thanks.
- It's beautiful.
- Yeah.
- It's so sad.
- It helps me relax.
Long day?
I work at a call center.
So yeah.
Two hundred strangers an hour.
I'll leave you alone. You probably
don't want to talk to another one.
It's all right. As long as you don't
hang up on me.
Do you ever just talk to them?
The strangers?
- We're not allowed to. - All I would want
to do is ask them about who they are.
What about you?
What do you do?
I... I work at the bookstore,
at the day-care center.
I had that same look on my face the first
time somebody handed me one of those.
- I'm just... I'm not religious.
- Just keep it.
Check it out. Or don't.
We've got really
good music there.
Thank you.
The House sent a bill to the
Senate. What Frank wants to
send back bears zero resemblance.
Because it's bipartisan,
unlike ours.
That sounds like
something Frank would say.
- I'm not Frank.
- He has a desk in your office.
- If this bill passes in the Senate...
- It won't.
We should be prepared, Bob.
Well, I'm prepared
to wait and see.
Have a good afternoon, ladies.
- Ladies?
- He's threatened.
- He's a pig. - Give him time. He used to
have two white, middle-aged guys
at his side. Now he's got a black guy and
a woman 20 years his junior.
Who knows how to shoot a rifle.
We just need to keep at him.
- Yes?
- Catalina Rodriguez is on line four.
Give me a moment.
- Catalina.
- Ted told me it was you.
-  You there?
- Yes. I'm here.
The press won't leave us alone.
For weeks.
They're showing up, trying to
get pictures of me and Emily.
- It wasn't me.
-  You're the only one who knew.
- I don't know how the story got out.
-  Why would Ted lie about that?
I don't know.
Maybe... maybe he's ashamed.
So, what do I do?
When will they leave us alone?
I... I don't know, Catalina.
I can't live like this.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
How... how is Emily doing?
Catalina?
- He's very confident.
- Yeah, but does he have what it takes?
- We'll see when I get his media plan.
- What about his personality?
Charming. Direct.
Very thorough.
He found our first
interview together, in '86.
I would love to see that.
Does he have a copy?
I don't think so. The TV
station made him watch it there.
We should screen that for the
president and the First Lady.
- Show 'em how it's done.
- Christina.
- What about her?
- Have you noticed anything strange
- between her and the president?
- How do you mean?
I passed them
in the hall yesterday.
They seem, I don't know...
very intimate.
They did seem cozy
at the prep session.
- Do you think...?
- No. Not necessarily.
An interesting thought, though.
- Sorry to interrupt, sir.
- We're having lunch.
The Republicans are backing out. Mendoza's
chief of staff just gave me the heads up.
- Get Mendoza on the phone.
- It's Curtis Haas. He got cold feet.
Too many cages. It's
really... kind of inconvenient,
but, you know, people look at
them. It's kind of funny. And...
- I got your e-mail.
- Now good for you?
Yeah, sure.
Can I call you right back?
What exactly did you
need to know?
We're doing some follow-up pieces
on the cyberwarfare thing.
I just wanted to get
a layman's understanding
of how the Chinese might
get through a firewall.
It's a bit complicated,
but I can show you the basics.
That's all I need.
We use a standard
N-tier architecture.
Think of it like a big sandwich,
with layers of bread.
Between each is the lettuce, the tomato,
the roast beef, you know, whatever.
What I'm pulling up here is the
org code which separates the database...
Shit, I forgot there's a meeting
with sales in a couple minutes.
- You wanna do this later?
- No, I'll just run over
and let them know I'll be
a few minutes late. Be right back.
Cool. I'll be here.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Yeah.
Come on.
OK.
Delete. Go.
- Something wrong?
- Can't find my phone.
It's weird,
I had it a minute ago.
Oh!
- Here it is. Sorry about that.
- No problem.
So the N-tier architecture, the
hi-tech sandwich I was talking about....
I thought Mendoza was
willing to work with us.
He is. The problem
is Curtis Haas.
- And have you spoken with him?
- His office isn't returning our calls.
- Neither is Mendoza's, but...
- I should've stuck to my guns.
The vote isn't until tomorrow afternoon.
I'll reach out to Mendoza...
This is the State of the Union,
Frank. I won't be left in limbo.
If we need to start rewriting that
speech now, I don't want to waste a minute.
I can turn this around, sir.
Raymond told me this was your
idea, to pursue this compromise.
- I suggested it as an option.
- No, he said you bullied him into it.
That he thought
it was a mistake.
If he felt so strongly,
he should've have
advised you otherwise.
Raymond's not a politician.
He relies on our political expertise
as much as we rely
on his business acumen.
Maybe we shouldn't
point fingers until there's a problem.
- You wouldn't call this a problem?
- Not if it's solved
before it becomes one.
You see, I wanted a vice president
who can manage Congress,
not one who bites off
more than he can chew.
Then have faith you made
the right choice, sir.
Whatever faith I have...
is quickly evaporating.
Don't humiliate the administration, Frank.
You're part of it now.
- Yes, sir.
- We're done.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Give me the private line,
please.
Tusk is blocking my way.
Goodwin at my heels.
There can be no false steps now.
The higher up the mountain,
the more treacherous the path.
Lucas Goodwin went up
to visit her.
- They may be looking for you.
- Nobody's contacted me.
I don't think anyone
knows I'm here.
We need to make sure
it stays that way.
Don't speak to anyone you don't have to.
Don't go anywhere you don't need to be.
- Tell me you heard what I said.
- I heard you. I get it.
I'm fine.
- Let me put some ice on it.
- I said it's OK.
What is this?
What, are you going
through my garbage now?
Someone gave it
to me on the bus.
You let me know
if anyone contacts you.
- Hey.
- Hey. Sorry I'm late.
No worries.
How much more you wanna
do right now? Fill in this area?
Yeah, and one
more poppy down here.
- That's a lot for one sitting.
- I know.
OK.
Francis?
- You're heading in?
- Mendoza's an early riser.
- You'll figure this out. - I need to prove
what the vice president is capable of.
Don't prove it to them.
Prove it to me.
Curtis has me by the
tea bags, Frank. I don't have
a working majority without him.
- He wasn't elected leader.
- True. But I have to pick my battles.
If you can't control him
on budgetary issues...
It's not just him. It's the 15
senators he has under his thumb.
I won't be the leader next year
if they turn on me.
So he wants to be courted.
Sit him down...
I already tried talking
to him. He wouldn't budge.
- We'll both talk.
- He's made his position clear.
We all shook hands
at this table.
The most I can do is put
the substitute amendment on the floor
with limited debate. And your people
can say whatever they want for the record,
but we're gonna vote
the amendment down.
I'm not interested
in symbolic gestures.
Well, that's all I can offer.
- Where's your courage?
- My power has limits, Frank.
Five Republicans makes
you the deciding vote.
Now, it's highly doubtful we can get
them to vote against their own party.
- But they might abstain.
- - You'd need ten.
Entitlement is the Republicans' white
whale. I can get at least two to flip.
Then you'd only
need six abstaining.
Erikson's already making calls.
- Donner.
- And Pulaski.
Get me a call list
so I can tag-team with him.
Got it right here.
We have to get medieval.
When it comes to parliamentary
procedure, there's not a rule I don't know.
Find me the ones we can bend.
Mark, you're a sensible man.
Yes, I... I know. I understand.
What if...
Tell you what, what if both
VA hospitals in your district...
Yes, both of them. Hold on.
- Who?
- Moriarty. I promised him an amendment
for his bovine research center.
- That makes six.
- Mark, if I can get you
funding for both,
are you with us? Excellent.
Well, you come by the White House
and have lunch with me sometime soon.
Bye-bye. We have the numbers.
Once you break the quorum call,
it's gonna be a little tricky.
Tell me on the way.
Sir.
- Sir, we might not have a majority.
- What?
The Dems are poaching people.
Donner, Pulaski. Maybe more.
- Voting for the amendment?
- Some. Others abstaining.
- I'm still trying to figure out who.
- We need to delay
- and figure out what is going on.
- Quorum call.
There's 49 hours until the
recess. We call a name an hour.
- Mr. Avendale?
- Here.
Excuse me, I do believe
you're sitting in my chair.
Mr. Drewery, what is the order
of business?
- We are in a quorum call, sir.
- Then why aren't you calling the roll?
- We are, sir, in a deliberate manner.
- Let's speed it up.
- Mr. Brown.
- Here.
- More expeditious than that.
- Mr. Burr.
- Here.
- Ms. Cantwell.
- Mr. Cerini.
- Thank you.
- Cornwall.
- Here.
- Mr. Colson.
- Ms. Douster.
Here.
They have a quorum.
We don't have the numbers.
- Out, let's get all our people out.
- Mr. Demerell.
- Mr. Darling. Mr. Daswani.
- Here.
- Mr. Donner.
- Faster.
- Mr. Dobben. Mr. Dwyer.
- Here.
- Erinburgh, Engle, Erikson.
Mr. Feld. Farrison. Gentry.
Mr. Haas.
- Mr. Whitehouse.
- Here.
Mr. Wicker. Mr. Wyden.
Mr. President,
a quorum is not present.
The chair recognizes the
minority leader, Mr. Erikson.
Mr. President, "I move to direct the
sergeant at arms to compel the attendance
of absent senators, that
warrants for the arrests of all senators
not sick nor excused be issued under
the signature of the presiding officer."
The question is on the motion,
all those in favor say aye.
- Aye.
- All those opposed nay.
- Nay! - The ayes have it,
and the motion is agreed to.
The sergeant of arms is hereby
instructed to compel the
attendance of absent senators.
It feels good
to be back in Congress.
The Democrats have now empowered
the Capitol Police
to arrest absent members
if necessary.
According to Republican
Senator Curtis Haas,
one of the staunchest opponents
of the entitlement amendment,
the vice president is, quote:
"Replacing democracy with tyranny.
He's transformed the Senate into
a police state within the Capitol." But...
Well, it'll be even harder
to stay out of the news now.
- Then why the joint interview?
- I watched the South Carolina one again.
Convinced them to make me
a copy. It's powerful.
Here you go.
I thought you might want it.
There's a moment where
you ran your fingers through his hair.
It's intimate. Human.
That moment alone
would've made me want
to vote for your husband.
Something like that
will buy you months
of flying beneath the radar.
And who do you have in mind
to conduct the interview?
Does this mean I have the job?
It means you still
haven't been ruled out.
Well, I'll
consider that progress.
This is the Democratic cloak room, Hector.
Yours is on the other side.
- What you're doing won't work.
- It might.
Which is why you made the long walk
over here. Ice water?
I have my people in planes,
trains and automobiles.
All I need is six
to make my quorum.
Think what I can do with
26 votes, and I've got 45.
You won't be able to get your planes
and trains back here fast enough.
I'll roll those dice.
The sergeant at arms
is very good at his job.
And this is the perfect way
to show Curtis who's in charge.
- I'm doing you a favor, Hector.
- Tell me what you want.
What I've always wanted.
The package we shook hands on.
Then I'll give you
your Senate back.
- They can't come back voluntarily?
- Pick your six best actors.
- We can't give in, Hector.
- We wouldn't be in this situation
had you toed the party line.
- Mr. Mendoza is present.
- Under protest.
- Ms. Cornwall is present.
Mr. Ullman is present.
Mr. Walsh is present.
Ms. Douster is present
and Mr. Haas is present.
- Mr. President, a quorum is now present.
- You can pass the amendment.
- I'll just filibuster the main bill.
- No, you won't.
- Watch me.
- As much as I'd like to see you
hold your piss for two days,
we struck a deal with Hector.
Passage of the substitute amendment
constitutes passage of the main bill.
- I wasn't informed of that.
- Pay attention to the fine print, Curtis.
It's far more important than
the selling price. Let's go.
I want an immediate call to the roll.
Don't let half a second pass.
- Yes, sir.
- A quorum is present.
The question is on the adoption
of the substitute amendment to HR 934,
the yeas and nays have been
ordered and the clerk will call the roll.
- Mr. Abner.
- Aye!
- Mr. Avendale.
Mr. Brown.
I'd like to propose an amendment
to HR 934.
Mr. Haas, you are out of order,
the roll call has begun,
- the clerk will continue to call roll.
- Mr. Brown. Mr. Burr.
- Aye!
- Ms. Catwell.
- Mr. Cerini.
- Aye!
- Mr. Chess.
- Ms. Cornwall.
- Nay!
- Mr. Colson.
- Hey.
- I'm glad you came.
- Yeah, me too.
- What did you think?
- The music was really beautiful.
- Not what you expected?
- I wasn't sure what to expect.
- I'm Lisa.
- Rachel. Sorry.
No. We've got cookies
and cake inside, if you...
- I think I'm gonna...
- If you want to meet some of my friends.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- OK. Yeah.
- OK.
We should add miracle worker
to your rsum, Frank.
Lazarus makes
for a good magic act,
but life would've been a lot easier if
the bastard hadn't died in the first place.
Well, the president wanted to go ballistic,
but I calmed him down.
I said don't worry,
Frank will pull this out.
Did you? I don't blame you
for being two-faced, Raymond.
It's good politics, as long
as you don't get caught at it.
Now, Frank,
if you think that I...
It's OK, Raymond.
Jesus forgives you. Good night.
Hello?
- Care for some wine?
- No.
Step into the room.
Closer. Closer.
- State your name and the date.
- Wait, why?
State your name and the date,
please.
Lucas Goodwin. February 13th.
- Year.
- Two thousand fourteen.
Are you currently or have
you ever been a member...
- What is this?
- Are you or have you ever been
a member of any
law enforcement agency?
- I already told you I wasn't.
- Two-step verification.
No. I'm not and I haven't.
Are you currently or have you ever been an
informant for law enforcement?
- No.
- - You think you might've been followed?
- Anything strange the past few weeks?
- You know what?
This is making me feel
uncomfortable.
We're not fucking around here.
If you think the FBI hasn't been
tracking your posts, then you're naive.
- You think they know who I am?
- No, you hid yourself well.
What are you going to do
with the Herald?
- Nothing.
- Then why did you want access?
I already had access. It's how I contacted
you in the first place.
I just needed to know
if you were serious.
That's Cashew.
Why did you contact me?
Because you're desperate.
And I'm not fond of authority.
Just today, under the leadership
of Vice President Underwood,
the Senate passed HR 934,
along with an historic
entitlement reform amendment.
By raising the retirement age
to 68 and 64
for normal and early
retirement respectively,
we will ensure entitlements
for generations to come.
And when the House passes that bill in
a few weeks, as I fully expect them to do,
we will put the government
freeze to rest.
We will continue the business of serving
our country rather than paralyzing it.
The American people
deserve no less.
We stand at the
altar of democracy.
Let us stand together.
I spoke to Jackie. You have
my support in the House.
But it hasn't passed
the House yet.
We've a long march before it
arrives on the president's desk.
As for me, I used to be
on the edge of the frame.
Now, I'm only three feet away.
Translated by: MemoryOnSmells
Synced by: KiNgKoNg
www.tvsubtitles.net