Jackie Sharp.
Terry Womack.
Bob Birch.
President Walker has surrounded himself
with a broken Congress.
He even brought one of them
into the White House.
Now, they've broken the economy and
put us on a collision course with China.
Put a stop to them
before it's too late.
Send a message at the midterms.
Let's start fixing the country.
Paid for by Friends
of a Better America.
Twenty-five million?
Out of thin air?
- That's our estimate.
- Where is the money coming from?
- Super PACs.
- These are issue-based attack ads.
- So who's giving to them?
- We can't trace the money
until this quarter's
filings come in.
We get killed in the midterms,
we can kiss 2016 goodbye.
You can deal with the Republican
majority and a Republican president.
We're trying to counter
with D-trip.
Make 25 million appear
out of nowhere?
- We can make a dent.
- Dents don't cut it.
No matter how fast we ramp up
fund-raising, we can't close the gap.
- We have to stop their money flow.
- I want to know how.
Locate the source
and then cut off the tap.
With this influx, you can be sure
that somebody's not playing by the rules,
but we can't whistle-blow
until we find the source.
Then find it. And you sure
as hell better find it soon.
In the meantime, I've been working
on a proposal to counter the attacks.
I've coordinated
national messaging effort.
I'll be sending copies
later today.
We should be open to every idea.
Now, go. Get to work.
Frank.
You were supposed
to steer Congress on my behalf.
- No one is as concerned as me.
- I should've kept you in the House,
like Raymond suggested
from day one.
But you've been distracted,
by the Senate,
the State of the Union,
meddling with foreign diplomacy.
- You asked me to negotiate...
- I know what I've done.
- And I know where it's gotten us.
- Sir, the attack ads are not
- a result of anything...
- You're scrambling from fire to fire
- instead of preventing them.
- I'm not the FEC, I can't wave a wand...
Give me more than excuses,
Frank! You're better than that!
- Or maybe you're not.
- If you need a punching bag,
I will stand here and take the punches,
as I have done time and time again,
since I swore my oath.
But I would much rather
get back to work, as you've asked me to do.
You are out of line, Frank.
Dismiss me or keep swinging,
Mr. President.
You're dismissed.
Thank you, sir.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
ReSync by Iar
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
http://TV4User.de
Dan Lanagin switched teams.
That doesn't make any sense.
I couldn't find any anomalies
among big Republican donors,
so I checked our own.
Lanagin hasn't given
a dime this quarter.
Yeah, but not giving isn't the
same as giving to the Republicans.
His casino's accounts.
Ernst and Young.
Eighteen million for donations,
and they're not going to us.
How did you get
your hands on those?
I've got friends.
That's why you solicit my services.
The estimate for
the ad buys was 25 million.
Those accounts are
up-to-date as of June 30th.
They could've made
more donations since then.
Tusk.
Lanagin's casino is in Missouri.
- Raymond Tusk?
- He's got an axe to grind with me
- and with the president. - I've never seen
his name on any FEC filings.
He doesn't make political contributions.
That's how he remains flexible.
You think he's funneling
the money somehow?
I don't know.
Get yourself to Kansas City.
I want you in that casino.
- Yes, sir.
- I'll keep digging.
Get me my wife.
- Where'd you get the recipe?
- My father taught me.
- You and your dad were close?
- Nah.
Cooking ribs was the only thing
that motherfucker did right.
- I guess you can't print that.
- I have ways.
This really gonna
be in the paper?
Well, at least in Boston, yeah.
Don't see why
anybody would care.
Well, it's a personal
interest story.
Vice President of the United States
comes here, of all places.
- You mean this shithole?
- That's not what I said.
It's OK.
It's not the Taj Mahal.
- How long has he been coming?
- About 20 years now.
- He's a good man, Frank.
- You still call him Frank?
Hey, in this joint, I'm the president,
the vice president and the Congress.
He just another customer.
A loyal one.
You think that's
why he likes it here?
'Cause you treat him
like a regular person?
Maybe. Mostly it's
the fuckin' ribs, though.
Now, if unemployment goes up more than
two-tenths, I want the Fed to consider...
- Get you something, hon?
- Club soda with lime, please.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
- Nothing to eat?
- No. That's it.
Tough spot to hang out
if you're in the program.
- How'd you know?
- Takes one to know one, right?
- How long?
- Little over a year. You?
Going on 15.
- Any luck with the ponies?
- None. Not yet.
- Pick a number, one through 12.
- Nine.
- Hot Fuzz.
- Sounds about right.
Club soda comin' up, darlin'.
With lime.
Hasn't moved, last two hours.
And he hasn't spoken to anybody?
Just been betting on the races.
- You want us to bring him in?
- No.
That's the vice president's
chief of staff.
- Really?
- We don't want to make a scene.
Just keep an eye on him.
Let me know what he does,
where he goes and who he talks to.
You got it, Mr. Lanagin.
You should've seen their faces.
They didn't know what to think.
Especially when
I made them hold the bag.
- You tried it out?
- I sure as hell did.
- I'm sorry I lashed out at you, Frank.
- No. I was disrespectful,
- and that was uncalled for. - My temper's
gotten away from me these days.
I need to be jolted back
into reality sometimes.
- It was a... a kind gesture.
- Just some good ol' fun.
Tricia tells me we're having
dinner, later this week.
Yes, Claire tells me the same.
Well, it'll be good to get out
of this place for a few hours.
It's been here since Kennedy.
It was painted the same year he was born.
It depicts, I think,
a World War I parade.
Well, I should know
every painting.
Well, you seem to
know quite a lot, at least about this one.
I try to soak it all in
while I can. All the history.
Presidents who obsess over
history obsess about their place in it,
- instead of forging it.
- Who said that?
I did... just now.
The White House.
All day long it's buzzing,
and at this hour
it's so... desolate.
The presidency is a great
and precious thing.
Loneliness is the price.
Let's assume...
...in one of these chairs,
staring at this wall,
is where Truman decided
to drop the bomb,
and see if we feel anything.
Nothing. You?
No, nothing.
Sorry, it's a mess.
- You don't have to clean up for me.
- Yes, I do.
Wouldn't want you seeing these.
I wore 'em last night.
You like these, or you want the ones
I'm wearing now?
- How long you been working in the casino?
- Too long.
- Bet you've seen a lot.
- Oh, yeah. I've seen everything.
- I should get going, got an early meeting.
- OK.
You want me to stay?
I wasn't planning
on sleeping here.
So... another one-night stand,
then.
- Is that OK?
- Not really my thing.
- Come on, you must play the field.
- No, I don't.
- But you are such a flirt.
- I flirt, yes.
But I only sleep with
someone if I'm into them.
And I prefer to stick around.
Remy Danton, serial monogamist.
Is this a joke?
I'm sorry. I didn't...
Sorry.
This doesn't happen again
unless it's leading somewhere.
I'm upfront about what I want.
In all things, not just politics.
Three or four times a year, they fly in
about a dozen Chinese guys, money to burn.
They got a whole floor of the
casino reserved just for them.
Word is they
throw away millions.
That doesn't
necessarily mean anything.
The Chinese love to gamble,
especially the rich ones.
Yeah, in Vegas.
This is Missouri.
- It's a much longer flight.
- I wanna find out...
I want to find out where these
planes are coming from.
- Who do we know in the FAA?
-  I don't know anyone, but Doyle does.
I already got him on it.
I'll text you when I hear back from Doyle.
I gotta go.
You leaving?
Yeah. Thanks for last night.
- I had fun.
- No, you didn't.
You were thinking
of somebody else.
I got that one after ten years.
Hope it brings you some luck.
Elaine Brooks will be sponsoring and the
First Lady has approved the early draft.
Jackie, take a look at the board.
Get a sense of who might cosponsor,
- besides yourself. - Absolutely. I'm sure
we can lock down a lot of heavyweights.
Lorrie and I will
get right on it.
We should talk
about a media plan.
- It's premature for that.
- Don't we want to get this out,
start building support
as soon as possible?
- Events, interviews?
- I want what's most effective.
A media blitz is the wrong way to go.
You want a single long lead
that coincides with the introduction
of the bill. Something classy.
- But you want broad support, to hit...
- A blanket strategy will
galvanize as many detractors
as supporters.
Not if the message is framed...
We want a key demographic
to get on board, and then...
- Let me finish, please.
- Then we let it percolate.
I suggest Matt Bai,
The New York Times Magazine.
I like that idea.
I like that very much.
So do I. Can you speak to Matt?
No promises. Just test the waters.
- Happy to do that. - I've got a
good relationship. I'll call him.
Great. Seth, you keep me posted
and let's all get together later this week.
Thanks, Jackie.
I want you to read the bill
and write me a summary.
Do not, under any circumstances,
share it with anyone until we've spoken.
- Don't want to go over the board first...
- No. Not yet.
Anything on the abortion?
Nothing.
It all checks out.
- One hundred percent?
- I turned over every stone.
- Mrs. Underwood was telling the truth.
- We need something.
- This is taking too long.
- The Underwoods are careful.
If they have skeletons,
they're buried deep.
Not a question of "if." Somebody like
Frank is gonna have skeletons.
Then I'll find them.
If you don't deliver, that means
I don't deliver. And I always deliver.
You gave me an assignment
with high expectations. I will meet them.
But it's not gonna happen overnight.
So don't fuck with me.
I'm a hired gun.
Not one that you own.
As long as you hit the target.
Then I need a favor.
- Connor Ellis.
- What about him?
I'll have more access
if he isn't around.
Arrange a cushy job offer
for him somewhere.
- Private or public sector?
- Private. Lots of money.
Something he can't turn down.
I'll see what I can do.
Here, this is half.
You can pay me when I've gotten
you what you want.
I don't take half pay
for a job half done.
- It's an interesting proposal.
- What we're missing is a unified theme.
If we coordinate on national ad-buys,
organize crossover events,
develop fund-raising apps,
I think it would go a long way...
Maybe, but I doubt the
leadership will go for it.
Which is why I'd like your
support. I set up a meeting.
If you came, and you
supported my position...
I just think they're gonna end up saying
we can't be thinning out our funds
on a national strategy. This is about
fieldwork, getting out the vote.
Right, but isn't it worth
at least some consideration?
Well, you know me, Linda,
I mean, I'm all for bold ideas.
But Birch and Womack, why,
they're... set in their ways.
I doubt very seriously that...
Listen, Frank, all I'm asking is that you
play devil's advocate with them.
Sorry, excuse me for a moment.
This is important.
I don't want
to short-shrift this.
No, I know, but I just
have to send this text.
I am busy too.
- Make sure that's an aisle seat.
- Of course.
I don't feel as if you're
taking this very seriously.
Linda, I apologize. I am sorry.
You are absolutely right,
I did not mean to sound curt.
And you are right,
this is important.
You and I should
go through your proposal
and discuss it right
down to the last detail.
I am not asking you to go
through it page by page,
just to help me initiate
some meaningful dialogue.
- You can count on my help, Linda.
- Thank you.
- I will have my scheduler
reach out to yours. - Thank you, Linda.
Get me a secure line, please.
The vice president
is on the line.
Mr. Vice President.
Normally, I would ignore your call,
but I am in a good mood today.
- Not even you could ruin it.
- Are you funneling
money to the Republicans?
What on earth
are you talking about?
About 20 million
in GOP Super PACs.
You know I never make
political contributions.
That's the fastest way
to upset my investors.
I know the money is coming
from a casino in Missouri,
and I know
it's coming from Feng.
Mr. Feng and I have
one co-venture together,
and it has nothing
to do with gambling.
A plane that he owns
flies to Lanagin's casino
- on a regular basis.
- What he does on his own time
- is no business of mine. - Are you trying
to create chaos in the ranks?
The Republicans appear to be doing
a fine job of that without my help.
Well, it's not gonna work, Raymond.
It'll bind the Democrats together,
- not pull us apart. - What has bound them
together the past decade has been
the means to achieve a majority.
- If I had to guess...
- He stacked Congress.
The majority I whipped.
So it's been you,
Raymond, all along,
even when Lanagin's money
was coming to us.
You keep making assumptions
that I have denied.
Once the quarterly filings come
out, anybody with a laptop
- is gonna see what's going on.
- The end of September.
That's a long way off.
But I look forward to seeing the reports.
Should make for some very interesting
reading two weeks before the midterms.
You cannot bully your way back
to the table, Raymond,
just as you cannot
buy the keys to Congress.
Best of luck keeping your
majority in the House.
I know how much it means to you.
When the money's
coming your way,
you don't ask any questions.
But now it's clear. Lanagin's
never been anything but a front.
Do I tell the president? No.
He'll wonder why I didn't know,
which makes me look uninformed.
Or he'll blame the messenger for involving
him, which makes me look careless.
I know it's a trap.
I must keep this to myself.
He wants to know who
you are buying on behalf of.
It's a hedge fund named
Mercury Capital. It's unlisted.
They need the names
of the principal investors.
Tell him I have
to protect identities.
The broker needs more.
He wants a full investor list.
Say, um...
Say that the principal investor
has strong ties to the White House.
And they want to know
if you represent Clayton West.
Clayton West?
- He's waiting.
- One second.
- What does it say?
- It's about a refinery in China
for rare earth elements.
Tell him yes. Tell him the principal
investor is Raymond Tusk.
...Raymond Tusk.
This is Doug Stamper...
- What should we serve the Walkers?
- Cyanide.
Saving that for dessert.
What about a main course?
Meat of some sort? Vegetables?
I mean, this isn't really
my area of expertise.
I was thinking,
what about Freddy?
- Ribs?
- Or is that gauche?
No. I like the idea.
Well, we can do the
nice china, gourmet sides.
But I think the ribs
make it more personal.
I'll make the call.
- Any word on the call you're expecting?
- Not yet.
I don't think he's landed.
This is really coming
along, isn't it?
You think it's childish.
I think it's better
than video games.
- Do you have my check for $5,000?
- Next time I get a raise.
- Bad luck at the casino?
- So Tusk knows I'm here.
- Daniel Lanagin knows you're here.
- Is Tusk involved?
- Why would I admit that?
- Tusk is in business with you.
You're sending money to Lanagin.
Lanagin's casino is in Tusk's backyard.
You didn't fly halfway around
the world just to confirm suspicions.
- Tell me what you want. - We want the
money to stop flowing to the Republicans.
- And what do I receive?
- I've told you what we want.
- Now it's your turn.
- So you can mislead me again?
Things have changed.
We have nothing to gain by misleading you.
Hm...
What do you think of my garden?
It's very beautiful.
When you only talk business,
you stop appreciating beauty.
- I don't have much time for beauty.
- That's a shame.
For people like you to smell the
flowers, some of us have to pull the weeds.
- When do you plan on leaving?
- I haven't bought my return ticket yet.
Good. I'd like to think on this for a
night. And I'm sure you must be exhausted.
Would you do me
the honor of being my guest?
- I'd be very grateful.
- Excellent. You can get some rest.
And if you like, there are many beautiful
things to enjoy here.
Please.
- Sir? Mr. Grayson is here.
- Seth.
You and I haven't really
properly had the chance to sit
and have a chat
since you came on board.
Is there anything
I can be doing better, sir?
No, no. I'm impressed.
You're very smart.
Excellent work ethic.
- But more importantly, you're
very observant. - Information is power.
It was right here in this room
that my...
...wife revealed a great deal of
information to a great number of people.
- Millions of them.
- Sir, if your concern is my knowledge
of any discrepancies,
let me assure you...
Claire and I are private people.
I can understand
why you might mistrust me.
I'm also observant,
like you, Seth.
But I still have my blind spots.
It would have never occurred to
me to reach out to Mrs. Marbury.
Her husband was dead.
He kept no records.
And yet, there it
was in black in white.
I respect the fact that you brought it
to us, that's what got you in the door.
But if you wanna stay,
I need more.
What exactly are you up to?
I was hired by Remy Danton.
He wants anything damaging
that I can find.
- Does he have a copy of the journal?
- No copies.
I gave the original to Mrs. Underwood,
and I told him that her story checks out.
- Did you give him anything else?
- I don't have anything else.
I wouldn't give it
to him if I did.
Why am I only hearing
about this now?
Well, you're the vice president
of the United States.
Remy works for Raymond Tusk.
That puts me between two
extremely powerful people.
- I had to be careful.
- I'm sure that Remy's offering
- you a great deal of money.
- But that's all he offers.
When I saw you push entitlement
reform through the Senate,
it was clear to me where
the real power in the White House is.
I want to work for a man like you, not
sail a yacht. Money doesn't interest me.
Do you want me to cease contact
with Remy?
No. I want you to find
the blind spots.
- Is he free?
- For a few minutes.
- Thank you.
- Mexico City,
where you'll meet
President Soto.
We can practice your Spanish on
the plane.
Hi.
- What is that?
- Frank gave it to me.
- Do you have a minute?
- Yeah, is it important?
I have a meeting with...
When is it?
- He's already in the waiting room.
- The archbishop of New York.
I'm just wondering if we should
bring a gift to dinner tonight.
Yeah, well, it's casual.
Maybe a bottle of wine?
You know them well. Any idea
what sort of wine they like?
Well, not extremely well,
but I'm friendly with their staff...
- I'll figure it out.
- I can make a call.
I'm having a conversation
with my husband, but thank you.
- OK. I apologize.
- I'll see you at the residence.
Seven-thirty.
No. Not now.
No. Just... Please go.
Get out. Please.
Rachel, it's me. I...
You should answer when I call.
I don't like leaving messages.
- Seth.
- Ayla.
I get 15 minutes to eat,
on a good day.
- Xander Feng.
- Means nothing to me.
Connor told me about a
back-channel with China.
There was speculation it
was a guy named Xander Feng.
- Fourteen minutes, 52 seconds.
- He's in business with Raymond Tusk.
They're working on a refinery in China.
Tusk has ties to the White House.
- Fourteen minutes, 30 sec...
- One of the wealthiest men in America
in business with an off-the-books
Chinese diplomat?
Influence in Washington
never been reported?
The White House pushes rare earth
subsidies when the energy crisis spiked?
Do you have a specific
question for me?
I'd like to ask
the vice president.
A specific question for me,
not an interview request.
Does the vice president
know Raymond Tusk?
- Not to my knowledge.
- You're hiding something, Seth.
I'm not hiding anything.
I'm just a guy with low blood sugar.
- Garrett?
- Hm?
- What is it?
- Christina.
She won't leave me alone.
It's like she's trying
too hard to be helpful.
- I'll have Linda talk to her.
- It's not just that.
I feel like it's a mask. I feel like
there's something else going on there.
- Like what?
- Sometimes, when I walk into your office
and see her talking to you...
...and you've been traveling
together so much.
- Jesus, Tricia.
- Oh, not you, her.
I think she's attracted to you.
And she does have a history...
I can't even believe we're
having this conversation.
I want you to relocate her.
Find her another position...
- Absolutely not.
- I know it seems overboard...
She's a good aide.
She's valuable to Linda,
- valuable to the administration.
- I'm your wife.
- I should be more valuable than them.
- Tricia.
I don't understand why you're
fighting me when she bothers me...
We're pulling up to Frank's
in two minutes.
Really, superb, Freddy.
I can honestly say I have
never had better ribs in life.
Well, I'm glad you
liked you them.
You know, I read the article in the Sun
about how you go to Freddy's.
I hope you don't mind me speaking
to that reporter, Frank.
- Not at all.
- Shit, I forgot I'm not supposed
- to call you that.
- I wouldn't let you call me
"vice president" even if you
tried. And I didn't mind at all.
I thought the article was great.
It's been a big bump in business
since it came out.
I'm talking lines
around the block.
You're not the only white person
to show up there now.
Well, I'm gonna call it a night.
I got a early start in the morning.
It was a pleasure meeting you,
Mr. President, Mrs. Walker.
- A pleasure. Truly.
- Thanks, Freddy.
Always.
Oh, no. None,
none for me, thanks.
Mr. President, a slice
of pie is good for the soul.
- I'm stuffed.
- You can have a slice of pie.
I'm fine, really,
but thank you, Frank.
I'll have some.
For the two of us, as well.
Oh, now she is gonna make me run
another five miles to work off this puppy.
Are you crazy?
I can barely keep up with you.
- You're so much faster than me.
- You two run together?
Yes. It's hard to find the time,
but somehow we find it.
We do. And it's something
that's just ours, you know?
Yes. Just ours.
And about eight Secret Service Agents'.
That's so nice
that you have that together.
I wish Garrett and I had more
time for things like that.
We did take a spinning class
together once.
- Should've seen Garrett hunched over...
- Please.
- Would you like some more wine?
- I would, thank you.
- I saw the punching bag you gave him.
- You know what?
- I will have a slice of pie.
- Pie, please, for the president.
Thank you.
I read it front to back. It's good.
It'll cause a shit-storm,
- but maybe that's what we need.
- Not during the midterms.
I don't see how we take flack.
We're trying to curtail rape, for godsakes.
Sure, some right-wingers
will do their usual song and dance...
Hold off. I want
to read it myself first.
We promised the vice president
we'd have cosponsors...
I know what we promised,
and we're gonna stall.
- Don't disseminate the draft.
- But you know the gist of the bill.
- I don't see why we can't...
- Lorrie.
All right,
I'll leave it with you.
- Anything else?
- No. I think we're good.
All right. Then I'm off.
Date night with the husband.
Slit my wrists, please.
Hey, go home at some point, OK?
The Capitol will still
be here in the morning.
This is really something.
Ways to go yet.
Now, who won this battle?
The North or the South?
Massive casualties on both
sides. No clear winner.
How do you find the time?
I carve out a half hour here
and there. Helps me relax.
I've forgotten the meaning
of that word.
Well, that's what the
punching bag is for.
It's very true.
Just a little. Trish and
I should get going soon.
You're never gonna make it
through this first term, Mr. President.
- How do you mean? - Well, not like this.
Letting the stress creep in.
You need to run the marathon,
not the sprint.
You need to enjoy
these little moments of escape.
You can pour more than that.
Thank you.
- This Union or rebel?
- Union, sir.
Enough "sirs" and "Mr. Presidents."
Call me by my name.
I respect the office
too much for that.
When we're in private, it's OK.
Tonight, I don't have
to be president.
I don't mean to get
involved in your personal life.
Oh, no. I brought it up.
Is this really about Christina?
Or maybe it's just
a symptom of something else?
- Like what?
- I don't know.
I barely see him at all.
He's so wound up in everything
that's going on overseas,
the elections, the economy.
When he was governor,
it wasn't a cakewalk,
but it was nothing like this.
How do you and Frank do it?
You both seem so close.
We're honest with each other.
We don't sweep anything under the rug.
Trish, if it's eating at you,
make him talk about it.
The White House is finite.
Your marriage... is for life.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- You don't like your soup?
- I'm not good with chopsticks.
I think you'll like this soup
more than you liked
the two companions
I sent you last night.
I was tired.
Have you had a chance to think
about what we discussed yesterday?
In China, it's polite to refuse a gift the
first time. Maybe I should refuse yours.
We can't offer you a gift
if I don't know what you want.
The Port Jefferson Bridge.
You pulled it,
during the back-channel.
- I changed my mind.
- Why?
I have allies who want the bridge.
Without it, they become my enemies.
- I've been put on trial twice.
- Corruption charges.
Everyone in China who works
on this level pays who they need to pay.
And they kill who
they need to kill.
People disappear all the time, Mr. Stamper.
I could disappear. You could disappear.
Stop the junkets
and we'll get you the bridge.
The bridge comes first.
The vice president
has lied to me before.
I need proof of his commitment.
Then the money will stop.
Please, Mr. Stamper... eat.
You have a long
flight ahead of you.
If it's what you
feel you need to do.
I've had a great experience
here, Mrs. Underwood,
but this is an opportunity
I can't pass up.
- I imagine the pay is substantial.
- It is.
But it's not just that.
There's room to grow at SpaceX.
Well, if your mind's made up,
I won't try and convince you to stay.
The truth is...
when I first came on board,
I thought it was to work
for both you and your husband.
Don't get me wrong, it's been
an honor working for you,
but I didn't foresee
having to work with Seth.
- You're not very fond of each other.
- No.
Which is fine.
We're professionals.
But I think this is
for the best.
Well, the problem with hiring great people
is everyone wants to steal them away.
I appreciate you
being so understanding.
- You'll be missed, Connor.
- Thank you.
Seth, it's me. He just left.
Talk to him and put out a press release.
Let's make this
as smooth as possible.
It's two opportunities
I'm interested in.
A family-oriented restaurant chain,
and a retail barbecue sauce.
What would that look like?
We give you an upfront payment
for the right to use your brand.
Either venture fails,
or if they both do,
- you still get to keep that money.
- How much money we talking?
Ninety-five thousand
as soon as you sign.
And then you'd have a share of
the profits if we're successful.
- What would the shares be?
- I tell you what.
Let me draw up papers, you look
them over, you show them to your lawyer.
- I don't have a lawyer.
- You should get one.
I don't want you to feel
like you're being cheated.
You're skeptical.
Look...
Money usually don't
come through that door,
unless it's looking
for a plate of ribs.
And we want to sell
thousands of those plates.
Millions, if the
franchise builds.
The Sun article
put you on the map.
Let's fill up that map
with Freddy's BBQ Joints.
- What are you looking at?
- Excuse me?
The knives are in the kitchen,
you have a pistol. You can stop staring.
Is he in here? Dan!
- How are you?
- Good.
- Care for a drink?
- I'm good.
Well, let's go into the
living room. It's more cozy.
- I'm just fine where I am.
- All right. Thank you.
Yes, sir.
I'm sure you've told Raymond
that I asked you here.
- Raymond who?
- Oh, you don't have to pretend, Dan.
- Feng confirmed what you're up to.
- Name doesn't ring a bell.
I have flight records. One of his planes
to Kansas City on multiple occasions.
Do we really have
to play this game?
I came here because I thought
you might have something to offer.
Why don't we just skip
to that part?
You've been
a loyal contributor, Dan.
You've thrown us fund-raisers, there are
pictures of you and I shaking hands.
So whatever you've done this
quarter can be forgotten.
But I need the money to stop
flowing in the wrong direction.
- I'm still waiting for the offer.
- You're a businessman, Dan,
- I know your primary concern is profits.
- That's right.
But I'm offering you something that's
far more valuable than money:
- a direct line to the White House.
- That sounds vague to me.
I have influence over the BIA,
over federal gambling legislation.
The sort of influence that my
contributions have already bought.
Not with my direct involvement
and the president's ear.
You know what
I like about money?
I can stack it on a table,
like this one.
I can measure it
with a yardstick.
I can see it, smell it,
buy things with it.
Houses, cars, clothes.
Things that are real.
You're gonna have to show up
with more than beads.
Dan, I invited you to my home
because I thought...
- Through the back door.
- Excuse me?
Through the back door,
like a servant.
The Secret Service makes
everyone come in that way.
It's a precautionary measure...
Unless you can offer more money
than Tusk, and I don't think
that you can, there's little
left for us to talk about.
I am offering you an alliance
with a man who goes to work
everyday at
1600 Pennsylvania Avenue!
I don't place my faith
in any white man.
Especially one that works
for the federal government.
I am just like you, Dan.
I know what it means
to start from nothing, to have to fight...
You know nothing about
what it means to be me.
Your version of nothing
was light-years ahead of where I started.
I respect you, Dan.
I take you seriously...
I'll let you know when I give
a fuck about your respect.
Holliday! Show Lanagin out.
I know where the back door is.
Francis?
It's not broken.
I can fix it.
Leave it.
I'll clean up later.
Let's go for a run.
Burn off some of this steam.
Sir?
- I'll be out in a moment.
- I'll go ahead. You catch up.
Why didn't you reach out,
before you got on a plane?
I was afraid our communication
might be monitored.
- Where are we with Lanagin?
- Nowhere. Where are we with Feng?
We might have an option,
but it's gonna be tricky.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
ReSync by Iar
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
http://TV4User.de
www.tvsubtitles.net