Strange not seeing
your name up there.
"To improve is to change..."
"To perfect
is to change often."
You know your Churchill.
Inscribed on the
watch you gave me
- when I left for Glendon Hill.
- Was it?
- Nancy arranges all the gifts.
- She knows you well.
- As much as I'm enjoying this little...
- I got you two more votes.
Partridge and Krauss.
Is this Raymond's way
of extending an olive branch?
- It's a start.
- Two votes is a twig. It's not a branch.
- Which is why I'm here.
- Well, the vote is at 5:00.
- We have less than three hours.
- Two hours and 49 minutes.
- We have made more happen in less.
- Is that the watch?
- No, it's nicer. - So why did Raymond
have a change of heart?
If the government grinds
to a halt, that benefits no one.
We want the president focused on China,
not distracted by furloughs and protests.
You take direction
from Jacqueline.
She's not gonna
like that very much.
- Bossing you around?
- Having me around.
I don't blame her.
Ashleigh will start
the interview with questions
about how you and your husband
met, your early marriage.
- Fine.
- Then she'll move on to more specific
- questions about your recent transition.
- All right.
She's gonna ask about you
having no children.
I thought we agreed
to take that off the table.
We did, but they insisted.
Now, I can speak
to Ashleigh directly and...
No, no. It's fine. I've been
asked the question before.
- I know how to answer it.
- It'll be quick and painless.
I'll confirm that with Ashleigh
when she gets here.
- I like it.
- Maybe something less neutral.
I'm sure you'll look good in
whatever you choose. I'll be downstairs.
Disori owes you for the
overpass funding you secured.
- Yes, he does.
- I'll call him.
- Where's Doug?
- He's doing the rounds.
Making sure our
hard ones stay hard.
Birch and Womack are doing the same.
But we're still 15 short.
I've got relationships
with most of these folks.
Money's not enough.
I already tried the D-trip route.
Retirement age is
the main sticking point?
- Old people vote.
- I'll target the AARP.
- That'll take most of the heat off.
- We're wasting time.
- I gotta get to work.
- Take Remy with you.
Shouldn't we divide and conquer?
It's harder to say no
twice than once.
I'll stay out of your way.
Like you did
on the watershed act?
We're on the same
side of the fence.
You're late to the party.
Think of Remy as the guy
who shows up
with a six-pack after
the liquor stores close.
- Who's on your plate?
- Donald Blythe.
Do you really think that's
the best use of your time?
If I can get him
to turn his people.
A lot of eggs
to put in one basket.
We only have one basket.
Jacqueline,
may I use your office,
- for old time's sake? - I serve at the
pleasure of the vice president.
Two hours and 17 minutes.
Normally all I need to sway
Donald Blythe is patience and time,
neither of which
I have right now.
Tick tock.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
- Donald. Good to see you.
- Mr. Vice President.
Please,
it's always Frank to you.
I came because you asked me,
but don't mistake that for false hope.
If you have other people
to lobby, you should.
- Ten minutes.
- It won't change anything.
Well, at the very least,
enjoy the free coffee.
- I don't drink caffeine.
- Then decaf.
- Still has caffeine.
- Well, enjoy the free oxygen.
It gets stuffy over there
in the Longworth building.
- Coffee for me, and...
- Seltzer water, if you have it.
I'm sure we do.
Now, I can understand
if you might hold a grudge.
I don't hold grudges, Frank.
I just don't negotiate
with people who are
fundamentally deceptive.
I never lied to you, Donald.
You promised to seek my counsel,
which you never once did.
We had to move the education bill in
a direction I knew would make you unhappy.
- I saw no reason to frustrate...
- You eviscerated the unions.
- You federalized performance standards.
- If we hadn't done that,
the bill would've
been dead in the water.
Now you want to cut
the pathetic level
of funding you
did manage to pass.
Isn't some funding better
than none?
A flatline will send a louder
message than life support.
Look, I'm impressed with the
little coalition you've cobbled together,
- but we...
- Not so little. Twenty-eight votes.
- And you need them all.
- Well, really only half.
- Half of zero is still zero.
- I had to pull every trick in the book
to get entitlement through
the Senate. If it fails in the House,
we don't get a round two.
This is a one-time deal.
It should never have passed
the Senate to begin with.
Can we start over?
May I offer you an apology?
Deaf ears, Frank.
I withdrew myself from the education
fight and that is my cross to bear.
But I will be damned if I will
make the same mistake twice.
This sort of stubbornness
makes you no better than the tea party.
- Except for the fact...
- that we happen to be right.
Just a few more minutes, Donald.
You haven't even had your seltzer yet.
They have seven other data centers
spread across the Northeast.
- Those aren't good odds.
- Well, if we can access one,
I should be able to talk to the
other seven. They all look like that.
- Fort Knox wrapped in a nuclear bunker.
- How do we get in?
Well, we don't. You do.
What...? How?
What's my reason?
You're writing a story on cyberterrorism.
It's free publicity.
- If they're so secure...
- They give tours all the time.
- Mostly to prospective clients.
- Then why haven't you done it yourself?
Because I run a white hat firm.
And if I were to show up in the tour logs
before a breach, it would raise alarms.
OK. Once I'm in?
These are what
servers look like.
If you can get inside one of
these cages, you will have this.
You slide it into
the server. Voilà.
- It's that simple?
- Yeah. Well, your part, not mine.
- Code's extremely complex.
- How do I do it without them noticing?
You get good at anything.
Practice makes perfect.
We've got a problem.
Everyone, stop what you're doing, head
into the nearest office and shut the door.
You, stay exactly where you are.
Retirement age is a done deal.
I might be able to
redistribute some appropriations...
That's not what I'm after. You can't fix
a wrecked car with new hubcaps.
How about a sister bill?
One that focuses entirely on education.
My coalition is fighting
for the integrity of the party.
We're not just
focused on education...
I'm sorry, Donald.
Excuse me.
Nancy, I said no interrup...
When?
But the vote is in
less than an hour. I...
I don't care what protocol... Quarantine.
There's white powder in the mail.
- We're locked in?
- Sir! Close the door now!
- Look, I have to...
- Now, sir! Please!
- I should call my wife.
- And I should call Claire.
- Should I tell Connor?
- No. It's better the press doesn't know.
Field tests should come in before the vote.
Soon as the tally's in,
- I'll come home.
- How's it looking?
Shaky. We may lose this one.
That could make
for a tough interview.
Well, I didn't want
to do it in the first place.
Well, we're committed now.
I better get
back to the holy crusader.
Let me know as soon
as the tests have cleared.
If we're lucky,
it'll be anthrax.
I won't live long enough
to see the bill fail.
- Don't say that.
- We're gonna be fine.
How many of these quarantines
we been through?
- I've lost count.
-  Wish me luck with Donald.
Heels crossed.
- It's ripping the caucus apart.
- Of course.
We took a united stand
on our version of the bill.
- Some of us have to stay on our feet.
- This is about party unity.
- It's about abandoning our base.
- No. That's what the freeze is.
Our base doesn't benefit
from sword rattling.
It gets left
bleeding on the field.
My district has the third largest number
of seniors in the country.
If we raise the age
of retirement, the AARP will raise hell.
I spoke with the president
of the AARP this morning.
They'll be receiving
a 45 million dollar endowment next week.
Voters will still revolt.
The midterms are gonna be ugly.
Many, and I can speak
for myself...
The choice is between immediate
discontinuation of services
and an age bump
five years from now.
You're comparing theoretical
discomfort to imminent pain.
I just feel like we're losing
touch with our core values.
The education bill
was a good example.
We all followed Frank's lead,
hoping it would buy us
- traction with the Republicans.
- Would you excuse me? Just one moment.
- Does the press know?
- Not yet.
Can you keep in touch with him?
I need to pummel our lunch
guests into submission.
You got 'em close,
but relax. Listen more.
They want their hands held,
not someone in their face.
I know how to whip votes.
Best caviar in DC,
ladies and gentlemen.
- We can't let you pay for that.
- Then don't eat it.
But if you do,
I won't tell anyone.
You were saying
about the education bill...
No, Marjory, honey. Remember,
we just talked about it.
I was telling you...
Right. Nothing to worry about.
If you have any questions,
ask Molly.
She knows what's going on.
I will call as soon
as I know anything.
I love you.
How's Marjory?
- She's OK.
- Long call.
You know, she... gets emotional.
Molly took a semester off
to be at home.
I told her she needs
to head back in the spring.
I don't want her mother
dragging her down.
- Must be hard on you.
- Harder on the girls, I think.
- Is she lucid?
- About half the time.
Just enough to be aware
of how quickly she's going.
It's awful.
I feel terrible saying it, but part of me
is looking forward to her not being lucid.
At least then she won't
realize what's happening.
I should have thought
of this before.
Appeal to the heart,
not the brain.
Forgive my ignorance, but...
...has there been any
progress with research?
Some. Genetic testing,
vascular manipulation. But it's slow.
They won't come up with
anything in time for Marjory.
We're focusing on quality of life.
Look, I know you have work to do, so...
I'm no longer the whip.
That's Jacqueline's job.
I just agreed to meet with you
because we have a history.
She would be tougher
to say no to.
But it still
would've been a "no."
- Yes.
- I admire your convictions, Donald.
You're a rare breed nowadays.
It didn't sound that way when
you were comparing us to the tea party.
I was being unfair. You're not
a reactionary. You're a progressive.
- I see where this is going.
- How do you mean?
When you've been in the
wasteland as long as I have,
you become immune to flattery.
I know you think I'm
fundamentally deceptive,
but I am capable
of a genuine compliment.
Then I will take it as one,
but it won't soften my resolve.
If it did, you wouldn't deserve
the compliment in the first place.
If you vote no,
I won't hold it against you.
We are all in this together
through the midterms.
But, if you stick with me,
we can show both the Republicans
and the American people that
we are capable of more than stagnation.
And that's worth something,
even if it hurts.
Who can I count on?
Copy that.
The fact that there's still
a door between us, I take as a bad sign.
One tested negative,
one inconclusive, sir.
That means we have to take
the samples to the lab.
- So how much longer?
- Another three or four hours.
We have an important vote going to the
floor. I have to be talking to my people.
The vote is delayed, sir.
We're evacuating this side of the Capitol.
- So no vote?
- Not until we get the all-clear.
- Good things happen to good people.
- Another thing, sir.
All cell phone service, WiFi,
land lines, we'll be blocking them,
in case there's
a legitimate security threat.
- I need to be able to call my wife!
- I apologize, sir.
- We can have someone notify her.
- No, it needs to be me.
She gets very anxious
if she doesn't recognize the voice.
Congressman, I have
strict instructions not...
Figure it out, unless you want me
to get the White House involved.
I'll find a way, sir.
There are advantages
to being vice president.
Ma'am, we'll have to ask you
to remain up here for a little while.
- Is it the quarantine?
- The Capitol is being evacuated.
We expect everything to be fine.
It's just standard procedure.
You won't be able to get through.
Communication's being jammed.
- You mean I can't even speak to Francis?
- Not until the all-clear.
- How long?
- - Four hours is the estimate right now.
- We're supposed to tape in 25 minutes.
- - Nothing we can do.
- You OK?
- Yes.
I'll go talk to Emma.
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
Em.
- So we might have a problem.
- It's all over the news.
- Yeah, it could be a while.
- Can we get audio from the vice president?
Communications are being
jammed until the evacuation's over.
- Have you spoken to Ashleigh?
- She thinks we should get
a sat truck down here
and wait and go live.
I can't guarantee
when that'll be.
The vice president is quarantined
in the Capitol and we have an exclusive.
The network will broadcast
whenever the hell we tell them to.
They're
holding off until you get here.
You should do the
interview solo.
- I'd rather wait.
- Who knows whether we'll win the vote?
If we lose, I don't want my face
on national television.
- This could be a silver lining.
-  I don't know, Francis.
- I'm sure you'll be terrific.
-  Let me run it past Connor.
OK.
Thank you, we're done.
- Sir, we were able to get Mrs. Blythe.
- Donald.
- Marjory?
- Hello?
- Yes, it's me, sweetheart.
-  It's hard to hear you.
- We're still stuck inside the office.
-  What office?
At the Capitol. It's going
to be a little while longer.
But why are you there?
It's Sunday.
- No, it's Friday, sweetheart.
-  Donald?
- I'm here.
-  Who is this man with me?
He's a police officer. They're using
walkie-talkies so we can speak.
- Who am I talking to?
- - It's your husband, ma'am.
- I'm not married.
- It's me. It's Donald.
Turn it off.
I don't know that man.
- Marjory!
- - She went to the other room, sir.
OK, thank you.
- If you could stay with her, please?
- - Yes, sir.
Drink?
Sure. Why not?
For all we know, it could be
midnight before he's out.
- He still needs to manage the vote.
- - We're fine if it's 2am.
When everyone's asleep.
- People would stay up for this.
- The whole point was primetime.
- Then we do it tomorrow.
- We've already set aside
half a day for this.
The vice president can't
rearrange his schedule
for an interview.
- I don't see any other options.
- I spoke to Francis over the radio.
- We think I should do it alone.
- Just you?
Mrs. Underwood and Ashleigh,
one-on-one.
Maybe we can
broadcast his voice...
Francis doesn't want
the entire interview
to be about the quarantine.
Neither do I.
That's just spectacle.
The quarantine is news.
We have an opportunity...
- We're done.
- What?
- Cancel the interview. No reschedule.
- Come on.
Please, pack up
everything and leave.
OK, let me call Ashleigh.
I thought I'd get used to it,
but no. Hurts every time.
You spend 30 years with someone and then
they don't have a damn clue who you are.
Oh... I really shouldn't.
If we never did anything
we shouldn't do,
we'd never feel good
about doing the things we should.
- Excellent point.
- If these are our last moments on Earth,
I don't know about you,
but I'd rather go out with a buzz on.
To Marjory.
- You love her dearly.
- More than anything.
I can't imagine what I'd do
without Claire, or if she...
...didn't remember who I was.
- Hopefully you'll never have to.
- It makes me angry that you do.
- That anybody does. - No sense being
angry over what you can't change.
How much funding
does Alzheimer's research get?
Just under 500 million.
Well, I'm no expert, but that
sounds inadequate to me.
It is. For every $100
we allocate to research,
- we spend nearly $30,000 on care.
- We oughta change that.
I tried. My bill didn't even
leave committee.
- Who opposed it?
- Howard Webb.
- Appropriations.
- He didn't even put it to a vote.
- I've never been fond of Howard.
- That makes two of us.
- What was his argument?
- He didn't feel he owed me one.
"Fiscally irresponsible,"
is all he said.
Walk me through the
specifics of your bill.
- I see what you're doing.
- Doing what?
- You're disgusting, Frank.
- Excuse me.
- Using my wife.
- Donald, what are you saying?
You think I'll give in on entitlement
if you slap some extra Alzheimer's funding
- on the table?
- I was not suggesting that at all.
- Bullshit, Frank.
- You think as little of me as you want,
but I do not barter
with people's health.
Then why are you trying to raise
the age of retirement?
Medical research we can afford.
Medicare we can't.
- There are realities, Donald.
- Don't talk down to me about realities.
My wife is dying!
That's a reality!
Other people will die, too,
if your package succeeds!
That's a reality! Goddamn it,
I wish I wasn't stuck
- in this fucking room with you!
- Donald.
I'm done talking!
- One more time.
- I've got it.
I want it to sound more natural.
Francis and I wanted to devote
our lives to public service.
And we didn't feel that we could both
do that and be the parents we wanted to be.
And by making that choice,
it allows more time for us
- to be in the service of others.
- Good, that sounds good.
We need you,
Mrs. Underwood.
Keep Derek at the Capitol. I want quotes
from evacuees and Homeland Security.
And Sarah should be finishing
that history of biohazard scares.
I'll be there soon.
- I have to go.
- No. We're not done yet.
This is a major story.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Come here two days in a row
and this is how patterns emerge.
The FBI likes patterns. And we do not
give the FBI what the FBI likes.
I can't disappear all
day in the middle of...
- I have eight reporters out in the field.
- Stop!
- Tell me why I purchased Cashew.
- I don't know.
Companionship?
Yes.
But more importantly,
a reminder that I am never more
than one wrong move away
from life in a cage.
You stay.
I'm gonna walk you through every
line of code I intend to write,
every attempt I make to breach
the wall. If we get caught,
you don't get to plead
ignorance. We go down together.
I didn't sign up for Bonnie and Clyde.
You need me for this one thing.
Just like I need you.
But whatever you've done before me...
You know where I live,
and you know who I am.
Sit down. The sooner we start,
the sooner we finish.
The Capitol is still on lockdown
as hazmat crews continue
a thorough sweep
of the building.
Earlier this morning,
a white powder-like
- substance was found
in a package...
...mailed to the office of
Majority Whip Jacqueline Sharp.
- Are we free to go?
- Almost, sir. Less than an hour.
- I've got a message from your wife.
- - What is it?
She's doing the
interview live, right now.
...Congressman Donald Blythe and 14 of Ms.
Sharp's staff.
Mrs. Underwood, I so appreciate
you taking the time to speak with us today
in what I am certain
is a very stressful situation.
- Thank you, Ashleigh.
- Have you spoken with your husband today?
Yes, I did,
and he's in very good spirits,
and in good hands
with the Secret Service.
Of course, he's very
disappointed he couldn't be here.
Well, our thoughts are with him
and everyone else quarantined
- at the Capitol today.
- Thank you.
I'd like to begin
with Claire Underwood
before you met your husband,
in Texas.
- And I have a couple of pictures.
- Oh, no.
Yes.
Oh, my goodness.
That was Red.
- An accomplished rider?
- An enthusiast.
- This one's from a couple of years later.
- Oh, my goodness.
You like those penny loafers?
Those are won...
Those are two very different girls.
Which one are you more comfortable being?
My family's ranch,
that was home for me.
You didn't like the prep school?
No, I think
I preferred the dirt.
You grew up in Dallas,
though. Highland Park.
Yes. My father, well, he was
a businessman, so we lived in the city.
But we're ranchers. I mean,
we go back three generations, our family.
Your parents were very wealthy.
We were comfortable, yes.
They made sure
I wanted for nothing.
It was a very happy childhood.
What is your most vivid
memory from that time?
My most vivid memory?
Wow. Um...
Probably, when I was
about nine or ten,
my father took me to Dealey
Plaza where Kennedy was shot.
And he said, "Claire,
a great man died here."
And I remember not
fully comprehending
the meaning of death yet.
And I asked him how he died
and he told me.
And I remember feeling so sad,
so angry.
It seemed so unfair.
I started to cry, and my daddy picked
me up and he wrapped his arms around me
and he said,
"Don't be sad, sweetheart.
He made the world a better place,
but sometimes that comes at a price."
I guess that was
the most vivid memory.
- We're only eight votes away.
- I'm sorry, I made up my mind.
Me too. I gotta stick
to my guns on this one.
You would rather
let the government shut down...
Don't put that on us because
we're on the ass-end of the whip list.
Don't get us wrong.
We have a lot of respect for you, Jackie.
You're doing a fine job since Frank's gone.
Different styles, but a fine job.
Excuse us just a moment.
- They're not taking me seriously.
- Because you're not Frank.
- You mean because I'm not a man.
- No, I mean Frank.
They're used to being offered something.
Ask them what they want.
Paul needs help with the
waste treatment facility.
You're being just
as condescending as they are.
Take some good advice when you get it.
I was right earlier, wasn't I?
Paul, Remy tells me you
need a waste treatment plant.
We've had some trouble
getting matching federal funds.
Ben, you mentioned once
a winery museum in your district.
We are making some
great wines in Long Island these days.
I've tried some. It tastes like piss
compared to what we have in Napa.
The sort of piss that belongs in Paul's
waste treatment plant.
- Jackie...
- We have a possible terror attack,
and you're holding out your
plates for more pork?
You should be ashamed of
yourselves. In my caucus,
people are rewarded for good behavior,
not trading their votes for ransom.
When we walk in there,
I expect the both of you
to vote yes without
a moment's hesitation.
Thank you for your
change of heart.
Six more to go.
You left Texas and spent the
last two years of high school
at the prestigious
Phillips Academy.
- And then onto Radcliffe.
- Yes.
Where you would meet
the future vice president.
Back then,
just a dashing law student.
I never dreamed he would become
vice president, of course.
Some people think that your marriage may
be a bit more calculated than you let on.
That perhaps he needed
your family's money.
- No, that's just not true.
- Your father did contribute an awful lot
- to his campaign. - Yes, he did,
because he believed in Francis.
Would he have won that campaign had it
not been for your father's contributions?
I don't know.
I mean, it certainly helped.
But I like to think
that it was Francis's ideas
and leadership that convinced
voters, not just TV commercials.
- You've been married 27 years.
- That's right.
You were just in school.
I mean, you married so young.
We did, but when
you've found the one...
Well, Francis was the one.
- You call him Francis.
- Back home they call him Frank, still.
But he likes
that I call him Francis.
He said that it makes him
sound more sophisticated.
- Is it hard being a politician's wife?
- It's thrilling.
- Not without its challenges.
- Always in the background.
Subsuming your goals
for his goals.
Well, I don't see it that way.
We're two very independent people
who have chosen to live our lives together.
I support him.
He supports me.
Which, you know, goes back
to the political partnership.
My husband happens to be a politician.
And I happen to do political work.
But our partnership
extends far beyond that.
Children.
Was that a sacrifice?
Because you haven't had any.
Francis and I wanted to devote
our lives to public service.
And we didn't feel that we could both do
that and be the parents we wanted to be.
So we made the choice.
- We've heard that answer before.
- Sorry?
You have given the exact same
answer in previous interviews.
Because it's the truth.
Forgive me,
but career and timing,
those are often
very convenient answers.
It is true that whatever it takes
for people to get from "maybe" to "yes"
- never arrived for me.
- Never felt the pressure?
No... maternal instinct?
- No.
- And it was a choice?
It wasn't because
you couldn't have any?
Francis and I did
what was right for us.
Because it is unusual,
I mean, even now,
for politicians at the
executive level not to have children.
Yes, it is.
In your husband's
second congressional campaign,
there was a Republican,
a pro-family candidate,
who made some pretty
unsettling accusations.
Well, Francis
is a Southern Democrat.
We have thick skins.
He suggested, in order to keep your
husband's political career on track...
Children are the center
of many people's lives.
And I think they just want to make sure
that their representatives will fight
for their children's dreams. And Francis
has again and again proven that he will.
And he will continue
to do so as vice president.
He claimed that...
...you may have been pregnant
during the campaign.
Was there a pregnancy?
Have you ever been pregnant?
- Break. Now.
- That's not gonna happen.
Yes.
- During the campaign?
- Before.
- Was it a miscarriage?
- No.
Did you...
Did you terminate the pregnancy?
If I said yes,
my husband's political career
would be in jeopardy.
My faith would be questioned.
Likely, my life would be threatened.
But I won't feel ashamed. Yes, I was
pregnant. And, yes, I had an abortion.
- Can you excuse me for one moment?
- Of course.
We'll have more of our live interview
with Claire Underwood in a moment.
That took a lot of guts.
Yes, it did.
No. It'll look like I am ashamed.
I'm not. And I won't.
Nothing you can say
will make this any better.
- I'd rather deal with...
- I'm not going to run from this.
She's going to ask why
you had the abortion.
I haven't had one.
I've had three.
Three? No, you need
to stick to one.
- OK. Fine.
- Tell me what you'll say.
Well, I can't
use the real reason.
The first two, I was a
teenager and I was reckless.
What about the third?
Well, the article that
she showed, it's right.
I was on the pill, it didn't work.
We talked about having the baby,
- and then we decided against it.
- Why?
- Because we were focused on the campaign.
- How many weeks in?
- Sixteen.
- You can't say any of this.
Go upstairs.
I'll deal with Ashleigh.
If we're going to continue,
we've got about 20 seconds.
- Connor, I...
- Please trust me.
You'll be making a big mistake.
Are you willing
to discuss the circumstances...
I became pregnant
as a result of a sexual assault.
- Are you saying that you... you were...
- Raped.
You've never spoken publicly
about this before.
No one ever asked.
Can you tell us what happened?
It was college.
A classmate.
We were dating
and it happened on a...
We had a fight,
and he forced himself on me.
Did you tell anybody about it,
I mean, did he...?
- Was he charged?
- No.
Because at the time I felt that I was
somehow at fault. I knew I wasn't.
But I just didn't
want to be stared at.
I didn't want to be known
as the girl who got raped.
And when I became pregnant,
I wasn't gonna drop out of school.
I wasn't going to
let this man ruin my life.
So I made a choice.
I ended it.
But if you never told
anybody about it,
the assailant could
still be out there.
Can you tell us
anything about him?
I saw him for the first time in
almost 30 years just a few months ago.
Where?
At a commissioning
ceremony that Francis and I attended.
- Did you speak to him?
- Briefly.
- Francis pinned stars on him.
- He was being commissioned?
General Dalton McGinnis.
And for the record, Francis
has always known about the assault,
he just didn't know the name.
And he's been nothing
but supportive all these years.
We're gonna have
to reach out to the general...
...for a response
to what you just said.
Would you mind
if we took a quick break?
Absolutely.
We'll be right back with
Mrs. Claire Underwood.
Take all the time you need.
The lab tests
all came back negative, sir.
- What was it?
- Talcum powder laced with flour.
It was pesticide from the wheat
that gave us the false positive.
- So are we free to go?
- Yes, sir.
- Nancy! Tell them I'm on my way down.
- I already did.
- Mind if I use your phone?
- Of course.
And Donald, I'm gonna get you that research
funding, no matter how the vote goes.
It's your call, because I'm
still voting against it.
- I understand.
- You have a brave wife, Frank.
So do you, Donald.
- Frank!
- How did you do?
We're down four.
How about Blythe?
- He won't budge.
- What did you offer him?
Alzheimer's research.
He was insulted.
- The vote's in 45 minutes.
- I need to get to Claire.
- Who should I call from the car?
- We have exhausted our options.
It's Blythe's people
or it won't pass.
- They're too loyal to him.
- Hey, go. I'll figure it out.
- I can stay if you need me. - No, get to
your wife. I know where to find you.
Nancy! I need every
ream of paper you have!
And get me dollies!
Almost done.
Twenty more minutes.
I hate lying.
- Did he do it?
- Yes.
- Then don't feel bad.
- What if he denies it?
Then we'll cross that bridge.
- Connor?
- Give us one more minute.
We have a young woman
on the phone, a private.
She says she was also assaulted
by the general. Two years ago.
She wants to share her story,
but she won't give her name.
We can't put her on
if she's anonymous.
- You want me to convince her?
- She's frightened.
Is she still on the phone?
I've never told anyone.
It took me almost half my life
before I could say anything.
But you can say something now.
I don't know.
Just think of how many
others there must have been.
But you want me to talk.
Well, would you have called
if you didn't want to?
I didn't think
I'd have to use my name.
Listen, I understand
you're afraid of the consequence.
I'm a private. He's a general.
And my husband is the vice
president of the United States.
We will protect you.
I promise you that.
What's your name?
Private Megan Hennessey.
- What is this?
- The names of every person in America
who will lose home care
when the freeze sets in.
Who will lose half
their welfare benefits.
Who will go on furlough.
Who will lose their student
loans, transportation services,
post-combat counseling.
Shall I go on?
This is about the big picture,
Jacqueline.
This picture looks
pretty big to me.
I can't vote for the package.
Then don't.
Just get four
of your people to do it.
And then, work with me
after we avoid the freeze.
I'm not Frank Underwood.
At least two
other girls that same year.
If that was true for all
the years he's served...
- It's just staggering.
-  And I've felt so helpless.
And he keeps rising in the
ranks. The system protects him.
Why do you think
no one has ever reported him?
Do you want to join her?
- We know it won't do anything.
- No.
Chain of command.
It's inexcusable
that you're willing
to put your life on the line
to defend our freedom,
and yet you don't feel the
freedom to come forward.
I love my country,
and I love serving in the Marines.
But not like this.
Private Hennessey,
thank you for your courage
in joining us tonight.
It was Mrs. Underwood
who gave me the courage.
Mrs. Underwood,
thank you for your honesty.
Sir, your wife is on the phone.
You've given us
a great deal to think about.
Thank you, Ashleigh.
And that concludes our live
one-on-one exclusive interview
with Claire Underwood. You can watch
the entire interview on our website.
And as always, we invite you
to give us your thoughts
and your comments
on Facebook and on Twitter.
But for now, thanks for watching
and good night.
And we're out.
This is going to make waves
like you never imagined.
Thank you.
- Where's Carter?
- You'll be reporting to me now.
- And who are you?
- Carter's boss.
You're doing good work, Gavin.
But you can't be assaulting the target.
That could compromise us.
I don't even know why you're
going after this guy. He's small-time.
- That's not your concern. - He couldn't
write a line of code to save his life.
He intends to commit an act
of cyberterrorism.
Well, that's intention, not capability.
He's not a real threat.
Maybe Carter
talked things out with you.
I won't.
- How much longer?
- Until what?
- Until I can stop.
- You prefer prison?
I've given you eight child
pornographers, three botnet masters.
But you still haven't
given us AVunit.
I told Carter I don't
know where he is.
- Yes, you do.
- I don't. Nobody does.
Then what about your
friends in Dec Sec?
I'm not giving you my friends.
Then you can keep doing this.
You're a productive asset,
Gavin.
But the moment you stop
being productive,
no lawyer can help you.
I wish we had the
real thing right now.
- Always prepared.
- Francis.
- I've missed this.
- So have I.
Shouldn't you be on the phone
getting your accolades?
They can wait till tomorrow.
Sing me something.
- What do you want to hear?
- Anything.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
ReSync by Iar
http://UKsubtitles.ru
http://TV4User.de
www.tvsubtitles.net