Who wants the
last dumpling?
Ooh, me!
Penny, a moment.
We just had Thai food.
In that culture,
the last morsel is called
the "greng jie" piece,
and it is reserved for
the most important
and valued member of the group.
Thank you all
for this high honor.
I've seen pictures
of your mother; keep eating.
All right, honey, if we're gonna
make the movie, we should go.
This may be hard
for you to hear,
but when I say "honey,"
I mean my fiancée.
Yeah, well, now it means her.
It's okay if he
wants to come.
Fine. But next time,
we get a sitter.
All right, I got to go to work.
I'll walk down with you.
Wait.
Which is closer to the new
train store in Monrovia,
the movie theater
or The Cheesecake Factory?
Neither of them are close.
Oh, well, then I guess
it doesn't matter which one
of you drives me.
Let's play a fun guessing game
to see who gets to take me.
All right, this four-letter word
describes either
a printer's type size
or a compulsion to eat dirt.
Okay, I'm not driving him.
Penny, don't give up,
you can get this.
Aren't you going
with Sheldon?
No, I have no interest
in model trains,
stores that sell them, nor
their heartbreaking clientele.
Oh.
Well, I have
some work to do, so...
I can't imagine
that would disturb me.
Carry on.
Okay.
Wouldn't you be
more comfortable at home?
Not really, no.
All righty then.
Guess I'll just
get started.
Leonard, please. I don't need
the running commentary.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory 5x03
The Pulled Groin Extrapolation
Original Air Date on September 29, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
(sighs softly)
- Amy?
- Yo.
You okay?
Oh, sure.
I thought you were reading.
I was.
Now I'm thinking about
what I read.
You all right, Leonard?
You seem very uncomfortable.
I-I'm fine.
Should I go?
I've been told sometimes
I overstay my welcome.
Wha... who told you that?
Well, most recently
my gynecologist.
Well, you stay
as long as you'd like.
I'm glad to hear you say that,
because I'm having
a wonderful time.
(chuckles)
I said the same thing
to my gynecologist.
What are you going to get
at the train store, Sheldon?
Oh, I'm not
buying anything.
They're having a lecture.
"H-O gauge railroading.
Half the size of O-gauge,
but twice the fun."
Very controversial topic.
Which side do you come down on?
I'll let you know after tonight.
Unlike some people,
I'm going in with an open mind.
Who am I kidding?
Of course we all know
it's O-gauge or no gauge.
Can you believe grown men sit
around and play with toy trains?
That's pretty big talk
for a man
with a closet full of magic
tricks at his mother's house.
First of all, they're not
tricks, they're illusions.
And...
secondly, when we get
married, they're all going up
in the attic so you can have
that closet for clothes.
Why would I keep clothes
at your mother's house?
Well, don't think
of it that way.
Once we move in,
it'll be our house.
Is she moving out?
Why would
she move out?
It's her house.
Hang on.
You seriously think I'm going
to live with your mother?
Howard, I think
I can help here.
Yes, Bernadette,
that's exactly what he thinks.
Why not?
It's a great house,
plenty of room,
and if we have kids,
Mom's there to help.
You know, en she tells "The
Three Little Pigs" story,
she actually has hair
on her chinny-chin-chin.
I'm not gonna live
with your mother.
Not now, not ever.
Wow, someone obviously
has some mommy issues.
Raj, take me home.
Don't listen to her.
Go to the movie theater.
Take me home now.
Movie theater!
(groans)
Okay, everybody
calm down.
There is a simple
solution here.
Raj, take me to the train store,
and then I don't care
what you people do.
How was your shower?
It was good, good.
Just out of curiosity, what time
do you usually go to bed?
Oh, I'm up all night.
I'm like a possum.
Boy, you were not liked
in high school, were you?
Not really.
- Is that my yearbook?
- Mm-hmm.
"Dear Leonard,
you're really good at science.
Maybe one day you'll come up
with a cure for being a dork."
Well, it wasn't spray-painting
a lightning bolt
on my briefcase,
I can tell you that.
If it makes you feel any better,
the only person who signed
my yearbook was my mother.
- Aw.
- "Dear Amy,
"Self-respect and a hymen
are better than friends and fun.
Love, Mom."
Well, you can add
Jerry's Junction
to the list of train stores
Sheldon Cooper will never
set foot in again.
Rough night, Casey Jones?
You don't know
the half of it.
It was billed
as a lively give-and-take on
the merits of model train sizes.
But it was actually a setup
to intimidate
weak-minded spineless rubes
into buying H-O starter sets.
What's in the bag?
I don't want to talk about it.
But it's not a spine,
I'll tell you that.
Well, I had a delightful
evening, Leonard.
We should do this
again sometime.
Ah, sure.
That'd be nice.
Glad to hear it.
I need someone to accompany me
to the wedding
of Dr. Moranelli
and Dr. Gustufson this Friday.
They're kind of
the Brad and Angelina
of the primatology department.
Wouldn't you rather
bring Sheldon?
I would, but the last wedding
we went to was a disaster.
He behaved like a child
the entire time.
Not my fault.
You said there'd be
other scientists there my age.
Doesn't matter.
You're out, he's in.
No date to the prom,
two dates to a wedding.
Hmm, how times change.
(singsongy): Ha-ha, you have
to go to a wedding.
(doorbell rings)
WOLOWITZ:
I'll get it!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Could you get it?!
I just said
I'm getting it!
Fine, I'll get it!
I got it!
Oh, hi.
Hey.
I don't want to fight.
I was just surprised
when you sprung
the whole living-with-your-mom
stuff on me.
Yeah, well, I'm sorry I
didn't run it by you first.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: I don't know who
you're talking to,
but in or out!
We don't need bugs!
The bugs
only come here
because you're
their queen!
Listen, how about this.
Before we make any
kind of decision
about where we live,
we have a trial run.
Stay here for a weekend,
see what it's like.
And your mom would be
okay with that?
Sure she would.
Ma, do you mind if Bernadette
stays here this weekend?!
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Hey, if she's willing to
give the milk away for free,
who am I to say no?!
See? She's
good with it.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Frankly, after all
your sleepovers
with the little brown boy,
a girl is a big relief!
All these years,
I've been so wrong.
The tinier the train,
the more concentrated the fun.
You're a brain scientist.
Can you explain to me
why a brilliant man
likes playing
with toy trains?
Not without cutting
his head open, no.
How about making my
eyes like Cleopatra?
Really? For a wedding?
Perhaps you're right.
My cheekbones and
beckoning pelvis
already have a certain "hello
sailor" quality to them.
Ready.
Aw.
So handsome.
Like James Bond.
He's better than James Bond,
because he's tinier.
I got you this
to give to me.
Oh, sweetie,
guests don't normally
wear corsages to a wedding.
That's more of a prom thing.
I never went to my prom.
My mom paid my cousin
to take me,
but he just used the money
to buy drugs.
Put the corsage on her.
When you're done copping a
feel, that goes on my wrist.
(high-pitched):
All aboard!
Woo-woo!
(normal voice):
It's official.
I'm an H-O trainiac.
So, dinner
went nice.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
Does your mother always
cut your meat for you?
Only when it's fatty.
Well, don't be jealous, babe.
Someday you'll get to cut it
for me.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Bernadette!
I found the extra head for the
Waterpik if you want to use it!
I'm okay, Mrs. Wolowitz.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
You sure?!
I just squirted half a
brisket outta my teeth!
Hey, Ma, how about
a little privacy?!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Oh, I know what that means!
Hubba-hubba!
Oh, God.
Relax, it'll be fine.
Okay.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Let me know when
you're done canoodling!
Mommy needs a foot rub!
♪ ♪
Would you like to dance?
No, thank you.
I'm really not
much of a dancer.
You're not exactly
winning any trophies
as a conversationalist, either.
I'm sorry.
The bride and groom
seem happy.
AMY:
Why shouldn't they be?
They have a feverish night of
socially-approved
copulation ahead of them.
In some cultures, we'd stand
outside of their bedroom
cheering as they
achieved orgasm.
That sounds like
a late night,
and I have work in
the morning, so...
Leonard, you may
not have noticed,
but I am being
a delight here.
And you're not holding up
your end of the evening.
Oh, sorry. This wedding
just reminds me
of my kinda-sorta girlfriend
9,000 miles away.
I have a kinda-sorta boyfriend
who's playing with a model train
right now, you don't hear me
bitching about it.
Leonard, a word of advice--
moody self-obsession
is only attractive in men
who can play guitar
and are considerably
taller than you.
I'm not moody.
I'm fun.
You have any evidence
to support that statement?
Well, hey, I'm just as
much fun as you are.
Really? Are you willing to draw
a mustache on your finger
as a conversational icebreaker?
I am.
Okay, fine, what
do you suggest?
♪ ♪
We just had a lovely meal,
the band... is on fire...
and you're sitting
next to a beautiful woman
wearing whorish makeup.
Why don't we head out
on the dance floor
and see if I can sweat
through these dress shields.
Once again, I-I'm really
not much of a dancer.
Don't worry...
I'll lead.
("The Chicken Dance" playing)
(imitating lightsaber)
Howard?
(imitates lightsaber
turning off)
Ready for bed?
No. I need to brush my teeth,
but your moth's
been in the bathroom
for, like, an hour.
Oh. Yeah, she sometimes has problems
doing her business. Hang on.
Ma, give up!
Tonight's
not your night!
MRS. WOLOWITZ: You don't know that!
I just sat down!
WOLOWITZ:
Come on, take a break!
Bernadette needs
to brush her teeth!
MRS. WOLOWITZ: She can come in
and brush her teeth!
I'm not embarrassed!
Problem solved.
No, it's not.
I'm not going in there.
Oh, come on, honey.
She's just sitting in there
reading a magazine.
You can't see anything.
I go in all the time.
(chuckles)
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Ha! The eagle has landed!
(toilet flushing)
And we have splashdown.
(clears throat)
Wait here, I'm gonna
go light a candle.
And then we make
passionate love.
There we go, last floor.
I just can't figure
out what happened.
I put my left leg in,
I took my left leg out,
I put my left leg in, and
something just snapped.
The hokey pokey
is a young man's game.
(chuckles)
I did have a great time.
Thank you for reminding me
it's okay to have fun
once in a while.
You're welcome.
And also for breaking
the head off the ice swan
so I could hold it against
my pulled groin.
I excel
at spatial reasoning, and I had
a hunch that the graceful slope
of its neck would cradle
your genitals nicely.
Well, okay.
Again, thank you.
And again, you're welcome.
Want to come in?
No, thanks.
I'm gonna head home.
'Kay. Well, good night.
Good night.
Ames, hi.
How was the wedding?
Great. Until I accidentally made
Leonard fall in love with me.
Come in, let's talk.
Do you want a
glass of wine?
Wine is one of the reasons
I'm in this fix.
That and this dang pelvis.
Okay, I'm sorry,
what exactly happened?
The inevitable--
he was lonely and vulnerable
from missing his girlfriend,
while I was charming,
supportive and,
let's face it, in this dress,
the perfect combination
of Madonna and whore.
Oh, God,
did he make a move on you?
No, but it's only
a matter of time.
How could I have not
seen this coming?
Now I'm gonna have to break
the little sad sack's heart.
- Yeah, I'm sure he'll be okay.
- Oh, Penny,
much as I would treasure
knowing that the two of us had
been defiled by the same man,
Leonard just doesn't get
my motor running.
So, um, what are
you gonna do?
Do you want me to talk
to Leonard, let him down easy?
No. I'll let him have tonight.
Then in the morning,
I'll send him an e-mail
letting him know
this body is never
gonna be his wonderland.
I mean, frankly, you've got
a better shot than he does.
Leonard.
Check it out.
I bought an N-gauge locomotive.
Half the size of H-O.
Look, it fits in my mouth.
Sounds like you
had a great night.
(muffled):
I did.
- How was yours?
- Not bad. I had a lot more fun
with Amy than I
thought I would.
What exact
do you mean by that?
Well, it turns out
she really knows
how to help a guy loosen up
and have a good time.
Although, truth be told, my
groin's a little worse for wear.
Ow!
Why did you do that?
To send a message:
she is not for you.
What?
Not for you!
Good morning, handsome.
Morning, Mom.
It's me.
Yes, it is, and you're
so pretty in the morning.
Your mom and I
made you breakfast.
(laughs)
Oh, wow.
So you guys are getting along?
Yeah, I guess.
We're very different
people, Howard,
so communication's
a little tricky.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Does he like the pancakes?!
He didn't try them yet!
Is there any butter?
- It's butter-flavored syrup.
- Oh.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
So, what's the word?!
He wants butter!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
It's butter-flavored syrup!
I just told him that!
I don't need any butter.
If you want butter,
I'll get you butter.
Well, I guess
I'll cut these by myself.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net