It's amazing
people keep coming
visit tvshowslatest.blogspot.com
to comic book stores
instead of just downloading
comics digitally.
It's probably for the best.
For a lot of these guys,
the weekly trip here
is the only chance
their mom has to go down
to the basement
and change their sheets.
Oh, that reminds me,
I get fresh sheets tonight. Yay.
Well?
What do you think
of New Comic Book Night?
Magic, huh?
Sheldon, I'm disappointed.
As a brilliant man,
you're entitled to a vice.
I could understand
frequenting an opium den
or hunting your fellow man
for sport.
But this? Lame-o.
Well, A) Comic books
employ storytelling
through sequential art,
an medium that dates back
17,000 years
to the cave paintings
of Lascaux,
and B) You play the harp.
Like that's cool.
Can I help you
find anything?
A comic that depicts
a woman whose bosom
can't be used
as a flotation device.
Sorry. Most of the guys
who come in here
like big boobs.
Couple of them
have big boobs.
Hey, look, the new
Warlords of Ka'a
expansion pack is out.
A new one?
Unbelievable.
They just keep making up
more cheesy monsters,
slapping them on cards and
selling them at 25 bucks a pop.
It's like a secret tax
on guys who can't get laid.
They're not even trying.
Remember the Satanimals pack
with the Hellephant?
Why, absurd.
What was he, a bad elephant
who died and went to hell?
What could
an elephant
possibly do that would cause him
eternal damnation?
"Wild West and Witches"?
What kind of loser cares
about a showdown
between Billy the Kid and
the White Wizard of the North?
A total loser.
Obviously,
a guy with a six-shooter
beats an old man
with a magic wand.
Well, h-hold on.
Uh, what if the wizard casts
a Helmet of Confusion spell
on Billy the Kid's cowboy hat?
What? Please!
This is Billy the Kid
we're talking about.
I mean, the wizard
would get shot between the eyes
before he could ever
get out the words,
"What the hell
is Billy the Kid doing
in the mystic realm of Ka'a?"
Leonard...
(clears throat)
What's the deal
with Sheldon's friend Amy?
Are they a couple?
Couple of weirdos. Why?
You interested in Amy?
Well, I mean,
she didn't look through me
with soul-sucking,
ball-shriveling
hatred and contempt.
I like that in a woman.
Could you run it by Sheldon
if I could ask her out?
Sure. I guess.
KOOTHRAPPALI: Stuart, settle an
argument for us.
Who would win,
Billy the Kid
or the White Wizard?
(chuckles)
If I tell you that,
I'm robbing you of the hours
of fun you could have
for the magical, rootin'-tootin'
low price of $24.95.
I'll take one.
Mm... make it two.
I hate all of you and myself.
Three.
I'll ring it up.
(muttering):
Like shooting nerds in a barrel.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory 5x10
The Flaming Spittoon Acquisition
visit tvshowslatest.blogspot.com
Hey, can I talk to
you about something?
It's a little
awkward.
I know what this is about.
Given the professional
standstill you're at,
you're wondering
if this is the appropriate time
to abandon your research
and focus on teaching.
Yes.
And if I may suggest,
consider changing disciplines.
Yeah, to the humanities--
perhaps history.
One of the advantages
of teaching history
is that you don't have
to create things.
You know, you just
have to remember
stuff that happened
and then parrot it back.
You could have fun with that.
Yeah, that's not it.
Stuart's kind of
interested in Amy.
Oh, of course he is.
She's very interesting.
Did you know,
when she was 14,
she severed the webbing
between her own toes?
No.
He wanted me to find out
if you'd have a problem
with him asking her out.
I'm not sure how to respond,
Leonard.
I don't own Amy.
Can't own a person.
At least not since...
1863.
President Lincoln freed the...
Slaves!
Come on, Leonard,
if you're going
to teach history,
these are the kind of facts
you'll have to know.
You know what?
Never mind.
I'm going to tell him
it's okay to ask her out.
The question is moot.
There is no way that Stuart,
an impoverished peddler
of picture books,
would be at all appealing
to Amy Farrah Fowler,
a noted neurobiologist
capable of performing surgery
on her own feet
with nothing but nitrous oxide
from cans of whipped cream
as anesthesia.
All right,
but for the record,
I checked in with you
to see how you'd feel about it.
Fine.
The record shall so reflect.
Now, getting back
to the problem at hand,
what to do with a washed-up
experimental physicist...
I am not washed-up.
Oh, Leonard.
Lots of people love you
and want to help you,
but they can't
until you admit the problem.
Well, ladies,
we killed the bottle.
I had half a glass.
I didn't have any.
Okay, don't judge me.
So, what do you want to do--
go to the movies, go dancing,
lay down for a little bit?
Or we play... Travel Twister.
Amy, really? Twister?
Excuse me.
I've passed many
an enjoyable evening
playing this game.
And I'm sure it's
a lot more exciting
when you play with other people.
What do you say, bestie?
We can do shirts and skins.
I'm shirts. Called it.
(cell phone buzzing)
I'm too small
for Twister.
And roller coasters.
And sitting with my
feet on the floor.
Hope you enjoyed the
prenatal cigarettes, Mom.
Hey, you know, my mom smoked pot
when she was pregnant with me,
and I turned out just fine.
Hey, look, I have
peach schnapps.
Thank God.
Guys, something happened.
What's wrong?
I think a boy
likes me.
"Hi. It's Stuart.
"We met at the
comic book store.
"I was wondering
if you'd like
"to get coffee sometime.
"It's okay
if you say no.
"It might be the kick
in the pants I need
to start taking Zoloft."
Amy, little vixen.
Just working it under all those
layers of wool and polyester.
What are you going to do?
Doesn't he know
you have a boyfriend?
Oh, she doesn't
have a boyfriend;
she has a Sheldon.
So do you
like Stuart?
I don't know.
He's nice.
He's funny.
He has the sallow,
drawn countenance
associated with an overactive
thyroid gland.
That's kind of hot.
Okay, look, sweetie,
we all love Sheldon,
but you've been with him
over a year now.
If it's not going anywhere,
what does it hurt
to look around?
Well, yeah, I guess
they're not engaged
like me and Howie.
Yeah, for what it's worth,
engaged people
can look around, too.
Lot of options out there.
Where's Stuart?
(giggles)
Out.
Who are you?
I'm Dale.
He left me in charge.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't get it, either.
I want to return
this "Wild West and Witches"
Ka'a expansion pack.
Sorry. I don't do returns.
They're hard.
Sure, sure.
Uh, when will
Stuart be back?
I don't know.
He went out for coffee.
With a girl.
(high-pitched giggling)
Oh, I guess I was wrong.
You okay?
Am I okay?
Leonard,
I'm on a lifelong trajectory
that includes a Nobel Prize
and cities named after me,
all four
wisdom teeth
fit comfortably in my mouth
without need of extraction,
and my bowel movements run
like a German train schedule.
Am I okay?
I'm okay, too!
Wild Bill Witchcock.
A tribe of Abra-Comanches.
Flaming Spittoon.
And for the record,
I'm very disappointed
in you cowpokes.
We're playing
our inaugural round
of "Wild West and Witches,"
and I'm the only one
who bothered
to dress for the occasion.
(spits) Patooie.
We're not wearing
cowboy hats, Sheldon.
It looks ridiculous.
And I suppose my boots and spurs
are ridiculous, too?
- Yeah. - Very. - Incredibly so.
Did it look ridiculous
when we got the Satanimals pack
and I dressed up
as a Beelzebobcat?
- Yeah. - Very. - Incredibly so.
All right, fine.
Let's just play.
We should go easy on him.
Amy's out with Stuart tonight.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me
that Sheldon's patented blend
of condescension and no sex
isn't enough
to hold on to a woman?
Cluck, cluck, cluck.
What are we,
ladies at a quilting bee?
Or are we men
playing a fantasy card game
set in a magical frontier town?
Sorry.
Creepy Tepee.
Annie Ogly.
Hocus Pocus Pocahontas.
And may I point out
it is the three of you
who are obsessed with
Stuart and Amy, not me.
I think you need
to ask yourselves
who's really being
ridiculous here.
(spurs jingling & jangling)
- It's you. - You are. - Totally you.
Hey, guys, check it out.
The deluxe limited edition
"Wild West and Witches"
expansion pack in the signed
and numbered collector's tin.
LEONARD:
Come on, no!
We just bought the regular pack.
Ooh, a sheriff's badge.
(chuckles)
Yeah, it's also a wand.
With a hologram? Nice!
Hey, do you see this?
I'm in the matrix, Leonard;
I see everything.
You got to be
kidding me.
You friended Stuart
on Facebook?
I thought you didn't
like Facebook anymore.
Don't be silly.
I'm a fan of anything that tries
to replace actual human contact.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Please.
You're looking at Facebook
to find out how their date went.
Really?
You think I care if a man, what,
"shared a pumpkin latte
with a dynamite lady"?
You're so full of it.
You are free to believe
whatever you like.
And unfriend
Rajesh Koothrappali.
You unfriended me? Seriously?
Oh, yeah.
Now he's gonna miss all
those great updates like,
"I can't believe
I waited this long
(Indian accent):
to make my own potpourri""
Sheldon, why don't you
just acknowledge
that you have feelings for Amy
and you don't want her
going out with other men?
And unfriend
Leonard Hofstadter.
Here's a radical thought.
Go old-school,
challenge Stuart to a fight.
I mean, nothing makes
the ladies hotter
than two skinny white guys
swatting at each other
with their eyes closed.
And unfriend Howard Wolowitz.
That's all of us.
- Can I use the laptop?
- Why?
I have to buy that
stupid collector's tin.
PENNY: Who do we love?
Penny.
Who do we love?
Hello, Sheldon.
Come on in.
Thank you.
What's up?
I came to ask if you would like
to go on a date with me.
I'm sorry, what?
A date.
You and me.
Dining, dancing,
perhaps you'd like to
take in a prizefight.
(microwave beeps)
God, are you trying
to make Amy jealous?
No.
Why is everyone so obsessed
with Amy and Stuart?
Whether or not they may be
having more pumpkin lattes
or intercourse tonight.
Okay, listen to me.
Playing games is not
gonna help get Amy back.
I am not trying to get her back.
But, out of curiosity,
what is a way?
All right, honey,
let me tell you a story.
There was a guy I liked,
and I never told him how I felt.
Eventually, he started
going out with someone else,
and I always regretted it.
Do you see
where I'm going with this?
I believe I do.
Mm.
I'm the guy.
You're not the guy.
Are you sure?
That would explain so much.
Your constant presence
in my apartment,
that baffling dalliance
with Leonard just to be near me,
the way you call me
"sweetie" all the time.
I call everyone "sweetie."
You tramp.
(sighs)
Look, Sheldon,
all I'm saying is
strap on a pair
and go talk to Amy.
"Strap on a pair"?
Of what, skates?
Oh, sweetie,
you are so not the guy.
(quiet, dramatic musical score
playing in movie)
If you're bored,
you can go.
I understand.
No, I'm having a nice time.
(scoffs)
Don't patronize me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Pardon me. Excuse me.
Hi, Stuart.
Hi, Sheldon.
Pardon me... Excuse me...
Sheldon, what are
you doing here?
The thought of you
sitting in a darkened theater
with a character
like Stuart is repellent.
No offense, Stuart.
None taken.
Although "repellent" is kind
of a... kind of a strong word.
I'm sorry this causes
you discomfort,
but based on the currently
established parameters
of our relationship,
I can put myself
in any repellent
situation I want.
Um, again...
Stuart, please.
You're being rude.
Anything else?
I believe I would
like to alter
the paradigm
of our relationship.
I'm listening.
With the understanding
that nothing changes whatsoever,
physical or otherwise,
I would not object to us
no longer characterizing you
as "not my girlfriend."
Interesting.
Now try it without the
quadruple negative.
You're being impossible.
Hi, Stuart.
Fine.
Amy...
will you be my girlfriend?
Yes.
Well, that's enough
of that.
Sorry to interrupt.
You two enjoy your date.
Here's a dollar
for your troubles.
Get yourself
some Sour Patch Kids.
Excuse me... Excuse me...
Pardon me...
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
So, other than you
taking your relationship
to the next level with
another guy, this was nice.
Yes, well, thanks for
seeing me to my door.
Oh, you're welcome.
(knocking)
SHELDON: Amy. Amy. Amy.
Let's wrap things up out there.
Um, good night, Stuart.
Good night.
SHELDON:
Take the hint, Stuart.
The lady said
"Good night."
How did you get
into my apartment?
Wow. Is that the kind
of nagging I can expect
now that you're my girlfriend?
Good thing I drew this up.
What's that?
I present to you
the relationship agreement.
A binding covenant that,
in its 31 pages,
enumerates, iterates
and codifies
the rights and responsibilities
of Sheldon Lee Cooper,
here and after known
as "the boyfriend,"
and Amy Farrah Fowler, here and
after known as "the girlfriend""
It's so romantic.
Mutual indemnification
always is.
Why don't you start perusing
while I set up my notary stamp.
"Section 5:
Hand-holding.
"Hand-holding
is only allowed
"under the following
circumstances.
"A: Either party is in danger
of falling off a cliff,
"precipice or ledge;
"B: Either party is deserving
of a hearty handshake
"after winning
a Nobel Prize;
C: Moral support
during flu shots""
Seems a bit
restrictive.
Feel free to retain a lawyer.
Penny, I said "right hand red."
Yeah, I heard you.
I got red.
Bernadette, left
foot yellow.
(groans)
We should play limbo next.
No one beats me at limbo.
(knocking)
SHELDON: Penny. Amy. Bernadette.
That's my boyfriend.
It's open!
I got a splinter.
What do you want me
to do about it?
Relationship agreement
Section 4: Boo-boos and Ouchies.
You have to take care of it.
I should've gotten a lawyer.
Looks like it's just us playing.
(snoring)
Penny?
Penny, we're out of wine!
You should probably drive.
visit tvshowslatest.blogspot.com
www.tvsubtitles.net