(Klaxon blaring)
(screams)
What the hell?
Emergency preparedness drill.
- Oh, no, come on!
- Yeah, you know how it works.
Once a quarter,
keep our readiness up.
Now, rise and shine,
sleepy head.
Half the town is probably dead.
I have to get
a lock for my door.
I think you'll like
the drill tonight.
I've tried to make it fun.
Each of these cards
contains a detailed scenario
of a possible apocalyptic event.
Everything from wild fires
to a surprise invasion
by Canada.
Pick a catastrophe,
any catastrophe.
Sheldon, Canada is not going
to invade California.
Yeah, really?
You think those hippies
in Washington and Oregon
can stop them?
Fine.
All righty!
"An 8.2 magnitude earthquake
devastates Pasadena,
"reducing mighty
edifices to dust,
"engulfing the city in flames.
"The streets flow with blood
and echo with the cries
of the wounded."
Oh, excellent choice.
Now, put on your hardhat
and safety vest.
Oh, fun.
I get to spend another night
in front of our apartment
dressed like one
of the Village People.
You make that joke
every three months.
I still don't get it.
Leonard... wait.
What are you doing?
I don't know,
what am I doing?
Look around you--
there's hypothetical
broken glass everywhere.
Really? You're going
to face Armageddon
without your orthotics?
Your choice.
Uh-oh, hypothetical aftershock!
(yells)
(thud)
Aah!
And that's why we wear hardhats.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory 5x15
The Friendship Contraction
Original Air Date on February 2, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Check it out--
press release
from NASA.
Um, "Expedition 31
will launch this spring
"to the International
Space Station.
"Crew members will include
Commander Tom 'Tombo' Johnson,
"Astronaut
Mike 'Supernova' Novacelik
and Payload Specialist
Howard Wolowitz."
(giggles)
This is going right into
my synagogue's newsletter.
D-Dude, if you're
going to be an astronaut,
you need to pick
a cool nickname.
I don't get to pick it.
The other guys
have to give it to me.
Oh. If I had one,
it would be "Brown Dynamite."
Are you not listening to me?
The other astronauts
have to give you your nickname.
Are you not looking at me?
I am Brown Dynamite.
Why do you put six
sugars in your coffee?
Because the cafeteria
doesn't offer
little packets
of methamphetamine.
Emergency drill night
last night, huh?
- Uh-huh.
- How'd you do?
I'll tell you
exactly how he did.
"Readiness:
unsatisfactory.
"Follows direction: barely.
"Attitude: a little too much.
"Overall:
"not only will he probably die
in a fiery inferno,
"his incessant whining
would most certainly spoil
everyone else's day."
You know what, I can't
even think straight.
I'm going home.
Will one of you guys give
this nutbag a ride back later?
You can't go home.
You have to take me
to the dentist at 4:00.
Oh... can't you take
the bus to the dentist?
Of course I can.
It's coming back,
under the residual effects
of the anesthesia,
that's the problem.
Two years ago,
after a deep gum cleaning,
I thought I got on a bus
but somehow wound up
on a booze cruise to Mexico.
They put you under
for a cleaning?
Yeah, they have to--
I'm a biter.
Whatever, Sheldon.
I'm exhausted.
I'm not taking you
to the dentist.
Wrong, sir.
Wrong. Under section 37-B
of the Roommate Agreement--
"Miscellaneous Duties"--
you are obligated
to take me to the dentist.
See? It's right here after
"providing a confirmation sniff
on questionable dairy products."
You know what, I am sick
of the Roommate Agreement.
(gasps)
It's ridiculous.
I'm your roommate,
not your chauffeur.
You know, I had
better things to do yesterday
than drive you all the way
to the "good" model train store
in Garden Grove
because the one in Pasadena
has gotten
"too big for its britches."
Well, it has.
Ask anybody.
I don't care.
I'm done.
Hold on.
Are you saying that you
want to invoke Clause 209?
I don't know what that is,
but if it means I can go home
and sleep, then yes.
Think carefully here.
Clause 209 suspends
our friendship,
and strips down the
Roommate Agreement to
its bare essentials.
Our responsibilities
toward each other would
only be rent, utilities
and a perfunctory
chin jut of recognition
as we pass in the hall.
'Sup?
Where do I sign?
Right here.
Use your finger.
There. Done.
All right.
That's it. We are
now no longer companions,
boon or otherwise.
We are not merely
acquaintances.
To amend the words
of Toy Story--
"You have not got
a friend in me."
I'm gonna go home
and take a nap.
Yeah, well, tell it
to someone who cares.
I got pretty exciting
NASA news today.
Next week I fly to Houston
for orientation
and zero-gravity
elimination drills.
What does that mean?
He's gonna learn
to poop in space.
Open the pod bay
doors, HAL.
Maybe your nickname
should be "Brown Dynamite."
Hello, dear friends.
And Dr. Hofstadter.
'Sup?
My apologies.
I would've been here sooner,
but the bus kept stopping
for other people to get on it.
I saved you a dumpling.
Oh, your concern
for me is touching.
It will serve you well
when you take me to
the dentist tomorrow.
I'm sorry, Sheldon, I'm busy.
I'm right in the middle
of my addiction study.
I've got a lab
full of alcoholic monkeys,
and tomorrow's the day
we switch them to O'Doul's.
You're my girlfriend
and you're not going to cater
to my every need?
Oh, where'd the magic go?
Sheldon, that's not
what girlfriends are for.
Although, you don't use them
for what they're for,
so what do I know?
Howard doesn't make
me do his shopping
or take him to the dentist
or pick up his
dry cleaning, right?
Absolutely.
But when Ma's hips
give out, you're up, kid.
Well, if Amy's too busy,
that gives the rest of you
an opportunity to
make my life easier,
thus assuring yourselves
a footnote in my memoirs,
tentatively entitled
You're Welcome, Mankind.
All right, then,
just shout when you hear
the task you want to undertake.
Uh, dentist.
Okay, w-we can
circle back to that one.
Um, well, who wants
to take me Wednesday morning
to get new heels
put on my dress shoes?
Anyone?
Oh. That one had hoot
written all over it.
Um, all right,
uh, dermatologist.
Allergist.
Podiatrist.
Supercuts?
Okay, okay, here's a fun one.
Um, I need a new picture frame
and I have a hankering
for Swedish meatballs.
Who wants to spend the day
with me at IKEA?
Their meatballs
are pretty good.
What's that?
Nothing, nothing.
Hello, Stuart.
Oh, hey, Sheldon.
Can I help you find
something today?
No, no.
I was just sitting at home
thinking about how it
might be nice to catch up
with my ninth favorite person.
Ninth?
You moved up one.
My pen pal in Somalia
was kidnapped by pirates.
So, uh... how are you?
Uh... not so good.
My shrink just
killed himself and...
blamed me in the note.
Great. Great.
So, what's new
with your family?
How's your mother?
Is she alive?
Yeah.
And your father? Alive?
Yes.
How about your grandparents,
they alive?
No.
Oh, I'm so sorry for your loss.
On a cheerier note,
I have a teeth-cleaning
appointment this afternoon.
What do you say you
take me over there, buddy boy?
I'm sorry, you want me
to take you to the dentist?
Yes. Now, I can't
make any promises,
but that's the sort of thing
that gets a fella
on the short list
for the number eight
friend slot.
Sheldon, I'm working.
I can't take you
to the dentist.
Also-- and I can't
stress this enough--
I don't want to take you
to the dentist.
Can't help a friend out
in a time of need, huh?
I see where your
therapist was coming from.
Ooh, ooh! What about we
make your astronaut nickname
Howard "Buzz" Wolowitz?
You can't do "Buzz."
"Buzz" is taken.
Buzz Lightyear is not real.
No, that's not what
I'm talking about.
Well, are you talking about
when he thought he was real?
No.
Okay, um...
how about "Crash"?
Howard "Crash" Wolowitz.
Yeah, terrific.
The other astronauts
would love to go hurtling
through space
with a guy named "Crash."
All right, um, how about...
Oh, how about "Rocket Man"?
That's not bad,
Howard "Rocket Man" Wolowitz.
Yeah, it's great,
but I told you,
I don't get to pick
my nickname.
It has to come from
the other astronauts.
Maybe there's a way to get
them to come up with it.
Like how?
Once I tried carrying
around a Duncan yo-yo,
hoping the other kids would
start calling me Duncan.
Did it work?
No, they ended up
calling me Sock Mouth.
Because they took away my yo-yo
and stuffed their socks
in my mouth.
Okay, uh, what if we make
"Rocket Man" your ringtone,
and the next time you
talk to those guys,
I'll call you and
they'll hear it.
Plant the seed.
That's actually not
a terrible plan.
They don't call me
"Brown Dynamite" for nothing.
'Sup?
Hey, did you ever make it
to the dentist?
Not necessary. No.
I found a service that'll
send a van to your house
for a teeth cleaning.
Mostly they cater
to dogs, but...
...the fellow on the phone
seemed to have an open mind.
All right, Sheldon,
if you need me to take you
to the dentist,
I will take you to the dentist.
Are you suggesting that
you've come to your senses
and wish to reestablish
the mutual benefits that stem
from full participation
in the Roommate Agreement?
Absolutely.
If you admit that
you're a 30-year-old man
who's incapable
of functioning on his own.
Ooh, Sock Mouth's
got him on the ropes.
I will admit nothing
of the sort.
And now if you'll excuse me,
I have
to call my dentist and see
if I can also get my hair
shampooed and my nails clipped.
(dramatic music plays on TV)
(music stops)
(knocking on door)
Oh, good, your power's out, too.
Why is that good?
(sighs)
Because last month,
I sent the electric company
a Starbucks gift card,
an apology note, and a few
snapshots of me in a bra.
(Klaxon sounds)
Power failure.
Implementing
power-failure protocol.
What happened to all your glow-
in-the-dark-emergency-exit stuff
you had painted on the floor?
Oh, that was
wildly carcinogenic.
Anyway...
it's too bad you're
no longer entitled
to the full benefits
of my friendship,
because I happen to be
extremely prepared
for such an emergency.
Please try not to see
anything by this light.
It's not for you.
It's just a blackout; I'm sure
the power will be back on soon.
And I'm sure some fool
in the Donner party
said the snow would
stop any day now.
I like to think
they ate him first.
You know, I got some candles
in my apartment.
But candles?!
During a blackout?!
Are you mad?
That's a fire hazard.
No, Pasadena
Water and Power recommends
the far safer glow stick.
You call that
a glow stick?
That is a glow stick.
Come on, let's go.
Before you go,
consider this.
Not only do I have a deep-cycle
marine battery power source
which is more than capable
of running our
entertainment system,
I also have
all 61 episodes
of the BBC series Red Dwarf...
and Fiddle-Faddle.
All yours
if you're willing to reinstate
the Roommate Agreement.
I've got wine at my place and
some bubble wrap we could pop.
Oh, he'll be back.
Wine and a girl in the dark--
he's gonna be bored
out of his mind.
To wine and bubble wrap.
(popping)
And to not having to watch
Sheldon demonstrate
his reverse osmosis machine
that converts urine
into drinking water.
You know, in Girl Scouts,
Tammie Dineesha said
you could do that
with panty hose.
Boy, was she wrong.
Anyway, you want
to make out?
I thought because our
relationship's in a beta test,
you wanted to
take things slow.
Okay.
Do you want to make out slow?
I can go so slow it'll be like
there's a snail in your mouth.
Ugh.
Well, lucky for you, there's
nothing else to do right now.
Excuse me, Leonard.
Since when don't you knock?
It's like the only
good thing about you.
Social niceties
have been suspended, Leonard.
We're in a state of a emergency.
The world has
descended into darkened turmoil.
Lawlessness and savagery
are the order of the day.
Fine, what is it?
I'm making s'mores.
I wanted to alert you
in case you smelled
caramelizing marshmallows
and thought a nearby
candy factory was on fire.
S'mores, huh?
Good for you.
Yes, or good for us
if you sign here
and reinstate
the full Roommate Agreement.
No, thanks. I'm good.
Really?
Huh! Okay.
In that case, I will have
a s'more by myself.
And then I'm gonna have s'more.
By myself.
- Aw.
- No, don't "aw" him.
He brought this all
on himself.
But he's sad.
No, he's crazy.
Sometimes crazy
looks like sad
so it'll suck you back in.
I think he misses
his little buddy.
Fine.
But mark my words,
this frustrating, bogus teenage
make-out session is not over.
(popping)
I thought you said
candles were dangerous.
This is a Bunsen burner.
I'm a scientist;
I know what I'm doing.
Oh, drat.
Aww.
It took me a gallon of urine
to make that water.
Listen, Sheldon, this is stupid.
I don't see why we can't
be friends.
And I'm willing to
drive you around
and help you out with stuff.
I just don't want to do it
because of some
silly Roommate Agreement.
What are you proposing?
That we go back to
the way things were.
But when I do
something for you,
you show a little
appreciation.
And how would I do that?
You say "thank you."
Every time?
It's not crazy.
Counter-proposal.
We reinstate the full
Roommate Agreement
with the following addendum:
in the spirit of Mother's Day
or Father's Day,
once a year, we set aside
a day to celebrate
all your contributions
to my life,
both actual and imagined by you.
We could call it Leonard's Day.
I kind of like
the sound of that.
Of course you do.
It's about you,
like everything else.
Oh, thank goodness.
I don't think I had it in me
to make another glass of water.
So, do I get breakfast
in bed on Leonard's Day?
No.
Can I sit in your spot?
Can I control the thermostat?
No.
Do I get a card?
Of course you get a card.
It's Leonard's Day.
Hey, guys, the building
manager said
the reason
the power went out is
someone went
down into the basement
and just pulled the
main breaker switch.
Really.
Who do you think
did that, Sheldon?
Oh, I don't know.
But whoever
that mystery man was,
you should be
eternally grateful,
for without him, there would
be no Leonard's Day.
Leonard's Day?
Oh, no pressure.
Just get him a crummy card,
you're good.
All right, test my ring tone.
(Elton John's
"Rocket Man" plays)
- That really is a good song.
- Oh, yeah.
There's a reason
he's Sir Elton John.
They don't make you a knight
for writing "Wake Me Up
Before You Go Go."
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard, are you
coming down for breakfast?!
Ma, I told you I have
a video conference with NASA!
I said don't bother me!
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Oh! Listen to
Mr. Big Shot Astronaut!
Yes, please listen
to Mr. Big Shot Astronaut!
(Skype rings)
Hey, good morning.
Hey, Howard,
thanks for getting up so early.
No problem, Dr. Massimino.
The guys here call me Mass.
Mass!
That's a cool nickname.
'Cause force equals mass
times acceleration.
Yeah.
It's just short
for Massimino.
Anyway, the plan for this
morning is to go over the...
(Elton John's
"Rocket Man" playing)
Sorry. My phone.
What is that?
Is that "Rocket Man"?
Yeah, my ring tone.
Kind of my favorite song,
"Rocket Man."
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard,
your Fruit Loops
are getting soggy!
Not now!
Who's that?
My mom. Sorry.
No problem... Fruit Loops.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net