It's from
Game of Thrones.
What do you think?
I don't know.
If we're going to start
a fantasy sword collection--
and I've long thought
we should--
is this really
the sword to start with?
What did you
have in mind?
Well, off the top of my head,
I'd have to go with Excalibur.
It gives you the right
to rule England.
It would be a replica
of a movie prop.
Fair enough.
It'd give you the right to rule
a replica of England.
Well, they don't have
an Excalibur here,
so what do you want to do?
Mm. Tough decision.
There's no weaponry from
Lord of the Rings
forged in a Chinese sweatshop?
Just Bilbo Baggins' sword
over there.
Two grown men with a hobbit's
dagger; wouldn't we look silly?
Okay, let's go for it.
Oh, I see
you guys have
found my little treasure.
Yeah.
It's okay, I guess.
Okay? It's magnificent.
Buh-buh-buh-buh!
What do you want for it?
Oh, it's hard to put
a price on something
that's a copy of something
that was on pay cable.
But for my friends,
let's say 250?
Oh, that's pretty steep.
Well, it's a limited edition.
They only made 8,000
of these bad boys.
Only 8,000?
We're wasting precious time.
Buy it.
Hang on.
Can you do any better?
Are you kidding?
I'm already giving you
the friends and family discount.
Oh, did you hear that?
We're getting the friends
and family discount.
We are honored
and we will take it.
Slow down.
Two hundred.
What are you doing?
250 is already the
discounted price.
Will you shut up?
Tell you what, I'll go 235.
Nope. Maybe another time.
Okay, 225-- my final offer.
Take it, take it.
Two hundred.
Man, you're killing me!
Killing you?
I can't breathe.
210, and I'm losing money.
Oh, now, we can't let him lose
money, Leonard. I'm so sorry.
210 and you throw in
the Iron Man helmet.
Are you crazy?
That helmet's signed
by Robert Downey Jr.
So?
Okay, if you're
going to question
the importance of an actor's
signature on a plastic helmet
from a movie
based on a comic book,
then all of our lives
have no meaning!
Okay, fine.
Just the sword, 210.
Thank you.
I can eat meat this week.
See that?
I just saved us 40 bucks.
I've long said, what you
lack in academic knowledge
you make up for
in street smarts.
You want me to wrap it?
No, it's okay.
I'm gonna stab my friend
in the chest.
Hey, Stuart.
Ah, hey, Wil.
Hello, Wil Wheaton.
Hi, Sheldon.
Nice sword.
It's part of
my sword collection.
- Do you have a sword collection?
- No.
I'm not surprised.
Here's the
Batman 612
with the Jim Lee alternate
cover that you wanted.
Awesome. What do I owe you?
40 bucks.
Good deal.
Sucker.
Didn't even ask for the
friends and family discount.
Hey, I'm having a party
at my house on Friday,
and I was hoping
you would stop by.
Will there be
girls there?
Yeah, of course.
'Cause there
wasn't last time.
There will be girls.
You guys are invited
if you want to come by.
Thank you.
All right, great.
Later.
I see what you're doing.
You accept
an invitation
to a party at the home
of my sworn enemy,
he tells everyone we're
going to be there,
and when we don't show,
he looks the fool.
Fiendishly clever.
I was actually
thinking about going.
And then declaring
the party a fiasco
and storming out,
leaving him humiliated
in front of his guests.
Love it.
No, I was gonna grab Raj and
Howard and have a good time.
Oh, great, more guys.
It's gonna be another
Wil Wheaton sausage-fest.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory 5x05
The Russian Rocket Reaction
Original Air Date on October 13, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Sheldon, can you
grab me a water?
Possibly.
Can you or can't you?
It's not that simple, Leonard.
It never is, is it?
SHELDON:
At this moment,
our relationship exists
in two mutually
contradictory states.
Until you either do not go
or go to Wil Wheaton's party,
you are simultaneously my friend
and not my friend.
I'm characterizing
this phenomenon
as Schrodinger's Friendship.
Got it. Can I have my water?
Of course.
Now get it yourself,
you traitor.
Wait, what is going on?
In case you have forgotten,
Schrodinger's cat is
a thought experiment...
No, no, I didn't forget.
Um, there's this cat in a box
and until you open it,
it's either
dead or alive or both.
Although, back in Nebraska,
our cat got stuck
in my brother's camp trunk,
and we did not need to open it
to know there was all kinds
of dead cat in there.
Homespun stories,
knowledge of physics
and a bosom that defies it.
You're the whole package,
aren't you?
Sorry I'm late.
Uh, I got great news.
NASA picked my team's design
for the deep field
space telescope that's going on
the International Space Station
this spring.
(all murmur excitedly)
Howie, that's wonderful!
Congratulations!
It gets better.
Someone has to go up
with the telescope
as a payload specialist,
and guess who that someone is.
Muhammad Li.
Who's Muhammad Li?
Muhammad is the most common
first name in the world,
Li, the most common surname.
As I didn't know the answer,
I thought that gave me
a mathematical edge.
It's me, Sheldon.
It's me.
I'm going up in space!
Technically, I'm an astronaut.
(all murmur excitedly)
That's amazing!
(chuckles)
Hang on a second.
NASA doesn't have
a shuttle anymore.
How are you going
to get up there?
Oh, well, it's really cool.
You fly to Moscow,
they take you out to Kazakhstan,
and then you get into a Russian
Soyuz rocket which shoots you
into a low earth orbit.
Or just sits there on the launch
pad because the Kazakhi mafia
sold the rocket fuel
on the black market.
Are those Russian rockets safe?
Well, I mean, safe as it
can be when it was built
by the good folks who
brought you Chernobyl.
I'd like to propose a toast.
The dream to go up into space
is one we all share,
and Howard's making that
a reality.
We're all very proud of you.
ALL:
Cheers.
That was a lovely toast.
Kudos.
Thank you.
Simultaneously, a festival
of cloying clichés.
You sicken me.
You're really quiet.
Is everything okay?
Fine.
Just a little tired.
I hope not too tired,
because I'm feeling
particularly masculine
right now.
All systems go,
if you catch my drift.
I always catch your drift.
All right, well, something's
obviously bugging you.
What is it?
I just can't believe
you signed up
for the space program
without even talking to me.
Oh, I get it.
You're worried about me.
That is so sweet.
You know, there's a saying
we have at NASA.
What makes
the right stuff so right
is that it always comes home.
Just stop talking, Howard.
This isn't the reaction
I expected
when I told you
I was gonna be an astronaut.
What did you think
was going to happen?
Honestly? Sex.
Howard.
Do you realize
what a big deal this is?
What an honor it is to be
chosen to go into space?
Yeah, I get it.
I just wish you included me
in the decision.
We're supposed
to be partners.
to be a team.
I'm sorry. You're right.
Okay, let's try this again.
Bernadette, an opportunity
has come up
that impacts both of us,
and I'd like to discuss it.
Okay.
I've been offered
a chance to go up
to the International
Space Station for three weeks.
What are your thoughts on that?
Well, first of all, thank you
for including me
in the decision-making process.
Hey, we're a team.
(chuckles)
So, what do you think?
No.
No?
Why not?
Howard, my father
was a police officer.
We never knew
from one night to the next
if he was going
to come home alive.
It was horrible.
And I don't want to live
that way with you.
Hey, my father abandoned me
and my mother when I was 11.
We never saw him again.
Oh, boo-hoo,
you're not going to space!
Pretty cool about
Howard, huh?
Don't talk to me as if
nothing's happened between us.
And yes, it sure is, buddy.
For God's sake, will you stop
with the Schroer stuff.
Would you prefer
a simpler application
of Heisenberg's
uncertainty principle,
in which I could either
know where you are
or whether I like you,
but not both?
You never stop
talking, do you?
I don't understand.
What differences
does it make
if Leonard goes to
Wil Wheaton's party?
Wil Wheaton is
Sheldon's mortal enemy.
Mortal enemy?
Mm-hmm.
Sheldon, I know you're a bit
of a left-handed
monkey wrench, but...
you really have a mortal enemy?
In fact, I have 61 of them.
Would you like to see the list?
Oh, say no, say no,
say no, say no.
You just got off the list.
Would you like back on it?
This'll just take a moment.
It's on a five and a
quarter inch floppy.
A floppy disk?
Well, I started the
list when I was nine.
How did Wil Wheaton
get on the list?
- Oh! Oh, God!
- Oh! Come on!
As a child,
I loved Wesley Crusher,
Wil Wheaton's character
on Star Trek.
So, I drove for hours
by bus to a Star Trek convention
at which Wil Wheaton
was scheduled to appear,
so that I could get my Wesley
Crusher action figure signed.
But he never
showed, because
apparently,
it was cooler for him
to be the lower-left corner
on Hollywood Squares.
Oh, damn!
The floppy failed.
Well,
whoever was in charge
of quality control
at the Verbatim Corporation
in 1989,
congratulations,
you just made the list.
Howard?
Change your
mind about sex?
I'm still mad,
but I'll do it.
No, I've just
been thinking.
It doesn't matter
if I'm afraid for your safety.
I don't want
to be the person
who stands between you
and your dreams.
Really?
Really.
If going into space means
that much to you,
I will never say
another word about it.
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
So, sex now?
Okay.
I just forgot
to brush my teeth.
I'll be right back.
(rhythm and blues playing)
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ I'm ♪
♪ I'm not in love with you... ♪
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Over my dead body
my son goes into outer space!
I'm ready.
Wait, let me see
if I got this right.
You actually asked Bernadette
to leave your house
in the middle of the night?
What choice did I have?
She went behind my back
and turned my own mother
against me.
Wow. You're not only
our first astronaut.
You're also the first one
of us to kick a girl out of bed.
You're like a rock star.
Little bit.
I hate to say it,
but she did kind of betray you.
Interesting.
You see betrayal in others,
but not yourself.
Going to Wheaton's party
is not betraying you.
Oh, of course you would have
to believe that.
Evil always thinks
it's doing right.
"Excuse me, Stormtrooper.
These are the droids
you're looking for."
I'm going to a party.
I'm not turning R2-D2 and C-3PO
over to the empire!
Not yet.
So, what's gonna happen next?
Are you and Bernadette going
to break up?
I don't know.
If we're going
to get back together,
she's going to have
to apologize and accept
that I'm a grown man
who can make his own decisions.
Then she's going to have
to convince your mother
to let you go into space.
Obviously.
I had no choice.
I had to tell
his mother.
He can't go to space.
He's like a baby bird.
Do you know
he once got an asthma attack
from reading an old library
book?
You're kidding.
No, I was there that day.
Sheldon threw his back out
handing him that book.
I don't know
what I'm going to do.
I don't want
to break up over this.
Okay, why don't you just
tell him you made a mistake?
Do you guys think
it was a mistake?
Am I the bad guy in this?
It's not for
us to judge.
We're just here to provide
comfort and support
while you come to grips
with what a despicable thing
you've done.
Oh, God, you're right.
I took our love and threw it
under his bus-sized mother.
I need to apologize.
Well, that-that's good.
I'm glad you came to that.
But before you do, let me just
ask you a big picture question.
What?
Are you
100% positive you love and want
to marry Howard Wolowitz?
I do, with all my heart.
(clicks tongue)
Got it.
Just had to check.
He's great.
All right, Sheldon.
We're going to Wil's.
This is your
last chance.
No, Leonard,
this is your last chance.
One day,
a historian is going
to come to you and say,
"Is it true you were friends
with Dr. Sheldon Cooper?"
And you're going to have
to choke back a hot sob
of regret and humiliation
as you mumble,
"I was, but
"I chose to go to a party thrown
by the one kid
from Stand By Me
that no one remembers."
You want to drive?
Sure.
(door closes)
Hey, Sheldon?
Oh, good. You picked me,
you picked me.
No, I just got a
text from Stuart.
Brent Spiner is
at the party.
Brent Spiner?
Yes.
I don't care.
Really?
Brent Spiner,
Mr. Data himself.
You love him.
I did, but I think I've kind of
outgrown Star Trek.
You know, stock characters,
ludicrous plots, "beam me up."
What a load of hooey.
I'm going.
Live long and
prosper, Sheldon.
Yeah, even that.
You look like a dork.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, Bernadette's here!
Tell her I'm not home!
What kind of a schmuck play
is that?!
She can hear you shouting!
Can we talk?
You can. I have nothing to say.
All right.
I just wanted to tell you
I'm sorry I said something
to your mother.
I was gonna tell her eventually,
but you went behind my back.
I know. I'm sorry.
I got scared.
If you're gonna love me,
you're gonna have to
love the whole package:
the tenderhearted poet
and the crazy daredevil.
I know.
Well, don't say it if
you're not gonna mean it,
'cause I'm not just gonna
stop with the space station.
Yeah, I want to go to the
Moon, I want to go to Mars.
I want to take a one-man sub to
the lowest depths of the ocean.
Really?
You got seasick
on Pirates of the Caribbean.
Well, those big kids
were rocking it.
I just did what I did
because I love you so much,
and the thought of losing you
is more than I can handle.
Really?
You're my soul mate.
This is where you kiss me.
Right, right. (laughs)
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Make up all you want!
Your tuchis is not
leaving this planet!
Hey, you know
that beautiful actress who plays
the Borg Queen in First Contact?
- Yeah.
- Well, I just met her gynecologist!
What are you doing here?
Fighting for our friendship.
As peculiar and annoying
as you can be,
you're still my little buddy.
I'm not going
to let that end here tonight.
Now put down that drink, let's
meet Brent Spiner and go home.
Hey, Sheldon,
I'm so glad you made it.
I found something
I think you might like.
What I'd like is for him
to have a more depressing home.
This is quite lovely.
This is for you.
An original mint-in-package
Wesley Crusher action figure.
I remembered your story
about the time you went
to a convention
when you were a kid
to get one signed,
and I didn't show up.
Look at what I wrote.
"To Sheldon, sorry
this took so long.
Your friend, Wil Wheaton""
It's my last one.
I want you to have it.
Look, everyone.
Wil Wheaton is my friend!
Oh, wow.
I haven't seen one
of these in years.
Remember how we used
to make these things look
like they were masturbating?
Brent Spiner, what
have you done?!
That was an original
mint-in-package
Wesley Crusher
action figure
signed by my close personal
friend, Wil Wheaton.
Sorry, Slim.
I've got some Mr. Data dolls
in the trunk of my car.
You want me
to sign one for you?
You've already signed
something, Brent Spiner.
Your name on my list.
From this moment on,
you are my mortal enemy.
Don't worry. It doesn't take
up a whole lot of your time.
Come on, buddy.
Let's not waste another
second on this loser.
Love your house.
Can we get autographed dolls?
Sure.
20 bucks.
Ten.
$18.
$12.
$16.
Two for $30.
And you come
to my birthday party.
Done.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net