And reverse the spin
on the antiproton...
and gamma becomes alpha...
Multiplied by a matrix
of negative I comma zero...
And there we have it.
Conclusive proof that I am
absolutely worthless
after 9:00.
CREEPY VOICE:
Sheldon...
Hmm.
(electrical crackling, popping)
All right, all right.
I see what's going on.
A little pre-Halloween
hijinkery.
(moaning, chains rattling,
cackling)
A ghostly moan,
a rattling of chains,
a witch's cackle.
The trifecta
of haunted house clichés.
Instead of "Eek,"
I say, "Yawn."
CREEPY VOICE:
Sheldon...
Oh, the walls
are dripping blood,
which looks nothing like
a phenolphthalein indicator
exposed to a sodium carbonate
solution.
"See you in hell Sheldon."
The most frightening thing about
that is the missing comma.
Ah.
Okay, all right.
That one was clever.
Skeleton with phosphorous
on a zip line.
Come on out,
merry pranksters.
Take a bow.
(laughing)
You should've seen your face.
Yes, there's
nothing quite like
the slightly widened eyes
of mildly startled.
Come on, admit it.
We got you, Sheldon.
Please, fright depends
on an element of surprise.
The simple fact is,
because I am much smarter
than you,
and able to anticipate your
actions, it is highly unlikely
that you two rubes
could ever surprise me.
He's probably right.
We can't beat him.
He's just too smart.
Gentlemen.
(screams)
(laughing)
Who had money
on "faints"?
I had "pee his pants."
Hang on.
Looks like everyone's a winner.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory 5x07
The Good Guy Fluctuation
Original Air Date on October 27, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Oh. Watch out, Sheldon.
This little boy Casper
is a g-g-g-ghost!
Droll.
Not as droll as a grown man
passed out in a puddle
of his own urine.
That was pretty droll.
With a hint of ammonia.
Yes, enjoy your japes,
gentlemen.
You think you've poked fun
at a milquetoast academic.
Well, you've forgotten
one thing:
I am also a son
of the Lone Star state.
I'm Texas through and through.
And we know how to settle
scores down there.
If you doubt me, ask Mexico.
(quietly):
Hot girl, nine o'clock.
Don't everybody look at once!
What is she doing
in a comic book store?
I don't know, she might be lost.
Doesn't matter. Watch and learn.
- Hi.
Um... it-it-it...
Shut up.
Are you getting
this Next Men?
Uh, yeah. It's
issue number 21.
First appearance of Hellboy.
I know. I've been
looking for it for years.
Sorry.
Hey, if I pretended
to hit on you,
could I distract you
enough to sneak it away?
Yes, but you'd be using
your superpowers for evil.
Damn, I'm forbidden by my
Kryptonian father to do so.
I'm Alice.
Leonard.
You're very cute, Leonard.
Thanks. You, too. You know,
go ahead and take it.
No, no. No, no,
I-I did evil.
Would you be open
to a trade?
Uh, yeah, yeah,
sure, I guess.
Okay. Here.
This is my number.
Call me.
Sorry, palm's a little sweaty.
What's that word?
- Alice.
- Oh, right, your name.
That makes more
sense than "penis."
Later.
Did we just see you pick up
a girl in a comic book store?
'Cause if you did, you get
your picture up there
on the Wall of Heroes.
No, I don't think
I picked her up.
Besides, I have a girlfriend.
Doesn't matter. This is the
closest anyone's ever come.
You're going on
the wall, my friend.
Be sure to check the mail.
How many times are you gonna
tell me? What's with you?
Nothing. It's not suspicious
that I'm fixating.
It's consistent with
my personality.
Right.
Hey, guys.
More Halloween candy?
Didn't you just buy
a bunch of it yesterday?
Oh. Yeah.
That's gone.
It's a rough month when
Halloween and PMS
hit at the same time.
Leonard doesn't have time
to chat, he has to get the mail.
Will you relax?
I'll get it in a minute.
- How was work?
- Open the mail!
Excuse me.
A couple of circulars,
nothing important.
- What's with him?
- Hang on.
(air horn blares,
screams)
You might be from Texas,
but I'm from New Jersey.
(air horn blares)
Check it out.
Jim Lee drew this
of me two years ago
at Comic Con.
What are you wearing?
Well, you know,
it's Comic Con.
I'm Lion-O from
ThunderCats.
Wow, you must have
gotten so laid.
No. But Jessica Alba
did rub my furry belly.
(laughs)
Want to see a comic I draw?
You're kidding.
You have your own book?
Yeah. It's kinda
based on my life.
Cool.
Oh, look.
That's you having
sex with a guy
in the top half of
a Chewbacca costume.
Comic Con?
You'd think, but no.
You're very talented.
This is really good.
Did you do...
So, can I trade you
my comic for the Hellboy?
You can have my car.
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear...
Oh, dear, oh, dear.
Oh, dear... oh, dear.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
Purell, Purell,
Purell, Purell.
Good morning, Sheldon.
It is, isn't it?
(gasps)
Oh, bother.
Isn't that just
always the way?
You go to staple something,
and you're out of staples.
Gosh, I wish I'd known
that earlier today
when I was at Staples.
You have a thing of paper clips
right there.
No, no, I need something more
permanent to join these papers.
Say, don't you keep staples
in your top desk drawer?
I don't know. Maybe.
Be a lamb and check.
All right.
(gasps)
Who do we have here?
It's a snake.
A terrifying snake.
Oh, did some bad man
put us in a drawer?
Stop talking like that.
You've been rendered
speechless by fear.
Let's go to the biology lab and
find you some nice yummy mice.
I tried to scare an Indian
with a snake.
Come on, Cooper.
You're better than this.
(knocking)
It's open.
Hey, you got a minute?
Yeah, sure, come on in.
Thanks.
Want some mac and cheese?
No. Lactose. Gas.
- Glass of wine?
- No. Sulfites. Migraines.
Okay, well, I'd offer
you Halloween candy,
but that's gone.
So, what's up?
Okay, we used to go out, right?
Oh, my God, that's
where I know you from.
I'm dealing with a situation and
it's kind of about my love life,
so I know that might be weird
for us to talk about,
but in this area, as you know,
all my other friends
are just so stupid.
All right, what's going on?
So, you're okay
talking about this?
- Yes.
- You're sure it's not weird.
It's okay.
You know what, if you ever want
to talk to me about a problem
in your life with a guy,
then I would be fine with that.
Okay, good, because there's
this one guy I used to date
who's about to be force-fed
wine and cheese
if he doesn't get to the point.
Okay, uh...
here it is.
Is it cheating
if a guy has a girlfriend...
Yeah, probably.
Come on.
I'm sorry, go ahead.
I met this girl,
and she's great.
we have a lot in common.
Did you guys do it?
No. We just made out a little.
Oh, look at you, you bad boy.
Did you tell her
about Priya?
Well, I was gonna, but
there were too many
tongues in my mouth.
That's gross.
Here's the thing,
I-I'm not one of those guys
who sneaks around and sleeps
with more than one woman.
Well, good for you.
The problem is, I want
to be one of those guys.
So sleep with the new girl
and lie to Priya.
Oh, that's not who I am.
All right, then break it off
with the new girl.
Now, let's not do anything rash.
She's really hot.
If you like this girl so much,
why don't you just
end things with Priya?
Priya and I are in love.
I think we could
get married someday.
Leonard, you're looking for
a way to sleep with both women
and have everybody
be happy about it.
Now we're getting somewhere.
What does your gut tell you?
"Go ask Penny;
she'll know what to do."
Hello, Howard.
I've realized that you
scaring me was all in jest.
Allow me to say, job well done.
(buzzing, grunting)
(buzzing, grunting continue)
(buzzing stops)
(panting)
Perfect.
What are you doing?
Science. You
wouldn't understand.
Hey, well, see you.
I'm going out.
(exhales)
I thought you were
leaving the apartment.
Yeah, me, too.
I can't make up my mind.
Are you concerned
because the world is filled
with big dogs and bullies?
No. I'm having a moral crisis.
Well, if it's of
any help, I've read
all the great
moral philosophers,
including Dr. Seuss.
Oh, what the hell.
I'm supposed
to go see that girl
from the comic book store,
Alice, but I don't know
if I should, because
I'm going out with Priya,
but she's in India.
All right. So the topic at hand
is sexual fidelity.
Probably won't be relying
on Seuss here.
Although One Fish, Two Fish,
Red Fish, Blue Fish
might be
surprisingly applicable.
Go on.
Well...
they say
at the end of your life,
you regret the stuff
you didn't do
more than the stuff
that you did,
and I'm pretty sure Alice
is the stuff I want to do.
You know,
the German philosopher,
Friedrich Nietzsche,
believed that morality
is just a fiction used by the
herd of inferior human beings
to hold back
the few superior men.
That actually does help.
It's worth noting that
he died of syphilis.
Screw it,
I'm going.
On your way home,
will you pick up
some orange juice?
Do you mind?
I'm questioning
a lot of things
in my life right now.
Is one of those things
your fondness for orange juice?
No.
Great. Tropicana, no pulp.
Hey, Sheldon.
Who is it!
It's me, Sheldon, Mrs. Wolowitz.
That's not my mom,
it's Bernadette.
Really?
That's very unsettling.
Hi, Sheldon.
- Hi.
- What's up?
It just occurred to me that I
never formally congratulated you
on your pending nuptials.
So I hopped on
the first bus and hightailed it
down here to shake your hand.
Put 'er there,
you old so-and-so.
Well, I-I'm gonna
see you at work in...
12 hours-- don't you think it
could have waited until then?
Holy smoke,
why didn't I think of that?
You're a better man
than I, Howard Wolowitz.
You put 'er there,
you son of a gun!
Whatever.
(chuckles)
(buzzing)
My... oh...
it's...
Oh, my God, Howard!
What did you do?
It was a harmless
Halloween prank. Look.
Howard has a heart condition!
You know that!
Well, I thought
he made that up.
I-Isn't hypochondria a common
idiosyncrasy of Jewish people?
This is adrenaline--
we're gonna have
to inject it into his heart.
- We are?
- You are. I'm not strong enough
to get it through
his chest plate,
and we've only got one shot.
Oh, no! I can't!
Hurry!
We're running out of time!
- Okay.
- Just do it!
Oh, God!
One... two...
three!
Trick or treat, bubbeleh.
What?
(laughing)
No. You mean
this was all a ruse?
Oh, how could I be so stu...
(buzzing)
(yelling) uuu....
Mmm...
Damn it, I can't.
I can't do this.
Uh, is it my tongue stud?
'Cause if that
freaks you out,
you're in for a real
surprise later on.
No, no, no.
I-I can't do this.
Believe me,
I really want to.
But...?
But I kind of
have a girlfriend.
Are you kidding?
You're cool with you and me
just being friends, right?
(laughs)
I don't believe this.
Wait, I don't...
Which part?
I'm so stupid.
I thought for once
I'd met a good guy,
but you're just another jackass.
Oh, no, no, you
have it wrong.
No. I-I was going
to be a jackass, but
I stopped myself.
I stayed
a good guy, so...
I'm gonna pass on the sex.
But you should
know, that's not
a comment on your hotness
but on my goodness.
That's kind of my superpower.
I'm, like, Captain Good Guy.
(exhales)
It's okay.
Did the right thing.
You idiot!
Hey, Priya.
Hey, sweetheart.
How's it going?
Uh, not so good.
We have to talk.
Oh, sounds serious.
What's up?
Okay, uh...
here it is.
I met this girl
and I kissed her,
and I feel
terrible about it.
But it's done, it's never
gonna happen again.
And I am so, so sorry.
Leonard, relax.
It's okay.
It is?
Yeah, these things happen.
They happen to everybody.
Oh, my God, you are amazing.
I mean, I don't deserve you.
Wh-what do you mean "everybody"?
Leonard, I didn't know
if I should tell you,
but I kind of cheated
on you, too.
Kind of?
A couple of weeks ago,
I slept with my ex-boyfriend.
So, I guess we both messed up
a little.
No, no, I messed up a little.
You messed up a lot.
Well, it's not a competition.
Oh... yeah, it is,
and you won.
I-I-I'm sorry, I have to go.
I don't believe this.
(sighs)
(yelling)
Bazinga, punk.
Now we're even.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net