Hello.
visit tvshowslatest.blogspot.com to download Big Bang Theory
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
and welcome to
the premiere episode
of Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun with Flags.
Over the next 52 weeks,
you and I are going to explore
the dynamic world
of vexillology.
Hang on, Dr. C.
What's vexillology?
Vexillology is
the study of flags.
Cool.
I think I just
learned something.
Did you have fun doing it?
I'll say.
Fun and information are two
sides to this video podcast,
not unlike the only
two-sided state flag--
Oregon.
Oh, look.
Hello, Mr. Beaver.
In future episodes, we'll answer
some burning questions:
What's the only
non-rectangular flag?
What animal appears
most often on flags?
What animal appears second
And more.
Sweet!
Why are you waving
a white flag?
I'm surrendering...
to fun.
(laughs)
Now, today's episode of
Fun with Flags is not fun,
but it is important.
"Flags: you gotta know
how to hold 'em,
you gotta know
how to fold 'em."
Let's start by identifying
the parts of our flag.
This edge is the hoist,
and it's used to...
Excuse me,
sorry, excuse me.
Cut.
Did you not see
we are rolling?
Sorry. I'm having dinner
with Penny.
I have to get out of here.
And I have flag knowledge
that I have to
get out of here!
(sighs)
You okay?
No, I'm a little rattled.
But like the flag over
Fort Sumter, I'm still here.
And... take two.
Hello.
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
and welcome to
the premiere episode
of Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun with Flags.
Over the next 52 weeks,
you and I are going to explore
the dynamic world
of vexillology.
Hang on, Dr. Cooper.
What's vexillology?
Vexillology is...
why is there a face
on that flag?
It's Ferdinand T. Flag.
I thought he might help bring in
some younger viewers.
Confound it!
You're right, it's brilliant.
Let's take it from the top.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory 5x14
The Beta Test Initiation
Original Air Date on January 26, 2012
visit tvshowslatest.blogspot.com to download Big Bang Theory
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
That was a really
nice dinner.
I'm glad you asked me
out again.
Me, too; I missed you.
You see me all the time.
You sure you just
don't miss the sex?
Well, yeah, sex with you
is pretty great.
Have you ever tried it?
I have.
You are not wrong.
I just think if we're
gonna try dating again,
we should take things slow.
Oh, I can take it slow.
Did I ever tell you
about my first girlfriend
in high school,
Karen Berberick?
To this day she doesn't know
we were going out.
Made it easier on her
when I broke things off.
Okay, well, maybe
not that slow.
How about this,
are you familiar with
the typical development
for computer software?
You know, just for fun,
let's say I'm not.
Before an application
is released,
they give it a trial run.
W-We could do that.
And if we hit a rough spot,
instead of getting mad,
just say, "Hey, we found a bug,"
and we report it
so it can be fixed.
You mean like a beta test?
Well, technically,
this would be an alpha test.
A beta test requires people
that weren't involved
in the development
of the appli...
Seriously, do I not get credit
for knowing beta test?
No, you should.
Absolutely.
That was me being pedantic.
That's our first bug.
You reported it.
I can fix that.
See? This is good.
All right.
Let's give it a shot.
Great. You keep a list,
I'll keep a list.
At some point, we'll exchange.
Okay.
- Good night, Leonard.
- Night.
Attaboy, Hofstadter.
Nothing gets the ladies hotter
than software development
analogies.
Hey, I'm back.
SHELDON:
Cut.
(sighs)
Take 47.
Here's an interesting
fact about flags.
I will take that action.
The flags
of Liechtenstein and Haiti
were identical by coincidence,
a fact that wasn't discovered
until they competed
against each other
at the 1936 Olympics.
And thankfully,
their embarrassment
was overshadowed
by the rise of Fascism.
Let's see the new phone.
I stopped on the way to work.
Hey, do you want to peel
the plastic off with me?
Really?
Me?
That's, like, the best part.
Grab a corner.
(chuckles)
Whoa, what's your
hurry, cowboy?
Savor the moment.
Oh, yeah.
Speaking of cowboys,
do you know what country has not
one but two cows on its flag?
The tiny
landlocked nation of Andorra.
Oh, the next classic episode
of Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun with Flags
is writing itself.
Oh, let me try
the voice recognition.
Hey, I let you peel the plastic,
don't get greedy.
(chimes)
Hello?
SIRI: Hello.
(chimes)
What's your name?
My name? It's Siri.
(chuckling)
Look at that.
There's finally a woman in
your life you can talk to.
(chimes)
Are you single?
I don't have a marital status,
if that's what you're asking.
Yeah, you're right,
that's too personal.
We hardly know each other.
(chimes)
How about a cup of coffee?
I've found six coffee shops.
Three of them
are fairly close to you.
I will see you
gentlemen later.
(exhales)
She is gonna break his heart.
(ethereal music plays on TV)
For someone
who has a machine
that can travel anywhere
in time and space,
Doctor Who sure does have
a thing for modern-day London.
Careful, it's that kind of sass
that can get a person uninvited
to this year's Who Con.
Uh, we're not counting
this as a date,
are we?
Um, I'm not sure,
but I think the right
answer here is "no."
Bug report: When a guy asks me
to spend time with him,
maybe he plans something
a little more interesting
than hanging out at home,
watching TV.
Even Doctor Who?
Even Doctor Who.
SHELDON:
All right, that's it.
(snaps fingers)
Who Con-- you're out.
Okay, bug report taken.
Next time I will
have a better plan
for our evening's activity.
Well, thank you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Oh, wait, here,
almost forgot.
Here.
What's this?
My bug report to you.
Well, that's quite
a list you got there.
It's color coded.
Oh.
Uh, red means
"fix right away."
Yellow is
"eh, whenever you
get a chance."
And green,
is "I could probably
learn to live with it."
There's a key down
here at the bottom.
It's neat, huh?
(smacks lips)
Yep.
So, have a good night.
(smacks lips)
Yep.
Look at that.
Some day, we will tell
future generations
that dating used to be hard.
What's baffling me
is what you
could've possibly put
on the list.
"Hair too golden"?
"Laugh too musical"?
"World too much a better place
for her mere presence in it"?
How about "constantly talks
with food in her mouth"?
Her heart's full of love, no
one cares what's in her mouth.
(chimes)
So, Siri, what's happening?
How are you?
(chimes)
I am well.
What are you doing right now?
(chimes)
What am I doing?
I'm talking with you.
(chimes)
You have a beautiful voice.
(chimes) Thank you,
it's nice to be appreciated.
I bet it is.
(chimes)
Why don't women like me?
Let me check on that.
How about a Web search
for "Why don't women like me?"
No need.
I've already done that.
(chimes)
Siri, do you have a last name?
My name is Siri.
Ah, one name.
Like, uh, Cher,
Madonna, Adele.
All the women who rock me.
(chimes) My name is Rajesh,
but you can call me Raj.
(chimes) Would you like me
to call you Raj?
(chimes) I'd like you
to call me sexy.
(chimes)
From now on, I'll call you sexy.
Okay?
Okay!
(chimes)
Siri, I'm in the mood for gelato.
(chimes) I found ten restaurants
whose reviews mention gelato.
Seven of them
are fairly close to you.
(chimes)
Thank you, darling.
(chimes) You are most certainly
welcome, sexy.
Well done,
Dr. Koothrappali.
I'm sorry?
You've taken a great
evolutionary leap
by abandoning human interaction
and allowing yourself
to romantically bond
with a soulless machine.
Kudos.
I haven't bonded with it.
Oh, no, of course.
I understand.
You're afraid the world
isn't ready for your taboo love.
Your secret's safe with me.
It's just a phone.
Cooper.
Kripke.
Heads up.
Professor Rothman urinated in
the particle physics wab again,
so we're going to move up
his wetirement party.
Fwiday, 5:00-- pot wuck.
Thanks, Barry.
(chimes)
Siri, remind me
Friday morning
to make my famous popovers.
(chimes)
All right, I'll remind you.
You got Siwi, huh?
Voice wecognition
on that thing is terrible.
Wook.
(chimes) Siwi, can you wecommend
a westauwant?
(chimes)
SIRI: I'm sorry, Bawwy.
I don't understand
"wecommend a westauwant."
(chimes)
Wisten to me.
Not westauwant; westauwant.
(chimes)
I don't know what you mean
by "not westauwant; westauwant."
See? Total cwap.
You suck, Siwi.
Hey, don't talk to her
like that.
She's a lady.
Well, that wady
took high-wes pictures
of my junk wast night
for Cwaigswist.
Waiter.
PENNY:
It's open.
Hey.
You ready to go?
Yeah, hang on.
Let me just finish this chapter.
Can you finish it later?
No, I can't.
Reading books is a big part of
my life now because, you know,
we'd have more fun things
to talk about if I read more.
Great. Good. Great.
What are you reading?
Two Weeks to Rock Hard Abs.
They kind of spoil the ending
right in the name of that,
don't they?
All right.
Look, just remember
how this works.
We don't get mad
about these things.
Uh, speaking of which,
I've addressed
your bug report on
my date planning.
Got a really fun
evening for you.
It's kind of a surprise.
All right. Terrific.
Well, let me just go find a pair
of shoes that aren't so tall.
We wouldn't want you
to feel like you were
out for a walk with your mommy.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh.
Here's my list
for you-- right there.
(clears throat)
All right, fair enough.
I certainly can be quieter
when we kiss.
I thought it was an expression
of passion,
but if it's coming across
as "juicy and weird,"
who wants that?
Uh, uh... I'm sorry.
Can you be more specific
on how my eyebrows are "stupid"?
Na, never mind.
It's right here.
Good timing.
Dinner's almost ready.
Great.
Oh, smells
amazing in here.
Oh, what are we eating?
Oh, an exotic little treat.
I was just talking to Siri
about Peking duck,
and she said she knew
about four Chinese grocers,
two of which were
fairly close to me.
Her spontaneity
is contagious.
Who's Siri?
Is he dating somebody new?
Yes. His phone.
Oh.
Is that cute
or creepy?
Uh-huh.
Can I pour you
some wine?
I think you'll
enjoy it.
The traditional
choice
with Peking duck
is a sauvignon blanc,
but Siri suggested
an off-dry Riesling.
I wasn't sure,
but I didn't want
to have an argument
with her in the middle
of Trader Joe's.
Now, what should we
put Siri in for dinner?
Leopard, sparkles, or
to paraphrase Coco Chanel,
you can never go wrong
with a little black case?
(chimes)
Siri, play some smooth jazz.
Playing smooth jazz.
(Kenny G music playing)
Oh, my God, Kenny G?!
This woman can read me
like a book.
I can't believe
I bought my soul mate
at Glendale Galleria.
(whispering): I don't know if
I want to stay.
(gunfire)
This is amazing.
How did you even get
this idea?
I called your dad.
I asked him what things
you liked to do
when you were a kid.
This seemed easier
than getting a cow out here
so you could tip it.
Okay, you're kind of
really great.
You mean for a person
whose neck massages
feel like an eagle is trying
to carry you to its nest?
Okay, bug report.
I just complimented you.
You should take it and shut up.
Right. Sorry, sorry.
And stop apologizing
all the time.
Right. Sorry.
All right,
let's shoot stuff.
You want me to show you
what to do?
I play a lot of
Grand Theft Auto.
I think I know how
to handle a gat.
Wow. You are cute
when you get all gangsta.
(gunshot)
(yells)
Ooh!
(yelling)
(whining)
(panting)
So, I've got a
gunshot wound.
That's pretty
bad-ass.
No, you've got a Reebok
with a gunshot wound
and an ouchie on your pinkie toe.
(laughs)
Hello? They gave
me a Band-Aid.
Hospitals do not
issue Band-Aids
unless it is
medically necessary.
That is the law.
(laughs)
Well, thank you
for a really cool evening.
Thank you for hiding
my Star Wars socks
at the emergency room.
(laughs)
Is it a good time to
evaluate the beta test
and see where we stand?
Things are looking good.
So, are we still
taking things slow?
Because a gunshot
wound today,
and last week, I slammed my
thumb in the kitchen drawer.
We don't know how
much time I have.
Good night, you.
(Bavarian music playing)
Guten Tag, das YouTube.
Ich bin ein Bavarian.
Und ich bin eine pretzel!
Und dis is Sheldon
Cooper Presents: Fun...
Mit...
Flags.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
First door on the left.
Thank you.
(sighs)
Dave, I found six vacuum cleaner
repair shops in your area.
Four are fairly close to you.
(clearing his throat)
Hello, sexy.
What can I help you with?
If you'd like to make
love to me, just tell me.
(guttural utterances)
I'm sorry. I don't
understand...
(guttural utterances)
No!
www.tvsubtitles.net