Gentlemen, I think
I've come up with a
fun way to get young people
interested in science.
Physics Mad-Libs.
- Now, give me a number.
- Five.
Uh-huh.
And an irrational constant.
"E."
And a funny Greek letter.
Gamma.
I said funny.
Upsilon?
Good one.
And an electrical charge.
Positive.
(laughs) Perfect.
SHELDON:
Okay. Get this.
(clears throat)
"Professor Jones told the
symposium he had a new method
"for calculating
the mass of a muon.
Five times the limit of (laughs)
'E' to the upsilon as..."
(laughing)
(clearing throat):
Okay. No, no.
I'll start over.
"Professor..."
(cracking up)
I haven't seen him
laugh that hard
since the day Leonard
made that multiplication error.
Oh, Oh, Lord, that
multiplication error!
(laughing): He thought
he carried the one.
But he didn't.
(laughing)
It's not funny.
That mistake got published.
Stop! I'm going to wet myself!
Hey, guys, guys, President
Siebert is headed this way.
I wonder
what he wants.
Doesn't look happy,
so I'm guessing
he wants to talk to Sheldon.
Dr. Cooper?
Told ya.
Oh, President Siebert,
I assume you'd like to respond
to one of the suggestions
I put in the box by your office.
No, and stop installing
suggestion boxes everywhere.
You don't like
written suggestions.
You don't like when I give them
to you while we're urinating
in the men's room.
If I didn't know you any better,
I'd say that you're one of those
stubborn people
who are not open to suggestions.
Dr. Cooper, the physics
department chair tells me
you're refusing
to take your vacation.
I don't need a vacation.
You're obligated to take one.
And I'd also like you to know
the most-often received
suggestion in my suggestion box
you installed without asking me
is "Can Dr. Cooper
take a vacation?"
Okay, settled, then.
I'll see y'all of you Monday,
except for you.
But if I don't come into work,
what am I supposed
to do with myself?
Read, rest, travel.
I hear Afghanistan
is nice this time of year.
Sarcasm?
No. You should go.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory 5x16
The Vacation Solution
Original Air Date on February 9, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ That tonight's
gonna be a good night ♪
♪ And tonight's
gonna be a good, good night ♪
♪ Tonight's the night, uh, uh ♪
♪ Let's live it up, uh ♪
♪ I got my money,
let's spend it up... ♪
Good Lord!
Would you stop
that caterwauling!
(sighs)
What the hell are you doing?!
Bleeding from my ears.
What are you doing
hiding back there?
I'm sneaking into work.
Now, if the guard
at the university asks
what's under the blanket,
you tell him
it's some lobster traps.
- Lobster traps?
- Yes.
That's how Velma and Scooby
smuggled Shaggy
into the old lighthouse.
What are you going to do when
you get to the university?
People are going
to recognize you.
Will they, Leonard?
Fine. Just get back
under your blanket,
and I'll drive you there.
And no more singing.
Fine.
SHELDON: I have GPS on my phone.
I know you turned around.
I'm so glad you
talked Howard
out of having your wedding
invitations in Klingon.
Turn it over.
I'm hoping my relatives
think it's Hebrew.
(sighs) This is
really happening.
I'm gonna be a maid of honor.
I'm gonna wear a beautiful dress
and walk down that aisle
and, finally, I will
have my special day.
You mean my special day?
They're gonna need an extra-
large veil for somebody's head.
If I ever actually
ever get married.
Why wouldn't you?
My dad...
'Cause I make a lot more
money than Howie,
he's putting a lot of pressure
on me to get a prenup.
Ouch.
Yeah. Howie's gonna freak out.
Parental pressure
can be daunting.
I remember the battle with my
mother about shaving my legs.
Last year, I finally gave in
and let her do it.
I just don't know how I'm gonna
break it to him.
You know, I'm a big believer
in breaking bad news
to a guy when you're
in bed with him.
That's how I told
my high school boyfriend
I slept with his brother.
That's how I told
his brother the same thing.
I don't know, I don't want
to manipulate him with sex.
Oh, sweetie,
that's what sex is for.
You know, the connection
between marriage and money
is nothing new.
In fact, the term "wed" referred
to the money and livestock
that the groom paid
the bride's father.
For example,
you're adorable,
intelligent
and a good earner.
I could conservatively see
you going for
at least two oxen and a goose.
You would fetch
a unicorn.
Sheldon, there are a million
great vacations you could take.
What about Hawaii?
Hawaii is a former leper colony
on top of an active volcano
where the disappointing ending
to Lost was filmed.
Mahalo for nothing, Hawaii.
How about Florida?
They got Cape Canaveral,
they got Disney,
they got my Aunt Ida
and the world's largest
collection of diabetic candy.
Plus, if you get sweaty enough,
her plastic-covered furniture
is like a flume ride.
My family took a trip
to Florida when I was a child.
A seagull stole a hot dog
from me on the beach.
I got the message.
You know, if I had a week off,
I'd go back
to the Two Bunch Palms Resort
and Spa in the desert.
I tell you, an hour on the
massage table with Trevor,
and you'll feel like
you were born without bones.
I don't think I could ever
let a guy give me a massage.
Really? What was I doing
to your neck last night
while you were playing X-Box?
It's like I'm living
in a dictatorship.
"You must take a vacation,
you must have fun,
you must enjoy life."
I don't think you have
a good handle on dictatorships.
Sheldon, everybody
takes vacations.
One time they tried to make
Richard Feynman take a vacation,
but he chose instead
to expand his mind
and learn something new.
He went to work
in his friend's biology lab.
Richard Feynman was a famous
American physicist,
part of the Manhattan Project.
Everyone in the world of science
knows who Richard Feynman was.
Now you do, too.
Oh! I have a
brilliant idea.
Amy's a biologist.
I'll go work in her lab.
Isn't that just Feynman's idea?
Ten seconds ago, you
never heard of him.
Now you're an expert.
Hey.
- Hey, you.
- Is that your laundry?
You only have, like,
six things in there.
Yeah, I didn't have
any quarters,
so I've been sneaking stuff
into other people's
loads all day.
Hey, if I tell
you something,
will you promise
not to tell anybody?
It doesn't matter what I say,
you're gonna tell me anyway.
What? That
is not true.
Bernadette wants
a prenup.
Wow. That's rough.
So you're saying if I
became a famous movie star,
we got married,
you wouldn't sign a prenup?
Absolutely not.
If I'm gonna be stuck
at home with the kids
while you're on location
cheating on me
with Ryan Gosling...
then Leonard gots
to get paid.
So, you think
about us getting married?
I think about
a lot of things.
I think about us
getting married,
breaking up.
Once in a while, I think
about how I didn't leave
a note on that Mercedes
I dinged in the parking
lot last month,
but then I have a glass of wine
and it passes.
Joke all you want,
but you think about it.
Well, tell you
one thing,
if I ever do get married,
no Klingon invitations.
Good luck catching a man
with that attitude.
Boy, oh, boy!
This vacation is off
to a wonderful start.
The smell of formaldehyde...
the whir of the centrifuge,
the distant chatter
of lab animals
being dispatched
for dissection.
Mm, I can already feel
my cares just melting away.
I'm excited to work
with my boyfriend.
It's gonna be romantic.
Way to kill the mood.
Come on, Sheldon.
We can be like Marie Curie
and her husband, Pierre,
who spent their days working
side by side,
bathed in the glow of their love
and the radium
that ultimately killed her.
Screw Beauty and the Beast;
that's the love story
Disney should tell.
Okay, what do we start with?
Maybe splicing some
genes, clone a sheep,
perhaps grow a human ear
on a mouse's back?
Ha-ha, I'm a freak!
Oh, I'm gonna
be doing
some brain stem histology
while you put yourself
on the business end
of a sponge
and wash those beakers.
Wash those bea...
Oh, I get it, a little
hazing for the new fella.
Yeah, I'd better keep
and eye out for, what,
shoe polish on
the microscope,
or mad cow disease in my
grilled cheese sandwich?
No, I just need
those beakers washed.
Hippity-hop,
quick like a bunny.
Wha...? Excuse
me, you have
Dr. Sheldon Cooper
in your lab.
You're gonna make
him do the dishes?
That's like asking
the Incredible Hulk
to open a pickle jar.
Sheldon, you've never worked
in a lab like this before.
You have no experience
in the field of biology.
I have plenty of
experience in biology.
I bought a Tamagotchi
in 1998.
And...
it's still alive.
Let's do this.
- Where's Howard?
- No "Hi, Raj"?
No "How are you, Raj?"
Just straight to "Where's the
other white guy?"
I'm sorry.
So, listen,
I heard something about him.
Can you keep it between us?
Ooh, gossip.
When I first got here,
I thought you Americans
really gossiped around
the water cooler.
So I hung out there
for, like, a month,
but the only gossip I ever heard
was about some creepy guy
hanging out by the water cooler.
Bernadette wants
to get a prenup.
Oh, that's a shame--
he's gonna be devastated.
I never know what to do
in these situations.
Should I give
him a heads-up?
Hmm. I'm gonna
give you the same advice
I yell at the TV when the
Bachelor's handing out roses.
Follow your heart.
Check it out.
Look at the size of that
Rice Krispie Treat!
Same price. (chuckles)
Hey, Howard, I need
to tell you something.
I know, it's not
on my wedding diet.
I don't care.
Uh, l-listen, I...
heard that Bernadette's thinking
about asking you for a prenup.
A prenup?
(laughs) Wow.
What are you gonna do?
I... don't know.
Follow your heart.
You know what, it's...
not a big deal.
She makes more money than me.
She wants to protect
her financial interests.
It's completely reasonable.
Good. That's a healthy attitude.
Yeah, actually,
it's good for both of us.
I have assets to protect, too.
Like what?
I've got some rare comic books.
The Vespa's almost paid off.
And Ma and I have a primo double
cemetery plot at Mt. Sinai
right near the guy who played
Mr. Roper on Three's Company.
Mr. Roper's dead?!
You can't just spring
that on a guy!
Here you go.
This is now
the only lab
with glassware washed
by a man with two doctorates
and a restraining order
signed by Carl Sagan.
Soap spots. Wash 'em again.
Y... You're
being ridiculous!
Those are perfectly clean.
Sheldon, this beaker used
to contain cerebral spinal fluid
from an elephant
that died of syphilis.
If it's, in fact,
perfectly clean,
drink from it.
Biologists are mean.
All right,
perhaps this task
will be a little bit
more up your alley.
I need you to count
the bacteria spores
on these petri dishes.
There was something wrong
with that detergent.
That was way too bubbly.
I'm sure it was.
I intend to write
that soap company
a strongly worded letter.
Yeah, good for you.
Now, start counting.
You know what this place needs?
A suggestion box.
366...
367...
How's it going?
How's counting going?
When I was in
kindergarten,
I recited pi
to a thousand places
for the school talent show.
I think I got this.
Great.
Aw, nuts!
One...
This is preposterous!
I think you're
giving me these tasks
because you're afraid
if you give me
anything meaningful to do,
I'll show you up.
Really?
Is that what you think?
Yes, that's what I think.
And I'm super smart,
so it's probably true.
Hey, I've been training
in the field
of neurobiology for 12 years.
You've been here
for three hours,
and you've spent one of them
in the bathroom.
I'm sorry!
It takes me a while
to get things going
on an unfamiliar toilet.
Sheldon, I've given you
the simplest things to do,
and you haven't done
one of them right.
Maybe that's because
I'm not being challenged.
It's the same reason
Einstein failed math.
Maybe the math was
too bubbly for him.
You think you're doing science
by cutting up that brain?
They could do the same
thing at any Quiznos.
And they'd offer
to toast it for me, too.
Okay, smart guy.
I'm about to remove
the locus coeruleus,
which is incredibly
delicate work.
Have at it.
All right.
I'm no stranger to
a little gray matter.
Locus coeruleus.
You're getting warmer--
it is, indeed, in the brain.
Hope your hands
are steady.
It's the width
of a single hair.
But this is just biology,
so I'm sure it's no problem
for a genius like you.
It's not. I'll have you know,
in the field of physics,
we work with particles so small,
they make fat jokes
about the locus coeruleus.
I.e., when your locus coeruleus
sits around the house,
it sits around the house.
Oh... are we nervous,
Dr. Cooper?
No.
What you see
is a man trembling
with confidence.
Does a locus coeruleus
normally bleed that much?
No. But your thumb does.
Oh, dear.
Yeah, you're a biologist.
What are you doing here?
I'm on vacation.
Social convention dictates
that I let my hair down
at a local watering hole.
Social convention is stupid.
What happened
to your thumb?
You know, I have
ten fingers and ten toes.
If I tell you a story
about each one of them,
we'll be here all day--
let's just move on.
What can I get you?
Ah, seeing as I'm on vacation,
uh, piña colada
seems appropriate.
Extra pineapple slices,
extra whipped cream,
extra cherries, extra umbrellas,
and, uh, hold the rum.
Don't let me have
too many of those.
Hey, what are you
guys doing here?
We're grown men;
we drink at bars.
No and no.
Everything okay
with you and Bernadette?
(chuckles):
Oh, yeah, sure.
You and Amy? Good?
Oh, better
than good.
You know those girls text me
every detail of their lives
as it happens.
I'm not signing a prenup.
All right, Howard Wolowitz,
listen up.
You sign anything
she puts in front of you,
because you are
the luckiest man alive.
If you let her go,
there is no way
you can find anyone else--
speaking on behalf of all women,
it is not gonna happen;
we had a meeting.
And you, a grown man
fainting at the sight
of a little blood.
Excuse me,
this is a fairly
substantial wound.
You...
(heavy thud)
(light tapping)
SHELDON: Amy? Amy?
Amy?
What do you want?
I was kind of hoping
I could continue vacationing
in your laboratory.
After all, I did book
the whole week.
Do you honestly think you
can just waltz back in here
after the way
you behaved yesterday?
I was not myself.
I had lost a lot of thumb blood.
That's not an apology.
That is your opinion.
I want a real apology.
I'm sorry that you
weren't able to...
No.
...that my genius...
...that the
soap was...
Sheldon.
Fine.
Sorry.
You're forgiven.
Now, if you want to stay,
get started on those beakers.
They're still dirty
from yesterday.
Next year I'm
going to Epcot.
Are you mad at me?
No. I'm not
mad at you.
I just...
wish you would have come to me,
so I didn't have to hear it
through the nerd-vine.
So, what are
we gonna do?
(sighs)
You really want me
to sign a prenup?
I don't know.
My dad's pretty insistent
on it, though.
Why don't I talk to
your dad, man-to-man?
Really?
Oh, that'd be so great!
Done.
I should probably give you a
heads-up about a couple of things.
Even though he's retired
from the police force,
he still carries his gun.
But don't worry,
he won't shoot it.
It's more
of a fashion statement.
Okay.
And just to be safe,
when you talk to him,
don't bring up Jimmy Carter,
gardeners,
foreign people, homosexuals,
Sean Penn, Vatican II,
gun control, organic food,
the designated hitter rule,
recycling or the fact
that you're Jewish.
Got it, got it.
Will you e-mail me
that list?
So the thing
to watch for,
if he's shouting at you,
you're okay,
but if he starts
to get real quiet,
leave as quickly as you can
without making eye contact.
Not in a straight line-- throw
some zigs and zigs in there.
You know, this
isn't that pressing.
Why don't I talk to him
about it in May.
In May you're gonna be on
the International Space Station.
They got a phone.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net