Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
_
Since I got here,
you're my third contempt of court.
First one was a contested
traffic ticket.
The guy cursed at the judge.
The second one was a lawyer.
- What'd he do?
- He cursed at the judge.
You're my first reporter.
I'm Will.
I'd shake your hand...
I know who you are.
So the traffic ticket,
he was just here for a night.
But the lawyer was here
for a weekend.
Three nights,
and you could tell he was starting to go a little...
You know, it affected him.
You're gonna be
locked in a cage now,
and it's not a natural thing.
Go ahead.
That's yours over here.
- You got toiletries?
- I'm sorry?
You didn't bring toiletries?
Uh, no, I didn't.
I'll bring you toothpaste
and a brush.
I can bring you a book
from the library if you want.
- You might get the whole weekend.
- Sure, thanks.
You'll be fine.
_
You fish.
I'm sorry?
You're a fisherman.
Yeah. No.
Not in a long time.
That's a nice fish.
- Yeah.
- Eight pounds.
You know,
I don't really remember.
And that's your father
there next to you?
- Yeah.
- That's a wholesome picture.
Looks like it came
with the frame.
- Yeah.
- And that's your wife?
Yeah, her name is MacKenzie.
- Whew, she's a knockout.
- She is.
- It's okay if I say that, right?
- Sure.
And those are your, what?
Your friends, your colleagues?
Yeah,
they're some of the people I work with.
We work close together.
- You have to explain it to me one more time.
- Really?
'Cause every time you say it,
it sounds like you're in here voluntarily.
I promise you, I'm not.
But you can walk out
any time you want.
No, I can't.
I can only walk out
if I reveal the identity
of a source.
- You want to read your book.
- I don't want to be rude.
You didn't ask me what I was in for.
I appreciate that.
Domestic battery.
Nine women on the jury.
My PD was a woman,
so she wasn't exactly my champion.
The prosecutor was a woman.
The judge was a woman.
I mean,
is that even constitutional?
The PD wanted me to plea...
Six months.
But I wanted to fight it...
Two years.
That wasn't your first offense,
though.
How do you know?
You wouldn't have gotten two years for
domestic battery if it was your first...
It was my third.
Strike three.
Oh, are you judging me now?
'Cause a judge just did that.
I don't need it.
- No.
- Yeah, you are.
I have an idea.
Tell me the name of the source.
I didn't make
a pledge or anything.
I'll tell it to them on the
condition they let us both go.
It's a hell of a plan.
Or I could just shake
the name out of you.
Stand up.
I want you to see that I
got four inches on you
and you're giving up 30 pounds.
I'm not your wife.
Raise your hands
above your hips
and I'll knock you
the fuck into next week.
Your father was a drunk,
wasn't he?
You aren't a consumer,
you're a citizen.
You aren't an audience,
you're an activist.
You aren't a viewer,
you're ACN.
You are ACN.
Which one of you...
It's as offensive as I thought it
was gonna be when I heard about it.
- Offensive to whom?
- Me. And him.
And Will and Sloan and everyone
who works here and you.
We are ACN.
It's a slogan.
It doesn't mean anything.
First, I wouldn't be relieved that our
new slogan doesn't mean anything.
- I meant...
- But it isn't a slogan.
It's a statement
of our new direction.
We're gonna cover the conversation
because this is just the first one.
Next one's gonna show
citizen journalists
filing stories
from the Coffee Bean.
- Don?
- It looks like urine.
It doesn't.
You're just complaining for the sake of it.
The best graphics house
in the UK
was paid $700,000
to build that spot.
I don't mean the animation.
U-R-A-C-N.
Our brains are trained to see
groups of letters as a word
and visually that group of
letters looks like urine.
Maybe if we separate
the U and the R.
Maybe,
but the best you can hope for
is something with the gravitas
of a vanity license plate.
- Maybe we should ask people to vote.
- After all, they are ACN.
- You know, Mac...
- Young people know when they're being patronized.
Everybody knows when
they're being patronized.
I've been hearing this
for 52 days.
Because in 52 days,
I've put three Twitter
monitors on our set.
Passing weather systems are reported
like al-Qaeda sleeper cells.
And a total of 84 air minutes have
been spent on the mayor of Toronto
while zero minutes have been
spent on the mayor of Detroit
whose city is about two
minutes away from bankruptcy.
Also in that 52 days,
we've gone from fourth
to third in households
and second in the demo.
In seven weeks,
the average age of our audience
has dropped three years.
And we did all that while
still managing to cover
a military takeover in Egypt
and most recently,
a pretty big scandal involving the NSA.
We've got two reporters at the
Moscow Airport right now.
Two. So can you do me
a favor and not worry
that the world's
most benign promo
is a threat to democracy?
- Sure.
- You?
- Can I have a second?
- Yeah.
So, the Princeton story.
The website.
There is an epidemic
of campus sexual assaults
in this country.
It's a perfectly
legitimate story.
In fact, it's an important one,
so what's your fucking problem?
I agree.
I just don't know
how to do the story.
- I don't understand.
- I don't know how to do it. I'm looking for some guidance.
You interview the student
with the website.
You interview one of the guys who's been accused.
Why is it complicated?
Well,
it's complicated for a lot of reasons,
and one of them is that Pruit
wants them both in the studio.
- He told you that?
- He called me.
He shouldn't be speaking
directly to you.
And he shouldn't be
making those decisions.
But if that's what he wants,
why don't you just do it?
Well, like I said,
I don't know how to.
Bullshit.
You do know how.
And if you don't,
I need to hire someone who does, man.
Okay?
Yeah.
Anything else?
No.
Anything happen over the
weekend I should know about?
Not much.
Dilma Rousseff pledged
to speak with protestors.
- The House voted down the Farm Bill.
- Yeah, I saw that.
France is sending Syrian rebels
17.6 tons of medical aid.
I'm sure that's going to get
where it's supposed to go.
A woman named Lilly M. Hart
shot herself in the mouth
on the steps in front
of the Justice Department.
We're not sure what
she was protesting,
but her bio had a lot of gun
control advocacy in it.
She was protesting guns
by shooting herself?
The FBI isn't releasing
any information right now.
- You mean DC Police.
- No, the FBI is handling it.
- Why?
- They won't release that information either.
Anything else?
Kim and Kanye named
their baby North.
There's our top story.
What was her name?
North. North West.
No, the woman who shot
herself in front of the DOJ.
Lilly Hart.
Again, I don't know how...
What?
She wasn't protesting guns.
They said it was an emergency.
Is everything okay?
Do we have attorney-client privilege,
you and me?
- I'm not your lawyer.
- What if you were?
Then we would have
that privilege.
I'm hiring you right now
on a $20 retainer.
- Do I need to sign something?
- No. What's going on?
I know the name of the source.
I've known since the party after
the Correspondents' Dinner.
And the day before yesterday,
she shot
and killed herself on
the steps outside the DOJ.
The woman...
She was the source?
Yeah.
Who else knows the name?
Neal, obviously, Will, and I.
That's it.
- Not the DC Police?
- I think they must...
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Lasenthal on the phone.
You know what?
Your husband is getting
out of jail today.
_
I was just chewed out for
10 minutes by Erin Andrews.
- Why?
- She was accosted by paparazzi last night
coming out of Man of Steel
at the El Capitan in LA.
Paparazzi were coming
out of the El Capitan?
- She...
- She was coming.
She'd just seen the movie and
waiting for her were a pack of paparazzi.
Got it.
Why was she chewing you out?
I'm the one here
she knows the best.
Didn't she have
an affair with Will?
It wasn't an affair.
Neither of them were married.
No, that didn't happen.
Will's in jail at the moment.
And none of this is the point.
The paparazzi knew she was in there
because of our creepy stalker app.
I'm coming to you
as my superior,
which I mean only in a sense
of our organizational chart,
and pleading with you
to have what's his name...
- Bree.
- Bree shut down the app.
Mac's been fighting
that battle for six weeks.
- And what have you been doing?
- Just, you know, my job.
Which should now include getting
the assassin's helper taken down.
- I'm on it.
- When?
Well, I'm in the middle of a tricky...
Now.
- Right now.
- There you go.
Excuse me, Bree.
Excuse me.
Hey, easy.
- I just wanted to talk to you about something.
- You are?
He's Don Keefer, executive producer...
You know who he is.
- And you run our website until Neal Sampat's back.
- I wanted to...
I'm senior editor of ACN Digital,
if you're going to be insulting.
- Nobody wants to be insulting.
- I badly want to be insulting.
Here's the thing...
Sloan got a call from Erin Andrews...
- You know Erin Andrews?
- Yes.
Yowza.
I want to get with that so bad.
I'll pass that on.
I'm sure she'll want you to have her number.
- Hey, fuck you.
- Yeah?
- You can't talk to her like that, my friend.
- What's the problem here?
Erin Andrews got stopped by paparazzi
last night coming out of the movies.
- I know, we've got it up.
- Now we're in Peabody country.
You're here to give me shit
about the app again.
Yes. Restraining Order.
Scum Bottle Guide.
- Whatever it's called.
- ACNgage.
It should be called
ACinvoluntary Engage.
I'll bring that up
at our next staff meeting.
You guys like
ACinvoluntary Engage?
- No.
- It got voted down.
Listen, no kidding around,
you need to disable the app until we can figure this out,
- 'cause it's a little not what we do.
- What's not what you do?
Giving deranged people with
access to semiautomatic weapons
the locations of their
targets while simultaneously
turning the rest
of our brains into Wheatena.
That app's driving
a lot of traffic.
I don't care if it's driving
in the Grand Prix of Monaco.
I need you to temporarily
take it down.
- Then permanently take it down.
- You need to speak to my boss.
- He's your boss.
- I'm your boss.
Lucas Pruit is my boss.
I pitched him the app
and he loved it,
which is why we have it.
This is a warmed-over version of the same app
Gawker had and took down five years ago.
They still have a version of it,
but this one's better.
- Look...
- No, you look.
We're all a little tired
of being treated
like we're not Neal Sampat.
I like my app
and it makes money,
both of which are more than I
can say for your 10:00 hour.
So if you have a problem,
and I got a hunch you got more than a few,
why don't you take it to Pruit?
Beat him up.
No, he's right.
Yeah, he's... What?
About the last thing he said.
About the last thing you said.
We haven't been very welcoming
and in a weird way we've
been blaming him for Neal.
If Digital can help us,
we should be supporting Digital.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
Come on the show and tell
people about your app.
Seriously?
I'll ask MacKenzie for a block
and I'll interview you.
All right.
Awesome.
An associate producer
will give you the details.
- You should apologize.
- Sorry.
- To him.
- Habit. Sorry.
Were you serious about
that phone number?
Yeah,
but I think you can do better.
- For real?
- I'm on it.
Okay,
so when you vivisect this guy
and especially his app,
Pruit's not gonna be happy.
I'll cross that bridge
when I come to it.
You usually blow up that
bridge when you come to it.
Would you mind giving me some space?
I have a show to prepare.
Sure, but this is my office.
Yes, it is.
Sorry.
Hang on.
There's an undergrad at
Princeton who started a website
for students who have been raped,
but who don't have enough evidence
for the police to take action.
Victims can go onto the site
either anonymously or not
and name names and describe
their experiences.
Pruit wants the undergrad and one
of the accused in the studio.
- That's a terrible idea.
- I know.
- Do you have a better one?
- Don't do it?
Do you have a better one
where I get to keep my job?
- Charlie's gonna back you.
- Charlie told me to do it.
What's happening to him?
I think you should consider
letting me do the talking.
At least at the top.
We won't have much time with him
and I want to ask him,
obviously, the extent
to which they've been
keeping metadata,
how much the agency learns
from this kind of information,
and in what ways the FISA
reports have provided
insufficient oversight
of the NSA.
I want to ask him at what point he decided
to declare war on the United States.
So I think you should
let me get the ball rolling.
You and your whole generation's
contempt for institutions.
I'm two years younger than you.
With your hair and your
clothes and your music.
Here it is.
Here's the gate.
You sure?
It says departs
for Havana at 11:55 PM.
- Are you sure?
- We had a nine-hour flight from New York.
I was brushing up on my Russian
with my Russian phrase book,
or Russkiy razgovornik,
while you were watching Star Wars on your iPad.
Trek. Star Trek.
Both excellent
examples of genius,
- but different in every imaginable...
- Yeah, shut up.
- Good evening.
Then we'll speak in English.
You're American press, yes?
I have not seen Edward Snowden.
I do not know where he is.
That's all right.
We just want to check in
for the midnight
flight to Havana.
That's Aeroflot seven,
departing 11:55?
Yes.
Margaret Jordan and James Humdrum.
Harper.
That guy's from
ABC's Moscow bureau.
And that's Reuters
and that's Le Monde.
He's going to Cuba.
He's gonna be on this flight.
I do not show reservation
for Margaret Jordan.
- Really?
- I'll try Humdrum.
Harper.
James Harper.
The office bought our tickets
while we were in the air.
I do not show reservation
for Harper.
Would you mind checking again?
What do you think will
happen the second time?
Would you ask her
to check again?
- Would you mind checking again?
- In Russian.
I understood in English.
And I have checked again.
And lo and behold,
got the same result.
All right.
Can we have two coach seats to Havana?
- The flight is sold out.
- Of course it is.
I'll call the office.
Unless the office can build
two seats and install them
on the plane in the next four hours,
it's not gonna do any good.
Excuse me.
Do you speak English?
- Agence France.
- You speak French. Great.
- I speak English, too.
- Okay.
'Cause when I said...
It doesn't matter.
I would like to buy your ticket
from you at a substantial markup.
- How substantial?
- Twice what your office paid for it.
You can catch the next flight
and pocket the difference.
- That's a good deal.
- Yes, it is.
I don't have a ticket
for the flight.
- You don't?
- No.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to photograph
Mr. Snowden.
This is a very big story.
You agree?
I do.
I do agree.
We have to get on this flight.
When did you decide you wanted
to be a TV news anchor?
Do you know how long this
interview is gonna take?
- You've got someplace else you're going?
- No.
When did you decide you wanted
to be a TV news anchor?
I didn't. I was a prosecutor.
Then I was a speechwriter.
Then I was the legal correspondent
for my network and I got promoted.
- You were a prosecutor?
- The Brooklyn DA's office.
You aren't afraid you're gonna run into
some of the people you sent here?
That's why I'm supposed
to be in solitary.
And you were
what kind of writer?
Speechwriter.
What does that mean?
I helped write speeches for
the first President Bush.
I worked on his campaign and when he won,
they brought me to the White House.
No kidding?
George H.W.?
- Yeah.
- Did you ever meet him?
Yeah.
Ah. I liked him.
He was an elite Harvard
silver spoon and all that,
but he didn't rub it in your face,
you know?
- He went to Yale.
- He didn't do that.
He didn't make people
feel stupid.
- That's not what I was doing.
- What?
You were just saying
that to the fatheads,
there's no difference
between Yale and Harvard.
But to the refined palate
of the eastern elite,
- the subtle nuances...
- Jesus, I'm from Nebraska!
You still got that northeastern
air of superiority.
- I'm in jail!
- And even in here you still think you're better than me.
You hit a woman, man.
You don't set the bar very high.
- Will.
- Yeah?
- You got visitors.
- On a Monday?
- I'll be outside the door.
- You look good.
- Yeah, you say that every week.
- It's true every week.
How you holding up?
I'm good.
What's this about?
He's going to ask you a couple of
questions I've already approved.
But if you need a minute,
take a minute.
- He'll step outside.
- What's going on?
The day before yesterday,
Saturday morning,
a woman named Lilly Hart
committed suicide
by shooting herself in the head on the
steps of the Justice Department.
Does the name Lilly Hart
mean anything to you?
That wasn't one of the
questions we went over.
- All right.
- Stick to the script.
Lilly Hart worked for BCD.
Her roommate and some of her friends
were trying to put the pieces together,
trying to figure out why she killed
herself and so theatrically.
- Mm-hmm.
- Her roommate starts going through her emails
and then some files,
and she finds some things which are alarming enough
for her to bring to the attention of
some agents who sweep the entire laptop.
Will you confirm
Lilly Hart as your source?
No, sir.
- Will you deny that she was your source?
- No, sir.
- You're not under oath.
- I understand.
Lilly Hart has no family.
Both her parents died
in a car crash years ago.
She's single with no children.
There's no one
to protect anymore.
Confirm the name,
and I'll inform the judge
that the government
no longer needs your testimony
and has withdrawn their subpoena
and you'll be having dinner with
your wife in your home tonight.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm not allowed
to reveal the name of a source
without their permission.
Well,
that option was taken off the table
when your source put
a loaded Beretta 9mm Nano
in her mouth
and squeezed the trigger.
Don't do that.
Don't try the side door.
Look, confirm that she's the source
and Neal comes home from Venezuela.
We'll buy the ticket.
First class.
And you won't pursue
criminal prosecution?
We'll give him
an ice cream cone.
Will you confirm that Lilly
Hart was your source?
No, sir.
- Will you deny it?
- No, sir.
Neal would pummel me if I got him back
by giving up the name of a source.
Did you think I was gonna
consider a deal like this?
I wrote down exactly
what I thought you'd say
and sealed it in this envelope.
_
Can I speak to him?
He's back in his cell.
Mac.
When are they gonna be
absolutely sure?
What percent of certainty
will it take?
- I'm gonna find out.
- What if we switch places?
- I have the exact same information Will has.
- Mac.
What if you convinced them I was softer
and more likely to give up the name?
- Are you?
- No.
Just a second.
- What if you told them that...
- Listen to me.
'Cause here's your $20 worth.
You don't tell anyone
you know what Will knows.
You want your friends to be
subpoenaed and get sworn in?
No.
Come on in.
Keep calling me.
I want to hear from you once an hour.
- What's going on?
- I need a block tonight. Five minutes, 4:30.
- For what?
- I want to interview Bree Dorrit.
Isn't that the temporary
ACN Digital editor?
- Yeah.
- Why do you want to interview someone who works for us?
I want to discuss
an app he has...
We have called Human Flesh
Hunter or something.
I know I've missed
some meetings,
but we really don't have an app
called Hunting Human Flesh?
No. Maybe.
I don't know.
I don't like to do
stories about us.
I know,
but this is about everyone.
Lady Gaga has been
relatively silent on Twitter
since her hip surgery
last February.
But today she broke
her silence and tweeted
in support of...
In defense of...
In support of overturning
the Defense of Marriage Act.
Sloan's going
to interview her manager.
You're still able to hear
yourself when you speak, right?
- Yeah.
- I'm glad Lady Gaga wants to engage people...
She has 40 million
Twitter followers.
Does her manager bring expertise
to the table on marriage equality?
What kind of expertise
is there on that subject?
- Someone who's familiar with state legislature.
- Just block out the time.
We don't have the time tonight.
We only have him for one night.
Well, I don't want to get
scooped on Gaga's manager.
Hey, you know what, Mac?
How about she brings 40 million
people to a civil rights debate?
I don't think gay couples
who'd just like to move
the fuck on with their lives are
as choosy about that discussion.
It was trending, Charlie.
It still is.
Lady Gaga's tweets,
they're trending number one.
So Pruit picked up the phone and said,
"Do this."
That's why you book her manager,
to report on the tweets.
Whatever.
Put it in the rundown.
- I don't have room.
- There's always room.
Tell me what you'd like to cut.
The Supreme Court
struck down portions
of the Voting Rights Act
this morning.
IAF fighter jets
attacked the Gaza Strip
after rockets were fired
at southern Israel.
Ed Markey won John Kerry's
seat in the Senate.
- Snowden's on his way to Cuba.
- Cut my thing.
I didn't have the time
for it anyway.
- What was it?
- Nothing.
- ACNgage?
- Yeah, how'd you know?
- Pruit wants it.
- How did he know?
The guy, Bree,
he's got a relationship with Pruit.
He told him you were putting him
on the air and Pruit liked it.
It's a promo for the site.
Yeah, that is what it is.
You'll have to cut something
else or make trims.
In an historic
5-4 decision,
the US Supreme Court did something
that we'll tell you about tomorrow.
- We're clear, right?
- We are.
- I'm really sorry.
- Not your fault.
Tell me about
the five-minute interview
we're going to do
with ourselves.
You sure you wouldn't rather
do this someplace else?
Those are the Footnotes.
The pitch pipe lives
in the room next door
and they practice
there sometimes.
You get used to it.
It's kind of nice.
I just meant...
If I can avoid it, I'd rather not be alone
with a young woman in her dorm room.
You want witnesses in case I
say you forced yourself on me.
- No, no.
- Don.
- Yeah?
- I was raped.
- I wasn't worried...
I went to a party
at one of the eating clubs.
I drank too much tequila.
There was molly, there was coke,
there were mushrooms,
and I took anything
that was put in front of me.
I wound up in a bathroom throwing
up and then passing out.
And the next thing I knew,
two guys were helping me into a bedroom.
They told me
I needed to lie down.
When we got in there,
they took my clothes off
and they took turns raping me.
And the next day
you called the police?
City police, campus police,
and the DA's office.
I know who the two guys are
and I know where they live.
That should be the easiest arrest
they're ever going to make.
- Nobody pursued it.
- The kind of rape you're talking about
- is difficult and usually impossible to prove.
- It's not a kind of rape.
Sure.
How did you find me?
- The original email?
- Yeah.
Just some detective work.
I really want to know.
Well,
on the web page there's a bio.
You say you're
a third-year psych major.
And later you say you live
across from Dillon Gym
and one of these days you're
gonna start working out.
- You also wrote that you love the Phat Lady.
- Right.
I got a list of all female
psych majors on campus
and cross-referenced it with students
living in the upperclassmen dorms
across from the gym,
which brought me to Cuyler Hall.
- Wow.
- I asked some people in my office
if they knew the band
the Phat Lady.
- Really?
- And a Princeton grad laughed and said...
- It's a sandwich.
- It is the most popular sandwich
not on the menu
at Hoagie Haven.
So we went to Costa,
one of the managers at Hoagie Haven,
with pictures of the four female
psych majors living at Cuyler Hall
and asked him if any
were regular customers.
He pointed at your picture and said,
"That's my girl Mary."
That's a lot of detective work.
That's old school.
I was trying
to impress my boss.
- My boss's boss.
- Did it work?
He wants you in the studio
along with Jeff.
At the same time.
Elliot Hirsch would be moderating,
I guess you'd call it.
It's very promotable.
It'd bring a lot of new
viewers to my show,
a lot of younger viewers who
drive a lot of Internet traffic.
And I'd score
some points at work.
And you're here
for a preinterview.
I'm here to beg you
not to do it.
The travel office transferred
me to talent relations,
who transferred me to Tess,
who said,
"It's so romantic that you guys
are on a stakeout together
in the Moscow Airport.
You're his destiny."
I said, "Tess, we were supposed to
have tickets waiting to Havana."
She said,
"Hang on, let me check."
Then she got back
on the phone and said,
"Did you know there's more
than one city named Havana?"
We have tickets to Spain?
There are layovers in Dvinsk,
Rotterdam, and Berlin.
And we change planes in Madrid.
How's it looking here?
There are three people in front of us,
five people in back of us.
As passengers come to claim their seats,
the people in back get dismissed.
It's like that last
helicopter out of Saigon.
I know how standby works.
I was answering your question.
It really would have killed
you to apologize to Hallie?
You would have gotten
sick and died?
As soon as you said
the word romantic...
- I didn't say it, Tess did.
- You recounted it.
I was telling a funny story.
As soon as you said romantic,
I knew we were heading for Hallie.
After all, it's been two hours.
- You would have tragically died from...
- I did apologize.
"I'm sorry I overreacted.
In fact, I'm so sorry that I
sent this apology in a text."
How should it have
been delivered?
- In person for starters.
- She doesn't want to see me.
You know what you should do?
Tess thinks you're my destiny?
- Call her right now.
- Tess?
Hallie.
Call her right now.
You're halfway around
the world on a big story,
but you just wanted
to hear her voice.
Do you want her back, Jim?
- Those two are on the plane.
- Do you want her back?
- Of course.
- Then do what I'm telling you
and wait for
further instructions.
- Do it.
- You can hold our place?
Yeah, I think I can handle
standing on the ground.
'Cause it's not a bad idea.
Don't get into any,
you know, areas.
Just tell her you wanted
to hear her voice
and that you love her and that
you'll call her from Cuba.
All right, I'll be right back.
- What happened?
- It was voicemail. I hung up.
- You'll keep trying, right?
- Yeah.
You did good.
I already know what he'll say.
So do I.
I've spoken to him.
- He denied it?
- Yeah.
What did he say happened?
You don't want to hear it.
- Yes, I do.
- It's upsetting.
I have a new standard
for what upsets me.
- He said it was consensual?
- Yeah.
How can it be consensual if one of the
consenting parties isn't conscious?
- It can't be.
- So what did he say?
Mary, he says you said,
"Fuck me. Fuck me. Fuck me.
Get two guys in here
who will fuck me."
Yeah, that...
That sounds like me.
And he's changing
his story a little.
That's something that
would come out in a trial.
There's not gonna be a trial.
There's not gonna be an arrest.
And there's not gonna
be an investigation.
Mine's gonna be one of the
700,000 untested rape kits,
so I started this website.
- Do you know who Sloan Sabbith is?
- Sure.
- She's my girlfriend.
- Well done.
About, I don't know,
a year and a half ago,
she was dating this guy and they
broke up and he was pissed.
She'd posed for him,
some naked pictures,
and he posted them on a site
called RevengePorn.com.
I remember.
What did she do?
She broke his jaw,
but I'm not recommending that.
This isn't revenge.
It's a warning.
It's a public service.
Do not go on a date with these guys.
Do not go to a party
with these guys.
Do not give
these guys a job ever.
Wait, they're avoiding jail and
you think I'm being too harsh?
Don't you think there's a chance that
somebody's gonna use the site as revenge?
That somebody's gonna make up a
story and ruin a kid's life?
Jeff got into Stanford Medical School.
Not anymore.
There were NFL teams looking at Brandon.
Yeah,
you can imagine how sad that makes me.
Don't you think there's a chance that somebody,
a woman who feels rejected...
Yeah, bitches be bitches.
I get it.
I'm just saying
that if a grown man
who works in arbitrage at one of
the biggest banks in the world
can post naked pictures
of his ex on RevengePorn.com...
Yes, I think there's a chance and
I've weighed the cost benefit.
I have. If another girl got raped
because I didn't say anything
or because someone else
didn't say anything...
- I know.
- You don't know.
And you're right about that,
too.
Then what am I wrong about?
What am I wrong about?
I don't like Jews.
I said it.
People are afraid to speak
their mind these days.
I haven't noticed that.
First of all,
we've got, what, 3%?
- Is that how many Jews there are, 3% of America?
- A little less.
Less than 3% of Americans
controlling the banks,
the media, Hollywood.
They didn't take those
things in an armed assault.
That's exactly how they did it.
Their grandparents came here
from the Polish ghettos
and the Russian villages
and they told their sons,
"Don't work with your hands."
Go to law school. You go to medical school.
You go to business school.
You don't get calluses on your hands.
You wear a suit to work.
Given the time they came from
and the one that was coming,
it was pretty good advice.
And guys like you worship them.
You'd give anything to be Jewish.
You're Protestant, right?
- Catholic.
- Nah, not on both sides.
- My mother was Catholic.
- So is my wife.
- Is that why you hit her?
- No, I'm not prejudiced.
You assume I am
'cause I do real work.
- What do I do?
- Please, buddy.
- You want to trade jobs with me?
- No.
'Cause you're too smart
for what I do.
Just like the Jews.
That's why your father drank.
I'm making
an executive decision.
Should I quiet everyone down?
We can't be in this line because A...
You know,
and B... He'll have already talked
to everyone who's boarded.
We need to be
on the plane early.
Let's go back
to the first plan.
No reporter is gonna
sell us their ticket.
There are people on this
flight who aren't reporters.
Let's look around
and identify them.
Those two are on
their honeymoon.
I do, just a little.
My husband does not.
I'm Maggie Jordan
and this is Jim Harper.
We are from an American
news agency.
Atlantis Cable News.
He says Atlantis is a lost...
Hercules, Zeus.
- Mythological.
- Mythological city.
It is,
but the news agency is real.
- Go faster.
- Shut up.
Are you on your honeymoon, too?
No,
we're reporting an important story
and we need to get
on that flight.
And we'd like to buy
your tickets to Havana
and give you two free
tickets to Madrid.
- Tell them Madrid's closer.
- They know where Madrid is.
- Just remind them.
- We know where Madrid is.
He wants your watch.
This watch was a graduation
present from my parents.
Could I write you a check
for some money instead?
We'll take the money, too.
He liked my shirt
and my pants, too.
And everything that was in
my suitcase and my suitcase.
Hey, she took my News Night
baseball cap.
I think we have more of those.
These are our seats.
All right.
We'll see him
come on from here.
- I look like an idiot.
- You look kind of cute.
I look like I...
just really, really,
really like the Olympics.
You never called Hallie,
did you?
No.
Jesus Christ, Jim.
The law is plainly
failing rape victims.
That must be obvious to you.
It is, but in fairness,
the law wasn't built to serve victims.
- In fairness?
- I know.
Do you believe me?
Do I believe you?
Of course I do.
- Seriously.
- I'm not here on a fact-finding mission.
I'm just curious.
Be really honest.
Okay.
I've heard two
competing stories.
One from a very credible woman
who as far as I can see
has no reason to lie.
The other from a guy I judge
to be a little sketchy
who has every reason
to lie and I am...
I'm obligated to believe
the sketchy guy.
This isn't a courtroom.
You're not legally obligated
to presume innocence.
- I believe I'm morally obligated.
- You know, you're a good guy,
but do people tell you a lot
that your head's up your ass?
They do,
and I absolutely allow for that possibility.
I'm the guy who goes around saying OJ's
not guilty because a jury said so.
I'm not gonna get a jury.
I know,
and I can imagine how frustrating...
No, you can't imagine.
No, I can't.
But it is a huge, dangerous,
scary-as-shit mistake
to convene your own trial
in front of a television audience
where there's no due process,
no lawyers, no discovery,
no rules of procedure,
no decisions on admissible evidence,
threat of perjury,
confrontation of witnesses
or any of the things we do...
To ensure that rapists go
to Stanford Medical School.
To ensure an innocent person
isn't destroyed.
The law can acquit.
The Internet never will.
The Internet is used
for vigilantism every day.
But this is a whole new level
and if we go there,
we're truly fucked.
- I'm not a vigilante.
- Do you want to live in a world where...
Do you want to hear
the advice I get?
I mean, this is real advice.
In pamphlets.
Say you have a boyfriend.
Wear a wedding ring.
I'm supposed to protect
myself from a man
by pretending I'm the
property of another man.
And, of course,
there's no shortage of good fashion advice.
- Mary.
- When you came in here,
you wanted to go
to a public place
because you were scared
I'd cry rape.
I'm scared of getting raped.
I'm scared all the time.
All the time.
So you know what my site does?
It scares you.
It scares the living shit
out of any guy
who thinks even once
about putting his hands
on someone
without an invitation.
You're right to name
your attacker.
You may even be obligated to.
But the site is gonna
clobber an innocent person
and there is no chance
that it won't.
And if you face off with
the guy you've accused on TV,
it is going to be
a lawless food fight
with irreversible,
irretrievable consequences.
Teams will be formed,
you will be slut-shamed,
and you won't get the
justice you're looking for.
That's why I'm asking
you to refuse.
I don't understand why
you need me to refuse.
It's your show.
Why don't you just not do it?
I've been overruled.
It's a promotable story
that'll bring in
a younger audience.
I don't have
a problem with that.
It's sports, Mary.
It'll be covered like sports.
I'm gonna win this time.
All right.
Thanks for hearing me out.
We'll be in touch with you.
- You miss your wife?
- Yes.
Uh, yes.
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
I miss my wife.
That's affirmative.
I was married to her
for 11 minutes
before I was taken to jail.
Yes, I miss my wife.
So is she like you or is she like,
I don't know, what do you call it?
- I don't know what you're asking.
- A trophy wife.
A guy like you could get,
you know.
Is she a trophy wife
or is she smart?
She's very smart.
Is that something you're saying
because people say that?
She went to school
at Cambridge in England.
She's considered one of the
best in the world at her job...
- You've got to stop being a prick.
- What did I do now?
I know that Cambridge is in goddamn England,
shithead.
Why is the first thing you tell
me is where she went to school?
My wife is smarter than I
am in every way imaginable
and it never makes me mad.
I don't feel a crippling
inferiority complex
turn into rage
and bad decisions
when I think about
her being smart.
- You're saying I do?
- It seems to come up a lot.
I don't like media types.
- East Coast elites.
- Yeah.
That's a thoroughly
original opinion.
I've never heard that before.
See, you people think
we can't recognize sarcasm.
We can.
We just call it being an asshole.
And we call you a shit kicker.
And you still don't think you
look down at some people.
Down is where some people are.
Hmm.
What's your mission
to civilize?
Who told you about that?
- You did.
- When?
- A while ago.
- I don't remember that.
Mission to civilize,
what is that?
Nothing.
- It's not nothing.
- It's just a joke.
- No, it's not.
- It's nothing.
What is it?
It's a reference
to Don Quixote.
- The knight?
- He wasn't a real knight.
He was an old man who was delusional.
He thought he was a knight.
He took on a world that was
bleak and morally corrupt.
How'd he do?
He got his ass kicked.
See?
And that's the thing.
I don't want to see you
get your ass kicked.
That's... That's not true.
That was dishonest.
I badly want to see you
get your ass kicked.
I know.
And that picture
of you and your father,
I'll bet he wasn't trying to
teach you about civic morality.
I'll bet he was just trying
to teach you to fish.
Please,
you have to take your seats now.
We're pushing back from the
gate and all passengers
must take their seats, please.
Thank you.
We had seats across
the aisle from him.
The honeymooners had two seats across
the aisle from Edward Snowden.
Boris and Natasha
had the golden tickets.
We'd have had him the whole
flight except for one thing.
- He's not...
- He's not on the plane. You know where he is?
- Probably back in the airport.
- Yeah.
So we'll be flying 600 miles
an hour away from the story.
Fuck!
Why didn't you call her?
What?
Why didn't you call Hallie?
You're a noodge, Maggie.
You know that?
I'm just asking.
If you really like her,
it's a stupid thing...
I like you.
And I don't really know
why you don't know that.
Because...
Because if you wanted to be with me,
you'd be with me.
That's just not at all true.
You were with Don
when I met you.
You never called me
from New Hampshire.
- Yes, I did.
- No, you didn't. Ever.
And you knew I had split up
with Don and you knew why.
You went through Lisa,
you went through Hallie.
And you never called me
from New Hampshire.
So it's really not as
obvious as you think it is.
And it's also
probably not true.
Well,
the rest might be right...
It's not,
but it had potential...
but the last thing
was unambiguously wrong.
- What language are you...
- I do like you.
I like you
and I'm glad I said it.
Even though now I wish
I had said it
at the end
of a 13-hour flight.
Yeah,
this is gonna be uncomfortable.
I'm gonna switch seats
with someone.
I'll switch seats.
I'll sit in Snowden's seat.
That's not far enough.
It's gonna be weird
if we can see each other.
Okay.
I'm making a motion
that the court
vacate its initial
contempt finding
because enough is enough.
Do I need grounds?
Sure.
The government
now possesses information
that will help it independently
find the source.
But mostly, enough is enough.
You can't lock up
a man for 52 days
without him knowing when or
even if he's ever getting out.
You can't lock up a reporter
for protecting his source.
- You can't have everything. And you...
- Rebecca.
I have not yielded the floor.
I won't be contesting
your motion.
I'm sorry?
I won't be contesting your motion.
I'll be joining it.
This isn't supposed to be punitive.
It's supposed to be coercive.
And plainly he's not
giving up the name.
He'll sleep at home tonight.
Follow me.
Where are we going?
Exactly where
you think we're going.
I don't know what...
I'm confused.
We're running into turbulence.
You have to go to your seats
and put your seat belts on.
This is awkward.
I was sitting far away from you.
I was watching episode four.
I'm sorry,
would you mind trading back?
We're in the middle
of turbulence.
It's nothing.
It's due to the action
of molecular viscosity
called laminar flow.
Okay.
- Where did that come from?
- Sit down. Put on your seat belt.
And we're joined now by Bree Dorrit,
editor of ACN Digital
and father of the ACNgage app.
- Thanks for joining us, Bree.
- Hi, Sloan.
We saw some of it in the package we just played,
but tell us about ACNgage.
It's a map that tells you
where celebrities
have been sighted in
New York or Los Angeles.
And soon we'll be expanding
to Vegas and South Beach.
Any time you want,
you can scroll around and see, you know,
Jude Law was shopping for condoms
at Duane Reade on 57th or...
So people are out there and they
can post a message to us and say,
"Kristen Bell and her kid
are at the 4:00 PM showing
of How to Train Your Dragon
at the ArcLight"?
And it goes right on
our map instantly.
So that when Kristen Bell and
her kid come out of the movies,
there are a dozen sociopaths
waiting for them?
- I don't think that's likely.
- Why not?
Well, it's the price of fame,
isn't it?
No, it's not.
It's a punishment for it.
Celebrities have been stalked and
celebrities have been murdered.
What this app is best at
is assisting in that, right?
I'm sorry you feel that way.
ACNgage is citizen journalism.
Can you talk about
the vetting process
- the citizen journalism undergoes?
- The vetting?
People can post
more than locations.
- They can post observations.
- That's right.
I'm asking if those posts
are fact-checked.
This is one specific
element of the site...
For instance,
in a post today a citizen journalist tells us
that Jimmy Kimmel was visibly
intoxicated last night
- at the Soho House in West Hollywood.
- That's right.
Jimmy Kimmel was with his family
in Cabo San Lucas last night.
People don't read this with the
expectation of it being true.
- Everyone...
- Excuse me?
- People don't have an expectation
that what they're
reading is true?
They read it for the immediacy.
But you're using
the word journalism,
which means there is an expectation
that what they're reading is true.
But let me take it
a step further.
Let's pretend it was true
that Jimmy Kimmel
was intoxicated last night at the
Soho House in West Hollywood.
It's not true, but we don't care,
so let's pretend
that it is since that's
what we're doing anyway.
Why does that belong
on our website?
Leave her on
as long as she wants.
Honestly,
I think there's a shifting definition
of what's public
and private space.
There is,
and we should care about that.
But my question is
why should we care
about a talk show host
drinking at a bar?
Don't you think it's great
that we're not putting people
up on a pedestal and
worshipping them anymore?
I don't think celebrities are one
of the bigger problems facing us,
but aren't we the ones
building the pedestal?
You've got a map that
gives us their location.
The idea is that we're acknowledging
that they're real people.
I wonder how many of us
didn't already know that.
But you're doing more than
acknowledging they're real people.
You're beating them up for it.
Aren't they protected by the piles
of money they're surrounded by?
Okay,
what's the line of demarcation?
You make over X dollars a year and
now you get to be treated by us
as a regular person
who's basically had
an electronic bracelet slapped on their ankle.
What does X equal?
It would be silly to name
an exact dollar amount.
- You're paid $55,000 a year.
- Well, that's private.
Sorry. That's almost twice the
national average for a family of four.
Do your piles of cash protect
you from this interview
in which I'm intentionally
stripping you of your dignity?
And, by the way,
I've managed to do it without lying once.
So I'm going to give you another
chance to answer my question
before I answer it myself.
What's the value
of an unsourced,
unvetted story about a grown
man drinking at a bar?
I can't give you all the time in the world.
It's entertainment.
My concern isn't
for the celebrities,
even though as sure as we're sitting here,
someone's gonna get hurt.
My concern is for
the rest of us
who you're turning into a
wild pack of prideless punks.
That's News Night for June 24.
I'm Sloan Sabbith
filling in for Will McAvoy.
Terry Smith's up next
with the Capitol Report.
We're clear.
Pruit's gonna
kill you for this.
I know.
- Did you put her up to that?!
- Let's go in my office.
- No! We'll go where I fucking say we go!
- Charlie.
- Did you put her up to it?
- Nobody put me up to anything.
What did you think
you were doing?
- You saw the questions she was gonna ask?
- 'Course I saw the questions.
I was doing the interview the
only way that made sense to me.
You were openly insubordinate!
I was told to do
this interview.
You knew what
I was looking for!
I did and I didn't like it,
but I did it anyway.
- That was my interview. Mac wasn't responsible.
- I tried to do the best I could, but I didn't...
I'm tired of this.
Did you get the Princeton kid?
Charlie, let's go into my office
and sit down for a minute.
Did you get the Princeton kid?
- No.
- Why not?
Couldn't find her.
You couldn't...
No.
- You couldn't find her?!
- No.
Is this a mutiny?!
It's an intervention.
I'm trying to keep
this together!
Her and her,
tell 'em to pack their shit and get out of here.
- I apologize for the interview.
- I don't.
- Pack up your shit and get out of here, lady.
- Look...
She tore apart our network,
except it isn't ours, it's mine.
So either Thelma and Louise vacate the
premises in the next five minutes
or I will fire the motherfucking
lot of you right now.
No, you won't.
'Cause you can't.
Only I can.
A parting gift from Mrs. Lansing.
Who on her worst day
would never...
We need to talk.
You and me, right now, okay?
Upstairs.
Nobody leaves the premises
until we figure out
how to fix
this fucking calamity.
I'll be back in a minute.
- Let's meet in my office.
- I'm there.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
It's okay.
It's over.
Charlie had a heart
attack a few hours ago.
He died.
www.tvsubtitles.net