Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
- Back up.
- Sure.
- How many?
- Bridesmaids?
- Yeah.
- Nine.
Nine bridesmaids?
My sisters, your sisters, Sheila,
Sloan, Maggie, and Diane.
- Who's Sheila?
- My brother's wife Sheila. You've met her.
- And who's Diane?
- Sawyer.
And because you have
nine bridesmaids...
You need nine groomsmen.
That's, like, a law?
The groomsmen have to walk the
bridesmaids down the aisle.
Well, Charlie's my best man.
What if I have him just keep going back
up the aisle and fetching bridesmaids?
Is there any chance Charlie is going
to be sober when the ceremony starts?
I have news for you...
Your sisters will have taken
a couple of dips
from the well, too.
Charlie, Don, Jim,
Elliot, and who else?
There is no one else.
I've worked very hard
at cultivating
no friendships outside of work.
And to be honest,
I was doing fine
cultivating no friendships
inside of work
- until you came along.
- You need five more.
Nine bridesmaids is madness.
The amount of time it's going to take
18 people to walk down the aisle...
You're telling me Diane Sawyer's going
to put on a dress with puffy shoulders?
The bridesmaids
are wearing Vera Wang.
Can Vera Wang make
that many dresses?
How about Brian Williams?
You love Brian.
And if he's up there next to me,
you're gonna start to think.
In fact, the whole idea of parading
a bunch of well-dressed men
in front of you right before
you're asked the big question...
And don't get me wrong,
but I've now seen you commit
to three different shades of tile
for the master bath before...
- Did you see that?
- What?
- What is it?
- Switcher.
Ben, what feed are you running
on 44B in the bull pen?
That's a local
Boston affiliate.
Somebody wanted
to watch the marathon.
What'd you see?
An explosion.
What just happened in Boston?
I've got multiple alerts,
all red.
Blast at the finish line
of the marathon.
Runners and spectators
fleeing the scene.
The finish line's
at the Lenox Hotel.
- There might be a fire.
- Look at that runner.
- Can we get some audio?
- The way he falls to the side.
- That's an energy force.
- That's an explosion.
- Break them into teams.
- Boston affiliate.
Boston PD.
FBI. DOJ.
Homeland Security.
Area hospitals.
- Jenna!
- On it!
And five, and four,
and three,
and two, and one.
Okay, take a breath and...
Okay, hot stuff, what you got?
Come on, focus.
Focus.
You're bad.
You are bad.
You're a bad fucking lady.
Give me 10 more.
No phone.
Tune that out.
Love the pain.
Eat the pain.
Counting six, and five,
and four, and you stopped.
Good session.
Can you confirm that the explosions were
caused by bombs and not a gas line?
Were there any credible threats
made in advance of the race?
This is Martin Stallworth
at ACN.
This is Tess Westin at ACN.
SWAT's on the
scene along with K-9 units.
I want to get accurate
information out quickly, Mike.
We're both doing a job and I'm at the
only reliable breaking news network.
Except for that one time, yes.
I've got an image of the area
around the finish line.
Throw it up
on the front monitors.
Can you tell me if you've
got terrorist groups...
Use the number in this.
It's the White House.
Don't ask who's on the other end of the phone.
Just say it's for me.
Is anyone getting through to the trauma
center or the ER at Mass General?
Nobody's picking up at Mass General,
Brigham and Women's, Beth Israel.
- That's not a good sign.
- When is she breaking in?
When she knows what
she's breaking in with.
- That's right, right?
- We're gonna do this thing well.
- We are.
- Do you know what that means, doing it well?
Yeah.
She's holding for you.
- Yeah?
- "2:52 P.M.
- I don't know what the fuck that was"...
- Hang on.
..."but I'm shaking.
Everyone's sprinting through the Back Bay."
"2:54, explosions
on Boylston Street."
"2:54, mass casualty
incident declared
at the end of the Boston
Marathon route."
I'm not putting Will on the air
to say something bad
may have happened in Boston,
but we're not sure what.
This isn't speculative anymore.
We're not going based on tweets
from witnesses we can't talk to.
What credible news agency
would do that?
Fox is up.
Ugh! Jim.
The president's been notified
of the incident in Boston.
What is the incident in Boston?
They were hoping we knew.
What am I looking at?
That's Boylston Street.
That's the finish line.
Over there's the Lenox Hotel.
That's where the blast came from.
- Inside the hotel?
- We don't know.
If I learn what happened
by watching the news,
I'm going to lose
my fucking mind!
We're dramatically
understaffed.
- Where's Keefer?
- Don's got jury duty today.
Are you kidding?
Get him out.
I'm a schoolteacher.
I teach fourth grade.
- Where?
- PS 40 here in Manhattan.
- Have you ever bought anything over the phone?
- Yes.
From one of those commercials you see on TV?
- What have you bought?
I bought something that removes
scratches from your car.
- Good. Anything else?
- No.
And did you have a good
experience with that product?
Your Honor,
may I approach the bench?
What? Why?
I really can't say
in front of all...
- If I could just...
- Approach. Hurry up.
Um...
my name is Don Keefer.
I'm a producer at ACN.
There's been an explosion at the
finish line of the Boston Marathon
and I have to get back
to my newsroom.
- Was anyone injured?
- I don't know.
- Was it a terrorist attack?
- Do they have a suspect?
- These are all things that I'd like the answer to,
but I can't find
them out from here.
- Mr...?
- Keefer.
All these people
have someplace else to be.
I'm sure your network
can do the news without you.
You're probably right,
but I'd hate for my boss to find that out.
Take your seat.
Uh, look,
you don't want leaders on the jury, right?
Anyone who can take charge
during deliberations.
I run a news broadcast
five nights a week
with a staff of 60 and I
bend them to my will.
Plus, I'm currently the
defendant in two lawsuits
being brought
by the same person,
so even though I bought
your client's bagel slicer
at 3:00 A.M. and it nearly
took my fingers off,
there is simply no way in hell that
I am finding for the plaintiff.
- Get out of here.
- Thank you.
Hey.
You got dismissed from jury duty?
Sort of.
What are you doing?
They finally got one for me.
A Bloomberg terminal.
This is a $24,000 system that
gives me instantaneous access
to all the financial
information in the world.
Do you know what's going
on outside your door?
It's not on there.
- When are we breaking in?
- When Mac says so.
- Neal.
- Yeah?
I'm tracking 2,221 tweets
describing two explosions
at the finish line
of the Boston Marathon.
What exactly
are we waiting for?
Are any of them
from official sources?
Do you guys understand the explosion
occurred in the 21st century?
Welcome to ACN.
By the way,
there's a message that came in
for you personally
over the secure site.
Someone wants
your encryption key.
It's just a conspiracy sleuth eating cat food.
Put it aside.
But if it was a bomb,
obviously that escalates...
There have
been a lot of questions
about how many
you've been able to treat.
- We haven't...
- Some who initially were unidentified.
The Supreme Court hears
a patent case
involving companies that
are patenting human genes.
No, no, guys.
Take your time.
...to debate gun control.
And on the lighter side
of things...
We have to ask ourselves if we're
being gun-shy because of Genoa.
I don't see anything wrong with
- I do.
- When Reagan was shot in '81,
the three networks went live.
Reagan was shot.
No, he wasn't.
Yes, he was.
James Brady is dead.
No, he's not.
It was mayhem.
We're not first, so we might as
well be last and know something.
I agree.
What about you?
It's more than getting
our facts straight.
It's more than getting our facts
straight or having facts.
- Facts are important.
- Facts are important, obviously.
But, look, Mrs. Lansing told us to
get the trust of the audience back,
and here it is,
an unwelcome opportunity to be sure.
- Will, there's not really...
- Here's what I'm trying to say.
These situations
can be like church.
They can be... They can show us what...
They can guide us in...
This isn't going to be
a reality show.
We don't do good TV.
We do the news.
- I said that.
- I know, and you were 100...
Americans are serious people
and we can reflect that back
to them in the worst of times.
Exalting their dignity by showing
a little of it ourselves.
- By showing a lot of it.
- Will, they've got to keep...
Don't reach for common ground.
Reach for higher ground.
Am I saying this right?
- He's saying we're the grown-ups.
- Get back to work.
- I think I blew that speech.
- They got some of it.
Nothing official yet?
We know the Supreme Court heard
a case about patenting genes.
- Pants?
- Genes!
- Human genes!
- Take it easy.
I want to go to Boston.
It's my hometown.
- I want to be on the ground.
- Take a producer.
Amy's on vacation.
Leon's in Prague.
Mac, Maggie can do it.
She can do it.
She knows Boston. She's cultivated sources.
She can do this now.
I don't make those calls, but she gives me
anything less than I want and she's fired.
I'll make that call 'cause I don't
think she's cut out for this anymore.
She is.
- Maggie.
- Yeah?
- Do you have a go-bag?
- What?
- A go-bag.
- I have a gym bag.
Go!
Confirmed,
Boston PD and the FBI.
- Two devices detonated...
- Herb, Jake, Joey,
- hijack the control room.
- ...at the finish line of the marathon.
- Multiple critical injuries. Affiliates at the scene.
- Let's go.
...where they
established a strategy
for this January's
bitterly contested budget,
after which President Obama
and Senate Republicans
agreed to a tax increase
on 77% of Americans.
So much for the president's
promise not to raise...
- Herb, let's get Boston up.
- Give her Boston on previews A and B.
- Graphics on C.
- DC control, this is New York.
We're making the handoff.
Herb's got the con.
This is Mac in New York.
Stay with me.
Two explosive devices
have detonated
at the finish line
of the Boston Marathon.
We go now to Juan Gomez with
our Boston affiliate WBAS TV,
who's standing by live
at the scene.
Tap your pen for me
if you copy.
Josie, I have to cut you off.
We're getting some breaking
news out of Boston.
Go, G1.
Stand by, Boston.
Two explosive devices
have detonated
at the finish line
of the Boston Marathon.
And we want to take you now
to our Boston affiliate
WBAS and Juan Gomez,
who's at the scene.
- Juan.
- Good job.
That was good back there.
Why wasn't I able
to put my finger
on what we're talking about,
you and me?
- You want to know why?
- Yeah.
Because it's obvious.
Where the hell have you been?
Shirking my civic responsibilities
as fast as I could.
If it was a suicide bomber,
there'd be a body.
So whoever did it is walking the
streets of Boston right now
and there's gonna be a manhunt like
we haven't seen since Dallas in '63.
This is gonna go on
for a while.
Elliot's on his way to Boston,
Terry's on maternity leave,
and we'll be a couple
of anchors short.
We'll take long shifts
and double up.
- Clear.
- Good luck.
The explosions
were 12 seconds apart
and right now we've got
14 confirmed injuries,
but that number is
obviously not gonna hold.
- Critical?
- We're hearing about amputations.
- Thank you.
- It was a good speech before.
Was it? 'Cause I didn't think
it was nearly specific...
Stand by, he's coming to you.
...and first responders
treating people on the scene.
Juan,
this is Will McAvoy in New York.
...what is clearly
a terrorist attack
at a sporting event
followed around the world.
Anthony Tagliano,
our law enforcement analyst, is standing by.
Anthony,
is there anything you're able to read from...
Welcome back to our breaking news
coverage of the Boston Marathon bombings.
A White House official tells us the
president received a briefing...
A trauma nurse at the scene
just told us the medical tent
is dealing with everything from
severed limbs to severe burns.
The victims are being taken away by
ambulances as they arrive at the scene.
The finish line is located
in the middle of four
of the best hospitals
in New England.
...press conference
just a few moments ago.
Police Commissioner Ed Davis
has confirmed two deaths...
- S-U-Z-I.
- Copy.
- Suzi Ochi.
- Okay, we've got Suzi Ochi,
an eyewitness who was finishing the
race when the explosions occurred.
Suzi, can you hear me?
- Maggie Jordan.
- Elliot Hirsch.
I'm Eddie.
I'm your cameraman and driver.
You want to go to your
hotel and get checked in?
We want to go to Boylston.
I'd literally just crossed
the finish line,
took three steps,
heard a loud explosion,
turned around and there was a cloud
of smoke that appeared to be...
Will, we've got another
confirmed casualty.
Male, eight years old.
...you hear
tons of applause.
For a second I thought that the
bomb might even be thunder.
Slow but steady
recreational runners...
Bombs need detonators like a
garage door opener or something.
How far away can a person be
from the device?
We've heard from authorities
that they believe these
to be improvised devices.
What kind of detonator would that need
and does the person have to be present?
No, it can be a timed device
and you can also be miles away and
set it off by calling a cell phone.
Sloan, truthfully,
it's not hard to blow something up.
- Recap.
- Thanks again to FBI profiler Frank Harris.
To recap...
Okay, sir, thank you.
Thank you for your time.
That was a nurse.
Surgeons are pulling ball bearings
out of patients in two different
operating rooms right now.
- Did he say...
- They're coming to you.
31.
Sloan, I'm outside Boston's
Brigham and Women's Hospital
where officials are telling us they're
currently treating 31 patients
for injuries that range from cuts
and lacerations to amputations.
- This is good, Maggie.
- Yeah.
...removing ball
bearings from a patient's leg.
Are the hospitals equipped to handle
the number of serious injuries?
The World Trade Center,
of course, involved
both thousands of people
and iconic buildings.
Right, Will, and here it wasn't
an iconic building that was the target.
How are you doing?
She got a ton of stuff first.
- It's just that Mac wasn't willing to go...
- I know.
Social media is going
to solve this crime.
Crowdsourcing law enforcement.
That went off
without a hitch in Salem.
Go home and sleep a few hours and
then come back and relieve Neal.
I've got to post a column.
Do it from home.
We're gonna need fresh legs.
- What about you?
- I'll stay a couple more hours.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Wait, what was the thing
from this afternoon?
The guy who wanted
my encryption key.
I put it in your desktop
under "cat food."
See you in a little bit.
As of yet,
no individuals or groups
have claimed responsibility.
She didn't seem surprised,
but she did suspect
it was an indication that this
wasn't an organized terror cell.
Did your source indicate
what she believes
might have motivated
the bombing?
At this time she
can only speculate.
The Boston Police Department
is questioning local people
in connection with the bombings,
but they have no one in custody.
The FBI is stepping in
to take over investigations...
...and we're being told that they've stopped
all transportation
into and out of the city
and are combing through airport records,
a very daunting task...
_
Among the three dead
is an eight-year-old boy
whom The Boston Globe
has identified this morning
as Martin Richard of Dorchester,
Massachusetts.
We understand friends and
family will gather tonight...
- You've got to like that.
- What's that?
Oh, God, no,
I didn't mean the boy.
I meant that the hotel TV
is tuned to ACN.
They change it over from CNBC
when I eat breakfast here.
If Maria Bartiromo walks in,
they'll find the remote in a hurry.
Listen,
I'm gonna need to get back...
Hang on.
You've got a tag.
- Thank you.
- Someone didn't sleep at home last night.
- I slept at my friend's and needed a fresh...
- Yeah.
- April 10.
A lot of investors got caught out
when the Dow and S&P popped,
and I'm hearing a number of hedge
funds were short the big indexes.
- Who do you think won?
- Our clients.
- Okay.
- Let me get that.
- No.
- Come on, you got it last time.
I'm not allowed to let Goldman
Sachs buy me breakfast.
You had an English muffin.
- Hey, you know Billy Posener?
- The head media guy at Merrill?
Wife and two kids and he was
caught having an affair
with his 24-year-old assistant,
whom he hired personally
after two years of... I'm not joking...
circus school didn't work out.
So he's gonna get fired and
Merrill's whole media department's
gonna be without
a rudder for a while.
Or acrobats, probably.
Thank you.
Thank you, Miss Sabbith.
In a news conference
that ended just minutes ago
behind me at the state house,
Governor Deval Patrick
has stated that only
two devices were found.
None of the other evidence
collected at the scene
indicates that any other unexploded
devices will be found.
The governor has also said...
- Yeah, it's my office.
- I'm just here.
- You all right?
- I'm hiding from the twins.
Who are the twins?
I'd guess you'd have to say
my brother and sister.
Until this moment,
I didn't know you had siblings.
How's that possible?
Half-brother,
half-sister.
My father's kids
from his second wife.
- Randy and Blair.
- Which one's which?
- Doesn't really matter.
- What do they do?
They go to parties.
They go to clubs.
They order bottle service.
They do a lot
of philanthropic work
as long as it's a party
at a club with bottle service.
They're like the brothers from
A Night at the Roxbury
if one of them was a woman
and the other one was dumber.
They're up from South Beach
for one of several
25th birthday parties
they're throwing for themselves.
I take it your dad
left them some money.
- You work for them.
- They're stockholders?
They will be when they turn 25.
I'm supposed to be giving them a
tour of the building right now,
but I just know they're gonna pass by
a monitor with coverage from Boston
and one of them's gonna say,
"Oh, God, I just can't watch that.
It makes me too depressed."
And I'm gonna put their heads in a wall.
So I'm hiding in here.
Why here?
This is embargoed
until it crosses the tape.
We're gonna miss our earnings
projections by a little.
By a little?
Did the Titanic miss New
York Harbor by a little?
- Feel free to pile on.
- You guys reaffirmed your guidance
- for the quarter a month ago.
- I know.
How could you do that if you knew
the numbers were gonna be this bad?
Qantas and Lufthansa decided they wanted to
use Rolls-Royce engines in their new Boeings.
- How did they keep that a secret?
- I don't know.
The message I want to get out
is that this is a one-time thing
and it's not gonna impact
our full-year guidance.
We're on track to meet
our final numbers.
This is just
a bump in the road.
You know I can't
carry your water.
I'm not asking you to.
I'm just asking you
to look at the big picture
and take it easy on us.
The big picture is
we're gonna be down
three to five points
by the end of the week.
Three to five?
All right,
it was fun talking to you.
I know everyone on this floor
thinks I'm an asshole,
but I run a good company.
And that's all
I've ever wanted to do...
Run a good company
that makes good products.
And we may have a political
difference on this,
but I take a lot of pride
in being a job creator.
Okay.
You really want to argue
the indisputable fact
that I cut paychecks
to 141,000 people?
Our difference of opinion isn't political,
it's religious.
I'm an economist,
and in my church
it's your customers
who are the job creators.
And no one here thinks
you're an asshole.
- Really?
- I do.
Way to be up fourth
with Boston.
I swear to God,
my Aunt Isadora,
who is in a nursing
home and blind,
called me with the news
before it was on our air.
If Mac allowed us to use
Aunt Isadora as a source...
- What was that about?
- It's embargoed.
How was breakfast?
Well, I left the tag on the clothes I
wore out of Brooks Brothers this morning.
- We're not good at this.
- And she tried to give me a message in a bottle.
What was it?
Merrill's media buyer
is gonna lose his job
because he's been
having an affair
with his 24-year-old assistant,
who used to be a circus performer.
Oh.
That was
an involuntary response
you'd get from any man
if he pictured a circus girl.
Pictured her doing what?
Why would she want
you to know this?
My guess is Goldman and Merrill
are competing to do a deal
and she'd like me to weaken
the competition for her.
The puzzle is, who's buying who?
And I like puzzles.
- No, you don't.
- I love puzzles.
You literally talk back to the
New York Times crossword. You yell at it.
Can I tell you something about the
New York Times crossword?
Very often they put the wrong number
of boxes in to house the correct word.
- Yeah.
- But this one I'm gonna solve
'cause I have
my Bloomberg terminal.
Tell me again what you get for
$24,000 that I don't get for 1,500?
- You wouldn't understand.
- Really?
You know how there are tall women
who don't mind dating shorter guys?
I don't mind that you're dumb.
And, Don, I mean that.
Thank you.
Can you tag Will out
for a while?
He's got to eat something.
Jim will catch you up on where we are right now.
- Where are we?
- Exactly where we were 12 hours ago.
I'm gonna give us a soft
B-plus for the first day.
Jenna!
I thought it was a solid B-plus.
- I'll tell you where we lost points.
- Yes?
I'm almost certain I asked for French toast,
scrambled eggs, and bacon
with a side order of bacon
and a Dr. Pepper.
- You did.
- What do we have here?
Greek yogurt,
a gluten-free muffin,
two hard-boiled eggs,
one-third of a banana, and green tea.
You're taking instructions from her,
aren't you?
I've always been taking
instructions from her.
And you are looking
at nothing out the window.
Listen up.
I'm from Nebraska.
I'm not like the rest of you.
I can eat food without fear.
Why did Greek yogurt suddenly become...
Never mind.
Did we overuse
the B-roll yesterday?
I didn't think so.
Did you?
Just keep an eye on the
smoke and people running.
- Why soft?
- Ryan Guidry on the DC desk
signed off with an affiliate stringer
by telling him to stay safe.
God damn it. He's not in the Sudan!
He's in Beacon Hill!
I agree that it's infuriating.
I don't care if there's
a shoulder-mounted,
rocket-propelled grenade
launcher pointed at his face.
I don't want anyone telling
anyone to stay safe.
- Do we have to point out how transparent...
- I will take him off the air...
- ...and manipulative that is?
- ...just long enough to pummel him
- with a snow shovel.
- Creating the illusion of a cast of characters
- who are in peril, so don't touch that dial...
- The last words he hears
- before his bruised and bloody head goes back on TV...
- because suddenly you might,
- you know, blow up.
- ...will be "Stay safe."
- You guys about done?
- Yeah.
Good. You're both idiots.
Rundown meeting.
All in all,
I think we're doing well.
I'm still trying to figure out
exactly what doing well means.
You know what it means.
Let's go.
- Jim.
- The source won't go on record yet,
but from everything she's seen,
she's sure it was a pressure cooker bomb.
If she's sure,
why isn't she going on the record?
And the FBI has a picture of someone
taking video at the finish line
at the time of the explosion,
so they're trying to identify that person.
- Got it. Gary?
- Vigils are planned tonight
at Harvard Memorial
Church in Cambridge,
Parkman Bandstand
in Boston Common,
and for the little boy
at Garvey Park in Dorchester.
No, I repeat,
no interviews with children.
What's the desk schedule?
1:00 and then DC takes
a three-hour block.
Neal, tell us what's going on
with the nocturnal nut brigade.
Somebody's trying to give me
classified government documents.
Somebody asked
for my encryption key.
That's not uncommon, is it?
No, but then they asked for a
higher level of encryption.
Less common,
but not unprecedented.
We use a site, CryptoHeaven,
which is for...
- Nerds.
- Yeah, and he told me to get an air-gapped computer.
- It's a computer that's...
- Never been connected to the Internet.
There's literally a gap of air between
the computer and the rest of the world.
It's what I imagine the afterlife
is like if you've been good.
Once I do that,
he's gonna give me a flash drive.
How's he gonna get it to you?
I know you guys think I live
in a world of crackpots,
and I'll grant you
there's a troubling
normal-to-crackpot ratio
on my end of the field...
How's he gonna get you
the flash drive, Neal?
He's gonna tape it inside the tank of
a toilet in a restaurant men's room.
Bull's-eye.
- I think he's real.
- Why?
He's paranoid.
Well, why didn't you say so?
I was skeptical before,
but now that I know your source has a mental illness...
Anything else?
Good.
Neal.
Go buy an air-gapped
computer.
Thank you.
The homemade bombs
are considered
improvised explosive devices,
or IEDs.
It's created by
inserting materials...
Nails, ball bearings, glass...
into a pressure cooker.
- Just to be clear...
- You're coming to the top of the hour.
Let's hand off to John in DC.
It's what you would buy
at a Crate & Barrel.
And the fragmentation
of the pressure cooker itself
creates lethal shrapnel
when ignited
using a simple electronic
device like a digital watch.
You know what, sir?
I'm sorry, I'd rather not give out the recipe.
Unfortunately, the recipe and the
ingredients are readily available.
Nabil Chatilla,
FBI counterterrorism expert.
- Split 'em.
- It's 4:00 in the East
when you'd normally be seeing
Market Wrap-up with me,
but we'll send it to
Washington and John Bingham
for more continuing coverage
of the tragedy in Boston.
And I'll let you know how the markets
reacted later tonight. John?
- You're out.
- Thanks, Sloan.
I spoke to a source at B of A,
and he couldn't tell me much,
but he did say the private
equity's from out of town.
Great. Good lead.
Good work.
- You don't know what I'm talking about, right?
- No.
My puzzle.
Somebody's buying somebody.
So I made a list of the
out-of-town heavy hitters.
Gary!
TGP Capital, Oaktree,
Lone Star Funds, Golden State,
Silver Lake, Sequoia.
- Yeah?
- I have a list of 24 private equity firms
and I'd like to find out if anyone has
checked into a hotel in the last 72 hours.
There are 106,000
hotel rooms in New York.
No, they'll be staying
at a high-end hotel.
The Four Seasons,
The Carlyle, the Regency,
Ritz-Carlton,
Mark, Mercer,
Soho Grand, Gramercy,
Peninsula...
Yeah,
I'm a little busy with Boston.
I meant, you know how
after a 16 or 18-hour shift,
you like to unwind
with a little work?
- The tail numbers.
- What's that?
- They came on a private jet, right?
- Probably.
They either landed at Teterboro or White Plains.
Follow the tail numbers.
- Decent tip.
- Mm-hmm.
...with CNN's John King
reporting a few minutes ago
that an arrest has been made.
We have no confirmation
of this,
but again,
CNN's John King is reporting...
John King's reporting
an arrest's been made.
Do we have
a second confirmation?
Nobody has
a second confirmation.
This man doesn't make
a lot of mistakes.
There are more reporters in the
city right now than Celtics fans.
I don't see how they could have made
an arrest without anybody noticing.
Get a second source.
Find out where
he's getting this,
'cause somebody's talking
to him who isn't talking to us.
Okay, thank you.
Savannah Capital.
Yeah, you're supposed
to be sleeping right now.
I will,
but Savannah Capital's in town.
You want me to put
a reporter on this?
- I am a reporter.
- An investigative reporter.
I don't want to take someone
off something important.
I can do this.
I get information all the time.
You get information
people want you to have.
I'm gonna call my good
friend Lionel Barkley,
CEO of Savannah Capital.
And he's not gonna
tell you anything, right?
- I wouldn't think so.
- You don't want the CEO.
You want a low-level guy
who wants to impress you
by demonstrating
he's in the loop.
- I don't know low-level people.
- You teach.
Isn't it possible one of your
bloodless business students...
Is a low-level analyst at Savannah?
Yes, sir.
Jacob Geitfreund.
Sent me an email
a few months ago.
He'd been promoted
from the mail room.
The result
of a proper education.
The $24,000 computer
doesn't hold phone numbers?
Savannah Capital.
- Jacob Geitfreund, please.
- Transferring.
Very good student,
but he likes puns too much.
- Well, praise his blog.
- How do you know he has a blog?
- My phone can Google things.
- I don't like puns.
- That wasn't a pun.
- I'm saying in general.
Jacob Geitfreund's office.
Hi, this is Sloan Sabbith
calling for Jacob.
Just a moment, please.
I'll see if he's in.
Sometimes puns can be punny.
- What'd I just say?
- Professor Sabbith?
Jacob, you don't have to call me
professor anymore. It's Sloan.
- Got it.
- I love your blog.
Well, thank you.
Thank you very much.
- I didn't know you read it.
- God, everybody does.
I was thinking about doing
a 30 under 30 package
for top analysts and you'd
be perfect for that.
Wow, that sounds great.
I've love to, yeah.
- Is that why you're calling?
- Not this time.
Right now I'm calling because your
firm is doing a media deal in town
and I wanted to see if I could
get you on deep background.
Hey, you're the one who told us in class
that one of the perks of teaching
is that you can cultivate young,
unwitting sources.
- And that's you.
- Yeah, I know the deal you're talking about.
I can't talk about it.
You know, Sloan...
- Yeah?
- Are you seeing anyone?
- Nope.
- Well, I can tell you it's a big deal.
You're going to be interested.
- How big?
- Well, I guess it's all relative.
Hang on a second.
He's using puns.
He's talking about
sex right now.
That wasn't a pun.
It was a double enten...
Thanks for holding.
You mean the size
of the deal is relative?
Sure. Look, if you want to get together privately
and talk about the 30 under 30
segment you mentioned...
- What's going on down there?
- Excuse me?
I'm gonna call you back.
Not able to get any
more details at the moment,
but CNN is now retracting
its earlier report
that an arrest
had been made in Boston.
- What happened?
- CNN had to retract.
No arrest has been made.
Once again,
our own John King...
Hey!
What are you doing?
Worst moment in this guy's
life and you're cheering?
- Why?
Because you think
if someone gets in line
in back of you,
it means the line moved?
- We still blew Genoa.
- The line didn't move.
- And if there's anyone in the world...
- That's right.
...who should be able to empathize
with CNN right now, you would think...
- Wouldn't you?
- ...that it would be the people in this room.
- Empathy.
- He got knocked down.
You didn't get taller.
- Sorry, Charlie.
- Sorry.
- Dodged a fucking bullet there.
- No kidding.
The MSG is where
the flavor comes from.
The Chinese are a people who have
been around for billions of years.
No people have been around
for billions of years.
Okay, well, some of us have
read a book called the Bible,
which is pretty clear
about the Chinese and MSG.
Listen,
I will live a life of flavorless food
if that's what it takes
to be married to you,
but couldn't you give me
a different test?
General knowledge
or air hockey?
As soon as the life
insurance policy vests.
Hard B-plus
for the third day.
I think we're getting
our juju back.
- What do you think?
- You ever read Euripides?
Yeah.
I read it when I was in...
No, fuck you.
I haven't read Euripides.
In the first act of the story,
you chase the heroes up a tree.
In the second act,
you throw rocks at them.
And in the third act,
they get themselves down.
I think we're getting
ourselves down from the tree.
- It's Maggie.
- Put her on speaker.
Hey, Maggie.
You've got Will here, too.
Listen, I'm at the precinct.
I thought you were
staking out City Hall.
That's where everybody else is.
'Cause that's where the news
is gonna be coming from.
Then I won't have any
trouble hearing about it.
I've been talking with a desk sergeant,
a woman in her early 30s.
She was crying a little
and we got to talking
and I think I know
what happened to John King.
That's not really
the story we're chasing.
Yeah, but I just thought you should
know in an entirely unrelated incident,
the Boston PD was
disseminating disinformation
to a handful of detectives
to try to find a leak.
King's source was one of them.
Why was
the desk sergeant crying?
Her detective husband
had just been suspended
pending an investigation
into a leak.
- You have a second source?
- I don't even have a first source.
She wouldn't confirm it,
but I'm pretty sure I'm right.
Prove it and we'll
help a brother out.
But I don't like when
the media covers the media.
- Yeah.
- See?
Act one,
John King gets chased up a tree.
Act two,
everyone throws rocks at him.
I completely understood
the story the first time.
_
The Boston Police Department and
the US Department of Justice
would like you to know that
this headline is incorrect
and that the two men
pictured here are not suspects
in the Boston Marathon bombing.
And I'll bet the two men pictured
here would really like you to know
that they're not suspects
in the Boston Marathon bombing.
- Yes, sir?
- I'd just like to use your restroom.
The restroom
is for our customers.
Can I get some takeout?
Sure, what would you like?
What's the least expensive
thing you have on the menu?
- Go use the restroom.
- Thank you.
Welcome back to our
continued coverage
of the Boston Marathon manhunt.
ACN reporter Elliot Hirsch
is in Watertown. Elliot?
Will, over the last few hours,
a series of dramatic events
have unfolded on the streets
of suburban Boston.
As of this moment,
one police officer at MIT is dead
as is one of the two
bombing suspects,
who was killed in a car chase and
a shoot-out with law enforcement.
The other suspect
remains at large.
Police units
searched door-to-door
over a 20-block area
here in Watertown.
The entire city of Boston is on
lockdown as the manhunt continues.
Do we know
the circumstances surrounding
the MIT officer's death?
Was there a motive?
The shooting is still
under active investigation,
but we know he was shot during a
confrontation with the two suspects.
Campus surveillance footage is
currently being reviewed as we speak.
What details can you tell us
about the lockdown in effect?
The Boston Police
Department is asking residents
to stay inside and not
to answer their doors
unless instructed by
a uniformed police officer.
Public transportation
has been suspended
and authorities told people at closed
stops and stations to go home.
No vehicle traffic
is allowed in Watertown
and a no-fly zone
is in place over the city.
How many people
has this affected?
About 32,000 Watertown
residents and business owners.
_
Sunil Tripathi
was a student at Brown.
He was reported missing
about a month ago.
His family set up
a Facebook page
for anyone who might have
information about where he is.
Now, yesterday at 5:00 P.M.
in response to Thursday's Post front page
misidentifying two innocent
people as enemies of the state,
the FBI issued these photos
of the actual suspects.
Now, here's what happened next.
Within minutes,
users on Reddit...
All got together and decided
that the best thing to do
was to step back and let the
professionals do their jobs.
They began comparing
the FBI photo
of one of the suspects
to Sunil Tripathi.
By 10:00 P.M.,
it had become a leading theory on Reddit
that Tripathi
was suspect number two.
At 2:43 this morning,
a man named Greg Hughes
tweeted that the Boston
Police scanner had identified
the names of the suspects as
Mike Mulugeta and Sunil Tripathi.
Earlier in the night
Greg Hughes had tweeted, "In 2013,
all you need is a connection
to the Boston Police scanner
and a Twitter feed
to know what's up.
We don't even need
TV anymore."
Now he tells me.
I just bought a new plasma.
- How big?
- 28 inches, baby. The whole ride.
Seven minutes after
the Greg Hughes tweet,
Kevin Galliford,
a cameraman for Hartford's CBS affiliate,
picks up on the Hughes tweet and he relays
the same information to his followers.
Moments after that,
a reporter at BuzzFeed
sends a tweet out
to his 81,000 followers.
A reporter at BuzzFeed
has 81,000 followers?
- How many do you have?
- One. Him.
She's funny.
I like her jokes.
- I follow you.
- I'm not on Twitter.
- Really?
- Really.
- I wonder who I've been following.
- Guys, please.
The BuzzFeed tweet says,
"Wow, Reddit was right.
Suspect identified
as Sunil Tripathi."
Two questions...
Do we know who Greg Hughes is?
He's a guy on Reddit.
Second question
is that by this point,
at 2:43 this morning, has anyone at our
network checked on Sunil Tripathi?
- Of course we have.
- And?
Five senior officials
with the FBI,
three with the Justice Department including
one from the Attorney General's office,
another five
from the Boston PD,
all of them willing to be
identified on the record,
all of them categorically denying
that Sunil Tripathi is a suspect.
Also the Secretary
of Homeland Security.
When you put their certainty up
against Greg Hughes' certainty,
I don't know who the hell
to believe.
2:57 A.M.,
14 minutes after the first tweet,
an NBC News correspondent tweets
the Sunil Tripathi theory
to his 180,000 followers.
180,000?
At least it's been
downgraded to a theory.
A half hour later,
Perez Hilton sends it out.
- I don't even want to know.
- Six million.
The Internet celebrates that
Reddit has solved the bombing.
John King is a stooge.
The Post is irresponsible.
And the FBI is inept.
- Is that it?
- No.
Between 3:00 A.M.
and 4:15 A.M.,
Tripathi's sister receives
58 calls on her cell.
- Maggie's listened to them.
- Really?
About half the messages
are reporters
calling for a comment
on her missing brother
being named a suspect
in the bombing,
the other half are death threats,
and of those,
close to two-thirds
include rape.
Death threats also start
to fill the Facebook page
- the Tripathis had set up to find...
- Jenna!
- I agree.
- That's why we're telling you this.
Now they've taken down
the page which Reddit users
- saw as evidence of guilt instead of the result...
- Get me on the air.
- I need a suit.
- It's being cleaned and pressed.
There's a whole room full of suits;
I can wear any one of them.
You're nine feet tall.
You can't wear any one of them.
I think she's starting to get
the hang of this place.
Saw as evidence of guilt instead
of the hundreds of threats
of public lynchings, beheadings,
and bullets to the head
of family members as well
as the anti-Muslim messages.
- Out of curiosity...
- Are the Tripathis Muslim?
- Yeah.
- No.
Well done, faceless mob.
Let's go.
...was killed
early this morning
while the second one
remains at large.
Again, the FBI has announced
that the suspects
are the brothers
Tamerlan and Jahar Tsarnaev.
Because we prefer not to make
celebrities out of these men,
we'll be referring to them
on ACN as the suspects.
But right now
we want you to know
that no one is a suspect but
Tamerlan and Jahar Tsarnaev.
You're up in six minutes.
- Thanks for the food.
- Sure.
This is great chicken salad.
There's some cookies
in the bag, too.
They have walnuts.
I'm allergic.
The chicken salad has walnuts.
What are you talking about?
The chicken salad you're eating
right now has walnuts in it.
- These things are walnuts?
- What did you think they were?
I don't...
I wasn't thinking what...
When did walnuts start
going into chicken salad?
- Are you gonna be okay?
- No.
Here's what's gonna happen.
In about a minute,
my tongue is going
to swell up like a bassoon.
- A bassoon?
- A bathoon.
- A balloon.
All right, uh,
we have to pull the story.
- No, it's a good thory.
- Not anymore, Elliot.
Do you need an EpiPen
or a hospital?
You do it.
You do the thory.
- You have the faths.
- The facts?
Yeth.
Look at me.
I can't go on camera.
- What, Marie Antoinette's clothes?
- Leth's go.
- Okay... Calm down.
Uh...
makeup, passport.
What emergency
does she need these for?
Breaking news at the Met gala?
I'm calling the thudio.
- I think you should let me do that.
- Hmm?
- Give me the phone.
- Yeah, you got it.
_
All right, coming to you in 30.
- 30?
- 30.
- I can't tell...
- 30! No Ss.
- No Ss in 30.
- 30.
Well, not anymore.
Maggie?
Yeah, Jim.
I can hear you.
This is Jim.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, I can.
Can you not hear me?
Yes, yeah. You were one question ahead.
Here's Mac.
If you get a stain on the dress,
club soda and salt,
but it has to be right away
and you have to tell
the dry cleaner
that under no circumstance...
You know what?
Let's do this after.
- You think?
- Stand by.
Intro and then
take us to Boston.
Contact authorities
immediately.
FBI spokesperson Angela Brand,
thank you.
Earlier today,
ACN producer Maggie Jordan
was able to track down a former wrestling
teammate of the second suspect.
The young man was not willing
to go in front of our cameras,
nor was he willing
to let us reveal his name,
but ACN's confirmed
his authenticity
and Maggie Jordan is standing
by in Boston for this report.
Maggie?
Will, earlier today,
we were able to find
a 20-year-old man
whom we'll call Joe,
but as you mentioned in your intro,
that's not his real name.
We found him by going through
a series of Facebook friends
and confirmed his identity and
his connection to the suspects
using his driver's license,
high school photos
from Cambridge Rindge
and Latin,
and sources inside
the State Board of Education.
How did Joe describe
the second suspect?
"A super chill guy.
Liked soccer, hip-hop,
and girls.
He obsessed over The Walking Dead
and Game of Thrones."
That sounds like
a lot of people.
It does,
but here's the part that separates him.
Joe said,
"He thought 9/11 was justified
because of what the US does
in other countries
and that they do it so frequently,
dropping bombs all the time."
I want to be clear,
I'm quoting Joe, not the suspect.
It was a second-party
characterization.
ACN's Maggie Jordan
reporting from Boston.
When we come back, more coverage from
the Boston bombing investigation.
Clear.
Yeth.
Yeth! Yeth!
- He's saying yes.
- I know.
...two male
suspects they are seeking
in conjunction
with the bombing.
They have not been
apprehended at this time.
Is it just me,
or did she age 10 years this week?
I, um...
Yeah.
Hey.
What are you doing out here?
It's a nice night.
What do you want to talk about?
I thought you guys
did great this week.
My head's held high.
It's a good feeling.
- I've seen the numbers.
- I haven't.
Did we drop to third?
Fourth.
Fourth?
Fourth. Hmm.
I've always been able to live with second.
I mean, I get that.
Our motto around here is go for the silver.
But fourth?
We did everything right.
You think because
we went up late...
Look, I didn't ask you to come out
here to berate you about numbers.
Those days are over.
I want you to do the news well.
But your power
comes from your ratings.
And the autonomy of the news
division comes from your power.
You're not gonna be able
to do the stories you want.
to say whatever you want.
And, frankly, you're not gonna
be able to stay on the air
because my mother and I can
only protect you from the board
if you're making money.
Well, I think it's time
for me to quit.
_
Let's do sports, Charlie.
We love sports.
You mean, like,
try out for a team?
Do not mean try out
for a team, no.
- Excuse me.
- Neal.
What do you need?
I need to talk
to the two of you.
I can't find Jim or Mac or Don.
Go ahead.
Is it all right in front of...
Yeah, what is it?
I'm currently in possession
of a little more
than 27,000 stolen
government documents.
About half of them classified.
Yeah, I'm just gonna
jump off this railing.
You'll have experts
authenticate them,
but they're authentic.
This isn't Genoa.
- What's in the documents?
- Hang on.
It's Will.
Have Mac come out to the terrace.
Go ahead.
There's a PR firm
in Virginia called BCD.
They do contract work
for SOCOM.
- Propaganda?
- Hearts and minds, yeah.
They get stories
in foreign newspapers
about American soldiers
doing community outreach.
But it can go higher than that.
They're helping King Abdullah
stay in power in Jordan.
And it can also
be disinformation.
A growing pro-democracy
rebellion in Kundu
threatens stability in a region
that includes American interests,
including national security.
To undermine the movement,
BCD put false stories in the local press
claiming that a rebel leader
was about to wage war
on another rebel group.
Those false stories
caused riots last week
that killed 38 people
including three Americans.
Start at the beginning.
_
- Start again.
- I've told the story three times.
Tell it again.
I'm contacted over our website by
someone who wants my encryption key.
- I give it to him.
- How do you know it's a he?
I don't. I'm using the generic
term for an unknown person.
I give it to him. He tells me he
wants a higher level of encryption
and that I should
assume my adversary
is capable of three trillion
guesses per second.
I get him the higher
encryption and he tells me
he's gonna hide a flash drive
for me at a restaurant
and that I need to get an air-gapped
computer to view the flash drive.
I view some of the contents
of the flash drive,
but obviously not all because
there are 27,000 documents.
I'm convinced by the little
I've read to tell him or her
that to convince my bosses
right away I'm gonna need more
or something else and I remind him...
Them... About Genoa.
Now, you should know
that the DOD
doesn't store documents on the
same Internet you and I use.
They use a private network
known as SIPRNet...
Secret Internet Protocol
Router Network.
At first, he...
The source...
Has trouble transferring
them from SIPRNet,
so I tell him to try
using a CD-R and then...
Stop.
You left out that part before.
- What part?
- Where you asked for more documents.
It's a lot of computerese
that doesn't matter.
I didn't want
your eyes to glaze over.
I wanted one or two pieces
I could show you
so you'd okay
the cost of investigating.
Did he give them to you,
the one or two pieces?
Yes.
Neal, you induced him
to commit a felony.
You conspired
to commit espionage.
We were supposed to end the
week down three to five points.
According to who?
Me.
We missed the quarterly
targets and by a lot,
but ended trading up
one and three...
It was a pun.
"It's all relative."
It wasn't a double entendre,
it was a pun.
Should I just stay here?
No.
The moment you asked him to give
you stolen classified documents,
you committed a federal crime.
You don't have to scare him.
They're not gonna want him.
They're gonna want
the whistle-blower.
How do you think they're gonna
get to the whistle-blower?
What is everybody doing out...
Reese.
We're kind of in the
middle of something.
When's their birthday,
the twins?
Why don't we meet in my office?
When's their birthday?
- The party's tomorrow night.
- Not the party.
Their actual birthday.
When do they turn 25?
I honestly don't...
Next week, the 25th or 26th.
Get your mother on the phone.
She has to call the board into an emergency session.
- Right now, tonight.
- What are you talking about?
You went to Wharton, Reese.
Wake the fuck up.
You're in the middle
of a hostile takeover.
- What?
- Somebody's trying to buy this company.
They got him.
Jahar Tsarnaev is hiding in a boat
on a trailer in the backyard
of a house in Watertown.
SWAT teams are there along with
surprisingly heavy artillery
for a metropolitan police department.
He is surrounded.
Okay, I'm going out there.
But, Mac, you should know that
a few minutes ago, I quit.
I'm gonna do sports
or perhaps nothing,
because somehow in
regaining our credibility,
we went from second
to fourth place.
By the way,
Euripides can suck it.
Chase the heroes up a tree,
throw rocks at them,
and then get them down?
When does that happen?
That was supposed
to be this week.
We were supposed to get down
from the tree this week.
He's hiding in a boat
in someone's backyard?
I'd like confirmation on that
before I say it on TV!
I'm not spending the rest
of my career in a tree.
I have to be somebody's husband...
Hers.
You know who did
great this week?
The police.
The FBI. The DOJ.
Homeland Security.
In less than 100 hours,
they found two needles
in a haystack
the size of the world.
You know who sucked?
Everybody else.
Two times in 24 hours,
law enforcement officials
had to publically disclose
information before they wanted to
because either a paper or website
put someone's life in danger.
So I'm not so easily
surrendering
to citizen journalists
or citizen detectives.
Neal needs a lawyer.
Get Rebecca Halliday
on the phone
'cause he's in
very serious trouble.
We're gonna do a good show
people watch, Reese.
If you have our back,
then we're not gonna let you get shot in yours.
And apparently,
we're all up for sale.
You were wrong.
We're not in the middle
of the third act.
We just got to the end
of the first.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net