Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
_
- Unbelievable.
That is a subpoena for a reporter
to appear before a grand jury.
If they had grand juries in East Germany
and East Germany still existed,
then that's where
we'd be right now.
Put it away, Rebecca.
And nobody says a word about
this to anyone tonight.
- What happens now?
- Monday morning, he'll appear before a grand jury.
He'll be asked to name
his source and he'll say...
- No problem.
- He'll refuse.
Tuesday morning,
the prosecutor...
Who wants Will's head
hung in his den.
...will go to a judge to get an order
for Will to answer the question.
Wednesday morning,
armed with the order,
the prosecutor will ask him
again and he'll refuse again.
Thursday morning,
we appear before the same judge,
who the prosecutor will
inform that Will has refused
to comply with
a court order and then...
- Everybody goes home.
- Because you're too big to jail?
- That's right.
- Will, you've been wrong about everything.
- Every step of the way.
- Do you really think this administration is going
- to lock up a reporter...
- I didn't think they'd raid a newsroom and that happened.
...who exposed a disinformation
campaign that resulted...
I didn't think Neal would have to flee extradition,
and Neal's in Venezuela.
And I didn't think they'd have
the sack to subpoena you,
but you've just been served
by a kid in a rented tuxedo.
And the reason the kid
was wearing a tuxedo
was because they don't
want to make any noise.
Or maybe they sent out
a press release.
No shit.
- You know what this is gonna be?
- Yeah.
"Will McAvoy,
hypocrite in a monkey suit."
It's been posted on Carnivore,
but it's been picked up by everybody.
Carnivore?
It was posted on Carnivore?
Also,
what the hell is Carnivore?
It's a new website that
just got its first scoop.
"ACN won't be attending the Saturnalia
of incestuous ingratiation..."
- I remember that.
- "That does little to instill confidence
in the public that the press isn't
ensorcelled by the powerful."
- I have to go find someone. Don.
- Hmm?
Lead the team
on the Kundu story
which has to be on the air
by Wednesday night.
That's in four... Why does it have to
be on the air by Wednesday night?
Because it does.
- You and I need to talk.
- Yeah. Not here.
Will,
I'm Mimi Tassler with BuzzFeed.
- Nice to meet you.
- Any comment on the story in Carnivore?
I was wrong about
the Correspondents' Dinner.
I forgot what a great
time I always have.
Will,
I'm Zachary Webber with Politico.
Do you want to comment
on the story?
Sure.
I probably need to read it first.
- I'm going back to the hotel.
- You can't.
- No, I can't stay here.
- Think for a second.
- What's the reason we came here in...
- Pruit.
We have to sit with Pruit.
I've had a minute with him
and so far it's going badly.
You don't think he's going
to buy the network?
No, I think he is.
- I've never heard of Carnivore.
- It's new.
Why do they have
names like that?
Carnivore, Vulture,
Beast, Gawker.
I don't know.
And why do gossip columnists always
sound like gossip columnists?
Finke, Weasel, Snitch, Frump.
I'm not familiar
with Snitch, Weasel, and Frump.
What do you read?
Well,
I read Jonathan Weasel on a regular basis
before clicking over
to AngrySpiders.com.
- Anyway, my answer to your question...
- Hey!
You'll tell me later.
- We were thinking about calling it a night.
- It's early.
Don and I were just given
a new deadline on a story.
- What's the deadline?
- Wednesday night.
- Gonna rent a car and drive back to New York tonight.
- I'll go with you.
Maggie and I were just
discussing an ethical dilemma.
She has a friend
who's dating a woman
who just started writing for
a website called Carnivore.
- We should go.
- I just want to hear what they think.
Maggie's friend thinks that
websites like this are toxic
and are poisoning our national
conversation and culture,
but he likes the girl.
So my question is,
would he date a drug dealer?
How would you like
to handle this?
- Wait.
- Yeah.
- She works for Carnivore.
- Of course she works for Carnivore.
I just said you'll tell me
later as I waved them over.
How could you not
pick up on that cue?
- I've never been good at that.
- You're terrible at that.
Yeah, so we're gonna go get that
car and pick you up at the hotel.
Cool. I...
- Listen.
- Not yet.
- Drug dealer?
- He said that. I didn't say that.
You're talking
about this with Maggie?
- It came up at work.
- What came up?
It just...
Your new job.
Your disapproval of me
came up at work?
The page view incentives
in your contract.
They're bonuses,
you judgmental prick.
And why don't you
believe in me?
Why do you assume that as soon
as I take a job like this,
- I'm gonna be an asshole?
- I don't think that you're...
Yes, you do.
Why?
How did Carnivore
get that story about Will?
- Did you see my byline on it?
- No.
No. 2,000 reporters and he thought
he was going to get away with it?
He didn't knock over a bank.
He sang an aria about how messed
up the Correspondents' Dinner was,
said ACN wasn't going
and then showed up.
You weren't aware of the aria
until I told you about it.
That story was waiting and ready to
go and I'm the one who leaked it.
It wasn't going to be a secret.
You had nothing to do with it?
I told them what to look for.
- Yeah.
- If I hadn't, I would be betraying my job,
and you know that.
You know that.
It's horrible that I got it from you, but...
Listen, the new HR guy at AWM,
Wyatt Earp...
- Not his name.
- Wyatt Geary.
He's onto us, me and Sloan,
and he wants me bad.
He's gonna come asking questions,
and when he does, you say...
Don and Sloan
are just colleagues.
Should you guys be standing
next to each other?
Yeah,
what are you doing standing next to me?
I really don't know.
Scatter.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
- I get it.
- Do you?
- Where have you been?
- Looking for someone.
We're supposed
to be talking to Pruit.
Listen, a little while ago...
- Nothing.
- You sure?
Yeah.
Let's talk to Pruit.
Lucas.
Books are like the new art,
don't you think?
Yes. No.
I have no idea what you mean.
We don't need them anymore,
but they look nice.
- We don't need books?
- Not on paper.
I'll send you a Kindle, Grandpa Joe.
You'll like it.
- I'm Will McAvoy.
- MacKenzie McHale.
If you say you're not
gonna come to a party
and you say it loud
to a million people,
you can't show up to the party.
He came to talk to you because you said
you wanted to meet him at the party.
Why did you want
to meet him at the party?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Take it easy.
I won't take it easy.
The position you put him in,
all of us, for a laugh?
It was not for a laugh.
Don't be a child.
It was an exercise of power.
You shoved the Lansings
around for years
and I wanted to let you know right off the
bat that I'm not impressed by ratings.
Second, I want you to know that
I'm not in this for the trophy.
I'm in it for the ratings.
I'm just kidding.
But really,
second place does nothing for me.
Good, 'cause as of last week,
we're in fourth.
I don't know how you
managed to swing that.
I was very proud
of our Boston coverage.
Proud is generally what people
pretend they are when they've lost.
Cryptic is generally
what people are
when they're trying to pretend
they possess supernatural powers.
Okay,
we've gotten off to a rough start.
Lucas, we're naturally curious
about your plans for the network.
What if I told you you could
be the number one news network
and change the world
at the same time?
Change it into what?
A place where people say snappy,
sardonic things like that.
Hey, we really have to do better at
talking to each other right now.
- Who are you looking for?
- Me?
You've glanced around
a couple of times.
- Nothing, I'm here.
- Is that accent real?
Can we please cut the shit?
I'm gonna infuse ACN
with tens of millions
of new dollars in your budget.
How does that sound?
I'm gonna get 18 to
25-year-olds to watch the news
so it can support itself and
so it doesn't die when you do.
The news gathering
and newscasts
will have tentacles in every
reach of the Internet.
Interactives, podcasts, live streams,
Tumblr, Facebook, Twitter.
We'll make our audience
reporters in the field
through Instagram and Vine, Snapchat and blogs.
You still with me?
Our users become the audience
and our audience
becomes contributors.
That's my plan.
Needless to say,
I'm impressed by your indifference
to talent, experience,
and credentials.
And I assume the absence of the words truth,
trust,
and professionalism in your mission
statement was an oversight.
Your contempt for the second-rate
seems to be a contradiction, too,
since you believe
the best reporting
is done by anyone with a phone
and the time it takes to write
"epic fail."
And as an old guy,
I've got a lot more respect
for 18 to 25-year-olds
than you do
'cause I don't believe
their heads will explode
if you stop patronizing them
for an hour a night
and tell them what the fuck's
going on in their lives
and maybe even in the lives
of other people.
The air up on that pedestal
must be pretty thin,
'cause you are delusional, sir.
If I am,
I plan on staying that way.
And my network's staying, too.
We've got a problem now,
you and me.
Have a good evening.
_
You knew that the
documents were stolen by the source?
- Yes, sir.
- You knew the documents were classified?
- Did Mr. Sampat tell you anything about the source?
- Yes, sir.
- Did Mr. Sampat tell you his name?
- Will you tell us the name of your source?
- No, sir.
- Let me phrase that differently.
Would you tell the grand jury
the name of the person
you know to have stolen
classified government documents
containing secrets,
which if made public,
could calamitously threaten
our national security?
No, sir, I won't.
At this time I'll excuse the grand
jury until 10:00 AM Wednesday,
at which time I will return
with a court order
compelling the witness
to answer that question.
Thank you,
ladies and gentlemen.
And, Mr. McAvoy,
you can step down.
Hey.
Does anybody know if they got
that guy out of the country?
The writer.
The guy who wrote the fake story.
Been over a week since the
government's known about the breach.
They would have pulled him,
right?
You would think so,
but we need to find out.
Oh, come on!
Come on in.
Don't look at any of these papers,
don't look down,
- and don't ask anyone what they're doing.
- Got it.
I just wanted
to ask you in person
why you haven't accepted my
friend request on Instagram.
It was the very next thing
I was gonna do.
- How about now?
- Sure.
Gary, toss me my phone.
Martin, can you read this over,
and if it looks good to you,
take it to Mac?
Sure.
- Accepted.
- Awesome.
Come in.
It's from Don and it says
"Take to Sloan"
and then it says
"Sabbith" in quotes.
I was told to read it.
Do you think it meant take to Sloan Sabbith...
Was the new HR guy
just down there?
- Yeah, how did you know?
- It's his Instagram password.
Nice try, but my mama didn't raise a
fool unless you count my brothers.
So I don't know what we just did,
but I'm gonna go back to work.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
Have you been outside today?
How do you think I got from
where I live to where I work?
- I just mean it's a gorgeous day.
- Shut up.
All right.
There has to be another way.
There has to be another buyer
for this network in the next...
- Few hours?
- Few days.
Elon Musk, Larry Ellison,
Antoinette Dodd,
Michael...
Michael Bloomberg?
- Do you know any of those people?
- I know all of them.
But Leona and Reese
told you they exhausted
all their options
before they went to Pruit.
They exhausted all their options
for keeping control of AWM
before selling us,
but they didn't necessarily
exhaust their options
of who to sell us to.
Look, I want what you want,
but this is big business
and you're a news director.
You don't know
what you're doing.
You can't just write down
names of rich people.
I didn't just write down...
Those are all people
who would be interested
in media buys.
Elon Musk isn't interested.
Michael Bloomberg
has his own media company.
Larry Ellison is busy
winning the America's Cup.
Toni Dodd...
- Antoinette Dodd.
- What?
- This is unbelievable.
It's just...
So help me Hannah...
I read in Page Six,
like, two weeks ago
that Toni Dodd was looking
to buy a media group.
I remember because I thought,
"This is exactly what happens to
Melanie Griffith in Working Girl."
And, hand to God,
I was on the Staten Island Ferry at the time.
But there was nothing I could
do with that information,
so my mind went to how good a young
Alec Baldwin was in the movie.
And whatever happened
to that Carly Simon song?
You think Toni Dodd wants
to buy a news network?
Page Six wouldn't say it
unless it was true.
And she has in the area
of $4 billion?
That's not how it works.
Nobody has $4 billion.
But, yes, she has $4 billion.
- Are you able to call her? She'll take your call?
- Yeah.
You need to set up a meeting for her
and Leona as soon as humanly possible.
Leona can't meet with another buyer
while she's negotiating with Pruit.
Friendly, informal,
off-the-record meeting.
- Pruit will go away.
- Not fast or far enough.
I know you don't like the guy,
but...
It doesn't matter
that I don't like him.
It matters
that I'm scared of him.
You were scared
of Reese and Leona,
but you turned them around.
You'll fight with Pruit
and you'll win.
I don't want to fight with anybody, Sloan.
I'm tired.
I don't want to expand
the definition of the news.
I want to narrow it.
We'll be right back at the beginning,
only worse.
I can't fight these fights
with this guy.
I won't win.
We can meet with her.
- You and me?
- Yeah.
But quietly.
'Cause there's one option
worse than Pruit,
and that's this place getting sold for
parts and a lot of people out of work.
Very quietly.
And now.
- How'd it go?
- Exactly the way we said it would.
Now Lasenthal goes to a judge
to get court to compel Will
to answer the question.
Now,
tell me what's happening in here.
Tell me we'll be able to run
the story by Wednesday night.
We've got the motive,
but we don't have the ringleader.
The motive is what
we thought it was?
To disrupt and delay their elections.
We've got that cold.
Elections that would have yielded
a hard-line Islamic government.
Democracy is good as long
as we like the outcome.
- Yes.
- How do you circle that square?
By knowing that Islam is a religion
and not a form of government.
- When it becomes one, it is fascism.
- And the 38 dead bodies?
Are a bargain compared to what
it'll cost us in blood and money
when we have to bomb the
place five years from now
because it's al-Qaeda's
new home office.
But we've got
a different problem.
The writer of the story,
we think he's still on the ground.
Don and I are each talking to
a different source at State.
When I asked my source if the writer was out,
he said, "I don't know. Is he?"
They're trying
to slow down the story.
Then my guy said,
"No, the writer is not out."
- Do you believe him?
- 50-50.
But when our story comes out that
this guy worked with the US,
they're gonna slit the throats of
his children right in front of him
and then drag them
down Main Street,
so I don't want to pick
the wrong 50.
- Extend your arbitrary deadline.
- It's not arbitrary.
Work with State,
get the guy and his family out today.
- It's night in Kundu.
- The phones don't work at our embassy at night?
- What are you working on?
- A piece.
You're not allowed to tell me?
I don't want
to fight right now.
I don't either.
I'm really glad you said that.
Do you mean that?
I have to go back
to the office tonight.
We're crashing on a deadline
I don't even understand.
I just want to eat my sandwich
near you for a while.
Sometimes you say that
and then you ambush me.
What are you working on?
My editor wants me
to write more personally.
- Like an op-ed?
- Yeah.
- What's wrong with op-eds?
- Nothing.
What are you writing about?
I pitched a few,
but the only one they liked
was my experience
with the Plan B pill.
Cool.
- Come on.
- I said cool.
You said more than that.
What's wrong with writing in the first person?
What's wrong with sex?
And what's wrong with my new job?
Hallie, I said cool.
You're not going to give me
a hard time about this?
I'm your boyfriend.
It is my role to support you.
It's a role I'm grateful to
have and I want to do it well.
Thank you.
- Sorry I jumped the gun.
- No problem.
Does your piece begin,
"Dear Penthouse,
- I've never written a letter like this before"?
- Motherfucker!
_
You know how this is gonna end,
right?
Please don't directly
address my client.
We're in chambers, Counselor.
I don't care if we're
in your fucking hot tub.
Hey, I'm on a government salary.
I barely have a bathtub.
Good morning.
- Morning, Judge.
- Good morning, sir.
Does anybody need
any coffee or anything?
- No, thank you, Judge.
- No, thank you.
Mr. Lasenthal,
how can a man with your resume
possibly let this happen?
Your Honor,
there's a limit to my ability
to let or not let
things happen.
Not much of a limit.
Mr. McAvoy is aware
of the identity of someone
who has committed in excess
of 27,000 counts of theft
of government property,
disclosure of classified documents,
and conspiracy
to commit espionage.
The suspect remains
at large and presents
a clear and present danger
to national security.
Why is he not protected
by the First Amendment?
Because the court in
Branzburg denied the press
First Amendment protection
when they're subpoenaed
to testify before a grand
jury in a criminal case.
Counsel?
Sir,
the court in Branzburg also said
that a journalist need not comply
with a grand jury subpoena
where there's bad faith
or harassment.
The government has raided
my client's newsroom,
seized hard drives,
and threatened him
with criminal prosecution
under the Espionage Act.
In this case,
a journalist participated in the crime.
He didn't pull on a ski mask, Judge.
- He may have unwittingly...
- He didn't do anything unwittingly.
He is the senior
editor of ACN Digital.
You are speculating
on whether a third party...
All right, all right.
Mr. McAvoy,
is there anything you'd like to say?
I haven't heard a request from the prosecutor,
sir.
Am I crazy,
or have you argued in my court?
You're not crazy, sir.
Brooklyn Criminal Court, Part C.
- How'd I do?
- You were very fair.
Does Your Honor need
to recuse himself?
I want counsel
to take care of this.
I don't want to see the press on the
steps when I come in to work tomorrow.
And I absolutely don't want to see
you in my courtroom on Thursday,
which I strongly suspect
is what's going to happen
as Mr. McAvoy
does not strike me
as someone
who is likely to cave,
especially with
everybody watching.
It was foolish of you,
Mr. Lasenthal.
The DOJ should not
have let it go this far.
The Department of Justice, Your Honor,
is not playing a strategic game.
We have to arrest his source and the
government of the United States
will avail itself of every
legal measure to do that.
The government's request
is granted.
Mr. McAvoy,
you're directed to appear
before the grand jury
at 10:00 AM tomorrow.
- I have a logic problem.
- Maggie, what's going on over there?
- His logic is inconsistent.
- How?
He doesn't believe the source should
have leaked classified documents.
- Neither do I.
- But he's unwilling to help law enforcement
capture the source
by identifying him.
He can't.
I'd be unwilling and so would you.
I know,
but following that logic,
he should also not be willing
to broadcast the story.
If he believes no one should
ever leak because it poses
a critical threat,
then why is he broadcasting the story?
Well, I can't speak for Will,
but I will.
This leak, he believes,
is a good leak.
What he's very reasonably
worried about is the bad leaks.
So he'd prefer
there are no leaks.
You and Will are making
the same unilateral decision
you don't want
a leaker to make.
I trust strangers
less than I trust me.
Your logic is consistent,
though horrifying.
No one's gonna ever guess
you guys are a couple.
All right, listen.
Listen up.
He's refusing to leave
without his kids
- and his youngest kid doesn't have a passport.
- Jesus. All right.
We got to get the kid a passport.
The State has to expedite that.
The State Department
can only issue US passports.
- They've got to walk over to the embassy...
- And tell them what?
- Where are we?
- Just...
We need a favor. Whatever it is they do.
Can I talk to you a minute?
The youngest of his three
kids doesn't have a passport.
State's got 30 hours
to get him one.
We are talking to mid-level people
and the US Department of State
isn't hopping to it when
we give them instructions.
You have to tell me why
we have to air the story
tomorrow night and not a
week from tomorrow night.
All right,
I'm gonna be out for about four hours.
Once we run the story, we've shot the hostage.
Will has no more leverage.
If we don't run the story,
why don't we all just go home?
Four hours.
Don't ask me where I was when I come back.
And what we say is
important is important.
The news reflects back to us
our national character
and I don't like seeing a bored and
boring teenager in the mirror.
What we say is important
is important.
It's a solid business, Toni.
Locked-in carriage contracts with
every MVPD and they're staggered.
The carriage fees
are due for a hike
that could double revenues by
itself over the next decade.
Can you talk about valuation?
Earnings before interest?
You'll look at our books and
see it's in the sweet spot
and the deal would be
accretive to your earnings.
- It would pay for itself?
- And then some.
Have you decided
what you would like?
A news network.
You were on fire in there.
I didn't understand half or really
any of what you were saying, but...
You were able to follow when she said
she's meeting with her board on Thursday
and she thinks we'll have
an answer we'll like?
Just tell me one thing.
Is she eccentric?
- How do you mean?
- She didn't eat her food.
She pushed it around a little,
but she plainly doesn't like sushi.
Why set a meeting at a restaurant
where they only serve sushi?
Boss,
you may be overthinking that.
That's hardly ever the problem.
We'll find out Thursday.
It's ahead on the left.
Just here.
You can keep the meter running.
- No umbrella?
- You either.
Should we sit in your car?
They may be tapping my car.
I disabled the GPS,
but they can still get in.
- We need more time.
- I told you tomorrow night.
- Lilly.
- Tomorrow night or I just have to upload the documents.
- The writer of the story...
- We're the writer of the story.
Joseph Bartho,
who physically wrote the story,
whose name is on it,
and who is paid by the US government,
is still on the ground because one of
his kids doesn't have a passport yet.
If we run the story before
Bartho and his family are out,
the best-case scenario is he gets
a trial before he's executed.
And if you dump the documents
without them being vetted,
there's a very good chance other
people will be in danger.
You really don't need to speak
to me like I'm dim-witted.
- Please lift the deadline.
- Give me a reason to trust you.
You already did.
You reached out to us.
- Not the other way around.
- But you've been talking to the government.
We got an invitation to talk to the government.
It's called a subpoena.
They also made an unannounced
drop-by called a raid.
I'm not talking about that.
You said that you've been working with
the government to vet the material.
- Of course we are.
- You trust them?
- In my way.
- You don't trust them any more than I do.
Please lift the deadline.
I reached out to Neal,
not to you.
Well,
Neal's in Venezuela, Lilly.
And you know what?
Why aren't you?
Why haven't you said,
"This has gone too far. Let's switch places.
I'll go to a country with
no extradition treaty.
You're now free
to disclose my name.
Neal can come home and Will
can stop spending his days
in front of a grand jury."
Why hasn't that happened?
You really think the price for telling
the truth should be that high?
No, I don't.
I promise the story
will be reported.
Well, I can't promise anything.
- Really?
- Look, McAvoy's a Republican.
- I know he thinks I'm a criminal.
- He's a journalist.
His politics don't
have anything...
"Worst-period-generation-
period-ever-period."
That was spoken in the
middle of a very difficult...
I reached out to Neal,
so I can't promise anything.
You know,
it wouldn't matter if you did.
I trust you less
than I trust them.
Dump the documents
and I'll quit my job,
walk to the FBI,
and give them your name.
- Trust that.
- Fuck you.
We can go back
to the airport now.
_
Mr. McAvoy,
I have here a court order directing you
to tell us the name
of the individual
that is the target
of this investigation.
- Will you comply with the court order?
- No, sir.
- You won't comply with the court order?
I saw a lot of spirit in that shot,
a lot of guts.
Shut it, Fast Eddie.
Why are hot women in movies
always great at pool?
Is that what men like?
A hot girl who plays nine-ball?
You could have said
anything after "hot girl"
- and the answer would have been...
- All right.
- Oh, brother.
- What happened?
- Hallie posted a column. You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
"Old Media Guy
and New Media Girl:
An Analog Romance."
- What's it about?
- What do you think it's about?
- Him?
- Yeah.
It's pretty personal, but in her defense,
she doesn't use his name.
- What does she call him?
- Jim?
- Yeah.
- Tim.
Hallie is
an excellent reporter.
And she's reporting on a fight
she's having with her boyfriend.
- She's working a tough beat.
- It's a lot more than that.
Okay, read it.
"My boyfriend loves me,
but he doesn't like me.
He definitely doesn't follow me.
He disapproves of me."
Maybe he just disapproves of using the
word "me" four times in the lead.
How would you have
written it instead?
I'm not a professional writer,
but I'd have maybe tweaked the opening so it read,
"I am not making
my private life
and the private lives of others
available for entertainment
so I can get comments like,
'You stay strong, Hallie.
He doesn't deserve you.'"
Seven in the corner.
I have been a witness to Jim
being a condescending...
Look,
there's nothing wrong with this.
It's relatable and interesting
and she can write like crazy.
Did she ask Jim's permission before
deputizing him into her well-written...
Why are you so quick
to defend Jim?
to defend Hallie?
Because she's going
to be attacked by Jim.
Probably not in print,
but I don't think that's the reason.
I'm always grateful when a man can tell
me why I'm thinking what I'm thinking.
You're into Jim and you don't
want to be a jealous cliché,
so you defend Hallie for show.
And it's a classy thing to do,
but at some point we're going to have
to discuss how that makes me feel
to know that any man in your life
is going to be the runner-up.
You really believe that?
Still got my security key.
This place has gone
to hell without me.
Mm-hmm.
It's almost 1:00 in the morning,
Jim.
Are you not coming home
or answering my calls or texts?
I told you my editor wanted me
to write more personally.
There are classified
documents in this room.
You can't be in here.
It was an invasion of privacy.
I'm really sorry for that.
I was mad.
We had just had the last fight
and I went into the other
room and wrote it.
You know my computer
doesn't trust me.
It always asks are you sure
you want to do this?
But it never asks
before I hit...
I don't care about the invasion of privacy.
I wish I did.
I've been here for hours
trying to make myself mad because
it was an invasion of privacy.
And the crowd would be on my side.
That's a no-brainer.
- You don't like me very much.
- And I wish I didn't like you so much.
Took five fucking days, Hallie,
for you to give yourself
your own reality show.
I understand your wanting
to insult me right now,
but that's not what I did.
Writing about the media,
writing about the New York elite,
telling personal stories
that resonate with readers
doesn't take one cent
away from covering Syria
and Afghanistan and Washington.
There are foreign
correspondents,
sports correspondents,
fashion correspondents.
And an unbearable
correspondent.
Jealous of the New York elites?
I've got you covered.
A movie star was at
an environmental fundraiser
and they rode on a private jet?
Here's your phony outrage.
Feeling a little like
you didn't make the cut?
I hereby declare
that amateurs are awesome
and professionals
are so 20 years ago.
Only instead of professionals,
I'm gonna say old media,
and instead of Jim,
I'm gonna say Tim
because I'm Hallie Shea,
Senior Fuck You Correspondent
- and I've decided to become a star.
- Are you drunk?
Did you out yourself about the Boston tweet
to make sure no one suspected anyone else
or did you do it to let our
enemies know you were available?
Do you hear the way
you're talking right now?
- Our enemies?
- Did you?
I'm gonna stay
at my place tonight.
Do you mind
if I tell you something?
Your problem isn't with me
and it isn't with the site.
It's with the audience.
You don't like that they like what they like
because you need them to like
you and that's no different...
I don't give a shit
about me or liking me
or following me or
friending me or trending.
It's just ugly.
I think you're threatened
by technology.
I beam a signal into
outer space every night.
I'm not scared of your Samsung Galaxy.
What else you got?
I want to be part of the digital revolution.
I want to be part of...
Oh, my God!
I am not talking about the apparatus.
Just tell me
you know I'm right.
Please. Please.
At least tell me that.
Tell me when you knock away the
digital revolution bullshit...
"We're not beholden
to corporate masters."
Yeah,
or any standard of good taste.
Tell me, please,
that you know all you did
was have a fight with your boyfriend
and litigate it in public.
Because I have spent time
with hardcore drug movers
and they don't pretend
they're selling medicine.
Yeah, I'm drunk.
- I'm gonna miss you.
- You're gonna miss a lot of things, Jim.
- Yeah?
- If he sentences you, where do you go?
Nowhere.
He's not gonna find me in contempt.
- But if he does?
- Manhattan Correctional Center.
- That's a real jail.
- And you've been shot at and you've been stabbed.
It's 1:30.
I think that's your phone.
We need a table or a dresser
where I can put my phone.
Also walls and electricity.
Hello.
Is it Rebecca?
Is it Charlie?
It wouldn't be Charlie.
It'd be Rebecca. Is it work?
It would've been my phone if it was work.
Is it Rebecca?
Hang on.
Yeah?
Okay.
No court tomorrow.
The hearing's been moved to Friday.
Cedarman wants Lasenthal
and Rebecca to work on a deal.
Does he know there won't be a deal
that involves not airing the story?
What he knows is he doesn't want to be
the judge who locked up a news anchor.
I find your Irish stoicism...
- Sexy?
- Irritating.
_
Thank you.
He's out.
Everybody. The whole family.
Everybody's out.
Here we go, tonight.
Show me a rough sketch
to time by 3:00.
Good job, everybody.
Thank you.
We're not done yet.
Good job, Don.
Jim,
you look sleepier than usual.
Tess, Gary, Kendra, Martin,
Sloan, you did nothing.
- Maggie...
- Mac.
Jenna,
your future is limitless.
Reese wants to see you
in his office.
Now?
Reese?
Come on in.
Close the door, please.
Joseph Bartho and the Joseph
Bartho Family Singers are out.
We just got the word.
They're heading to France
via 14 connecting flights
and a team of oxen.
So we're running
the story tonight.
You can't.
I'm sorry, you can't run it at all.
Why?
Pruit.
He signs a deal at the end of the day
and he won't
if we run the story.
Because of Will?
Says he doesn't think there's a
chance Cedarman's gonna send him.
It's not because of Will.
He likes that Will's going to jail.
He wants him to broadcast
from there.
- I'm certain they won't allow that.
- I'm certain they won't, too.
- What's the problem, Reese?
- The fines.
His lawyers had to be told
about the story
and they've advised him that if
the story was gathered illegally,
the Justice Department can and probably
will impose crippling criminal fines.
- This is horseshit.
- I know.
The source risked everything.
Neal's hiding in South America.
Will is facing a grand jury.
Bartho and his family
fled the country.
- And it was for nothing?
- Mac.
- It was for nothing?
- Yeah.
Selling the company is the only way
you get to live to fight another day.
Do we ever get to win one?
I've got to go
and tell the staff.
Hey, Mac. You know,
the fight with the grand jury isn't over.
- They still want his source.
- I know.
Since the day you got here,
Will's been having a battle with himself.
Is he a real journalist
or just good on TV?
You ever think he might
be doing this for you?
Because I don't think there's not a
chance he's gonna be sent to jail.
I've got his ring on my finger.
He's not doing this
to win my approval.
Then it would be the first thing
I've seen him do that wasn't.
I'm going to tell the staff.
- I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
Can I make a suggestion which,
if you think about it, makes a lot of sense?
Don't say anything.
Have Rebecca go to Lasenthal
and say we're willing
to kill the story in exchange
for everybody's off the hook.
Do you think there's a chance Will
would let Rebecca utter those words?
No.
Let's pack the documents
up in cartons
and label everything.
Yep.
Who's the most responsible
reporter you can name?
- You.
- Thank you.
Who doesn't work here.
Maybe someone who could
use a break.
Responsible how?
There is an old teacher
of mine from Columbia.
She mostly gets garbage assignments
now 'cause she's in her 70s.
Write her name down.
I just heard.
Sorry, Bubba.
Good afternoon.
I'll tell you, Mr. Geary,
this isn't the best time.
You two are a couple.
We're not,
but maybe we can do this later.
No, you are.
I have a signed letter declaring that you are.
It was sitting in my office in a pile
of things I hadn't gotten to yet.
- Somebody ratted us out?
- Yes.
Nobody around here would drop a dime.
You're blowing smoke.
- Who cheesed?
- Okay, Mugsy.
- You did.
- Huh?
- Which one of us are you talking to?
- I think you know.
- What's he talking about?
Sloan wrote a letter to HR
declaring the two of you a couple.
Yeah, it was after you made $125 on the
Chipotle trade I tipped you off to.
We spent the last two weeks trying to
conceal from this man that we're dating
and the whole time you knew you'd sent
him a letter saying we were dating?
- Mm-hmm.
- Why?
Well, obviously I was
hoping he'd never find out.
But you knew he was gonna
read the letter eventually.
Eventually is a wonderful
time of day.
This was a cross that bridge when
we get to it situation for me.
And here we are.
We're at the bridge.
- Wyatt...
- Is lying to corporate something you do habitually?
Don and I like to make decisions
about lying on a case-by-case basis.
Maybe you've helped enough.
Please,
don't transfer one of us.
We don't work together enough,
but the little we do works.
And if you ask Sloan to choose
between me and her job,
you wouldn't be able to get that
sentence out before she said her job,
and I really like her and I'm
trying to be good enough.
And this here is the
best thing that I do.
And can I say one more thing?
It's just occurred to me
that your company is only going to own
my network until the end of the day,
so what the hell has this
all been about?
- Come to think of it...
- I'm blown away you let me do it this long.
Why did you do it this long?
Fun.
I work in HR.
Our days aren't scored
by the "Hallelujah Chorus."
I don't know anything about the
story you were all working on,
but I know enough to say sorry.
Good luck to the two of you.
I'm a big fan.
Put those Instagram
photos back.
- Yes, sir.
- Why haven't we heard anything yet?
- The board's still meeting.
- Pruit just walked into the building.
- He's an hour early.
- Yeah.
What are you guys
talking about?
The Bloomberg terminal will tell
us everything we need to know.
Bloomberg terminal, tell us what's going
on with Toni Dodd's board meeting.
It's not a Ouija board.
I wasn't...
I was just, you know, praying.
- What are you two...
- Hang on.
Their press rep just tweeted,
"Exciting announcement
about major media acquisition
coming at 5:00 PM."
Go. Tell Reese.
So what's going on?
We found a white knight.
Antoinette Dodd's gonna buy ACN.
- Are you kidding?
- Hang on.
- No, seriously.
- How did you do that?
- Shit.
- What?
- This can't be happening.
I don't know what
you're looking at.
Options on Halifax
just started trading up.
- The Halifax Group.
- Halifax Group options...
Fuck!
She's buying Halifax.
She met...
I don't believe this.
She met with us.
She wanted them to think...
We were leverage.
God damn it!
There's no need for airports.
Just runways and a fence.
That's a hell of a plan, Lucas.
Dude, I told you in college that one day I
was gonna buy a company out from under you.
I gave you, like,
15 years' warning.
I remember you telling me you
were sleeping with my girlfriend,
but not the second thing.
You were probably in shock
from the first thing.
Call it off! You don't have to
sell us to this pretentious ponce.
Toni Dodd just got out
of her board meeting
and she's gonna make
a competitive offer.
So fuck you and fuck you again,
you fiber-optic yak.
Charlie. Charlie.
What Sloan's telling Charlie is
that people are buying Halifax
at the current stock price with
an expiration on the assumption
that Toni's about to
announce she's buying it.
It was leverage, Charlie.
She wanted people to think
she was looking at ACN.
That's why she had you guys
eat at that sushi place.
She knew there was a Halifax
board member there.
- You're gonna love me, Charlie.
- No, I'm not.
Yeah, you are.
I'm gonna take you
into the 21st century
right after I drag you
through the 19th and 20th.
- You couldn't have gotten here 10 seconds sooner?
- I just saw it.
- What's the point of having a Bloomberg terminal...
- It's not the terminal's fault.
You want a ceremonial pen?
It can write in a zero
gravity environment.
Yeah,
I plan to take a trip through the ionosphere.
Keep that sense of humor.
You're very entertaining.
- No, whoa. Come on.
- Whoa. Whoa.
We're sworn enemies now,
he and I.
He can still hear you.
- Did you see Charlie?
- After the show.
He was cleaning his
12-gauge with Maker's Mark
and muttering,
"Kill the wabbit."
It's not Irish stoicism, is it?
This is some kind of
internal baptism for you,
which would be heartbreaking enough,
except I think maybe it's a little for me.
Don't you know that
anything that can be proven
by courage and character,
you proved to me a long time ago?
You want me to give up
the source?
I just want you to say
you're scared.
All right, here's the thing,
MacKenzie.
'Cause I love you,
but you've had me on your couch for three years
and this one time
we're switching places.
You're tearing yourself up
because you either prioritize
the story over me,
which you think
makes you a bad person,
or you prioritize me
over the story,
which you think makes
you a bad reporter.
Either way, you're wrong.
The source came to Neal
and then I asked Neal
for his name and then...
- You can stop saying "his."
- What do you mean?
His name.
The source is a woman.
I've spoken to her
in person twice.
I know just as much
about her as you do.
Why are you standing in front
of a judge and not me?
Oh, God.
You can't ever repeat
what you just said.
_
- Mr.
- McAvoy refused to comply
with an order of this court.
Title 28, Section 1826
of the United States Code
directs this court
to hold a grand jury
witness in contempt
if he refuses the order
and does so without just cause.
We're here today to determine
if the witness
can show just cause.
Miss Halliday,
I'll hear argument for the witness.
Thank you, Your Honor.
And may it please the court.
Mr. McAvoy's cause exists
because he is protected
by a reporter's privilege
to withhold information,
a privilege that's been recognized
by a wide range of courts.
If we were to
apply that test here,
we would find that the information
given by the reporter's source
poses no harm to the public
and we would weigh that
against the newsworthiness
of the US government
swift-boating a foreign
election with disinformation
that got 38 people,
including three Americans, killed.
No one disputes that this is a tragic
story of unintended consequences.
No one intended
for anyone to die
and no one did
anything illegal.
Our intelligence professionals
engage in covert operations
all over the world to keep us safe.
It's their job.
It's how we won World War II.
It's how we won the Cold War.
It's how the Berlin Wall fell
and it's why more buildings
didn't fall on September 12.
But not only can't they do
their jobs if their identities
are revealed by a rogue
government worker,
their lives and the lives
of their families
will be put
at great risk immediately
and perhaps without
even their knowledge.
Judge, when they do their jobs recklessly,
the public has a right to know.
And how does someone who isn't
an experienced professional
in the clandestine
services presume to know
when one of our agents
is doing their job well?
In this case,
we can put a stethoscope on the 38 bodies.
The court is sufficiently convinced
of the news value of this story.
Mr. Lasenthal,
please speak to any harm it poses.
Judge,
someone with a high level of security clearance
has committed an act
of espionage.
That fact is not in dispute.
This person is still
inside the government,
still has access
to classified materials.
This person must be
apprehended.
Law enforcement doesn't know the identity.
Mr. McAvoy does.
And I can't imagine what other
argument the court needs to hear.
Mr. McAvoy.
What do you want me to do?
Your Honor,
if you're leaving it up to me,
I'd just as soon go home.
It's funny, but the first time the
Supreme Court ever supported a claim
of protection under the First
Amendment wasn't until 1919.
The amendment says
Congress shall make no law
abridging freedom of speech
or of the press.
And we went 125 years
without that law protecting
critical expression.
The legislation that
sparked the dissent?
The Espionage Act.
I just thought
that was interesting.
I appreciate the defense
my attorney mounted,
but my heart is with
the prosecutor.
I'm sorry, Rebecca, it just is.
It didn't used to be
that so much damage
could be done by so few people.
It just used to be harder.
It took more manpower.
So, for me,
I don't like the cost benefit.
But I can't give you
the name of my source.
I'm just not allowed to,
Your Honor.
It's as simple as that.
I'm not allowed to.
And as Your Honor well knows,
prison time
in a civil contempt case
can't be punitive,
only coercive.
So with that in mind,
I'm telling the government and the court
that there are no number
of prison days
after which I will reveal
my source's identity.
Well, I hate to say this,
but we're just going to have to find out.
Mr. McAvoy,
I find you in contempt of court
and order you to surrender
yourself to the US Marshals
in this building
on this day at 5:00 PM.
Yes, sir.
Hey, you know this is bullshit.
I don't think you
should wait for me.
I think you should forget
about me and move on.
- Okay.
- Listen, remember,
only my conversations
with my lawyer are privileged.
Right?
What we were talking about last night.
- Yeah, or your wife.
- Yeah, but you wanted to be a June bride...
I don't anymore.
I want to get married now.
I think you should have
thought about that... Wait.
- Are you serious?
- I'm more than serious.
We get a waiver
from the mayor's office
and use the chapel
at City Hall.
Honey, we've got 300 people
coming to a wedding
you've been planning
for 25 years.
Remember the seven weeks I
spent picking the invitations?
- I really do.
- Done.
"I'm marrying Will today at 3:30 PM at City Hall..."
"...if you guys
want to come."
- Congratulations!
- Finally!
That... That's what...
I was begging...
for seven weeks
we were looking...
Different cardboard...
Okay.
For that little stunt,
I'm gonna marry your ass off.
Charlie, Don, Gary, Jim, Martin,
we're putting on a wedding.
- This is men's work.
- All right.
- Let's go. City Hall, here we come.
- You finally grew a brain.
_
- I saw on the news.
- Thanks for seeing me, Phil.
You really want to spend
your last hours of freedom
arguing with me about something
that's 2,000 years old?
No, we can do that another time.
I wanted to ask a favor.
Mac and I have moved our wedding
up from June to this afternoon.
MacKenzie, while not being as religious as,
say, you are,
- she's not a full-on whack job or anything...
- Yeah.
She is devout and a Catholic
service would mean a lot to her.
I can do that.
Where are you being married?
At the chapel at City Hall.
Catholic service has to be
performed in a Catholic church.
Doesn't that sound like one of
those rules we've talked about?
God's omniscient,
but He's only willing to work in certain buildings?
- That's not...
- Like it's a union thing.
Fine.
Thank you.
I'll have a car waiting at 3:15.
Will.
You want to pray with me?
♪ Ave Maria ♪
♪ Gratia plena... ♪
You have to make
a grand apology to her.
- Really grand.
- I know.
- Canyon grand.
- Where's Professor Ethics?
- We had a fight.
About what?
Nothing.
Rejoice with those who rejoice.
Weep with those who weep.
Have the same regard
for one another.
Do not be haughty,
but associate with the lowly.
Do not be wise
in your own estimation.
Do not repay anyone
evil for evil.
Be concerned for what is noble
in the sight of all.
If possible, on your part,
live at peace with all.
- The word of the Lord.
- Thanks be to God.
Do you take this man to be
your lawful wedded husband?
I do.
Do you take this woman to be
your lawful wedded wife?
I do.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net