The most powerful woman in New York
is not Tina Brown...
or Diane Sawyer
or even Rosie O'Donnell.
It's the hostess at Balzac...
which had overnight become
the only restaurant that mattered.
And we were there to celebrate
the moment.
This is humiliating.
We've been waiting for 45 minutes.
I think I'm gonna faint.
- Doesn't she know who we are?
- Who are we?
I own my own PR firm.
You write a newspaper column.
This should not be happening.
I'm going back up there.
Excuse me.
Hello. Excuse me.
Hello! We've been waiting 45 minutes.
Look, I'm not sure you understand...
but I'm kind of somebody...
and she's definitely
kind of somebody...
and we really need to eat now.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
- Give me a 20.
- You must be joking.
Do you think I should
make it a 50?
If I had $50 with me,
do you think I'd give it to that girl?
She cannot do this to us.
- We're leaving.
- Oh, God.
Let me tell you something.
I was that woman ten years ago...
but I wielded my power
in a benevolent manner.
Can we please talk about this
over lunch somewhere else?
Where, somewhere like New Jersey,
where we might actually get seated?
Do you realize, if she were a man,
not only would we be eating now...
but they'd be sending over
free drinks.
I know a great Thai place
around the corner...
where the owner's son
practically always sends over...
a complementary order of mee krob.
How sad.
Do you think we can get it to go?
A short time later,
Samantha headed back to her office...
while I decided to investigate
this theory I had...
about shopping as a way to unleash
the creative subconscious.
All right.
I'm gonna take them.
I was already planning
on returning them when...
Miss?
They told me to do that.
And now they want to talk to you.
- That won't be necessary.
- Oh, my God! I don't believe it!
- When did you get to town?
- Just yesterday.
- Darling, you look fantastic.
- I can't let you do this.
Of course you can.
And you can pay me back never.
Besides, it's on Carlo.
Wow. When did you two...
About two months.
His family has this gigantic ranch
in Argentina. Very, very wealthy.
He has a tiny little penis,
but he knows exactly how to use it.
Wave, darling. Wave.
Ciao, ciao, ciao.
That's very nice of you,
but I just can't accept these.
But of course you can.
When have I ever given you a birthday
present or a Christmas present?
I mean, you are like
a sister to me...
yet I never see you.
The truth was,
we'd only met a few times.
Most people would classify Amalita
as Eurotrash.
I thought she was fun.
So call me. I'm staying
at the Four Seasons with Carlo.
- Don't you live in the city?
- I'm a citizen of the world.
A citizen of the world, darling.
Now take the shoes,
and we'll talk soon.
- I can't do this.
- Of course you can.
- Go, go.
- Thank you.
I couldn't understand a word
she was saying...
but I felt I had in my possession
all the Italian I'd ever need to know.
While at home, all the English
I seemed to encounter...
was "bills, bills, bills."
I envied Amalita.
Her life was a blur of rich men,
designer clothes...
and glamorous resorts.
She didn't actually work for a living,
yet possessed a dazzling sexual power...
that she exploited
to her full advantage.
Which presented
a certain conundrum.
Where's the line
between professional girlfriend...
and just plain professional?
Women have the right to use every means
at their disposal to achieve power.
Short of sleeping their way
to the top.
Not if that's what it takes
to compete.
But that's exploitation!
Of men...
which is perfectly legal.
Saturday night.
In an effort to save money...
and maybe even pick up
a few extra bucks...
I invited the girls over for poker.
- I'll buy two.
- I'm in for three.
So you advocate a double standard.
Women can use their sexuality
to get ahead whenever possible...
but men should not be allowed
to take advantage of it?
I'm just saying that men and women
are equal-opportunity exploiters.
- I fold.
- What if you sense that someone...
is giving you a professional advantage
because they find you charming?
- Charming?
- This I gotta hear.
A few days ago, Neville Morgan,
the notoriously reclusive painter...
paid a visit to the gallery.
Neville was making his yearly
pilgrimage to Manhattan...
to check out what was new and hot
on the art scene.
And he found it...
Charlotte.
It was only a matter of moments before
he invited her to his farm upstate...
to view his latest work.
If I could get him to show at the
gallery, it would be an incredible coup.
- But what if he wants me to, you know.
- Hold his brush?
If he so much as suggests
what she's suggesting...
you give me a call
and we'll sue the hell out of him.
That's the only proper way
to trade sex for power.
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
You're like the Harvard Law
Lorena Bobbitt.
It's Skipper.
I told him I was here.
He insisted on picking me up, but he's
not supposed to be here till 11:00.
He's like a sweet little seal pup.
That you sometimes want to club.
You're an hour early.
I can wait in the hall.
Skipper, come in.
It's all right.
I'm leaving anyway.
You guys have cleaned me out.
Good night, ladies.
Keep me posted.
A couple of hours later,
I was looking forward...
to calling it an early night,
when...
- Hello?
- Carrie, you bitch! What are you doing?
- I'm getting ready to go to sleep.
- Why don't you come and join us?
We are at Balzac, and there is someone
here I am dying for you to meet.
I'd love to,
but I'm really trying to cut back.
You know, pinch a few pennies.
You are crazy, you know that?
Why don't you just come down here
and be your fabulous self?
The truth was I could
barely afford that either.
But I rationalized
that my new shoes...
shouldn't be punished
just because I can't budget.
Sorry. You're not on the list.
I don't need a list.
My friends are already in.
Darling, what took you so long?
You won't believe what Carlo bought me
this afternoon at Van Cleef & Arpels.
What?
Oh, my God, it's gorgeous.
Twelve thousand dollars.
Listen, I want you to come and meet
the world's most fabulous man.
Sounds like a trendy sideshow act.
You're crazy!
Carrie, I'd like you to meet
my boyfriend Carlo.
- And his friend Gilles.
- Hello.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Gilles is an architect from Paris.
- How long are you here for?
- Just a couple of days. On business.
I've told Gilles all about you.
I told him
you were the most beautiful...
talented and fascinating woman
in New York.
And single.
How is this possible?
I get it.
You're an architect and a comedian.
I don't understand.
Nothing.
I'm just being un peu stupide.
You? Never.
I suddenly recalled my terrible weakness
for gorgeous French architects.
Can I get anyone something else?
You would like another
bottle of wine?
Wonderful.
And what will the rest of you
be having?
During the next couple of hours, I put
my journalistic skills to good use.
I discovered that Gilles
was recently divorced...
with a five-year-old daughter,
Beatrice...
who lived with her mother in Paris.
He was passing through New York
on his way to Brazil...
to supervise construction
of a new hotel.
I think you are too beautiful
to be a writer.
I think you're too charming
to be an architect.
I think you should
give up your life here...
and move with me
to Paris immediately.
I thought you were spending the next
six months in Brazil.
You can join me there first.
Don't tempt me.
I'm so broke these days
I might take you up on that offer...
just to save on rent.
Writing does not pay well?
No, it does.
It's just, I have
this little substance abuse problem.
Expensive footwear.
I see.
I'm only here for the weekend...
but I would love to see you tomorrow.
Maybe you could show me the town.
You've never been to New York?
About 12 times...
but I've never seen it
with someone like you.
You really have that certain
je ne sais quoi, don't you?
Yes.
And so do you.
So, I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Sure, I saw some red flags...
divorced, French
and almost uncomfortably handsome...
but I felt like
I was floating on air.
The next morning
I was brought back down to Earth...
as I confronted that eternal puzzle...
a closet full of clothes,
nothing to wear.
Just a minute!
Who is it?
- Hey.
- Hey. I'm sorry. I should go.
Skipper, come on in.
What is it?
It's Miranda.
She's got me totally whacked.
It's like I'm obsessed.
And I know that I shouldn't be
because I can sense...
that it's totally turning her off.
But I can't control it.
I can't.
It's like she's got
this power over me...
and I'm helpless.
Keep going.
I have to get dressed, all right?
Is it possible
to be addicted to a person?
The sex is so awesome
that it's, like...
it's all I can think about.
I've never considered myself
a horn dog before...
but I'm worried I might be starting
to scare her off.
Well, is that what she said?
No, but mostly we just have sex
in the afternoon.
She never lets me spend the night.
Well, I have an idea.
Why don't the two of you
just spend a night together...
and not have sex?
That would be hard.
That would be really hard.
Well, I think it's really important
that you try.
I don't even shower afterwards.
I like to spend the whole day
smelling like Miranda.
I began to fear that Miranda's sexuality
was overpowering poor Skipper.
Later I spent the most incredibly
romantic afternoon with Gilles.
I felt like I had landed
in a Claude Lelouch film...
A Man and a Slightly Neurotic Woman.
Wait. Wait.
I kind of have this rule.
I don't sleep with men
I've only known a day.
I see.
I gave in. After all,
it was already tomorrow in Paris.
You look so beautiful
when you sleep.
I didn't want to disturb you.
- Are you leaving so early?
- I've got a plane.
I'll get up.
Stay in bed.
Order room service.
Enjoy yourself.
- I can just get dressed.
- Relax.
I'll call you.
Okay.
As he walked out the door,
it suddenly dawned on me...
that he didn't have
my phone number.
And I didn't have his phone number.
But he had left me a note...
with $1,000 in cash.
"Thanks for the beautiful day."
Must have been
a hell of a beautiful day.
Well, it was.
We had such a fantastic connection.
Then he leaves me money.
I don't understand.
What exactly about me screams "whore"?
Besides the $1,000 on the end table?
I just can't believe
that you had dinner at Balzac.
Wait a minute. I thought I ordered two
eggs benedict and one spinach omelette.
It's all right.
I'll take the omelette.
This isn't right. We're gonna
pay for all this ourselves, all right?
He said order anything.
The room service is one thing,
but the money... uh-uh.
What are you getting so uptight about?
Money is power.
Sex is power.
Therefore, getting money for sex
is simply an exchange of power.
Don't listen
to the dime store Camille Paglia.
I don't know whether to take it
as an incredible compliment...
or as an incredible insult.
Just take it, period.
I wouldn't know how to return it anyway
because he didn't leave me his number.
He paid in full.
What more is there to talk about?
Who is this Amalita Amalfi character,
anyway?
I'm concerned that you've been drafted
into a ring of high-class hookers.
She isn't a hooker.
She's...
She's like
an international party girl.
She's a hooker with a passport.
Do you ever have any conversations
about money?
I did allude to the fact that I was
a bit cash poor these days.
So maybe it's supposed to be a loan?
I don't remember filling out
an application.
Sweetheart, men give, women receive.
- It's biological destiny.
- Do you really want to say that?
That's the argument men have used
since the dawn of time to exploit women.
I'm just gonna write the whole thing off
as a bad date with a cash bonus.
You know, that salmon is really good.
I think we should order another one.
As I struggled with the dilemma
of how to manage my newfound money...
Charlotte arrived at the secluded
Connecticut home...
of the painter Neville Morgan...
in an attempt to secure
his latest work.
Welcome.
Hi. I feel so privileged.
Meeting you is without a doubt
the high point of my career.
Thank you.
I'm frankly surprised that someone as
young as you is familiar with my work.
Are you serious?
I studied you in college.
Oh, my God.
I apologize.
- I really do.
- You're much too modest.
Here we are.
Excuse me.
The canvasses you're about to see...
are what I consider to be
the apotheosis...
of every great idea I've ever had.
It's the closest I've ever come...
to pure, universal God force.
The cunt.
Oh, my.
They're very powerful.
Exactly.
The most powerful force...
in the universe.
The source of all life...
and pleasure...
and beauty.
That's true.
I used to paint full nudes...
but as I got older I realized...
that the truth...
was to be found only
in the cunt.
Charlotte hated the "C" word.
But Neville Morgan was not a man
to be corrected.
Hi.
I thought you might like
something to drink.
Charlotte, this is my wife,
Gertrude.
It's a pleasure.
- Lemonade and cookies?
- Thank you.
Each of these portraits...
is of a woman
who has touched my life.
Incredible.
I wonder...
would you consider
posing for me sometime?
Me? L...
Well...
I'm very flattered.
Excellent.
So long as you're here,
I could sketch you this afternoon.
I bet you have
a beautiful cunt, dear.
As Charlotte pondered how far
she would go for her love of art...
and the gallery...
Another Saturday night.
With my hooker money still
burning a hole in my pocket...
Samantha and I showed up
at Balzac.
She reasoned
that since I was there once...
I was as good as in.
I don't understand.
I made these reservations weeks ago,
and she's already been here.
I'm sorry.
Is there a host
that I might talk to?
I will snap her.
I will put her over my knee,
and I will snap her like a twig.
I'm sorry. I'm hungry.
I'm going to go to the bathroom,
and then we're leaving, all right?
Come here!
They all looked so chic and glamorous.
Part of me wanted to grab Samantha
and make a run for it.
- While another part...
- Hi.
How are you?
Carrie, I want you to meet Mario...
Allen, Justine and Peter.
Mario's family has one of those
gorgeous palazzos...
on the Grand Canal in Venezia.
And we are all going there next week
for the film festival.
- You should join us.
- Absolutely!
Yes, you must bring your little laptop
and write all about it.
You'd be mad not to go.
Carrie is one
of the most fascinating...
talented and beautiful women
in New York.
I have no doubt.
I've never been to Venice.
Venice is the most beautiful,
the most romantic city in the world.
Really?
I heard it was sinking.
That's why you must come immediately...
before it's all gone.
I couldn't say I wasn't tempted.
I realized
that I could leverage myself...
like the human equivalent
of a sexy junk bond.
I'd parlay that $1,000
into a trip to Venice...
into a nice piece of jewelry...
a rich husband,
followed by a richer divorce.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna have to say good-bye.
I'm here with a friend.
She's waiting for me at the bar.
What a pity.
Call me. I'm staying
at the Carlyle with Peter.
Just because Venice was sinking...
didn't mean my morals
had to go down with it.
And as for Gilles and the $1,000...
I figured
there was nothing to be done.
For better or worse,
I had just established my rate...
for a one-night stand.
Excuse me.
And then the most powerful woman
in Manhattan asked me for a favor.
Do you have a tampon?
Oh! Sure.
Of course.
Thanks a lot.
I never told Samantha the source
of my newfound power...
but from that moment on,
we never had a problem...
getting a table at Balzac again.
A couple of weeks later,
we were all there...
to celebrate Charlotte's coup.
Hi. Excuse me just a second.
Are you number nine?
Oh, my God.
I am so not number nine.
Five.
Yeah, right.
It's this, right?
Really?
They say a picture is worth
a thousand words...
but in this case...
I was speechless.
www.tvsubtitles.net